<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jon L. Jacobi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Advisor</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon Pixma MG6220 review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>If you&apos;re a fan of futuristic controls, you&apos;ll love the handsome Canon Pixma MG6220 colour inkjet multifunction (print/scan/copy). The controls and LCD screen are embedded into the scanner lid, and you&apos;ll feel like you&apos;re operating the transporter in Star Trek the first time you use them. Beyond that, the Pixma MG6220 serves up high-quality printouts and decent scans, and it&apos;s fast for an inkjet MFP. However, you pay a lot for this model&apos;s good looks, and its ink costs are a tad high as well.

Setting up the MG6220, whether through USB, ethernet, or Wi-Fi, is easy. Canon has updated the look of the installation-routine dialog boxes, though they still aren&apos;t as professional in appearance as Kodak&apos;s. Fortunately, the software bundle that handles scanning, OCR, and other chores is as ef ... ficient and capable as any of the competition’s.

Yes, the MG6220&apos;s control panel, which debuted last year on the pricier Canon Pixma MG8120, looks futuristic. And yes, it has undeniable &quot;wow&quot; appeal. But we have the same complaint about it now as we did before: It isn&apos;t as efficient as it could be. The three buttons below the flip-up three-inch LCD screen, which you use for selecting options on the display, seem like an unnecessary alternative to the usual navigation and selection buttons. Frequently, you have to lift your fingers off the navigation controls and shift over to the selection buttons, which adds up to a lot of wasted motion.

Despite our gripes about the control panel, the MG6220 is generally easy to use, with the possible exception of printing on CDs or DVDs. The task, which involves inserting a tray into a separate feed slot, is easy enough after you&apos;ve done it once, but Canon&apos;s convoluted instructions make getting up to speed harder than it should be.

The MG6220&apos;s media handling is a bit beefier than it might appear at first glance. In addition to the 150-sheet rear vertical feed for all media types, you&apos;ll find a 150-sheet drawer for plain paper hidden at the bottom of the unit. The MG6220 automatically duplexes (prints on both sides of the paper), but it offers no ADF (automatic document feeder) for the scanner—this is not an MFP for scanning long documents. The unit includes media slots for CompactFlash, MultiMediaCard, Memory Stick, and SD Card, and it also has a USB/PictBridge port.

Speed and print quality are high points for the Pixma MG6220. Text looks quite good—sharp and dark—and arrives at a brisk 7.8 pages per minute on the PC, and 8.14 ppm on the Mac. Photos printed on plain paper look nice, though a tad washed out, and they print at over 3 ppm (snapshot size). Full-page photos printed to glossy paper appear vibrant and clear, but print at only 0.6 ppm; that&apos;s about average for an inkjet MFP.

The MG6220&apos;s ink costs are a bit pricier than average. The 341-page black cartridge costs £7.82 inc VAT, which translates to 1.9 pence per page. The cyan, yellow, and magenta cartridges cost £7.63 inc VAT each, and last for 204 photos (about 3.1 pence per page per colour).

Buying advice

If you want an MFP that delivers the basics with better-than-average speed and style, the Canon Pixma MG6220 is a worth a look. If you need an ADF (and can do without the space-age looks), check out its more business-oriented cousin, the Canon Pixma MX882, which includes an ADF and a more conventional control panel for about the same purchase price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LAPTOP Magazine</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>LAPTOP Magazine</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon PIXMA MG6220</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Crisp and vibrant color printsResponsive touch panelCloud Print connects to Picasa without PCBuild-in AirPrint support

Cons: Relatively slow overall printing speedPricey replacement cartridgesSomewhat lengthy setup process

With a glossy black finish, sleek curves and a wide variety of mobile printing options, the Canon PIXMA MG6220 looks like a good choice for anyone looking to buy a serious all-in-one printer for their home or small business. Still, compared with competing all-in-one printers from HP and Kodak, the $199 Canon PIXMA MG6220 features a price tag as hefty as its weight. Is the PIXMA MG6220 worth the money?</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great print quality, Easy setup, Good price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Tech support elves will walk you through setup via phone.

Cons: Ok, the footprint is a little big, but the same as comparable models that have scan + print + wifi.

I bought this to replace my Canon i9900 large format printer, figuring I can send large format prints to a lab for a reasonable price these days so A4 size should suffice.
PRINTING:
It prints excellent fast&gt;plain paper quality as well as standard&gt;matte/glossy photo paper quality. I found the fine quality to be too heavy on the ink for everyday printing, but would prob be good for premium photo paper printing.
SETUP:
This model needs a firmware upgrade, especially if you are on a Mac, or it won&apos;t take advantage of the WiFi printer sharing between iOS devices. Not to worry- go to the Canon web ... site, look up the model, and call the tech support number. You&apos;ll reach a real tech support person in Virginia within a few rings - who will ask you a couple questions and forward you to a tech - and they will speak good ol&apos; English to you while walking you through your entire installation, firmware upgrade, software update, etc. Who knew this level of tech support service still existed!!!
My total setup time was 1.5 hours - while on the phone with the tech. Granted, I was in no hurry and he was patient- it just took a while to download, install, download, install all the different packages. It wasn&apos;t stressful at all. When we hung up my printer was shared, on my WiFi, and I even installed a couple software packages to bridge from the scanner to Photoshop.
INK:
So far I&apos;ve done a good amount of photo printing and document printing with no need to replace the starter cartridges yet. The cartridges are smaller than what I&apos;ve used in the past, but they seem pretty efficient.
NOISE:
I set it for quiet mode, and it&apos;s very quiet. That said, it also moves a little slower in quiet mode, but Im not doing high volume printing. I do like that you can keep the printer door closed and it opens it when it&apos;s ready to spit out a printed document.
SCANNER:
Never thought I&apos;d use the scanner, but I did. Scanned my Italian Vogue magazine photos for my modeling portfolio - and used the Canon MP Navig ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NAG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quiet, is a great sound!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time

Cons: Too much ink used

Love my new Canon printer. Have gone through two other brands of printers before and the quality of them isn&apos;t comparable to the Canon as far as I&apos;m concerned. I do a lot of photo printing, and the quality of the prints is wonderful, on any paper. Any size print. The one reason I really love this machine, quiet, yes it is so quiet, not like previous printers that I have had.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>majort123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great home printer/scanner/copier</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great product, great price

Cons: Ink consumption

Product was easy to setup in wireless environment and software was simple to install. Menu functions and software relatively easy to use. Print quality for pictures and documents is excellent. Ink use seems to be a little high but probably have not done enough volume to fairly assess.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Toyman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Printer - Great for IPAD Use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is one of the latest new multi-function &quot;photo&quot; printers by Canon for 2011. The only function it lacks is a fax..which many people don&apos;t require. It is piano black, average size and very attractive from an aesthetic standpoint. The built in touch screen is intuitive to a beginner user. After a firmware update (download from Canon web site and installs with USB cable) it enables &quot;AIRPRINT&quot; and you can use it to easily print from your I-Pad 2. This new model printer also easily allows you to print directly on CD/DVD blanks. Wireless set-up was quick and painless...but if you upgrade the firmware via a USB cable you will need to go into the Control Panel and re-select your original wireless icon. There are 6 ink cartridges for which you can buy name brand or generic. Photos are high qual ... ity with no banding and comparable to those printed at your favorite local drug store.
Directions are easy to follow. Canon includes a 1-year warranty and does a quick replacement if your unit malfunctions within the first 12-months. I highly recommend this printer! You will NOT be disappointed. Office Depot had the BEST price..anywhere..better even than those mail order places.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Self-Proclaimed Photographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>EXCELLENT printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is an overall excellent printer! Very easy to set up the printer and load the cartridges, and equally as easy to set up the wireless function. The quality of the photos is excellent! I love taking photos, and it is exactly what I was looking for to print my photographs from the comfort of my own home. Sleek, cool-looking design. Awesome that it not only is wireless and I can print from a computer anywhere in my house, but I can print from other devices, too (iphone, ipad) and it has google cloud print which allows me to print when I&apos;m away from home. The only negative is the pricely ink cartridges, but then again most printer have expensive refills, and not nearly all of them produce the quality you are looking for in photos. I definitely recommend this!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Puppeteer76</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon PIXMA MG6220</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this product to have in my office. I have a MacBook Air and wanted something that would work well with it. I was very pleased with the setup and how it works through the wifi access point. I had no trouble configuring it to work, but chose to add the USB cable so that it would print faster. So should I move it across the room I know it will work well. Excellent product. I am a bit concerned with all of the color cartridges, but the good news is I can print pictures in vivid colors.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>paulsa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good all around printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: wireless

Cons: nothing yet

Had to purchase this to replace my previous printer, easy to set up, two sided printing, good color, wireless. I haven&apos;t tried the printer for photos yet but judging from my everyday use I would image that the colors should be accurate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NurbXtrusion</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great wireless printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless printer easy to set up. Print clarity.

Cons: Poor color calibration. Difficult to adjust. A little dark.

Great photo printer. Easy wireless setup. Great quality and definition. The colors are a little dark and it&apos;s difficult to adjust though.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim the Artist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>New defective from store.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design

Cons: Unreliable; Hard Setup; Too much ink used

Unable to set up to print. Would only print in black. Had to have Canon Tech try to talk me through set up. Still wouldn&apos;t work. Sent me a new print head from Canon. Works OK now. Was without printer for 3 days because of faulty part. Staples offered no help except to charge me to set it up.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HJK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My second Canon Pixma, great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy set-up; Compact Design; Easy To Use

I&apos;ve had other printers such as Lexmark. They do well for everyday, but the Canon gives me great color photo prints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pupinstuff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, not too big, good print quality, versatile

I love this printer. Easy to set up. Nice size. Versatile. Good price for this product, esp. since I bought it on sale @ Best Buy. I have used it for copies, document printing, and photos, and I have had no problems so far.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gail the Tech Challenged</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fabulous quality and easy to use!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Reliable

It was easy to set up and had very clear instructions. I did have a problem with wireless set-up with my Mac. I called tech support who was American! He quickly diagnosed the problem as being with a 6 year old modem. I called my IP, he concurred, and got a new modem. I called back Canon the next day and got the SAME GUY! Set up was a breeze. Then he walked me through updates since the printer was made before the latest Mac version of Lion OS. This techie was very knowledgable, patient and pleasant. Can&apos;t say enough good things about Canon tech support. Buy it for that! Printer is much better than my old Dell.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pjstargazer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price great product

Cons: Wish it was a little smaller, but then it would probably not be as great a product.

Photos and docs print out great quality. It does not take long for it to print if you choose quick print as opposed to what others say. It does go into a standby mode when not in use - probably a good thing from a &quot;saves energy&quot; standpoint. Love the hands on feature that lets you operate the printer from the top of the unit and not just from the printer. Great printer and great price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>The bicyclist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Conon MG6220</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Fast Operation

Nice printer with compact footprint. Excellent wireless capabilities. Startup is noticeably slow as multiple ink cartridges are charged up. Automatic duplex printing of Adobe documents is super.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrsChip</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Quiet; Great Print Quality

Very nice printer. Easy to set up and use, love wireless. Has a quiet mode which is great too. Pictures print perfectly and look like professional quality. Regular documents print fine, but I would reserve this printer for special paper or pictures</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PRB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very versatile priner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Print Quality; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Slow Operation

After a couple of weeks of use, I&apos;ve copied, scanned and printed with it. It takes a minute or two to come back to life if it&apos;s been idle for a while. 
Copying requires a couple of button pushes, so it&apos;s not all that quick.
Scanning was controlled from the computer. One document was actually a book, and the expandable hinge on the cover allowed me to close it easily over the book before scanning. Nice feature.
A document feeder would be nice, but when I have multiple pages to scan I use the Canon MX870 with the document feeder.
Printing is just like any other printer, so not much else to say. 
I did send it a 4x6 picture from my iPad and it came out beautifully - very nice colors.
T ... he printing directly to the CD/DVD is great! It produces a very professional looking disc. It took less than a minute to print a colored &quot;label&quot; on the DVD. The software that helps you lay out the &quot;label&quot; was relatively easy to use - allowing me to place text and graphics where ever I wanted on the disc.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Don</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easeiest wirless setup I have ever had on a printer. Printer quality very high. Does Professional job on dvd&apos;s. Print quaility great. Obviously I would not know abaout ink usage but it is a Canon so I expect it will be a little more but the quality of print is worth it. You can&apos;t get a good print without spilling a little ink. My OS is Windows 7 64 bit

Cons: The only thing that was a little confusing was the cd printing. Once your through your fine

I use Surething Label Printing software whch has the pixima as a printer choice. A little tweak in positioning and the labels are perfect. You will not be unhappy with the Performance of this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>q5ka</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great features, quality, and price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We were looking for a photo printer, not one that acts as the everyday printer but one for photos only. Since it seems that everyone quit making a dedicated photo printer, it was time to see what was out there. After lots of searching the internet for best photo printer, this printer kept showing up from different reviewers. Since I use a t1i from Canon, this seemed like a good fit. After getting it, everything setup quickly. then it came for the first test, print directly from SD card. The picture used was dark with some light sparkle in it to test the printer. It came out as well as I expected. Then came a bright picture to see how washout it can be and it performed much better than expected. The last was a photoshop picture from lower res camera on Mac. This printer does a very good job ... of printing the image that was sent to it. I am greatly impressed with this printer as it prints very well for the price. I dont expect photographer quality prints (that is what the much more expensive Canon printers are) but I would say the prints I got was as good if not better than the 1 hour prints you get at local big chain store. If there is an improvement, the printer itself should have the ability to remove redeye and crop. Simple photo editing features like these could be possible since the LCD on the printer is large enough you could reasonably do this along with it would make it more independent from a computer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>takled</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just like the reviews</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Easy To Use; Reliable; Wirelesslife is good; Great Print Quality

Cons: Ink goes fast

This thing took about 35 minutes to setup. Works like a charm. Didn&apos;t think I would like the wireless, but it is really nice. Prints from 3 of the 4 PC or Mac machines in our home. The basement PC does not have wireless or it would work there too! Photo prints are just like the ones you get at a retailer. The quality is top rate. Had it in 1 day. That is fast shipping.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ray310</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Photo printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Photo Quality, ScannerQuality)

Cons: Sloooowwww

Many thanks to BB for their 30 day return policy because I took full advantage of it while choosing a new printer. Tried 2 HP printers and returned them. Maybe because I&apos;m a long time Canon user I could never grasp HP&apos;s technology. In any event, I had a Canon Mp950 for years (7) and was extremely happy with photo quality. When the printer head went bad (I think) I had to either replace the head (risky) or get a new printer. To be safe I chose to get a new printer paying not much more then I would have for a new printer head. Also much thanks to BB for their no hassle price match policy. Although this printer is extremely slow in my opinion, the quality results are worth the sacrifice. Especially in the Photos. I know ink c ... onsumption is important to many of you and in my experience Canon has always been a bit heavy in that sense. But to me the little extra ink consumption is worth the benefit of quality photos. To sum up, this printer gets 4 stars instead of 5 solely because its slow speed and frequent self cleaning. Two suggestions, leave on all the time or turn off only @ end of day.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zana</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Clear Print</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

Cons: Slow To Boot Up

Well - so far I like this printer, the ink on paper is super clear. The print time is pretty fast. I have not noticed the ink cartridges going down exceptionally fast. The only think I can find annoying is when you print from say a word doc and you have not manually it the okay button to light up the panel on top - it goes through some sort of crazy processing conglomeration. Seems to take forever to print then.. I have found if I just touch the oka button on the top of printer - it prints without an issue. I did set it up that it does not turn off at all, which does keep it from cleaning the print heads all the time. Thus the reason for 4 stars. Maybe there is a way to set this up differently to avoid ... this processing thing it goes through - haven&apos;t found it as of yet. If I do I will let you know. Still very nice printer for the price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EricEB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Replaced my HP DeskJet 5500</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Copies Without Computer

The scanner part of the printer is not ideal for making high resolution copies of photos. I re-hooked up and kept my Epson V500 Photo scanner after seeing what kind of job the Canon did. It was OK for general photo copies only. My Perfection V500 Photo scanner is far better in this area, but the Canon printer does great on printing photos and documents. My HP Deskjet 5500 ink was the drawback in using it. The ink dries out even when they are put back into the storage brackets when they are not in use. The Canon uses individual inks with an LED to tell you which one is out. It uses 6 different ink tanks. Costco sells the color tanks but not the gray.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wanda always looking for easy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the fact that it is wireless..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless; Scan Print Copy; Easy To Set Up; Compact Design

Cons: Not Found Any Yet

So far I like this printer. I have only had it set up for one day but it was easy to set up. Had to manually configure my wireless set up but it wasn&apos;t too hard.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>flyfisher</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon MG6220 a good choice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Works Well With Apple; Easy Of Setup; Compact Design

Cons: Varied Print Setup; Slow Print Time; Slow To Get To Print

Excellent print quality. I found it some what difficult when printing documents then switching to photos. Works well with Apple I-pad and I-phones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ViaWelt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Prints CD&apos;s and Digital Photos

I needed to replace an older Epson printer that printed on CD&apos;s and DVD&apos;s as well as quality photo paper. The MG6220 prints great photos and is far more user friendly when it comes to printing on discs. I also like the way the buttons you need light up on the top. I did need to run the cleaning command to get all the colors printing the first time though, but it has been trouble free since.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Framez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great overal printer for the tech challenged!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I love how sleek this printer is! I have limited space and it is very stylish for a printer!

Cons: Regular paper supply only holds a small amount of paper.

Overall I LOVE this printer. It is sleek and stylish. The buttons &quot;appearing&quot; on the printer is very cool and I&apos;m hopeful that they won&apos;t malfunction anytime soon.

Wireless is a must for me as I no longer have a desktop and want the ability to print from my laptop, iPad, and iPhone. This certainly fits the bill.

I am NOT tech savy in any way! This was easy set up and the only issue I had was realizing that the paper tray on the back of the printer is for PHOTO paper only. The regular paper goes in a small drawer at the bottom of the printer. That is my only &apos;con&apos; on this printer that I wish it held more ... paper at once. Overall that is a small price to pay.

Give this one a try, I really don&apos;t think you will be disappointed!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>linzyminzy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is easy to set up; it prints fast. The price was great and it is wireless!

I love this printer. I have had a Canon PIXMA before and I loved it, but it died so we got this one. As expected, this printer is a great printer. It is quiet, prints fast with great quality. Photos look professional.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>masonsdad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer for a Great Price!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, size, qualtiy

Cons: Set up was a little difficult. Used as a Network printer

Great printer for the price. Can&apos;t beat the quality. Photos look outstanding!!! Fast printing speeds on regular paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roadtripgirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon printer doesn&apos;t disappoint</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

We had an earlier version of this Canon printer and loved it so chose another Canon. The graphics and back-lighted buttons made it easy to see and use all the functions. This is a much improved product and a great value for the price. I don&apos;t use the wireless funtion and just plugged in the old USB cable to my computer. I also set it on &quot;grayscale&quot; as the default.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>peggyclem</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Prints great pictures!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

I got this printer because I had the Pixma 5220 previously. Because I had an extended warranty with Staples, I replaced it with the 6220 because it was closest to what I had. I really liked the 5220, but after a year and a half it just shut off and would not come back on. Canon had no real sensible explanation for that and said it can&apos;t be repaired. But because I loved the pictures it creates I wanted another one. I again bought the extended warranty for my protecton. So the new printer only cost me $30, the price of the warranty. I am having trouble setting for wifi. It isn&apos;t as easy as the first rpinter was. Will have to call Canon to help me with that.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>winoco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy Setup, Great Results</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have a home network with a wired Windows 7 pc, wireless Windows Vista Laptop, and wireless Windows XP Netbook. I chose wireless setup which was a breeze following the setup disk instructions from my pc. When done, the laptop found the printer &amp; loaded drivers with out using the disk. The XP Netbook did not see the printer until I used the setup disk via an external disk drive (though there was an option to download drivers online I did not try)End result I was test printing in under 30 minutes.For the printer, color photos on glossy photo paper look better than [*] prints, and the special photo paper rear feed pulled 1 sheet at a time with no problems (unlike my old HP printer that would pull 2 sheets at once!)Document printing from the plain paper cassette worked equally as well wit ... h crisp clear detail. The copy function was perfect too.I don&apos;t have any printable CD/DVD&apos;s to try yet so can&apos;t comment on that.Bottom line, I&apos;m very impressed with all the options this printer has, I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll be learning new tricks for years to come!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>c_d</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer easy setup</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very easy to setup and great print resolution. Contrary to other reviews, I do not think the ink usage is any more than other brands. The airprint function in fantastic and worked right out of the box</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cheri2057</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Compact Design

Cons: Slow Print Time; Too much ink used; Flimsy Construction

Nice pictures But ink is used very quickly. Printed 4 baseball tickets and it used half of blue/gray/and red I print pictures a lot so I will have to keep ink on hand.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mirastro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-In-One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Reliable

Got it on sale for [$] @ Staples. $50 cheaper than [@] price and so far it&apos;s doing as good if not better than our Epson RX680 that went down. I love the CD printing on it also.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Finalwords</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Having been a HP Printer owner for years, I decided I needed a changed after my last HP printer’s mother board went out after 2 ½ years. The Canon printer got great reviews and scored very well with Consumer Reports. The printer was super easy to set up and the wifi works great. The print quality is better than the HP and it’s design is cleaner. I love this printer!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cipher469</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good buy.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pretty much everything.

Cons: No document feeder

This is a very nice device with excellent features at a reasonable price. I did return it for another model, because it does not have a document feeder, even though the Best Buy description said it does. That was the only reason I returned it; and, based on a Canon&apos;s tech rep recommendation, I bought the Pixma MX882, which has essentially the same features plus a document feeder. When I made the exchange, it was on sale at BB, which made up for the inconvenience caused by the erroneous description. I would really rate it a 4.5 (not a 5.0 because of the lack of a feeder), but the rating process doesn&apos;t allow that. Also, wireless set up on both Canon devices was among the easiest I have ever seen!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nbloom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wi-Fi Wonder</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Quiet; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

Had this printer for a month now. It was very easy to set up and I love the wireless functionality. Print quality has been excellent and all the features were so easy to use my 11 year old figured it out with no help. It is a little slow to start up when it has been sitting idle a while, and I am already seeing &quot;low ink&quot; warnings after 1 month of moderate use. Overall, I am very happy with this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sethook</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up/install.
Output quality is great.
Footprint is within reason.
Wireless a snap to set up.
Airprint firmware update went real smooth.

Cons: Haven&apos;t found any real weakness so far.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rich</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Impressive</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Fast Operation; Quiet; Compact Design; Great Print Quality; Easy To Use

Am very pleased with the printing function. Now on to scanning and copying. Lots to learn.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Satisfied!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use the printer and scanner at home and have found it to be very reliable for our situation. I have it set for fast black and white printing and the quality is excellent. The setup was easy except for the wireless networking part. The price was right too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JW Duke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceeded my expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Quiet; Great Print Quality; Reliable

Cons: Slow Operation

The gray ink for b/w photo printing makes a big difference! The door to the front tray opens and the printer turns on automatically...great features when you&apos;re printing from another room. A little slow on the startup, but well worth the wait.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chemicalman588</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>$$$ Five Dollars is $$$ Five Dollars</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>B&amp;H had the best price by $5.00 This Printer prints to DVD (Does a great job prints look first rate, Super great for home or small Business). For the price you cannot beat print quality. Worked right out of Box. Installation was easy and software support by Cannon was top of line. Great product!, Good Price and easy to work for a 69 year old Computer Geek!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Critical Wheel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great AirPrint Color Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This All-in-One PIXMA MG6220 from Canon really sparkled compared to the HP AirPrint we had to return because of all the programming bugs. Our expectations have been exceeded from the time it came in the door in only three days through setup and use. We had to go to Canon&apos;s website to download updated software for OS X Lion, but it was as easy as going to the dentist. Best of all, it works as advertised! We use it with two MacBook Pros and two iPad2s. Definitely would recommend. Especially at the B&amp;H Photo value pricing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nicholem1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Uses ink way faster than it says</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality

Cons: Noisy; Uses too much ink

I swapped my hp for. This one because. Of expensive ink. The ink for this one is cheaper but the color ink runs out quickly!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SeeMART Studios</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy Setup and Great Interface</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to setup product, I have a wifi network in my house and I was able to connect to my AP without any issues with password compatibility. Setup with my Windows 7 PC was a breeze it loaded the drivers without needing to download all sorts of software. The Buttons don&apos;t have any tactile on them but it doesn&apos;t make them hard to use. Printing itself is good, there are many cartridges and I printed out around 15-20 4x6 full quality photos taken by my Rebel T3i and they all came out great and the ink hasn&apos;t dropped at all, it came with full cartridges and not half ones. Cons? Setup time from out of the box was a bit long but I paid for a high quality printer and it has the goods... also the CD/DVD printing tray is a bit of a loose item, I wish there was a better built in holder for it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JRV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great photo printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Print Quality; Easy To Use; Quiet

This is a replacement for an Epson photo printer which I considered good. I was surprised to find the picture quality so much better, and the output speed is also much quicker.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Avicena</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This printer offers amazing features and print quality for its size/price. I did find it a little annoying, though, to set up. I know i&apos;m not very knowledgeable about Mac (which is a computer that i recently purchased) so that didn&apos;t help, but i did have issues in the beginning with the installation CD but i followed suggestions of another reviewer in this site (his name is Brent Peters) and i admit he gave pretty detailed instructions, thank you Brent. So after i downloaded what he recommended, i also downloaded the scanner driver, the Easy Photo Print, etc. And everything is working well. I gave 5 star and not less because i figured the reason i bought it is to print, and it does an excellent job at that; i didn&apos;t want to take in consideration the setup process because that&apos;s only a one- ... time deal. I hope this helps.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Canonfan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing printer!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Quiet; Easy To Use; Fast Operation

This printer took me about 20 minutes to set up and that time was mostly just to remove packaging. It was super easy. Just basically install the ink...very user friendly. I printed my first 4x6 photo and tested it out without changing any settings and it was beautiful quality. The buttons are also fun. The top of the printer is plain black but once you power up the control lights appear and everything turns into touch sensing. It&apos;s a very cool feature. I haven&apos;t played with the wireless feature yet, but I&apos;m excited to do so.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brent Peters</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This printer works great with OS X Lion! But... If your having issues downloading or installing the correct software, you need to make sure that you go to the product page: http://usa.canon.com/cusa/consumer/products/printers_multifunction /pixma_mg6220 And click the Drivers &amp; Software button to install the correct (Mini Master Setup) software for your OS. Also, I&apos;ve seen that owners (including myself) have had issues with the AirPrint functionality not working at all! To fix this problem, you will need to update the Firmware. To do so, go to the same link (Drivers &amp; Software) and select your OS. Then click Firmware and follow the instructions. If you have a MG6220 printer without Ver. 2xxxx or later, you must do this to use AirPrint. Note that to perform this firmware update, ... you will need to connect your printer to your computer via USB. This initial setup for your printer drivers can be quite a pain depending on your proficiency or if you even need to do it at all (hopefully your printer shipped with an updated firmware version so you don&apos;t have to update your software or firmware) When you get all this set up; this printer is amazing! Great quality photos and a intuitive UI. I&apos;ve owned a lot of printers; This is by far my favorite all-in-one for home use. Hope this helps!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Durable construction

I got this printer on the recommdation from a fellow photographer. Easy to set up, I use a usb connection, not wireless. Excellent color rendition, 5 ink wells, costly to replace all the cartridges. I am using this strictly for photos. So far, no complaints, very pleased with print quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bobby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great printer! It is the 2nd PIXMA I have bought recently. This one went off to college. Print quality is good for photos and standard printing. Offers wireless, wired and USB connectivity. I dropped the printer while still boxed and it still worked fine too!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon Beats HP by a Mile</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Reliable; Easy To Set Up

I have several printers in use. Two of the three are HP&apos;s. I think HP&apos;s quality is declining, since the newest one lasted one year. After using this printer, I do not intend to buy another HP printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Buffalo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Versatility is incredible</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Durable construction; Reliable

Cons: Too much ink used

So far the WiFi capability is nice, print from multiple PC&apos;s, Android Tablet/Android phone (Android App Needed) on network. Photo prints are more true color with the additional &quot;Grey&quot; tank added as compared to other previous photo prints. Multiple paper management options as well as double sided printing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tcj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice but beware network limits</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Multiple functions. Easy setup (if easy network- see cons), works with Canon cameras

Cons: Limited to one network subnet.

Per Canon support, this printer can only work on one subnet. So, if you are an IT guy like me and have a separate subnet for wireless and wired networks, you cannot use this printer from both. You have to decide which one you want to use. So, I can either use the printer from my laptop and tablet, or from my desktop, not both.

If you don&apos;t know what subnets are, you probably don&apos;t need to worry about it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cruzer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceptional value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Reliable; High Quality Copies; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

Best printer we have ever owned. Completely worry free. Set it up, and just use and use and use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TLMedic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Takes much too long to get going.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good quality prints with both documents and pictures

Cons: Sucks ink cartridges dry like no other printer I have had.

I bought this to replace another Canon (MP600) that failed after 5 years.This was the next logical model, wireless with pretty much the same features as my previous Canon printer. I was very disappointed with the time it took to print the first document after turning on the printer. You must way at least 3-4 minutes for your document to print if you have just turned on your printer. Also I have had the printer for about 3 weeks now, no great amount of pictures printed (maybe 6-8) ,mostly documents.
The yellow cartridge is almost empty. I think I will end up spending way more $$ on cartridges than any other printer I have owned. I still like the print ... quality, but not sure it is worth it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Glider4</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>OK printer if you get one that works....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use

Cons: Too much ink used

First one was dead. Replaced it the same day with another one from Staples. Second one worked fine. Seems to take a LONG time to set up for printing. But then the printing is fast. Uses a LOT of ink.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spicerpro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great B&amp;W Prints - Small Ink Capacity</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Reliable; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

Cons: Small ink cartridges; EXPENSIVE ink

Most printers tend to print B&amp;W photos in every tint other than black and white, but the Canon PIXMA MG6220 provides a Grayscale Mode that works great. That is why I purchased this printer and am extremely pleased with the results. Of course, this Canon prints great color photos too. On another note, it is sad that all printer manufacturers give away their printers just to gouge you for their skimpy ink cartridges. We all know that and the Canon PIXMA MG6220 is no exception. Through research I learned remanufactured ink works adequately well with this printer...and indeed it does. With that said, I love this printer and highly recommend it. But pers ... onally, I will never buy genuine Canon ink until they make the price reasonable for the tiny bit of ink their cartridges contain.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mike.s</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>There is a lot in the box</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Use; Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

Canon makes the best imaging products in the industry. I have Canon camera and printer and love both.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ringo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I wouldn&apos;t buy this product again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up

I use a printer primarily for photo printing. I have owned two HP printers and was very pleased with print quality. I have been very disappointed with the print quality I get from this Canon. Printing directly from the printer yields poor prints, printing from my PC, fair.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lb westcoast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the extra money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this with my laptop, iPad, &amp; iPhone , I would have given 5 stars but having to pay for an app to make it work lowered my rating. I prints well. It takes awhile to start. I upgraded from the 5320 so I could use google print and so I could read my cf card from my original cannon eos rebel. Customer service was excellent. FYI do your research first. I returned a printer with no problems, but it is very expensive to ship it back. Free shipping on your purchase is an added benefit</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Meg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Printer is great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I just recently got into photography and I needed a good printer to be able to try and sell some of my photography. This printer works great and is easy to use. I think I picked a very good choice and it was very well priced also. I wouldn&apos;t have gone with any other printer. The only downfall I feel of the printer is the price of the ink is a little high but in the end it gives me great photos that people enjoy and it fits everything I need.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EDO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LACKS OPTIONS FOR PRINTING PHOTOS HIGHQ</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I got this printer to use with my macbook pro. Everything works fine including WIFI. However, I will send it back because I have very limiminting option when printing proof photos. There is no HIgh, Medium or Low quality selection and the software that Canon provides to be use with Photoshop CS6 is slow and lacks this options. It is hard to select the back tray where photo paper goes and the main tray when printing photos leaves a line every half inch because it is saving ink although I was looking to print in high quiality I was unable to select this option anywhere! Nice design though but needs a better companion software to utilize the best of it. I am going with EPSON eventhough I own several Cannon cameras! It was nice to know that wifi works great on MAC! you just select the other se ... t up options and imput your wifi password and you are ready to go! Note ther eis no instructions on how to print a DVD either!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CaroleM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good value but feels flimsy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good value, easy setup

Cons: Feels flimsy

I have a Canon MP 830 printer and have long enjoyed its quality printing and scanning, I purchased this printer to give me air print capability with my Mac products.

While setup was good and the print quality is as well the plastic trays feel cheap. Not solid like the MP830.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PontiacPeggy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Small paper tray

I had planned on purchasing another HP OfficeJet printer to replace the one I had but the Canon was in stock and had all the features I wanted - especially duplex printing. Unlike my previous printer, this one cannot fax but I rarely used that feature anyway.

I have been extremely happy with this printer. All the things that annoyed me about the HP are non-issues with the Canon. It prints footers and the last lines on a page every time. It scans without a hitch - no more beating the printer into doing it.

The duplex printing is good. And, while the Canon is rated at a much slower pages per minute than my HP was, the Canon shoots out pages at a much greater rate. No more long coffee breaks :)

Set up, including wi-fi- ... , was a breeze and I&apos;m not a real techie person. I have not printed photos so cannot comment on that. However, I have printed greeting cards and they look very good.

I am very happy with this printer and highly recommend it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sebby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Extremely Easy Setup</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So far so good. Bought this Canon Model Pixma MG6220 on a recommendation from one of my company&apos;s IT staff. Set up and connection was a breeze with the instructions. Printing was fast cmpared to my old printer. Haven&apos;t scanned or printed photos yet. The wireless feature allows me to put the printer anywhere</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Forensics</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can only print one photo per page</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>When printing directly from a photo card the printer will only allow you to print one photo per page no matter the size of the photo. Additionally, the quality of the photo printed on matte photo paper with the best photo image quality setting is much darker compared to our current photo printer (Canon iP6700D), which has been discontinued.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing customer support</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Fast Print Time

High quality prints. Initially I had some difficulty with set up, but Canon&apos;s customer support was amazing and they provide free support for a year! They even helped me with other software to make the printer work better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gramma</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple and sleek</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Quiet; Photo printing is good; Fast Operation; Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Great Print Quality; Compact Design; Photos are great

Haven&apos;t used print on both sides yet, but all other uses are great. Am a 78 yr. old grandma and totally untechy, so it must be an easy setup. Love the low profile and smooth service.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sloco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Operation; Well documented; Great Photos; Great Print Quality

Cons: Buttons are touchy

A very nicely done product. Canon goes a long way to make this
printer useable. Manual is terrific. Output unmatched quality. Very flexible useage for text, 2 sided printing, photos. Their support programs are excellent. I have an iMac 27 with OSX 10.7.3</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>graphics</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent printer for photographs</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Beautiful pictures.

Cons: Not many envelope sizes.

My pictures are outstanding since I have this new printer. Pictures are almost 3 dimensional. I think the secret is the grey ink that this printer has. Does use a lot of ink though. The only thing is it only does a few size envelopes. Does not print borderless half fold envelopes. I do my own cards &amp; envelopes. I use another printer for my envelopes as it only has sizes for business &amp; a few others.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BillS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>PIXMA MG6220 Photo Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Beautiful color; Very Stylish; Great BW photos

Cons: None

This is a wonderful printer. The manual is very complete and thorough. Drivers for Mac 10.7 are excellent. Trade in an old printer at Staples and get $50 off.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brian964</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far, so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Great outward appearance; Easy To Set Up; Airprint Compatible

Cons: Cumbersome FW upgrade; Tedious SW installation

This is our second Canon printer, and will be used by my daughter for school work and the occasional photo project. The overall build quality appears to be very good, as is the appearance, and the LCD based user interface was very easy to navigate, making initial set-up a breeze. 

Wireless connectivity went off without a hitch. The primary selling point for this printer was Apple Airprint compatibility, which required a firmware upgrade that had to be done using a USB cable. There was one bump along the way, where the upgrade initially failed, but a 2nd try worked w/o issue. It would have been preferable to have been able to do the upgr ... ade via wireless, but since the printer was located adjacent to the PC, using a USB cable was not too much of an issue. That may not be the case for others, in that being a wireless enabled printer, it can be installed anywhere. 

We have not had the printer long enough to really exercise its capabilities and to assess reliability, but based on my previous Canon printer, I do not anticipate any problems. Lastly, given the price, I would say this printer represents excellent value for the money.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Teacher for 21 yrs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The BEST printer I have ever had!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Fast Operation; Easy To Use; Quiet; Great Print Quality

I am a teacher and I do a lot of printing every week. THis is the BEST that I have owned and I have NEVER had any PROBLEMS printing or aligning the print!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doebee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>so glad I bought this printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Reliable; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality

Cons: Slow Operation; May not be fast emough

This is a great home office printer. It may not be fast enough for some users, but for me, it is just fine.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nicemort</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME PRINTER AND EASY TO USE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, prints great pictures, color is perfect

Cons: haven&apos;t found any problems so far

i got to pick out a new printer as my christmas present. i asked a lot of people for advice, did a lot of research and read a lot of reviews. i was very nervous ordering this printer because i was afraid i would never figure out how to link it to my computer. when i finally sat down and tackled the task it ONLY took about 30 minutes and was EXTREMELY SIMPLE!!!!!! everything was step by step and self explanitory. the pictures i printed are awesome and look professional. love this printer!!!! i would highly recommend this printer to anyone and everyone!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ripstar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Reliable; Compact Design; Fast Operation; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Easy To Use

I have had a couple of Canon printers and have been very pleased with them. When my last canon printer finaly died after 9 years. I was given a free Epson printer from a family member. I&apos;m glad I didn&apos;t pay for it. It was noisy and used/wasted a lot of ink. It had the 3 color inks in one cartridge. What a waste of ink that is. We only used that for a few months. It was noisy slow and used a lot of ink. So I decided to shop around for a new printer. I knew I wanted a Canon again and I bought this all in one printer and have not been disapointed. It is fast, quite, and easy to use. I love the seperate ink cartridges I don&apos;t fill like I am throwing my money away evertime one color ne ... eds to be replaced. Print quality is awesome. The wireless capability is great for printing with my laptop, A great printer for the money.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Karaboo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great phot quality, faster than expected.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set up.

Cons: Black finish shows dust, smudges (only negative I could think of).

Scanning old family photos is easy with installed software. Printing is the best quality we have experienced. Speed printing web pages or any text and graphics documents is very good. Speed for photo printing is actually faster than expected.
My wife uses this printer for scrap-booking projects, while I do general photo printing and general document printing.
Setting this printer up for our wireless network was simple, with no surprises.
This printer is also very quiet and takes almost no time to come off of &quot;sleep&quot; mode.
Overall; glad we bought it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JD Admin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Decent Printer for the Price...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Quiet

Cons: Slow warming up

I would only recommend this printer for specific projects, that would require photo or graphic printing. Not for everday use. Scanner is good quality and so is the prints but the speed is very slow to start printing the first page! Can take up to 5 minutes!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: IPhone printing; Great Color Photos

Cons: Inks- Used up fast

We have lived this printer. Very easy SETup. Wireless. Works with iPhone after updating the firmware. Prints amazing photos. Ink used quick and genuine canon ink is not cheap. Love the scan to iPhone feature. And canon has it&apos;s own app which works well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>reyno71</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really Like this Printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Very good quality. Got it for photo and printing uses. I print directly to DVD and that feature works well. Just follow directions and it will work great for you. Had to call customer service to get air print to work with my iPhone and they were great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wildbillc13</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sleek and Solid Performance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features

Cons: Proprietary s/w

I finally decided to stop buying HP printers and so far I&apos;m glad I picked this one.
Pros: The features are great, especially the wireless. You are not forced to use the rear paper feed unless using specialty paper. Auto duplex is great. Pretty slick that you can print right from Picasaweb w/o a computer, not that I would ever use it. I didn&apos;t need a copier, but it&apos;s nice having. The interface is very simple and easy to use, you just have to be careful not to inadvertantly hit a button with your hand at times.

I was diappointed that you need to install the proprietary software in order to see the printer, so it&apos;s not as simple as discovering another WiFi device on the network, but that was minor. It&apos;s also annoying that the manual ... is a program instead of a simple PDF. There is a bit of mechanical gymnastics it goes through occassionally which slows things down, but I think that all printer do this nowadays.

A lot of other reviews complain about ink usage. I think they forget that the ink that comes with a printer is never a full retail cartridge, so I don&apos;t expect them to last.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>searose</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>As Reliable as it is Beautiful</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Great Print Quality; Easy To Use; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Fast Operation

Cons: Large Footprint

The Canon Pixma replaced a competitor&apos;s printer that died after just 3 weeks. The first thing I noticed about the Canon is its superior construction. It is a substantial machine that doesn&apos;t rattle and creak. It operates smoothly and relatively quietly for a printer. It is easy to operate and prints, scans and copies easily and quickly. I love the way the tray opens silently when the printer is engaged. Also the tray is large and tilted up so your copies don&apos;t fall all over the place. The set up was easy and straightforward. I haven&apos;t had the printer too long, so I cannot comment on ink use. I expect it will be comparable to most printers in this class.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Diana the soap lady</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Fast Operation; Reliable; Great Print Quality; Compact Design; Quiet

We only have this printer for a short while, but so far it is everything I expected and more. My husband and I both use it for our businesses as well as personal use. I love the fact that I can print from my laptop without having the office computer on. Also that I can send pictures from my iPhone. The wireless ability of this printer is great. Setup was easy and I found any questions could be answered in the manual.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sstoloff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So far I&apos;ve had excellent results from this printer--easy to set up, simple wireless connection, appealing controls, great print quality. Have only had it a couple of weeks, so I can&apos;t vouch for its durability, but the machine is off to a good start.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>T man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality but burns through ink</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Great Print Quality; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Goes through ink faster

I go through more ink cartridges than my old Canon printer. I beleive the reason is that the newer cartridges are simply smaller than the older ones. I like the quality of the canon products and my previous Canon printer lasted a very long time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pablo D</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>2nd All in One in 4 years !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Really Improved Product

Cons: Too much ink used

If the ink lasted longer, this would be a really super product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Curt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Had a Kodak printer that was a complete waste of money and time so finally threw it out and bought this printer, very quick and easy set up and prints great</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>scooter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far, so good!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve only had this printer for a couple weeks. It replaced our old Canon printer that died without any warning after 4 or 5 years. We were happy with the old one so I stayed with Canon. It prints and scans better than our old one and it&apos;s even quieter. I&apos;m very happy with the results I&apos;ve gotten so far. I have not tried printing anything duplex, printing on a CD, or from camera cards and the like, but I do print out a lot files from photoshop, Illustrator and Indesign and it works just great -- even on plain old paper. I haven&apos;t had to replace any ink cartridges yet so I can&apos;t weigh in on it&apos;s consumption of ink. . I like it and think I made good choice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>I am Technologically Challenged!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT PRODUCT...B&amp;H HAD THE BEST PRICE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great Price, Easy Set up, Great Prints, only gave it a 4 because it was larger than I expected, though had I read the dimensions, it probably wouldnt have been a suprise! My order was delivered the very next day (in Manhattan)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tim Cornillaud</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple, simple, simple.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use the product at home. My wife and I both work at home and print only a few pages a day. Now and then I use it to print photographs. The color and quality in general is pretty amazing. Just used it to print a batch of envelopes for invitations. That was also incredibly easy - though much of the ease came from using Contacts, Numbers, and Pages on my Mac -- loading the envelopes was a snap and they came out perfect. (Other printers I have used tended to crinkle the envelopes.) We print from Thinkpads running windows XP and 7, and from my Mac, iPad, and iPhone. It all works great. Now if I could buy ink without having to take a second mortgage on my house... well... that would be swell!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>brianysf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer - DVD printing a hassle</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is my 3rd Canon printer replacing an office MX882. I no longer needed a home office work horse and wanted something more compact. The MG6220 fit the bill and as a bonus gave me Airprint and Google Print support. If you are getting this to print on DVDs a lot be aware that you need to use a plastic caddy to do it. Not very convenient if you are going to do this a lot. For casual users it&apos;s ok, but just one more thing you might lose/break. Overall I continue to be pleased with the print quality of Canon printers and how quiet they are. I just wish the included software wasn&apos;t so clunky, but if you run Lion or Mountain Lion there is no real need to install anything if all you want to do is print or scan documents.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Squirrelman Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best All-In-One I&apos;ve ever owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Durable construction; Compact Design; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Low Ink Consumption

I like having two All-In-Ones in my home office, just in case one went down, and I was pressed to get something finished. So, I have two of these MG6220s. One of the great things I like about this printer is that when it says you have to replace an ink cartridge, the old one really IS empty. My previous Epson (which I had to do too frenquent of head cleanings) would not let me perform a head cleaning until I replaced an ink cartridge that it said was OUT. On every one of those occasions, the old cartridge was not anywhere near out of ink. So, all that ink got wasted. The Canon MG6220 ROCKS. It also prints directly to printable CD and DVD media.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JIMMY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Already Broken!! Paper feeding broke</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time

Cons: Hard Setup; Too much ink used; Unreliable; Jams Easily

After spending over an hour to set the wireless printer, paper feeding does not work after printing 2 documents!! So far, I am not pleased with this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BOG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

Cons: Too much ink used

AS WITH ALL THE CANON PRINTERS I HAVE OWNED, THIS ONE GREATLY EXCEEDS MY EXPECTIONS!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WVWC Bobcat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Would buy this again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Reliable; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Fast Print Time

Great for what we do around the house and wife&apos;s stampin&apos;up hobby.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sunshine141</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I have had Cannon products in the past.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It fits in the space that I needed it to fit in.

I really like this all in one. I didn&apos;t want the fax option on this, so this works out really well for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>etxxz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t beat Performance &amp; Feat for price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Been using daily for about a month. So far -Pros:Easy SetupWorks amazing - Great quality photos, color, *pixelage!*, and its even fastLooks greatNo-Buttoms/Touch feature is super slickPivoting Screen Super helpful. $ ? seriously? Sold!Opens print gates automatically. Great Packaging!WIRELESS scanning to PC/iPhone, printing backwards no cables needed its the #1 reason i got this.Cons:Ink Expensive? yes - buy aftermarket.No instructions for CD, but that relatively straight.No Fax, continuous scanning - its relatively small.Unknown:Ink Consumption - have no point of reference here.I highly suggest this cannon product. It just needs a power cable to operate. Its 100% wireless there-after. Mine came AirPrint ready. I also downloaded Cannon&apos;s iPhone app which allowed me to scan to my phone/PC. T ... his little printer is amazing. 6ink cartriges. Great vivid colors, no complaints. (i&apos;m no professional photographer, but this is pretty good!)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>arfaith</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice printer for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Upgraded from an older printer. I has impressed with print quality. The standard photo print is a lot better then the max setting on the old printer. The high quality print setting looks like you took them to a pro to have done. I use a Canon T3i camara and the pictures are great. The every day printing and photos looks great but is slow at times to load and print from my wireless connection. Only had a week so can&apos;t comment on the price of operation or durablety.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Retired Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does everything I want well.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Prints on Card Stock; Reliable; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Long Wait to Begin Printi

I looked forever to find a printer that would print on card stock. It isn&apos;t in any of the specs. I finally saw this one in the store and they tried it out for me. It Worked! I also love the duplexing. What a great paper saver.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Charlie Brown</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sweet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>5 stars for the abilities the printer claims it does. For start up though it gets a 1 star slowest start up ever. If you are in a rush to print something then this will cause more anxiety. But if you don&apos;t really care about waiting like a 2 minutes then more power to you. I got Lion for mac and everything works smoothly. Either way Overall Great printer cool look just a bit slow but again if that doesn&apos;t bother you then you&apos;re going to love this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MadisonBoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome prints!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m Amatuer Photo went to Africa recently and all my prints have been from an online service. I bought this printer because my old one had died. I was amazed at the quality of the prints, far superior to the online print service I was using. Just amazing!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This printer is geat. Prints quality photos for the consumer price. Note that one must change the ink settings for the default is too dark. Printing in Adobe 1998 and downloading an ICC profile using the right paper gives professional looking prints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fdorf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>alternate to HP</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Fast Print Time

Cons: Hard Setup; Too much ink used; Hard To Use; Jams Easily

nice machine to look at, but ink cartridges have a quite tiny capacity, setup is more difficult than HP, does not allow full utilization of advanced Photoshop quality prints, does not have high-capacity ink cartridges for an up-price choice, likes to turn itself off overnight, lack of hard-copy owners manual with product, and multi-pack ink packages do not include all the colors</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>John</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My second and best Canon printer by far.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Durable construction

Easy to set up a default printing preferenc with a name like &quot;basic&quot; so it will duplex print on 8.5x11 plain paper vs the photo default it comes with. This way, there is very little nozzle cleaning at the start of a print job, and the printing process is very good. The onle real problem is that this printer comes with too much information with too many options, but you quickly learn to set it up how you need it to work, and it fantastic after that.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Celtia398</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cannon makes great printers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Print quality is excellent

Cons: The wireless printing isn&apos;t flawless

I bought this printer to replace an old Cannon printer I&apos;ve been using for years. This one would allow me to print from my laptop, iPad and iPhone wirelessly, hence the upgrade. Things I&apos;ve printed so far look awesome, but the connection to my laptop drops, which is my bone of contention. If I could consistently connect to the printer, I&apos;d give this a 5 star rating.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GladIswitchedfrpmPC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well done!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy set-up

Cons: Nothing yet

Pictures and documents not only print quality as expected, they also print fairly quickly as touted. I do hope this does not loose steam and will update further if I run into any issues...so far great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Liz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Photo Printer - For Home Use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Prints fast; Fast Print Time; Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint; Wireless Set-up Confusing

Like it so far, Prints fast, great for photos, scanning.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daughter and Father Photo Business</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Choice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So after much research I found this printer that fit all my needs. Prints 8x10, allows you to basic editing and triming on the LCD screen, exceptional quality even on standard quality ( don&apos;t let anyone tell you different). Able to connect and print directly from COMPACT FLASH!! and is pretty darn quick. I originally bought the Canon Pixma 5320( or something similar) from this website being unfamiliar with specification and what i needed I later found out that it doesn&apos;t take a Compact Flash Card. I returned it to the store and opted for an in store credit. After to speaking to all their verrrrrrrrrrryyyy helpful in store reps I found the 6220. It is slow to start but after you print that first photo I would say it takes 40 seconds to print a full 8x10. I used this printer for a Red Carpet ... event, everyone was so pleased and I couldnt of asked for better. Go with this!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Major Miner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Flawless performance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Perfect w Apple device; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Compact Design; Low Ink Consumption; Reliable

Perfect for iPad and iPhone wireless printing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hammer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Use; Low Ink Consumption; Durable construction; Compact Design; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Needed firmware update

Allows direct wireless printing from iPad. Instructions did not address this. Had to go online and download firmware update to get it to work. Color printing on plain paper is only moderately bright</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tmak</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been looking for a photo printer that is reasonable until i came across this printer. The device is exceptional and affordable. It produces great quality prints. Highly recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jagged</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canons are ink eaters</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: If not for the cons this is good printer that takes up less space than others I&apos;ve had and prints well. Wireless is great and allows all my computers to use it.

Cons: When you need to print something fast you had better hope the printer doesn&apos;t decide to clean its heads. A 30 second print job can take a while when it cleans itself first.

Oh and its cleaning procedure seems to use up a lot of ink as well. I rarely use color for most of my printing but the printer still seems to eat the color ink like crazy. I assume the cleaning process is eating the ink!

Not a terrible printer but expect to buy a bunch of color ink even if you rarely print in color!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JICS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Purchased as a replacement for an older HP Inkjet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality of print.. Scan and copying modes a plus.

Cons: Required # of separate ink tanks and speed at which they need replacing.

Probably purchased a printer somewhat beyond my needs, but does have a nice print quality. Seems to take longer to prepare for printing than I would like (after print tab has been chosen). Biggest complaint - this thing goes through ink &apos;tanks&apos; like there&apos;s no tomorrow. Perhaps with additional setting changes, this can be remedied. May need to check w/ the Canon folks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>eZAK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-In-One printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent photo printing!

Cons: None

The Canon MG6220 is a great all in one printer. It does everything but fax.
It produces &amp; re-produces great documents at a very decent speed.
It also prints fabulous photos from cards, the internet, or your PC.
Hook up (USB &amp; Ethernet) and install (disc) are easy, as is adding ink.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GPeters</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All In 1 Printer / Scanner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Print From Phone

Wireless Or Wired You Choice... Or Network.
Even Use It With Your Smart Phone.
Even Pauses Between Pages To Let The Ink On The last Page Dry.

Love It !!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kennedy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pixma=great product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this printer for everyday use. I&apos;ve printed one photo and it looked great. I have not used the cd printer yet. I like how this printer gives you different print options to save paper!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MacMarc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great performance, just not sure about i</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been a Canon enthusiast for many years and also have a Pro 9000 Mark II, This PIXMA replace an i6700 that served me well for many years. They have obviously improved and I&apos;m thrilled with this machine. Like some other owners, it looks like ink consumption is high, as it seems to re-prime the heads often. However, this may be a start-up issue. I would still recommend this printer to anyone looking for a great all-around machine that also prints great photos!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Owllady</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love, Love, Love!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Print Quality; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Fast Operation; Reliable; Quiet

Cons: Hard Setup

I had someone set it up for me, but easy to use afterwards.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NickD1234</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great quality, quiet, nice features and low consumption of ink compared to HP and Epson printers I have had in the past. I can&apos;t think of any negatives. I would highly recommend this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OaklandJohn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No real complaints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless printing, photo quality

Cons: Goes through ink fast

Finally upgraded my All-in-One and I&apos;m impressed by the Canon.
Love that it&apos;s wireless; sits on standby until your ready for it. Updated the software so I can print from my iPad...very handy.
Scanner works great and the photo prints are excellent.

Print speed is good once it gets warmed up, but seems to take a bit of time to get the docs queued up or into the printer memory...
It does seem to go through ink pretty fast. I&apos;m already needing to replace a black cartridge. If you do a lot of document printing, I could see it getting a little pricey.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RRecords</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works well</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this product specifically to print directly on CDs. Instructions manual, however, does not explain how to insert the tray. Print is smearing on my Sony discs, will be trying another brand to see if it&apos;s the disc or ink. It&apos;s very high-tech, really like the wireless connection. Printing on regular paper isn&apos;t as good as my laser printer, have not yet tried photo paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joe M.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-in-one Printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Great Print Quality; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

Great print quality as well as good copying and scan quality.Much quieter than my old Lexmark S604 which broke after little more than 1yr use out of it.Hope this printer last longer than Lexmark as many Cannon users experienced.It was easy to set up with WPS button on my router.Very comprehensive software package.I got this printer while it was on sale at [$] with extra $10 off coupon which made good value.Overall, great printer. I am happy with my purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>oswego</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great easy set up to print wireless with no issues</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy

Cons: Tray feed on bottom

Great easy set up to print wireless with no issues seems to even print thick post card paper stock. Use it at home might even buy one for office.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ali</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good, solid printer for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Fast Operation; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Compact Design; Reliable; Easy To Use

Cons: Flimsy Construction

I received this printer as a Christmas gift. I like the touch function buttons and the fact that I can download an app to my iphone and ipad to print wirelessly to this printer right from those devices.I&apos;m happy with this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>carezee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wireless printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you are looking for a good wireless printer, this is the one. It has all the bells and whistles. It can print from your computer , scan or make copies. Color photos are superb.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Buzzy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does Exactly What I Wanted It To</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Fast Operation; Quiet; Great Print Quality; Compact Design; Airprint Works

Cons: Expensive ink; Hard Setup; Lots of Time to Setup

Great Functionality - Looks &amp; Works Great Too !

But why does such a new product need such extensive work &amp; downloads to obtain some of the featured functions (like Airprint) - come on Canon; you can do better !

Staples - you need to offer some Canon ink coupons not just HP. I only have (1) HP Printer left and it&apos;s getting tossed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JB cat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Prints cd&apos;s and dvd&apos;s; Compact Design; Easy To Use; Fast Operation; Reliable; Quiet

Cons: None

As always, Canon manufactured a sturdy, reliable, and dynamic printer...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jack</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer so far.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>The printer has worked great so far. The few pages I have printed look very good. My only complaint is the ink levels. I have only printed about 30 pages and they were mostly black. Both black tanks show full but the other four show 1/2 full. If that is a true indication of the ink usage I can&apos;t afford to use this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Old school techguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Right printer for photos, right price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Wireless easy setup; CD printer

Cons: Slightly large footprint

Good choice for a photo printing, better than the quick digital prints within local stores, which then pays for itself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sonny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Print Quality; Reliable; Fast Operation; Easy To Use; Quiet; Compact Design

Mine required download of additional software for Lion. 
So far, it has been great printer. 
As with all Canon printers, ink is costly. 
They could probably give the printers away because I am sure they make a killing on the ink.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nogrey</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t bother if you are a Mac lion User</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this printer based on canons web site and their proclaimed Mac comparability. Much to my surprise, that&apos;s only true if you&apos;re using older Mac OS. I&apos;m a very avid Canon proponent, and have been a user of their pro cameras and camcorders for years. It surprises me that a tech savvy company like Canon that I personally respect would be remiss to consider the vast group of professional photographers that use Mac products, and leave them out of their consideration on a new product release. After inserting the software cd and finding the not compatible with your OS message, I spent 3 hours on the canon website wading through their convoluted and totally non-descript software, firmware and driver downloads for Mac lion OS users. After a very long installation process without the benefit ... of instruction, I finally arrived at the apps software and installed it. All I can say is it was a very lame attempt by canon to throw together some very poor apps that operated with minimal efficacy. VERY DISAPPOINTING! This could be the best printer in the world but Mac lion user will never know it. Back in the box and returned. Needless to say I didn&apos;t purchase another canon printer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Maine Coone</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great photo prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Great Resolution; Great picture quality

Cons: None

I wanted great photo prints and this printer delivers</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>me</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>returned printer for HP 7510</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design

Cons: Hard To Use; Slow Print Time; Hard Setup; Unreliable

no commnts</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>difficult to connect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design

Cons: Hard To Use; Hard Setup

took us 2 days to set up and reset and reset wont recognize the wifi connection. pain in the neck!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sonoerin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Typical Canon Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

Cons: Large Footprint

Great results at a great price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: GOOD DESIGN; Great Print Quality; Easy To Use; Fast Operation

Cons: Hard Setup

Once set up, the printer is very easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>REVDOC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good replacement for bad HP</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy install, great paper handling

Very pleased with operation, delivery..
Installation took awhile, but easy to follow instructions</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Oski77</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time

We were tired of the smart printer that spent 5 minutes spooling up and then misfeed paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Macman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use

Great printer, easy to setup and prints great photos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Carlsbad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer for an upgrade for photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Eady to install. Quality of pics is excellent

Cons: Nothing bad

I am loving this printer. Excellent ink life. Easy to set up on computer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HappyGS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the colors and how fast it prints.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is very easy to use.

Cons: It is big in size.

My pictures come out looking amazing. They look professional.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mikey Sanchez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy setup and awesome photo printing!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use it for household text printing and amatuer photo printing. It was easy to setup on both computers and doesn&apos;t use up a lan cord.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I am pleased with this product,</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Easy To Use; Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption; Reliable

Top Quality</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gordon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Use

Construction of the bottom tray seems a bit flimsy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Don</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good all around</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Fast Operation; Easy To Use; Quiet; Compact Design; Great Print Quality; Easy To Set Up

None</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Maverick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great looking but poor color</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Slow Operation

I thought it would have better color quality!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Walrus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice weather</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Quiet; Fast Operation; Great Print Quality; Compact Design; Easy To Use

Cons: Print cartridges too smal

otherwise works well</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>over the hill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good with faults</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Good quality output

Cons: Very slow startup; Noisy; Large Footprint; Annoying idling shutoff

I&apos;ve had Canons that I liked better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tammy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this product!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Great Print Quality; Fast Operation; Reliable; Compact Design

Cons: None

We love this printer</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>caseybhen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love this printer so far. I haven&apos;t tried the disc printing yet, but all other functions have worked as advertised, and it was easy to set up.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>155</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Buy as recmded by Consumer Reports</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to set up and works great</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>156</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Merc1120</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Photo printer there is !!!!!!!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quility of print &amp; the speed of the print

Cons: n/a

You just could not do better for the price !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>157</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>G. W.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I am very happy with this product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Durable construction; Low Ink Consumption; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use

very good</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>158</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Danz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>like that generic cartridges are availab</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

like that generic cartridges are available</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>159</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Happy Jack</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy set up but</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to set up but the paper tray seems flimsy and it takes a long time to print if its been awhile since the last print job. Only had it a short while.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>160</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cindy the Photographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great printer, but</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast; Reliable; Quiet; Easy To Use

This is a great printer, but it prints darker than my actual pics.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>161</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fadecruless</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>cannon always rocks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Thanks B&amp;H for a great deal and fast service to my door.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>162</ID>
     <Item>Canon PIXMA MG6220 Color Ink-jet - Printer / copier / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/9807708144286832200/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CPEBEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nemo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Seems like a solid build quality. Easy to use. Does it all.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

