<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LAPTOP Magazine</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>LAPTOP Magazine</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson WorkForce 845 All-in-One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy setupLarge variety of printing optionsFast wireless print speedsFaxing capability

Cons: Files print slower than competition via appsLarge and heavy

Aimed at home offices, the $139 Epson WorkForce 845 takes advantage of its extra-large size to bring you paper capacity more than three times as large as competing all-in-one printers. This all-in-one also features quick wireless printing speeds, a bevy of mobile printing options and an intuitive setup process. Plus, the WorkForce 845 offers two-sided printing to save you time, in addition to copying, scanning and faxing capability. You won&apos;t find a more versatile all-in-one for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>geojtod</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer for Home Office</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features, Size, Quality

Cons: Ink Cost

The Product has a very nice Dsigh and preforms well in a Home Office environment. The setup instructions could be much better.
Tech Support is reasonable and faster than expected but understanding of customer problem is weak. If Tech support can not answer your problem they just drop you. I hope to find the CEO to report this.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Au Naturale Health and Wellness Center</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I Bought Two!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

My previous printer, a Kodak AIO, was nothing but trouble with frequent paper jams and slow printing. When the printhead went out at less than 2 years old I was back to printer shopping again.I have had Epson printers in the past when photography was a hobby and was familiar with their high quality inks and printing. The reviews for this printer, the Epson Workforce 845, were so good on [@]that I quickly decided it was &apos;the one.&apos; I ran into Staples on my way to work and bought it, took it back to the office and had it set up and running in just minutes. Compared to what I was used to, the print quality in &apos;normal&apos; mode is better than the high quality on my Kodak. The print speed in &apos;normal&apos; mode is much faster and it is much more q ... uiet as well. And then... the print head went out on my Canon at home (at least it is 6 or 7 years old). I really didn&apos;t even need to shop, it was a no-brainer to purchase another 845. I love this machine!So far, printing receipts is fast -- we no longer stare at each other awkwardly while waiting for the printer. Print quality on labels with graphics is excellent. Copying is very fast and the touchscreen controls are simple. Scan quality it perfect - I can hardly tell the copy from the original. I put the double sided printing to work immediately and breathed a sigh of relief -- no more turning paper by hand and trying to figure out which side goes up! Booklet printing, which took HOURS by hand, just happens. The wireless connectivity is so easy (something that took hours to achieve on the old Canon). A few touches on the screen and its on my network and available. I didn&apos;t think I needed the two paper trays, but the convenience of that is more than I dreamed. At home we have paper in the top and labels in the bottom. At work, using both trays, the printer holds an entire ream of paper. AND, it comes with full size ink tanks! I bought extra ink since most don&apos;t and you run out within a few prints. So, when considering the price of this printer, factor in that you don&apos;t need to immediately purchase replacement inks.Set up tips: don&apos;t connect it to your computer right away. Plug in the printer and follow the prompts. When it is initialized, having a USB cable handy to connect to your computer speeds up the driver download and computer set up. Then set up the wireless connection and you are done. About 15 minutes altogether. Now, if it lasts forever, it will be the perfect printer!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kwiktrax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just short of Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>After 10 years in a public agency developing, writing, and supporting customer service applications, it is easy for me to say that installing network pirnters was almost always a bit of a pain. I remember one printer that came with a 30 page installation guide and 10 pages of trouble shooting instructions. Now retired, I do have a home network, 3 PC&apos;s and an Android Tablet, and the 845 printer fully installed on this network in about 4 minutes: including the download of the combination drivers. That is impressive software design from my point of view. When setting up my laptop, running on a Win 8 preview install, I received a small window on start up asking if I wanted to search for printer drivers. I consented and by the time I found my way to the devices folder, about 1 minute later, thi ... s Epson 845 was installed and selected as the primary printer. That is customer focused software design. Both the printer and photo memory card slot show up as Network folders in the Win 7 Directory automatically and selecting the memory card quickly brings up photos on the card ready for printing or editing. MORE GOOD The 845, while big and tall, has a compact design and appearance. It fit and looks just fine in our home library setting. My last higher priced network printer, which died of acute print head failure after 3 years, produced hard to beat very good text, graphics, and exceptional photo prints in best format. But the Epson-845 does this better in all categories. I have compared photos, graphics and text with work from my last network printer and I am really pleased. The touch menu screen is clear and easy to read. It has a well organized menu stucture and is quick and easy to use. I have found myself in circular hunting for specific selections now and then, but I do like the touch menu concept. The NOT so good This printer is a noisy creature. The best sound comparison I can make is that of a cardboard carton being pulled across a cement floor. It is a bit noisy even for a small office setting. I remain annoyed with this so far. The paper edge slider on the document feeder is disappointing. Instead of having two guides that slide paper toward the center of the document feeder, there is only one sliding guide on the left that moves about 1 inch. This means for you that smaller sized documents, like my many bills and other erata, can skew when pulled in for scan-copying and selecting the software designed to auto straighten these skews is not always successful. This means that documents less than 8 in width are subject to skewing. A reckless design oversight. Everytime I load the paper trays, (the sliders bend and don&apos;t move smoothly), I find myself thinking, how long before the plastic cracks or breaks. The trays and sliders may last for the printer&apos;s lifetime, but the feel and sound is not reassuring or confidence building. I have read remarks about inconvenient enevelope tray design. That the user needs to pull all paper out of tray 1, where envelopes must be loaded every time you want to print envelopes. If you have an office that does a lot of printing and needs both trays for paper, this may become an issue for your situation. In fact, all specialty papers, including photo paper must go in tray 1. While I print frequently, I have not found using tray 1 for storing envelopes an issue for me. Even though I do have to pull the envelopes when photo printing: which is an occasional use for me. My conclusion There is a lot I like about this printer and, in the end, the overall quality of Epson-845&apos;s printing is what is convincing me to keep it. But if I start getting complaints from family about skewed copies, or noise, or I am lost in the menu, I may choose to give it up. If quality business grade printing and graphics is primary for you, which it is for me, and the specifics of my complaints are way down on your list, then for the price, this unit is a genuine bargain.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>garagefather</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A real powerhouse for the home office</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Downsized version of a full office document center

Cons: Nothing so far

I found this printer to exceed my humble needs by a large margin. It is basically a downsized version of a pro office document center.

I found the setup very basic and straight forward. There is the option of setting it up from the printer control display or connecting via USB and setting it up using you computer and the setup disk. I just set up the printer manually from the touch panel and it was quite easy. The provided disc runs you through the step but the display does as well. I connected to the wireless router quite easily and was up and running in about 5 minutes. I then used the provided disk to load the drivers on my devices and was able to select out most bloatware. I am sure the d ... rivers are available from Epson if you want to avoid all bloatware. One item that was loaded onto my laptop was and Epson scanner utility with a shortcut to my desktop. It also installed a download navigator and event manager which I haven&apos;t looked into further. Basically standard bloatware you may find interesting or not.

I did the full setup which sets up the fax as well as the web address to enable you to email pics from your connected devices from anywhere. It is a long and random address so you will have to save it in each device or you will never remember it. You can also send it to family and they can send pics directly to your printer from anywhere with a wi-fi or cell connection.

I found the touchscreen to work quite nicely with the virtual buttons large enough to prevent fumbling through selections. The screen is a monotone orange but it is pleasing enough and works well. It can adjust from fully flush to the face of the printer or it can tilt out up to about 45 degrees for easy viewing while standing. I felt it was a nice touch which made the printer a little more ergonomic.

It has a top feed for scanning and copying and the lid lifts for placing oddly shaped or smaller items for scanning or copying. The unit holds 500 sheets of paper in 2 trays that front load. T ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mattysue</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Happy with Workforce 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use NCR paper for our work orders, but use plain paper for our printed schedules and all other documents. I love how you can choose which cassettes to use for which type of document and it remembers. No need to change settings each time we print or even restart the computer. We can also set faxes to default to the cassette we have plain paper in. Saves time as well as NCR paper. The quality of print is great. The display pad is adjustable and easy to use. We have used it daily now for 3 weeks and I&apos;ve only used 1/3 of a black cartridge and barely tapped the colors, even after printing 500 watermarks. The document feeder for faxes and copies folds up and disappears when not in use. The price was reasonable and it&apos;s very economical to use. I would highly recommend this printer!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Majikk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-in-One with many features.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless and tons of features

Cons: Loud when printing and high cost when color printing

The Epson 845 is great at providing the All-in-One function for the home user or home office.

There are an abundance of features and each feature works easily without any problems. The initial setup of just to the wireless network and installing it on 3 home computers (2 Win 7 and 1 Mac ) took about 15 mins total. A few days after the initial setup I setup the scanning over wireless, fax line, and print from cloud features. All setup was simple and straight forward. Actually because of the simple setup there is a limit on how many advanced settings you can change. I typically like the more difficult setup with the advanced setting to change/modify everything. My complaint abo ... ut the features is that not all features available over USB (scanning functions mainly) are available via LAN or Wireless.

Although I do not print a lot of color it does not appear to be very economical for color printing. Black and white printing seems to be ok for the price. Both types of printing have mid to excellent quality where even the mid quality is beautiful. Where it is really helps economically is the automatic Standby function. It goes into Standby mode when not in use saving on power where my old laser printer would waste electricity even in Sleep mode. My biggest complaint about printing is how loud it is, but as long as somebody is not sleeping in the same room you should be ok.

All things considered this is a great All-in-One machine and I like that it can be on the other side of the room (or the house for that matter) and I can do everything I need to wirelessly with just a power cord.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PCGremlin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid, stable drivers, great print quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Stable drivers, easy installation, very good print quality, solid construction overall

Cons: Paper trays made of a thinner plastic and adjustment is stiff

Drivers, hardware, print quality and speed are excellent and stable.

Out of the box, the printer is well packed and secured with lots of areas taped down: be sure to examine the printer carefully that you have removed all of the taped and wrapped parts before using.

Installation of the drivers under Windows 7 64-bit, 32-bit, Vista and XP is smooth and essentially foolproof with one minor exception: the instructions refer to the temporary use of a USB cable when setting up the wireless connection. You might think that you&apos;d have to set the printer up as a USB connection first, then set it up in wireless m ... ode...not true.

If you want to set it up in wireless mode, select that option when installing the drivers and you will see a separate window giving you the option to either use a USB cable temporarily or use the front panel of the printer.

Installation of the full set of drivers and support software can take over 20 minutes, depending on the options checked. I initially set up the printer in USB mode, then Ethernet, then wireless: all were easy to do. Once you have the printer online, Win 7 finds the printer on the network automatically and downloads a driver for you, for any other computers on the network you may have. Win XP requires a manual install, but is still easy to do.

In addition, Epson has released an Android and iOS compatible app for printing/scanning wirelessly from your iPad/Phone or Android Phone/Tablet. It worked perfectly on my Samsung Galaxy Tablet 10.1 (Honeycomb) and Samsung SII 4G (Gingerbread) phone. For the Android version I tested, printing is limited to PDF documents and JPG pictures. Scanning a document results in a PDF on your phone or tablet. Scanning a picture results in a JPG. Printing is painless: just be careful to pay attention to the paper size you select. If it is not a standard paper size, like 8.5X11, the app assumes you are printing a photograph of some sort and only gives you photo quality paper options.

The printer itsel ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dinotaco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent with one small flaw</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: True ALL in one - great value.

Cons: Dual cassette tray setup is backwards but easy to bypass.

Super true ALL in one machine. Love the auto document feeder. The one flaw is with the two paper cassettes. Cassette 1 is designed to hold special sized papers for photos. Cassette 2 holds a large volume of standard paper. However, cassette 1 is the default cassette. When leaving the machine you have to have regular paper in cassette 1 in order to receive faxes. When I have a large print job I have to go to print preferences and change the settings to cassette 2. I feel the cassette that holds the special papers should be the one to require the special settings. Seems backwards to me. BUT WOULD STILL BUY THE PRINTER AGAIN EVEN WITH THIS SMALL FLAW!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Papua</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great device for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet,easy to use,reliable

Cons: Somewhat large size

I was pleasantly surprised by the quality and good performance of this Epson product. Set-up a little tricky but doable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LairdL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I like the thing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

Setup was a breeze. Works with Smart phone iPrint app...scan from smart phone (to phone) or print from phone. WiFi setup perfectly. Prints fast. In eco mode it prints a page in 2 seconds.
Multi trays are great because I do a lot of photos and documents. And it comes with a 20 page automatic doc feeder. Scan to one file or 20 separate files.
Abby OCR hasn&apos;t missed a word, including small newpaper text. 
FAX too. 
I like the thing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>epson01221112</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great all around printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great wireless range, easy to set up

Cons: Not the best for pictures

I bought this printer for the wireless capabilities and home office printing features and it has not let me down. It was super easy to set up. It has good print speed. The auto duplex printing is a great feature and helps cut down on paper usage. The one down fall is that it doesn&apos;t have the best picture printing quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Epson user</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Workforce 845 easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use

Cons: Hard Setup; Large Footprint

Would like to have seen more improvements like speed and quality of print. But appears to be reliable like the 610 (until it jammed and then had to replace it.) Good printers for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gundar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great MFD for a good price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to setup, good price (on sale), cheap ink, Wifi connection

Cons: Nothing

I love this MFD. I got it for $129 on sale and I couldn&apos;t be happier. I like it so much I&apos;ve bought a total of 3 (2 for family and friends). It prints great quality documents quickly and without fuss. I haven&apos;t printed any pictures yet so I can&apos;t vouch for that. The ink is cheap (relatively) and lasts forever. It doesn&apos;t &quot;self-clean&quot; constantly so you aren&apos;t losing ink all the time. The Wifi was easy to setup and get connected. The menu is bright (but not annoying), clear and concise. I would recommend this to anybody in need of a new MFD. I think the only people that wouldn&apos;t want this are those that are set on getting a Laserjet. I wanted a Laserjet but I couldn&apos;t pass this deal up and I&apos;m g ... lad I didn&apos;t because I&apos;ve had it for maybe 6 months now and I&apos;m still using the &quot;sample&quot; ink package that came with it. I bought a replacement B&amp;W extra large cartridge for less than $30 (color is less than $50) and haven&apos;t had to use it yet. Stop the hunt! Buy this MFD!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>2thman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great features for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy setup with good prompts, wireless a breeze, firmware upgraded automatically, 2 paper trays!

Cons: paper trays are the usual flimsy ones, would like a switch on display to manually select which tray

Picked up at Best Buy tonight after our Canon MX700 printer died today (it was 4 years old). Loving the wireless - setup real easy. Was deciding between HP and Epson after reading reviews. All were marked down from $199, this one happened to be the least cost, but I chose it mainly because it came with 2 paper trays, usually something (especially on HP) that cost extra.
Time will tell of course how it does with the usual printer problems: paper jams, ink not recognized, cost, ink thirst and cost per copy. Speed seemed slow in specs, but seems faster than what we ... had previously. Print quality appears good - no pictures yet.
This model was not on display, so sales rep offered to open it so I could check it out. After I decided to buy it, I jokingly asked if it is reduced because it was an open box item. She laughed, but at the checkout she told me she gave me an extra 10% off because of the open box. Loving Best Buy right now (I do buy a good amount though as silver premier member).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>landdog49</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does Not Meet Expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Slooooooooooow. There are too many steps to scan and save a PDF document. You have to click open the application, then click to scan, then click to save (slooooooow) and then to click to close a new window that automatically pops up showing your desktop where you saved the file. It sticks an ascending number behind each new saved file. This causes problems if you have a number as the last part of your file name especially when you do a file search and that number is a unique identifier. In the Home mode there is no auto document feed. It has a Magazine option but you have to place each page on the scanner bed. Then manually turn the page over to copy the other side. Or try to use the Office mode which has an Automatic Document Feed (ADF) setting which jams every time a magazine page is pla ... ce in it. Also, if your letter or legal size page is not perfectly, that is has a fold or wrinkle it will jam. Most of the time when I load pages that were stapled at the top, then read by turning the pages creating a fold, the pages will jam. Even after smoothing the folds as much as possible. Pages have to be 8.5 inches wide or they ADF will jam. Sometimes the printer will make you turn it off then back on after a paper jam. And there is always at least one button to be pushed on the printer if there is any problem. There is no way to clear up problems from the computer alone.
In the Home mode you have to Preview the page first. You can’t just scan it and there is no ADF.
My 5 year old Canon that this Epson replace was faster and easier. Epson ink cost is less. The print quality and speed are average.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TutorMonster</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Printer/Scanner/Fax for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

Grabbed this while shopping for a 545 noticing the price was only $20 more. Was THAT a great move. The two-sided printing is superb, worth the price of admission. Scans well too. Great buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mary7324</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Produce</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast printer, large paper trays for lots of documents

Cons: Paper trays flimsy. Not a real biggie

It is extremely fast. I print flyers for marketing. They are full color pages, but not photos. Don&apos;t know how photos look. All around a nice printer for lots and lots of pages. Installation relatively easy. Love the duplex printing. No need to print even or odd pages, flip them, etc. Like the touch screen control panel. Well organized. The price of this printer is amazing. Haven&apos;t had it long enough to rate it for the distance. Faxing is easy with the document feeder.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer , love the double side printing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: double side printing

Cons: print speed, while using the wireless

Found this printer at a competitor&apos;s store while on SALE. I buy most of my electronics at Best Buy. So looked on BB.com to see what store had one in stock. They did and went down to see if they would match the extreamly low price. The sales person checked and said that they could. Saved $65!!
Up graded from a old Lexmark, ink was getting too expensive.
Love everything about this printer except the transfer speed using the wireless feature. Just seems to have a 15 second lag time from the time I hit print. Not a major issue for me.
Not sure about ink consumption! These cartridges are initially cheaper to purchase (under $15). And don&apos;t forget Wednesday&apos;s @ BB, ink cartridges price reduction. I cann ... ot afford to spend $35 - 40 a pop when it runs out. Plus, I like having all colors sold individually.
NOTE the dimensions listed. That is with all the paper trays (2) and printed sheet holder open. The actual footprint is approximately 14 x 17.5. I&apos;ve had this printer for 2 months.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JPoirier</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT All-in-one, but a little slow</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features, wireless, quality

Cons: Prints a little slow, slow to warm up.

I LOVE the design of this printer. I needed something for light home use and heavier business use (scanning, emailing, document printing). It&apos;s sleek and the thought put into everything makes up for it&apos;s slightly bulky size. In the past when I&apos;ve had auto-feed scanners I&apos;ve had issues with the trays because they get bumped or something is set on them and breaks the tray. This slick printer has a well-thought out design that allows you to safely tuck everything out of harms way (the touch screen, the scanner tray, etc). All GREAT features so you never have to worry about breaking your investment! Set up was extremely fast, including with the wireless. My only complaint is the printer takes quite a l ... ong time to warm up when it&apos;s been in sleep mode, and takes a bit longer than I&apos;d hoped to print. But the sleek design, clean wireless set up and available features definitely make up for what it lacks in speed! (I don&apos;t think waiting 30 seconds as opposed to 15 is going to hurt when it saves me from having multiple different items to do all these tasks!)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson Workforce 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This printer is very fast, and very full featured. I wanted a printer that was wirelss and all in one. When the price was reduced, I bought it, and was pleasantly surprised with all of the little extra bonuses. Double sided printing is not easy to come by, and if you have ever worked in an office, or been in college or university, you know it is really handy. Even the scanner is fast. About the only problem I had was when I was setting it up, had a problem with the password for the wireless router being accepted, but the tech support helped me out (although they were reluctant at first, suggesting I call the router tech support, but I suppose I would have done the same thing). I would recommend this product to others, and also am happy with the tech support.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tony</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Compact Design

Works great, love having two paper trays. Prints fast. Only downfall is picture quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Farn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Printer, Good Price from Staples</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Low Ink Consumption; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Reliable

Prints fast and clear. Copy function is great, especially the two-sided option. Haven&apos;t used the fax yet. Have it about 2 months and so far no complaints. Also, price from Staples was $60 less than Epson site.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ms. Williams</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Happy With My Choice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Durable construction; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Fast Print Time

I am so happy with my choice. This is one of the Best printer&apos;s that I have ever owned. The set up was easy and the performance is unbelieveable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bruce</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Reliable; Easy To Use; Low Ink Consumption; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

This is the best printer I&apos;ve owned. I bought a HP 8600e first but returned it because the auto document feeder &quot;cocked&quot; the pages &amp; the scans or prints would look skewed. Also, the 8600e would not feed photo paper from the paper trays.
This printer has neither problem. It not only prints dual sided but will scan dual sided from the auto doc feeder. It prints very fast with excellant print quality. The wireless print feature works well with both my PC &amp; iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JungleJack</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Truly an Excellent All Around Package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: WiFi, Paper Capacity, Excellent All Around Performance

Cons: Given the Price, Nothing

Hello,
The Epson Workforce 845 is Epson&apos;s Flagship All in One Printer. It is perfectly capable for Small Businesses and excels in the Home Office.

Printing Speeds and Quality are excellent. As is the 500 Pages of Paper holding capacity. Add in a 7.8 Inch Touch Panel, WiFi Capability, Auto Duplexing (Copying on both sides of a page of paper) for up to 30 Pages automatically loaded via Automatic Document Feeder (ADF), and a very slick User Interface via Epson&apos;s Business Application Suite.The ADF also allows for regular Copying of up to 30 Pages One Sided as well. There are also Ports of a USB Memory Thumb Drive and Memory Card Reader. I should note In regards to the Software, t ... hat I used a PC throughout, but have read that the Workforce 845 is also Compatible with Apple Computers.

As for Industrial Design, I really like the Black Finish and thanks to the aforementioned Touch Panel, the only phyical button is the On/Off Switch. It all makes for a very attractive package.

In addition to WiFi, the 845 can be connected to a Computer via USB and Ethernet. For an Inkjet Printer, I was quite impressed with the quality on all materials. I used the Fine Setting for all applications and while it uses more Ink, I really think the quality approaches that of a Laser Printer.

Speaking of Ink, Epson uses a good bit larger than average capacity Ink Cartridges. Especially if using in a Business Application, this will be an excellent feature.

At 22 Pounds, the Workforce 845 is light enough to preform dual duty as both a Home and Business All in One. I still cannot believe the Feature Set, Printing Quality, and Industrial Design considering the price. While currently On Sale, the 845 is well worth the full MSRP.
I have been so impressed with the Workforce 845 that I have urged many friends and family to get one as well. Not one who has done so has had a single complaint. Truly an excellent product at an excellent price.
Cheers,
JJ
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BSquare</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Printer Yet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Reliable

love the fact that it has two document bins that you can setup for either letter or legal paper.
saves me from having to get up and change the paper manually. 
A great multifunction printer.
Still wish I could find one that is capable of printing two-sided legal size paper. Must be too difficult to control flipping 14&quot; long sheets?</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Like it so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

I can&apos;t get the fax to answer properly with the answer machine. I replaced a all-in-one HP because the printheads went out and I could buy this machine for the cost to replace them. Never had a fax problem with the HP, but was frustrated that if the printhead needs replacing the machine will not do anything until replaced. This maching went on sale the next day at a different store but Staples did the price match.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ZackaryStorm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Purchase this printer. Seriously. It&apos;s amazing.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up, awesome double sided printing, mind-blowing photos, extra high capacity ink

Cons: Nothing. It rocks!!

THIS PRINTER ROCKS! I am a nursing student, so every week before clinical, I am printing a mountain of paperwork. This thing tackles it like it isn&apos;t anything. Prints so quickly, and is so ink-efficient. I have been using it heavily for about a month now, and the black cartridge is still just above half (and mind you, I mean VERY heavily.) It prints photos that look like they were professionally done. They look marvelous.

The scanner is amazing, also. The automatic document feeder runs through my documents like they are nothing, and the copy speed and quality are amazing as well. Scanning into your PC can be done wirelessly, a functionality I have ... n&apos;t seen before in other wireless printers.

The AirPrint feature for iPhone, iPod, and iPad is amazing. Set up is so easy, and I love it. Wireless networking set up was a breeze, walks you right through it. Range on the printer is fantastic as well, it is about 50-60 feet away from me, through like 6 walls, and has absolutely no connectivity issues.

The onboard EPSON software is also amazing, EPSON Scan is so user friendly, and the status monitor shows very accurate ink information and detailed error information if the printer encounters a jam or something.

The two cassettes for paper are awesome, you can change the default cassette in the printer and in the EPSON software. Cassette 2 is plain paper only, Cassette 1 can do just about anything.

The automatic double sided printing is something else I cannot live without anymore. It never smears, and has yet to jam in the duplexer. In fact, the printer hasn&apos;t ever jammed for me.

Included cartridges are extra high capacity 127s, they last forever and a day it seems. The nice thing about 4 cartridges is that they can be replaced as needed, rather than having to waste extra ink in a tricolor cartridge.

Long story short, best printer I have ever had, and you need to buy it. I got it on sale for $140, but even $199 is a FANTASTIC PRICE for this device. It&apos;s just plain amazin ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mobilemaf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well rounded machine - reasonable price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Well featured, easy to set up and use

Cons: Print cartridges (for any printer!) are expensive...

I had two Artisan 835&apos;s which I loved but, for whatever reason, failed to print correctly. Because I had purchased the extra protection plan (which I recommend), I had a Best Buy credit to apply toward a new machine. I liked the 835 but they didn&apos;t have any in stock - so I upgraded. The Workforce 845 is a well rounded machine; prints fast, has good features and has a fairly fast scanner. It was easy to set up. I have appreciated the document feeder, dual paper trays, duplex printing and I love the button that allows you to &quot;print ruled paper&quot;. I can recommend this printer, especially if you can find it on sale - at full retail price I may have chosen a different brand / mode ... l.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HeartSleeve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works like a charm! Wicked fast!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Compact Design

Cons: Too much ink used

Ive only had it a few weeks. Just finished a print-heavy project and it worked quickly, easily and cost-effectively. Havent tried all the bells and whistles yet but does b&amp;w, all diff sizes of photos, sticky labels etc with no problems at all.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mdefoe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than HP OfficeJet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Couldn&apos;t be easier to setup and use

Cons: On the louder side of inkjet printers

I review, review, review before buying anything over $20. I was about ready to purchase an OfficeJet 6500 when I read a review, probably on reviews.cnet.com, and they listed this as the go-to home Do-It-All printer.

After witnessing first-hand the decline in quality of HP products, I was ready to try something new. I looked throughout the usual on-line stores, NewEgg, Amazon, etc; and all this listed this printer at $175-200. As a last, before I buy check, I came over to bestbuy.com, found the printer for over $20 less, bought on-line, picked it up in the store later that same day.

Printer is flawless. Drivers all installed perfectly on one Mac desktop, and two PC laptops. Faxi ... ng through Comcast worked great, scanning is a breeze, and document scanning couldn&apos;t be quicker.

The screen is large, bright, easy to read and understand. Hooking up to my network over wireless was cake. Adding into my Google Cloud so I can print documents at home on this printer, but from anywhere else was painless.

Highly recommended if you need all four functions.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dstress</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great printer for multiple uses</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set up, easy to work with. Double sided printing. Picture scanning

I am amazed at how simple this printer is to use. The top document feeder has been great for making copies especially double sided ones. The wireless function has saved me from having to unplug and plug in a printer as neither of our old ones were wireless and only one of them printed in color. I haven&apos;t tried to print photos, but so far I am very impressed. I also like the fact that it comes with full size ink cartridges and not the sample type most printers come with. The first time I scanned pictures I was impressed that it was able to to save the four pictures I had scanned together in four different files. I have really enjoyed this printer and for only having it a month I have no complaints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chris</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Fast Operation; Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Easy To Use

I was comparing this to the Canon MX882 and the Brother MFC-J825(J835). I was also considering the HP 8600. 

I have had a Canon MP730 which lasted for years, but was on its last legs. So I was partial to the MX882 and knew it had really good reviews, but that printer was just too big for the space I had available. (Note: Check other sites for dimensions also when comparing sizes - I believe Staples has some incorrect info on one or more of these printers, but don&apos;t recall which)

There was a good deal on the EPSON and I decided to go with that one as it also had pretty good reviews. In fact the previous model (840) was highly rated. I think the Brother would have been good too, but I chose th ... e EPSON.

Speed...

I am pleased with the print speed and once I picked a lesser DPI (150 or 200) for my business docs the scan speed is quite good. The Epson scan app is not super, but it&apos;s pretty simple to scan right to a PDF.

The duplexer is neat, but not really speedy in my opinion, but I&apos;ve never had one in an inkjet before so have no basis to compare. Currently, I don&apos;t really use that feature anyway, so not a big issue for me.

Connectivity...

I connected the PC via ethernet and the PC apps found the printer easily.

A couple nice additions...

-- The touchscreen is nice (and impressed the kids).

-- The printer has built in options to print lined (wide and college rule) and graph paper and can also print a memo page with personal graphics (did not try that). That was a nice touch. 

!!My biggest complaints and one worry.

1. I was disappointed that you cannot trigger a scan to PC from the printer unless you have a USB connection. 

2. The flatbed scanner lid has no support, so you have to open it all the way up or hold it while you put a document in it. I was spoiled by the Canon I had as it had a support which held the lid open for you without having to open fully.

3. The EPSON bloatware software. I suppose this is normal with all vendor&apos;s. I remember years ago HP was awful with this - don&apos;t know about these days. I had 2 PC&apos;s to connect to this. I loaded the CD software on an XP laptop. It must have loaded 7 different applications. Then I downloaded the latest drivers from the Web and installed the basic print driver and scan app to my Win 7 PC. That was much better!!!

4. The paper output &quot;tray&quot;. This is a piece of plastic you pull out to hold the paper - fairly flimsy plastic. I&apos;m worried I&apos;m going to break this off. 

All in all - a pretty decent printer. No &quot;real&quot; complaints with it and I think I&apos;m going to like it just fine.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lissette</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME PRINTER</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this printer because it was on sale and i wanted to try a different brand other than Hp. The one I have now goes through so many prep cycles (before and after printing) that it drives me mad with all the noise that it makes. but make no mistake, she&apos;s an excellent photo printer. So I bought this Epson Workforce machine and tried out all of its features. Printing from the computer to the printer was slow at first, but i fixed that problem by assigning the printer a different port. Now it prints with no delays. A very speedy printer. Black and white text look great and photos look very good after you tweak with the printers color default settings. Copying, faxing (I love the fact that you can fax directly from the printer, or you can use your PC software), and scanning were ... all put to the test and everything looks great. She&apos;s gorgeous. I love the sleek black shiny body. And it&apos;s almost lightweight. Though the flap attached to the top feels a bit flimsy, just be careful not to overfill with paper. The ADF (automatic document feeder) is also a plus. The printer automatically detects the paper you place there. The 2 paper trays makes tasks much easier by holding more paper. Wireless setup was a breeze. 2 sided printing was very fast. Darn I&apos;m IMPRESSED!! I tried their e-mail feature, smart phone printing features and they all worked without a hitch. Its front USB port can also be used to charge your mobile devices. Real cool. Oh, and the 845 is almost always quiet. What a blessing!! I&apos;ll keep my Hp for printing special photographs, but the Epson Workforce 845 will do the rest, it&apos;s more than capable. I had a great time testing this printer. It&apos;s an excellent machine. I highly recommend it. :D
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brewski48</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far this is the best printer I have owned.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It was easy to set up and has awesome print quality.

Cons: Nothing so far

It was very easy to set up. I use it wirelessly for 4 computers in my home. So far the ink consumption is very low, even while printing several pages of photos. It prints very fast compared to my past office jets. The cost was surprisingly low. I think you will agree after you use it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JMS Associates</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Could of been a 5 star</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Durable construction; Easy To Set Up

Very professional styling and performance. Only draw back I&apos;ve found so far is that if you&apos;re copying a document it forces you to pull the copy paper from Tray 1. So if you have Tray 1 set-up for photo paper you need to reload it. Should be capable of getting the paper from Tray 2 (my default tray).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rebellion</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>fantastic printer!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: User friendly, good price, easy set up, prints excellent!!

Cons: Cant find any faults.

This is my 3rd printer. It is the best one yet. Prints much faster. Does double sided copies. Holds way more paper. Very easy to set up. No paper jams as before with the other two I owned. Very satisfied. I highly recommend this printer!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kyle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent All-in-One</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Compact Design

Cons: Too much ink used

This machine does everything quickly! I use it for faxes, printing, scanning, and copying. It is a little loud sometimes when printing, but I don&apos;t have to leave my desk like I used to! It also scans double sided so I don&apos;t have to constantly be flipping over pages every few seconds. This is a fantastic all-in-one!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for two side scanning</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design

Cons: Hard Setup

It is very well built with two papar trays. I liked it specially about two side scanning. It works fine but needs to setup and learn about it. I had to install 3 times to work wireless.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jason</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for what I need</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

Wanted a wifi printer, that scanned and copied. Really wanted a laser device but I couldn&apos;t beat the sale price of the printer. Does what I need. Having two paper trays is nice. I would like set them up to have better ink jet paper in the one and the other for everyday printing. Set up was fast and easy, could do without all the epson software. Overall I like the printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great multi function</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great price, great set up, great features, wireless functions

Cons: no 11x14 flatbed scanner

After 3 HP 4 in 1s I opted for this Epson. Setup is easier, ink use is less, cost of the unit is less. Overall I can&apos;t believe I paid 3 times as much for HP&apos;s. No brainer - set this up with a CISS and printing is virtually free.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Indiansfan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good quality and easy set up</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simple to use

Cons: Large footprint

I purchased this printer for two reasons. First it has separate ink cartridges and second it prints wirelessly from my iPhone, iPad and MacBook. This printer does everything I want.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>X789</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very satisfied with the Epson Workforce 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Includes regular print cartridges, great price, prints fast

Cons: Missing single sheet feeder for one time print jobs, fax to email would be great

My other office/print/scan/fax went out after years of service right in the middle of me scanning some important documents. After a quick trip to Best Buy I almost bought a different brand due to price but then someone pointed out to me that Epson includes regular ink cartridges with the printer where many other brands either include &apos;starter&apos; cartridges that only print a few pages or they use cartridges that do not print as many pages as the Epson cartridges do. On average my experience has been $30-$45 a pop for a cartridge so this can easily add up to the price of the printer within a short amount of time. I confirmed this ... Epson included the large capacity cartridges (which is an initial $ saver) and completed my purchase . I have been very satisfied with my decision. After the initial setup (which did take some time but went well), I was able to complete my scan job to .pdf which was a much nicer experience than my prior printer. Print jobs are fast (after is is warmed up) and the wireless feature and power saving mode are great. I also like the 2 paper trays. Well worth the money.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HappyPrinter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Inkjet Printer I&apos;ve ever bought</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low Ink Consumption; Reliable; Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

I&apos;ve always been a fan of laser printers. Ever Inkjet I&apos;ve bought over the eyars just did not live up to expectations. This WorkForce 845 gets teh job done. I would reccommend this printer to anyone who needs a great printer at decent price. Love the fact I can print directly to it via my Apple iPhone and iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Greenebeane</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great home office printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use

Easy to set up. Buy a USB cord if you want to connect it directly to your computer and not go wireless. Really happy with the operation. I like it way better than my HP all in one printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>X234</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Since I dropped HP am happy with Epson printers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Customer service, the few times I needed it.

Cons: So far everything is perfect

It is quiet, fast, 2 sided printing is fantastic, color accuracy terrific.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brandon H</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Works as advertised. Setup was easy and straight forward. I did use a USB cable to during setup as I heard this makes the process easier. I am now able to print from my PC, iPad, and iPhone; all wirelessly. Also, the email print feature is a lot more useful then I thought it would be. I can print remotely from anywhere via email.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike prints-a-lot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic printer, saves time and money.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Use; Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Bulky

I love this printer. Being able to replace only the color of ink that is out saves a lot of money and buying the XL capacity ink cartridges saves even more money. This printer duplexes so you also save on paper cost. It is fast and prints photos beautifully. Having two 250 sheet paper trays means having to fill the paper much less often than most comparable printers. I would highly recommend this printer. In my opinion it is one of if not the best printer in its price range. If I had to find something to complain about is that it is a little bulky but for the features it has I really don&apos;t find that a problem.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Heavy school work user</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good performer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

I primarily purchased this for home school and online college this fall. Running great as of 25Aug12.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>YY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to install</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

I like the two paper trays. I&apos;ve loaded tray one with paper that has already been printed on one side; printed side up so my document prints on the bottom, clear side to save a little bit of money on paper. Tray two is for new (clear on both sides paper). The paper catch tray feels flimsy, but no problems so far. I have printed duplex, works fine. I&apos;ve set my printer up using an RJ-45 network cable to connect to the computer. It took me a few minutes to find the RJ-45 slot! As you are facing the printer, it is on the left side of the printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SBStudio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Up and running in 10 minutes</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this all-in-one in my home for everything including my art and design business. It worked right out of the box - even the colors were accurate. Printing from my iPhone and iPad was as easy as downloading the app.One caveat: the paper tray construction seems a little flimsy, so I&apos;m handling it gently. This is not so bad as to take away from the terrific value of this item.Great purchase especially from B&amp;H - the lowest price I found with the customer service I always love.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HomeBiZ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy Installation!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Compact Design; Easy To Set Up

I replaced my HP 8500 printer with the Epson Workforce 845. It was a HUGE improvement over my HP!! The set up couldn&apos;t have been any easier either!! I set it up to use with both my Mac and my PC. No problems with my wireless at all. I would recommend using a USB cord for the installation only and then use your wireless.

The only negative thing I can say is that it wouldn&apos;t stay on after having it for 3 days. It was an unusual mechanical problem. However, I had the service plan ($20 extra) and it was immediately replaced with another new printer. No problems with the new one.

I would definitely recommend this printer for home or small business use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lady Bay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Be sure to buy INK</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to set up as a network printer. Unfortunately, I have not really been able to run it, as it came with only teeny-tiny ink cartridges. Be sure to buy real ink at the same time you purchase the printer!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>smoky1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to set up</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love the wireless printing

Cons: photos are good, but not as good as my old printer

This printer was easy to set up. I love printing from any device I own because it is wireless. Photo quality is good, although not as good as my HP Printer. That said, the HP started failing me with ink cartridge changes, always an error and wouldn&apos;t work. I am, so far, happy with the printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lenny The Pianist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson Again Proves Why They are the Best</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

The fax feature is fast and clean - printing speed is astonishing. One of the fastest I have used. Two trays for different types of paper (photo).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jack88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for Photo</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to setup and friendly user

Cons: fast and quite with great color for photo

I am sure that I will recommended to my friend and very affordable. Color and set up was very friendly user. Great product that EPSON put on the market.

I am satisfied with it..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tsans</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time

So easy and fast to set up! I can print invoices from one tray and address lables from the other. Great product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BCWI</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Photo printing should be standard</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Document feeder and wireless connection

Cons: Photo quality is poor.

When buying a printer of this caliber, you would think it would be capable of printing a nice photo. Not the case.

Great for everything else, but if you want to print an occasional photo and not want it to look like it came of a printer, then this is not what you&apos;re looking for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lakeside Office</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson WorkForce 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Epson WorkForce 845 - so far the printer function has been perfect, the duplex scanning/printing is a must for my home office. Setup was a no-brainer, with the printer on ethernet as well as setting up printer on 5 or more wireless devices. The fax functions well, with an easy &amp; intuitive menu on the display screen. Operation is fast and quiet. For my office, the WorkForce 845 does everything I need without any issues. Not sure about cartridge life or replacement costs yet. The 845 just works and works well!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dungeon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson 845 is lacking</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Although the wireless was reasonably easy to set up, the printer speed in color printing is below par. The setup for print to email Epson connect did not install properly at the first attempt. I called Epson support and that was a waste of time. I did get it to work after uninstalling and reinstalling the software.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Elder72</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-in-One, Fast, Lots of Capability</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up, fast quality printing, faxing &amp; scanning work great, great value

Cons: Ink is a little more expensive (I bought the large capacity ones), menu could be more intuitative.

I did a lot of research before buying the 845, and am very happy with it. Haven&apos;t used it enough to replace ink cartridges yet, but it seems to go a long ways. Replaces a fairly new LexMark with printhead problems. I set it up using the key pad, very easy. I am using the USB cable. Scanning works great, for emailing I just select the &quot;scan to email&quot; and get a quality copy. One can select a black or color copy for any job. The fax works great! I have it on my home phone line, and even if I happen to pick up the phone, the fax will still take over. Lots of paper capbility, I like the 2 ... trays. Printing and copying result is quality output. Printing is very fast. I have an old HP All-in-One that I used as a backup (when LexMark quit) and it is very slow in comparison. Picture prints are very good considering that this is not a photo printer, really good enough for all the prints I use. The printer is priced right and an excellant value. I talked a friend into buying one for her business, and she is also very impressed. I haven&apos;t used the card reader yet, so no comment on that.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>herbz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best printer I&apos;ve owned!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Reliable; Easy To Set Up

Very reliable, easy to set up, and wireless connectivity is the deal maker! No problems whatsoever.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Coach Nye Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well equipped for a small package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

Very well equipped for the money. The printer was incredibly easy to set up, and easy to figure out functions. The auto page feeder works surprisingly well, and is a nice feature.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dewly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice and great .</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to use and easy to understand how to use .

Cons: Nothing so far I had use this printer

Easy setup. Took less than five minutes. Product and print quality both seem to be above standard.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RootlessAgrarian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>First Impressions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have only just configured this printer and printed a couple of test pages. It&apos;s attached to a home wifi network (setup via the front panel was extremely easy) serving a couple of Macs, one desktop and one laptop. The software installation was very straightforward except for filling out the registration form (very last step): for some reason, all the form fields were black on black, so I had to highlight text to proofread it after typing blind!

The printer paper trays feel very frail and flimsy and I will be handling them gently. The rest of the printer feels fairly smooth and solid (hinge action, etc). The flip-out front panel is a pleasant surprise, being very easy to read (and the touchscreen feature seems stable and accurate), good contrast, good colour choices. The ink cartrid ... ges slotted into place with reassuring accuracy and a definite, solid Click. Installation instructions were extremely clear (no head scratching).

For a fairly cheap multifunction printer this looks good so far. I am hoping that this generation of inkjets will not suffer from the earlier generations&apos; vexing issues: ink drying out, nozzles clogging, etc. It has been 10 years since I owned an inkjet printer and I&apos;m hoping that the technology has improved quite a bit since then. So far my impression of this product is favourable: considerable engineering has gone into making it easy to install, and I hope some engineering also went into making it reliable!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daveh153</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing small office product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless network printing that actually works w/o hassles, auto 2 sided printing, 2 paper drawers, easy to setup &amp; use

Cons: A bit on the large size, kinda loud

I was looking to replace my old HP all-in one that was dying a slow death. Haven&apos;t used Epson since the dot matrix days, but lately I&apos;m a bit frustrated with HP products and the Workforce 845 got excellent reviews on multiple sites. After unpacking it and starting the setup process, I was in full agreement. The wireless features worked first time and are very reliable. I&apos;ve had a Lexmark wireless printer and it&apos;s a pain in the butt to get it to connect and stay connected. The print quality is good, scanning works well and the product reliably does 2 sided printing automatically. I worked in development for 2 ... 0 years on high speed copiers and printers and I am amazed by this product. Hope it holds up for many years, but at this price you can&apos;t go wrong!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jim52910</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, easy to use, good quality

Very happy with this printer. Light years faster than my old one! Scanning is fast and easy and so is printing! Great value too!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mixologist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Impressive Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to operate

Cons: Using the cd for set up

Had some issues using cd for set up, had to go to website. Once set up was completed this printer has been a joy to use. The wireless feature is definately a huge plus. I have two laptops (1 mac) and my cell connected and they work flawlessy with this printer. I&apos;ve used a lot of printers in the past and and I honestly think that this is the Best by far in both quality and value. Don&apos;t take my word for it, get one and see for yourself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Juliaann3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT PRINTER</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Photo print quality is outstanding, especially in 5x7 prints

Cons: Nothing so far

I did a lot of research before selecting this printer to replace my old Brother 435CN
I use it primarily for document and photo printing.
The printer is really fast and quiet
One word of caution. Be sure to align the print head before printing any photos, I missed that step when I set up the printer and my first photo had visible lines in it.
Not a problem once I accessed the online user guide and figured it out.

Well worth the money</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Iradj99</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent value and quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Good price value

I expected good general printing but was pleasantly surprised with the quality of the photos printed. I printed pictures on the glossy photo paper and did not see any bleeding or awkward edges.
Also, it came with full-size ink cartridges which is better than most.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wheel rider</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable

This printer has done everything I have asked of it without skipping a beat. Double sided copies and printing is great. So far no jams.

Print speed is impressive and quality of prints is well within the bounds of acceptable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mcmo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Upgraded from another Epson model. Very good!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: reliable and dependable. Easy to operate.

Cons: Ink cartridges are too expensive!

Have been using Epson printer products for 6 years. This model is top of the line, easy to use. I needed a technician to set it up, as it was too heavy for me to pick up. I saved around $35 from the listed price in purchasing this equipment from Best Buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fixedit4sure</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great workhorse of a printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Cost effective, prints fast &amp; versatile.

Cons: Bigger that last printer.

Bought this on sale at Best Buy to replace an old brother inkjet. This unit does it all and is really fast, print quality is very good. Network capable and it was very easy to set up. Automatic duplex printing, its great for a small business owner.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>FrequentPrinter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Would buy again.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Set Up

Well worth the money. Plus staples even bought back my old printer!!! Would buy it again and again!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Franklin13</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All in One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use and quality

Cons: It&apos;s a little loud

This printer was bought to replace the Kodak All in One. There is absolutely no comparison. From the moment we opened the box on the Kodak all In One it was nothing but problems. This print is the opposite. It was easy to set up, it prints quickly, the quality of the prints is excellent and the software is great. I would recommend this printer to anyone with a small business or for home use. You cannot find a better All in ONe for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CatherineJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent print quality/speed, not great feature</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: smooth easy fast printing with really nice quality output

Cons: does not print 3&quot;x5&quot; cards, doesn&apos;t have great output controls

It is too soon for me to rate the economy of the toner and ultimately that is the most important factor in the cost/benefit of a printer as you purchase the printer only once, but the toner over and over again.

That said, the printer does print fabulous documents including those with photos and graphics. The speed it really fast and so smooth. The output tray works well.

I have two disappointments with this printer.
1) the smallest paper it can print is 3 1/2&quot; x 5&quot;. It will not print a standard 3x5 index card. We print loads of flash cards and recipes in this size and it is a major loss not to be able to do so any more.
2) th ... ere are not enough settings available for the output. On my prior Lexmark I had much greater control over the output. The Lexmark toner was, however, ridiculously expensive.

In the end, I will only be able to know if this was a good purchase after we see how well the toner lasts along with what it costs to refill.
.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PNAIR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Value for any small business / household</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent feature set for the price, solid build, high capacity

Cons: Only comes in black? :0

This printer was supposed to be a backup for the Canon Pixma MX410 Wifi Printer I own. Little did I know that this will soon become the Primary and ONLY printer I use!!

I do a fair bit of printing since I&apos;m in the IT consulting line of business. You need to print a fair amount of technical documents at times.

I purchased a Canon Pixma MX410 (yes, I know this is an Epson 845 review; but hear me out :) You&apos;ll thank me later :)) due to its low price point and hey - it was Thanksgiving :)

I&apos;ve been using the Canon printer for a while now; long enough to know its faults and benefits.

I&apos;ll get to what stands out the most in the Epson Workforce 845

S ... ETUP -
If there&apos;s something known as true plug and play; this has to be it. Epson provides a bundle of software that sets up your printer over the Wifi network quickly and easily. What makes this so different from other Wifi printers? Its the stability of the software provided. I&apos;ve had tons of problems getting to print over Wifi with my Canon. Sure; Canon gave me bundled software too; but the printer just wouldnt work most of the time I sent something to it - I had to manually reconfigure or refresh the connection between the laptop and the Canon. With the Epson 845 - not a SINGLE print failure to date.

SOFTWARE/FIRMWARE -

-EPSON Scan - Standard software that helps to scan and receive files over Wifi
-Provides iOS and Android apps that aid printing from your smartphones. The apps also show you the ink levels in the printer - thats pretty handy if you&apos;ve walked into BestBuy to pick up something and quickly wanted to know if your printer ink levels are low. You just saved a trip.
-Firmware - Once the application is installed on your laptop; it checks for firmware updates and applies the update OVER WIFI. Yes, the printer updates its firmware over the air; just as your cellphone would. Absolutely hassle free.

PRINTING -

Epson can stake their claim to this being the fastest double sided printer in the business. I&apos;ve tried ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kickie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great wireless all-in-one unit.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast printing, all-in-one features, auto double-sided printing

Cons: A bit noisy when printing

I replaced an old printer with this wireless unit. I love it. The print quality is excellent; auto double-sided printing is a great paper saver. It is a little noisy when it prints but not a big deal. I did ALOT of research before making this purchase. I wanted a unit that could copy and scan multiple sheets (auto document feeder) and single sheets. The ability to fax is a money saving tool as I was paying at a local service $1.00 per sheet to fax documents. The printer will pay for itself in no time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GMoney</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Average performance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design

Cons: Hard Setup; Jams Easily

The wireless communication between the PC and unit is a challenge. The scanner jams far too easily. Any firewall will need to be adjusted to allow for installation.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>farm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>efficient</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design; Easy To Use

Cons: No slot for check printin

Meets our needs. Wish I had known that I would have to use the trays for checks. I might have looked at a different model.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Redshar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time; Durable construction; Compact Design

Great printer, alittle noisy. We are pleased with this printer. We also have the Epson Workforce 590 series and the workforce 610 series..Try it,
you&apos;ll like it..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rock14</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little all-in-one printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up. Good price.

Cons: Cannot print in black ink only.

This is my first wireless printer and I love that feature. It prints relatively quickly, and, between the two paper trays, can hold a whole ream of paper. I have used the scan, copy and fax features also, which all perform as required. I haven&apos;t found a way to print strictly in black ink, which would be a nice feature to have, but overall, a great all-in-one printer for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>phamhlam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best value printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Reason for purchase: I needed a reliable printer and since I am a college student, I wanted something that would last long while providing great quality. The Epson 845 was that printer.

Pros:
500 sheet capacity
Industrial strength look
Wi-Fi
Touch screen
CMYK (cyan, magenta, yellow, and key/black) ink cartridge
Waterproof ink
Document feeder tray
Quick single and double sided printing

Cons:
None compared to other printer

Why you should buy this printer?
This printer will last you a long time. At 139.99, this printer is a great bargain. They provide xl size ink cartridges instead of some small sample pack. This printer will serve most people need. You will be better off getting this printer then paying for a cheaper printer that won&apos;t has a ... s many great feature or a expensive printer that just waste your cash.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>digi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great All-In-One!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I would rate the Work Force 845 a 4.5!
Great All-In-One! I used an ethernet cable to my Mac Airport device and I can print and SCAN wirelessly! Easy to set up! Comes with FULL XL ink tanks! The photo scanning quality is the only thing I&apos;ve been a little disappointed by. The photo scanning quality is probably good for most people but as a graphic designer I think it should be better for the scanning specs. However, printing is QUICK, great color. Two sided ADF scanning and two sided printing is the best! You can even scan legal paper with the ADF option. It is a little noisy when the inks are charging but actual printing is not loud. A huge step UP from our old HP &amp; Espon All-In-Ones!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Elder Jock</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good choice1</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Compact Design; Low Ink Consumption; Reliable

Replacement for a Lexmark all-in-one. Have been extremely pleased with this all-in-one as of this date. Scans documents and photos well and prints very fast. Seems to be much more frugal with the printer ink. 5 Stars in my book.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Adam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson gets it done...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Easy To Use

I just purchased this printer the other day. I spent some time researching for my Insurance Agency which one to get. We currently have two laser printers and we had a copy machine. Well now we are going paperless so I needed something to scan and copy for the most part. This machine excels with the scanning and copying. It copy&apos;s fairly quick and scanning is very easy. I chose this over the Lexmark 915, while I was in the store there was a Lexmark rep so all the associates (4) total were just really pushing me towards the Lexmark. So I bought the Epson because I like Epson a little better with past experience and also just to spite the store employees (sorry)anyway, the biggest difference between the Epson and LExmark I saw was that ... the Epson was about 5-6 pages faster copying which for me was a huge selling point. I am not to concerned about ink because we don&apos;t print on it and we probably are under 80 copies a month as we are mostly paperless or a heavy printing operation which is why we have laser printers. All in all a great machine that does everything it says. Just a note- Setup is easy, but if you setup wireless from a laptop, have your laptop hooked to the ethernet or else you won&apos;t get it to install properly.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Popcorn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for Home/Office</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Fast Print Time; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Double sided printing

Easy to put on home network. Paper handling for duplex printing reliable so far.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fitz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent easy install</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy to Use; Quality Construction; Easy setup instructions; Reliable; Easy to install software; Efficient

Cons: No Cons BUY THIS EPSON

I can&apos;t say enough about this Epson 845. I am elated about how fast it was to set up with all 4 computers and Mac&apos;s in the house. Easy to follow setup instructions. From any where in my house my family can wireless use the printer.
GREAT PRODUCT!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VirtualLadyBoss</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer for a small business.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use all the way around for a phenominal price.

Cons: I don&apos;t particularly like that the legal paper tray extends outside of the machine when in use

This printer is excellent. I do a variety of documents including presentations, spreadsheets, proposals, etc. and this Epson puts out crisp, clean copies quickly. With all of its features, it covers all the needs for my virtual administrative business for copying, printing, scanning and faxing. I definitely recommend it for the small businesses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gayle Sells San Diego</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer for the Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Efficient; Easy To Set Up; Easy to Use

Cons: A little noisy

Great all in one for the price! My only complaint is that I had to go to 3 different stores to find it as the inventory stated online was not accurate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ValueHunting</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t go wrong for the price and features.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set-up and it seem to be what was advertized

Cons: Like all printers the cost of ink, hundreds of $ per gal

Was very easy to set up wireless connection on 2 desk tops and 2 lap tops (about 1 hr ). Printed on the first try and the quality was so much better then my old HP 960. I&apos;ve only had the Epson for a month so I can&apos;t say much about cost to operate. The price ($138.00 Bestbuy sale + $20.00 off for signing up for a Bestbuy credit card = $108.00) grate deal. The speed, all-in-one features and print quality for text and photos is more then expected.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>campdog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good printer for Two Sided and If you need 2 Trays</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Set up fairly simple, display is easy to read and navigate

Cons: Speed compared to advertizing.

This is my first Epson product, before that it was HP. As far as the value and price it does have a realy good price for all the features you get, I was looking to upgrade my HP printer to have wifi and i was tried of wasting paper by printing on one side and did not have the patience for turning the paper over. With that said this Epson fills all of those requirements pluss it has two paper trays i have them set up for letter and legal.

I am a little disapointed in the print quality though, with my hp I could set it on economy and read the print without any problem I find the Epson is a little fuzzy until you get up to the normal print setting. There are two setting b ... elow and two setting above the normal so you have many to chose from i am just not sure how this will affect the number of pages to to ink ratio. Time will tell I have had the printer for about 1.5 months and have used about 400 pages (200 sheets) in it so far and my Black ink level is at about 50% maybe a little less. I print most thing in B/W or Greyscale so the other colors have bearly moved still have 95% or better. One thing is nice about epson is the individual ink colors not a tricolor like my old HP (still working by the way as a second)

Let me comment on Speed the epson is no where near the speed for the clarity as the HP but if you need that minute to veg out and rub your eyes from the computer you get that minute.

As far a the features go two sided printing Great, separate inks Great, two paper cartridges Great (two sided not available on Legal come on epson how hard would that be). Also the wifi feature is great i am able to print right from my Iphone
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BaseballBirthdays</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good All-In-One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very good scanner

Cons: lack of cables

I&apos;m quite happy with the Epson WorkForce 845. The print quality is quite good and the setup process was simple as could be.

I can&apos;t imagine a better All-In-One Printer for the price ($160 sale price). I recommend the Epson WorkForce 845 without reservation, but be warned that the unit does not come with the cables needed to link it to your computer or router.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rockinranman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: speed, paper trays hold 250 sheets of paper

great printer so far have only had this for about two weeks, easy setup took about 20 minutes. the ink cost is a little high but rated at 900 hundred sheets for black ink. I was a fan of kodak printers for the ink cost, but when you must replace the printer every year.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dad2peep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good home office printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Good value for price. Effective home office printer. Easy to use and set up. Color print quality is pretty good, had some streaking in initial print jobs. May need to use color quality paper for best results. Love the wireless print capability from PC, iMac, iPad, and iPhone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>golfpro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Workforce 845 All in one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>very easy set up. works great in the whole house, no problems with the wifi connection. The print quaility is great. It was on sale so we got a great deal on the unit The extra money above the 645 model was worth it to get a bigger screen to see</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gordo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Best AIO Printer I&apos;ve Owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a personal home/office multifunction printer. It does everything I need it to do and it does it better than the other brands I have owned. The exterior design is sleek and free of all the sticky-out pieces that I&apos;ve had to deal with before. It is much quieter that previous printers and significantly faster. I am looking forward to the lower cost of ink than comparable units. I am very satisfied with this printer and would recommend it to a friend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>People in the office love it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use this printer every day for faxing, printing and scaning. Wi-Fi was easy to set up and works everywhere in building (3200 Sq.Ft.). We have had if for three weeks and no problems at all. After researching the market, for the price this unit is tough to beat.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>amit</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson work force 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>bought this workhorse yesterday from best buy. setup was done in half hour. printed wirelessly and from my smartphone without any hassles. Will keep you posted after I have used it for a while</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SW1006</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Value AIO</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Too much ink used; Flimsy Construction; Still Too Much Ink Used

Better ink useage than many, but still too much. A little slow, but not a major problem. Good value for the sales price, would not buy at retail price - better choices at the $200 range.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leftshot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Value and a Real Performer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low Ink Consumption; Durable construction; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

We bought three on sale after deploying several WorkForce 545. We love them both. But the 848 is a real workhorse. Fast, ruggedly built, two ample sized paper trays. We&apos;re thinking of deploying one as a departmental multifunction printer/scanner. It&apos;s that good!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Churchitguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great multi-function printer even better price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Print quality, speed, paper capacity and easy setup.

Cons: Haven&apos;t found anything to complain about yet.

I was in the market for a new color printer and fund a fantastic buy on the Epson Workforce 845. I don&apos;t use the fax function, but all other functions work very well. It is a great home office scanner, printer and copier. I liked it so well that I bought the Epson 645 for my wife&apos;s office.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Wireless Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up, great price, I got it on sale for $100

Cons: nothing

I needed an easy to use printer, so that I could print shipping labels and google maps from my two desktops and a laptop from any where in my house. This printer is perfect for the job. Its fast and sharp quality. Its probably more then I need or will ever use, but I got it on sale for $100 and at that price, it is so worth it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GrinderCB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great upgrade for a home office</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to setup, great price, wonderful print quality

Cons: Lacks a single sheet feeder for one-time print jobs; needs a fax-to-web feature

The Epson Workforce 845 is a tremendous upgrade over my previous printer. Nearly everything the 845 does is better and/or faster. I use mine to print postage and the postal scanner never misses on labels printed by this printer because they&apos;re so sharp and clear. So far, ink cartridges run about the same price but I go through them less often than with my previous printer, making the 845 less expensive over time. Two paper feed trays mean I don&apos;t have to reload very often, although I&apos;d really like a single sheet feeder for those one-shot print jobs; as it is I have to pull one of the trays to load one sheet of special paper or labels. ... Faxing can only be done if you have a phone line; I wonder when the developers will wake up to the fact that many folks are going wireless.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>STLRob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Elementary teacher approved!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sharp printing, very fast, easy wireless connection

Cons: Noisy

A very easy set-up process, including wireless to desktop and two laptops. Sharp copies that print fast (be sure and extend the tray or they&apos;ll shoot all over the place!). The only reason for losing 1 star was it&apos;s pretty noisy as it cycles the paper through. Almost sounds like something needs oil or grease. But it&apos;s a small price to pay for the good points. Oh, and I set it up to print remotely from my office via email and that worked, too!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So Far So Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The installation went easy. So far the printing has been fast and the print quality is good. Copier is easy to use. I have not used the fax yet, but I am sure it will be fine. I bought the printer for a small personal office and it working great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OREGONCHART</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DON&apos;T Buy this Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Jams Easily

I tried to print some business cards on this printer using Avery business card blanks purchased at Staples. It consistently jammed in spite of anything I tried. I wrote to Epson Customer service and received the following reply:
hank you for contacting Epson regarding your Epson WorkForce 845.

I do apologize if you are having some difficulties making the printer feed and print on your card stock paper. Unfortunately, Epson does not recommend any third party paper as they may cause damage to the printer which will not be covered under Epson&apos;s warranty. Furthermore, only with Genuine Epson papers and Genuine Epson inks we guarantee our customers to get the best quality output. Below is the link of all Genuine Epson p ... apers supported by this specific printer:

http://www.epson.com/cgi-bin/Store/pamPaperFinder.jsp?0&amp;cookies=no&amp;printer=63091944

There are no similar papers available from Epson which means, either print what they want you to print on what they want you to use, namely, their paper, or forget about it. WHAT A RIP OFF!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bluec10</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Printer, Setup a Hassle</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>My WorkForce 845 has all the features I need and I&apos;m excited about having it in the office. It prints clearly and the document scans look good.

It jammed the first time I used the document feeder to scan an multi-page document, but the papers were dog eared and I&apos;m not ready to blame the printer for it.

The biggest problem has been connecting the scanning feature to the scanning software on my computer. When I activate the scanning program I get a message that it is unable to communicate via USB. I uninstalled and reinstalled the software several times with the same message. Printing works, so I know the USB is working, but not with the Epson scanning software. VERY frustrating because I scan a lot of documents and really need this feature to work.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BrianCanadien</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The ability to print by simply sending a document to a Epson email address is brilliant. It just works. The scanning and fax work well too. Overall it&apos;s a great deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>this printer rocks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption

I print a lot. Mostly word and excel documents that don&apos;t use a lot of color. But I also print hundreds of pages of reports every month. This printer handles everything that I&apos;ve thrown at it. It even prints on both sides of the page. After being continuously disappointed with HP products, Epson has stepped into the lime light with a great alternative.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LillyVonS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buy this printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

I know I&apos;m going to sound like a cheerleader for Staples and Epson but you can&apos;t go wrong with this printer. I went in looking for a personal use printer and saw this on sale with a huge reduction in price. I had a coupon and Staples gift card and the rest is history. I have purchased and returned (not from Staples) three printers this year because the scanner would not install and work even with assistance from product support. This Epson set up in minutes without any problems. I love this printer and It has all the features of an office printer; I will never need anything else.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tony</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: EPSON WorkForce 845 All-in-One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Simply the BEST printer I have ever owned. User friendly and easy to set up. Wi-Fi is Awesome. 2sided print saves on paper. Worlds faster printer for black printing. Love it. Thanks</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>skadooshness</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it so far!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had a Kodak all-in-one...you know, the one that was featured on The Apprentice. Hated that printer because it was an ink hog and pictures were not printed clear on it.The WorkForce is a work horse. I love being able to email documents to print, wireless printing, and the pictures I have printed so far are very clear. It beats Kodak, HANDS DOWN. Even documents for school print clear and look very nice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rapid Ralph</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An amazing machine for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This machine has it all - great photo quality, decent speed, convenience, a multitude of useful features, and especially wireless versatility. Highly recommended.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ng</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good document printer, scanner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use

It prints very fast. It scans fast, but for some reason the software on my computer is very slow to process, and put together the pdf document. I&apos;m not sure if this is a printer, network, or software issue, but did not have this with previous printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sparkplug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Far exceeded my expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Low Ink Consumption; Durable construction; Reliable

I use the Epson 845 primarily for personal use and some business applications as well. I upgraded from an Epson 500 which was OK, but did not have nearly the features as this new one. I dreaded the set-up but that was totally unnecessary. I decided to follow the directions and not do it intuitively and everything worked out just fine. The price at the local Staples store was very attractive, much less than I expected. I really like the wireless feature and enjoy having 3 other computers that can use it to print throuighout the house.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr. C</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer, GREAT price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Nice Printer, GREAT price Chose this unit after several hours of internet searching because I was in need of a MFC for my home office. I have never owned an Epson product, however I must say that I was impressed at this unit and it&apos;s capabilities after a few days of playing around with it.I will also add that my first time ordering from B&amp;H was TOP NOTCH. Less than 36 hours from clicking the purchase tab, the printer was at my door (with their free shipping).For the price I paid ($ , total). There is no way to beat this printer for general home office use. I have owned a lot of printers of many grades, brands and quality. So far this one is near the top of my list of general home/ office printers.So read the online review and make your own choice, all I will say is that most of them ... are correct. My experience with the Epson Workforce. 845 has been wonderful thus far.Here are my first impression P/C listPros:B&amp;H price, tracking and extremely fast delivery Auto duplexTouch screeneasy WiFi setupBetter than average print and picture qualityCons:A little noisyFirst page out takes usually 30 -40 seconds(Remaining pages print quickly)Too much plastic in unitHigher priced ink cartriges than other leading brands
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Boost</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very capable home office All-in-One</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The workforce 845 is a very full featured printer. The black ink cost is comparable to OEM toner cartridges and the colour ink cost is exceptionally low.

Speed is very good and build quality is acceptable relative to the selling price of the printer. The printer earns 4 stars for its speed, reliability and features, but falls short of 5 stars because of the low quality and relatively frustrating to use touch screen. Another strike comes from the odd requirement to use only the number one tray for Google Cloud printing, with no way to override. Since this is the tray that can accept smaller glossy paper, it doesn&apos;t make much sense to force it to be used by Google Cloud printing, since the user might want to keep this tray loaded with photo paper, leaving the number two tray dedicated ... to plain paper.

Other than these two abnormalities, this is an affordable printer with great features and I highly recommend it for personal and home office use.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Senior70</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable; Easy to Customize

Cons: None Yet; Large Footprint

I like the easy wireless setup, plus the LED screan on the printer. The 2 paper trays make easy to print photos and documents.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Albert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Espon WorkForce so far !!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design; Reliable; Easy To Use; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up

I&apos;ve owned HP printers for a long time and when it finally died and wanted to try something else. The Epson 845 workforce seem to do the trick. I like how fast it took to setup and the prints are fast TOO!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Carol</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very easy to use; excellent performance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Durable construction

I really love this printer! I&apos;m not technologcally adept, but was able to set it up to print wirelessly with three laptops and my iPod with no trouble at all. It&apos;s very easy to use, and I like the touch screen. Good-looking documents too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TWDDBQ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful Printer!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use

Cons: Flimsy Construction

This printer replaced a Canon MX860, which broke after a few of years and could never receive faxes. This EPSON has been wonderful right out of the box. Easy set up, it receives my faxes. Prints great quality and it is fast. I have only had this a couple of weeks and have not printed much color prints yet so this is based on black/white prints. I have a small at home business and I love the second paper tray for my letter head instead of having to switch the paper out when I am making up invoices. Just have to remember to select properties and select getting paper from the second tray. I have not had any problem with jams and also love being able to put a large stack of paper in the tray. I ho ... pe nothing changes because right now I am super happy with my purchase. I do have to work on the eprint features, I tried it once and it didn&apos;t work but I feel it was my error. Also our &quot;i&quot; products worked right off the bat with this printer without any troubles.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Objective</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than my previous Canon MX860</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Totally wireless; Fast Print Time; Great customer support; Low Ink Consumption

This printer is a lot faster than my old Canon that died after only 3 years of moderate use. User controls are much more intuitive than the Canon&apos;s as well.

I have it set up to be totally wireless between my main desktop and two laptops in different rooms. And it is not wireless just for printing but for scanning too. It did take me one 10 minute phone call to get it properly set up, but after that, it was good to go.

Photo quality is decent, although I haven&apos;t used it much for that, yet.

I love that the ink doesn&apos;t saturate and distort the paper like it did on my Canon.

All around, a winner!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>susan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>printer is heads above the HPs i&apos;ve had</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Reliable

i have purchased 3 different HP printers....none have survived much over a year, if that long. This Epson has worked wonderfully from day 1.
will never go back to HP</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mtl8826</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, sharp printing

Cons: Nothing

Got rid of a Kodak 5500 because of repeated print head problems. This Epson wireless printer has exceeded all my expectations. I can print from every device on my home wireless network. It has never lost the connection with the network. Wireless printing was very easy to set up; I used the USB cable to set it up in minutes. I give this printer 5+ stars. Also love the two paper trays.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice unit</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>setup was easy, printer, copy, scanner worked right out of box. I like the front panel display very easy see fax did not work on first try but i will go through setup again and check it out print speed is very good so far so good</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Emperor Crow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Purchase</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It took less than 15 minutes to install and print the first page. Instructions are so easy to follow there is no way to make mistakes. The print quality? Superb! I will give it 10 stars. As always, Epson has delivered a great quality product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Grant</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This Is The Printer To Choose</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design; This Printer works; Easy To Set Up; Low Ink Consumption; Durable construction; Works With Mac Computers; Easy To Use; Reliable

Cons: None

This Printer Replaced an HP 8500 Pro , It is easy to set up and prints fast and easy. Scanning is a easy. Color in Documents is Perfect . Photo prints will match Professional Prints. Set up to my wireless network fast and easy, same with e- print, App set up also fast . I an so Happy I got this printer!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ace Handyman of Santa Barbara</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fast printing &amp; Fast cable free setup</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Reliable; Easy To Use

This was the easiest printer I have ever set up with my mac. I didn&apos;t even have to connect a USB cable! Take note HP!! With 2 cartridges for paper, I can keep my company checks in the printer. And I can print from anywhere in the house with my computers, iPads and iPhones.Well Done EpsonDavid http://www.youracehandyman.com</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Skihard</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Workforce 845</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very easy to set up on both PC and Mac. Epson Iphone app works very well also. Prints fast and the ink lasts much longer than the the brand I had for 3 years. Would strongly recommend for home based business</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TRobins</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well Desinged All-in-one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: connectivity and print speed

Cons: nothing so far

This All-in-one lives up to its many high rating reviews. It has excellent print speed and connecting it to my home network was painless.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Crazy Creek Woman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>NOT SURE YET</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Durable construction

Cons: Hard To Use; Slow Print Time

Still having problems with printer. Don&apos;t know if my ccomputer causing problems. I have a few days to make a finally decision. I have used Epson for the last several years with little problems but this is getting hard to cope with. I need a fax and scanner and hope I can get them to work.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dukeir</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for home use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: speed, features, easy installation

Cons: dose not like photo paper (Epson photo paper!) Jams

Over all it is a good printer. It is easy to install, fast printer and works well with small home network. If you have a paper jam..., it is easy to clear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CF</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: EPSON WorkForce 845 All-in-One Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very easy to install. Recognized network with no problems. As with all hardware they try to shove a bunch of useless software at you. I find that part irritating. And makes the install a way to long to finish.
But, when it got itself ready, it was ready!
Printed 2 sided brochures. Set it to 35 copies and it did it great. Had to improve the print quality to fine instead of standard. Much better for photos in brochure. Which slowed printing down, but still very good. What a nice feature that worked fantastic.
Epson inks are still toooo expensive, so I&apos;ll use no name, like I have for years on many Epsons.
Epson has been our choice forever.
The C88&apos;s just won&apos;t quit.
Hope this is as good or better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Musipilot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredible deal for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Reliable

Cons: Too much ink used

Love the two-sided printing, the machine does it very well. Scanner is good as well. Very happy with the printer, and I think it does an incredible job for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gud1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It was very easy to set up and network connectivity was very simple.

I have used it only for a month so I can&apos;t say how it will hold up in the long term. Cannot comment on the ink usage either</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PriMed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for a Small Business.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good printing w/speed. Holds 1 pack of paper. Wifi. Easy prints from iPhone. 2 sided copies. Overall great buy.

Cons: Confusing to set up, but when you do, your fine. Touch screen features are scattered which makes it bothersome.

Great buy! This is my first time using Epson and pleased with this unit so far. I use it for my small business and it handles well. Even the cons I wrote doesn&apos;t take away its overall performance. Will continue to use Epson products. (Like I said, so far so good)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>4 out of 5 - Great printer overall!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Low Ink Consumption

Immediately I loved this printer. At first I thought I would not be able to print my own business cards or labels, but after I checked the settings within the computer I realized you need to change from FAST printing to QUALITY (slower). Once that is done it prints and registers fine. For most uses I would recommmend this printer. I do not print many photographs, so if that&apos;s what you want to do, I would focus on buying one that advertises for that purpose. However if you are printing documents, business cards, etc., this printer works great. Don&apos;t get me wrong, I&apos;ve printed a few photographs and it&apos;s fine. 
You can put it on fast printing for black and white and it is amazing. I couldn&apos;t believe it when I se ... t it up. I had been using a Canon before and it took it 45 seconds to a minute to &quot;warm up&quot;! This printer is fast if you need it to be and you can change the quality speed otherwise. I liked the two tray option, digital screen, wifi was a quick set up. 
Some people have mentioned the noise level, but this printer is so fast, so what? I didn&apos;t notice any major noise level myself. The only thing I wish it had was a rear load tray for the card stock and business cards, only for convenience. Since it has two trays I do load card stock in there so that works fine. This machine is shorter and a little smaller than last year&apos;s model. It seems that the ink cartridges are staying full longer on this printer than previous ones. 
Overall, I would give it a 4.5 stars, 1/2 star taken off for the slightly flimsy paper rest that you pull out and no rear tray.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SupraChica</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect all in one!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set up. Great price. Perfect for small business use.

Cons: Black color makes dust visible

Compared to my prehistoric HP I was using this is FAB! I mainly use it for faxing and scanning documents. It is user friendly and quick. I&apos;m not printing from it alot so don&apos;t know about the ink consumption yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Todriq</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So Long HP. This EPSON is the best I&apos;ve ever had.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simple to use and very fast. Software is easy as well.

Cons: It doesn&apos;t make coffee.

I have been a loyal HP user for over 20 years. That all ended when I decided to switch to this Epson after doing a little research. I am SOO glad I did my research. This Epson is by far the best printer I&apos;ve ever owned. I work from my home and need a reliable printer for photos and documents. I also need a good scanner to email documents and occasionally a fax. This printer does all of that and very easily and it works with my wireless network seamlessly. The printer screen is very user friendly and is a touch screen. I recommend this printer for anyone that runs a small business from their home.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Aliscabob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty good value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, numerous features, easy to use, individual color ink tanks

Cons: Print quality not the best, but decent for the price

Needed a printer that could print/fax/scan/copy and this one does all of it well enough. Use the copier part the most and am pleased with this function. Would recommend for an everyday printer, but not for someone who needs high quality print outs/photos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dawn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Easy touch screen

Cons: Couldn&apos;t scan wirelessly

Within the past 5 years, we&apos;ve had 2 HP printers, both of which stopped working correctly within the first 2 years of limited use. We decided to try Epson this time to see if our experience was better. Though we&apos;ve only had the printer for a few short months, it has been easy to use and figure out. The print quality is great and we noticed that if a printed page accidently gets wet, the ink did not run like the HP. We haven&apos;t had to replace any printer cartridges yet since it is relatively new and we have not printed a great deal since purchasing it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PRHSR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A lot of printer for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great quality, easy to set up.

Cons: It&apos;s bery big

This printer is great for home use if you have a big desk.
The ease of use, quality and speed make up for its bulk.
Would recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Drj5j</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Seems solid enough</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, reliable (so far)

Cons: Menu not intuitive; software not all-in-one

I am reluctant to review this printer after using it for only a few weeks, because to me one of the most important properties of a printer is how reliably it functions after months and years of use. I bought this printer because my previous printer (manufactured by a major, well-known company) suddenly lost the capacity to print in black ink after over a year of excellent, reliable performance. I went with the Epson Workforce 845 because it was the highest-rated printer (with a substantial number of reviewers) at Best Buy and because I have had an excellent experience with an Epson printer I use at work, the RX595.

Thus far, the printer has functioned solidly, printing clear pages quickly. ... The paper has jammed a couple of times, but it was due to user error, and the jam was quickly and easily cleared with no lingering problems. I have only a couple of minor complaints so far. First, the menu system on the printer itself is not intuitive, in my opinion. The initial, home menu is clear enough, showing basic options to copy, fax, scan, print pictures, and a few other choices. But after choosing one of these options, I found myself faced with an icon-based menu in which it was not clear what all the icons would do. For example, what will happen if I touch the box with the letter &quot;c&quot; in it on the copy page? What about the diamond shape with a vertical line through it? Obviously the functions of these icons can be learned by trial-and-error (not ideal) or by reading the manual (god forbid), but it would have been nicer to have icons with clearer meanings and/or text options.

The other minor complaint I have is the software provided for my computer. My previous printer had a nice &quot;all-in-one center&quot; where I could begin no matter what my task (print settings, fax, scanning, etc.). With the Epson workforce, I have to pull up a different program from my Windows 7 menu for any task. Choosing &quot;All Programs&quot; from Windows 7 start, I find three different Epson folders: EPSON, EP ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GQuiz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great all in one printer; great value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The extensive features for the price!

Cons: Haven&apos;t found anything yet.

Purchased the Epson Workforce 845 to replace an existing Lexmark all in one that required expensive ink cartridges too often and didn&apos;t have fax capability built in. We have been very pleased with all the great features of the workforce as well as the auto document feeder, dual paper trays and the ability to print to it via the web and from iPhones! This printer is a phenomenal deal! Highly, highly recommend it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Epson</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>845 printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have always had a different brand of printer, I found this one to be easy to set up and has nice features. The larger ink cartridges are also a bonus. Overall I would recomend this printer to others..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>scballou</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Terrible design flaw!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Compact Design; Quality scan image

Cons: Can&apos;t scan from printer; Jams Easily; Unreliable; Flimsy Construction

Originally bought this for an artistic (photographer/graphic designer) Mac user. Printer scans nicely but it only scans and copies certain sizes (legal &amp; letter). If you go beyond a traditional letter or legal size paper, you&apos;re just SOL. Returned it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sunshine50</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>i have one and my hubby has one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: it does it all

Cons: ink cartridges aren&apos;t cheap

I love mine for everything I use it for. I needed one with double sided and mine doesn&apos;t do that. I didn&apos;t want to trade it with my husbands so I bought him the one that I wanted and I use his for two sided copies and I use mine for everything else. The Epson is better than the HP he bought. We took it back because it didn&apos;t meet our standards.
This prints pics really nice and I use mine for documents which works great. Best printer out there with the price and usage.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Annie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson, it has to be good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time

Cons: Bigger than my WorkForce

I thought, OMG, this is going to take forever to set up. 15 minutes and we were up and running.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TranceGirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson WorkForce 845, All-in-One.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Fast Print Time

Cons: Flimsy Construction

Good printer! Fast printing time, good quality prints, but kinda big in size, would like for printer to be smaller and have the same features as this one I have. Would recommend to a friend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bev in Seattle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better for home use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact Design

Cons: Flimsy Construction

Sure it&apos;s fast - but not at high-quality. So high-quality copies were as slow as our old HP. 
There are two trays, only one lets you put special size paper in it (envelopes) and the trays seemed flimsy and fragile. I&apos;m sure the overall cost of ownership is lower, but we ended up buying the new imaging drum for our old HP workhorse to keep in the office and sent the new Epson home w/ someone who needed it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>danhector</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent buy,</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: eprinting was flawless

Cons: injet cartridges are expensive

easy set up, flawless performance. has a solid build and quiet operation. would recommend for home or small office use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>155</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Erricht3000</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Wi-Fi Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great value for the price. Nice touch screen that works well. Wi-Fi is a huge bonus if you&apos;ve never had it before. Holds 500 pieces of paper which is really nice. Scanner works great. Setting up the printer and Wi-Fi networking was simple. Printer is a bit large, but it will fit nicely on any smaller sized table/desk.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>156</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>grace2live</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson always great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality of printing and ease of use

I&apos;ve never had anything but Epson for printing. Haven&apos;t owned this for long, but it was a snap to set up, and the quality is wonderful. This particular model is more than we need, with 2 paper trays, etc., but the deal on it made it too good to pass up when my old one bit the dust.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>157</ID>
     <Item>Epson WorkForce 845 Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/1275228908325965905/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.87&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=M6mRULPiCaq22gWK3IGYDg&amp;ved=0CNABEPQCMAM4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>venkat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fast, Crisp and sharp prints, duplex</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Compact Design; Low Ink Consumption; Easy To Set Up; Fast Print Time

Cons: A tad bit noisy

This is a great printer, the prints are sharp and great quality. The printer is a tad bit nosier than the cannon Pixma MX860, but the speed of print far compensates for this noise.

Prints from iPad, iPhone etc. no issues. 

Two trays to load papers, duplic printing is fast and reliable. 

High canacity ink tanks (#127) last lot longer than redular ones.

Touch screen is easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

