<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Superb photo prints, faster printing than the Epson R2880, can print on roll paper, CDs and DVDs, bigger ink tanks are more economical, uSB, Ethernet and Wi-Fi connectivity, auto-switching between photo and matte black ink

Cons: Wasteful ink purge during auto switching, expensive

The Epson Stylus Photo R3000 is an upgrade -- but not a replacement -- for the Epson Stylus Photo R2880, which is one of experts&apos; favorite high-end photo printers. The R3000 fixes the R2880&apos;s biggest flaw, reviews say: You no longer have to manually switch the black ink tank every time you switch between matte and glossy paper (the R3000 now makes the switch automatically). ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Neiman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up

Cons: Large Footprint

I previously used an Epson R1800 which I was happy with except for the fact that I could see printer lines in skies in my photos. Now, I am talking about holding the print up to my nose and really staring. The other minor issue with the R1800 was that the clouds in most of my photos had a color cast. Also I was never happy with black and white photo results; too much metamerism and some color cast, therefore I never printed black and white. As well, if I was to print a sheet of text, I noticed that the characters were slightly misaligned; the letters looked a little jagged. I wondered if text was slightly jagged, is it really printing my photos as well as it should?Enter the R3000. Transitions in the sky are smooth (which they ... were on the R1800 as well). I might be able to see printer lines from the R3000 only if using a loupe. I also downloaded a test print photo. Print gradations on the test photo were incredibly smooth as well. I was really impressed when I saw no color cast at all in clouds in my photos. I wanted to see how vivid the printer will print, so I printed a photo of Hawaiian print clothing from the swap meet in Honolulu. Colors are vivid and true except for slight difference in the yellow. See that photo in this review.It has an advanced black and white mode in the driver where you can select neutral, cool, warm, and sepia. It works very well. If you want some tips on printing black and white, check out Eric Chan&apos;s tips here in his chart at the bottom before you print (chart is for Epson 3800 but also applies to R3000): http://people.csail.mit.edu/ericchan/dp/Epson3800/abwprofiles.htmlI printed a sheet of text; letters have no jaggies! They&apos;re perfect! If you print only glossy photos, perhaps better to stay with one of the printers that have a gloss optimizer. If you print glossy on the R3000, there is sheen differential in the areas that have little or no color. However, if you can live with that since the variations are hardly noticeable. In addition, you could spray the photo with a glossy spray.It seems to suck ink like a pig. In fairness, however, during the initial setup you lose a lot of ink. Admittedly, I have printed a lot since this is new for me. According to [@], the cost of ink to print an 8.5 X 11 for both the R1800 and the R3000 is about 70 cents.I was hoping that since the cartridges are roughly twice the size of the R1800, that they would cost less. The 3880, they say, is much more economical on ink. I had considered this printer as well. For me, though, the cost of the 3880 is so much higher than the R3000, it would take forever for me to make up the cost in ink saved. The other drawback of the 3880, for me, was that it takes two people to set it up because of the weight. The big advantage I see for the 3880 is the wider format, which is really nice. Cannot comment on matte paper nor fine art paper yet, since I haven&apos;t tried any of those yet.The R1800 certainly met most of my needs. Photography is just a hobby for me. The incentive for my getting the R3000 was the rebate until the end of September. I am glad I bought it. I can see where it can take my photos to a new level.There are two reasons why I only gave it 4 stars instead of 5 is because of the cost of the ink. Epson isn&apos;t giving you a discount for buying cartridges that are twice the size of the R1800, but they are giving the owners of the 3880 a &quot;discount,&quot; proportionally, for buying larger. In addition to that, ink is wasted each time you change from photo black to matte black ink and vice versa. I think this waste of expensive ink is a travesty. As far as print quality, I can&apos;t imagine that it can get better.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BCLW</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson R3000 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Durable construction; Reliable; Easy To Use

Cons: Hard Setup; Large Footprint

Great quality photo prints.
Great inks.
Wireless setup is difficult and time consuming.
Setup with monitor and matching with photo papers is not straightforward. 
Inks are expensive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just OK.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>It is a good quality printer, but only useful for small number of pictures. Each picture needs to be re-sized to match the paper size before printing. For example if you are printing a 4x6 print, you need to open the picture in something like Photoshop and resize the print to be 4x6 else the software will print just the top left part of the picture. I called Epson customer service and was told the fit to page option does not resize the print by design. They assume that if the user is using an advanced printer they don&apos;t want to change the print in any way. To me that is a bug in their driver. They should give the user the option to do it manually or automatically. They said this is by design on the R3000. This printer is not for the person who just wants to print 20 or 30 quality pictures ... off of their camera. Each picture requires some work before printing. Epson customer service was great. I did not like their answers, but still they did a good job of answering my questions and even did some investigation and called me back. You cannot ask for better service than that.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dr Mickey</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have owned the Epson Stylus R3000 for almost three weeks, so it&apos;s a bit premature for any final thoughts, but what I have seen so far, I like. The R3000 has done a superb job printing on Red River Aurora, Polar Matte, and Polar Gloss papers as well as Moab Colorado and Ilford Gold Fibre Silk. Colors are true and well-saturated, with a surprisingly good image on glossy papers. Black and white is deep and well-defined, and the R3000 solves an issue I had with my previous brand C pro printer where black and white images printed with varying shades of a green tint. This is a true higher resolution printer and it rewards your efforts to shoot a tack-sharp image. The black ink swapping is reasonably painless, as the R3000 selects glossy or matte once you choose the paper&apos;s ICC profile and pr ... int. If you turn on the printer and send a print job that requires an ink swap, though, the R3000 does chug and whirr for a few minutes and a screen pop-up lets you know it&apos;s changing ink tanks. Paper handling has been faultless so far, and 13 x 19 sheets have fed with ease through the front paper path. I have not yet had occasion to use the roll-fed option as I prefer not having to deal; with paper curl. The size and weight the R3000 seem unremarkable; it&apos;s actually a couple of inches narrower than the printer it replaced. Nice, solid build as well. I know that the C brand pigment printer is a strong competitor, but I decided that I didn&apos;t want to deal any longer with its limitation on print length and its imposition of its own borders on fine art paper. I really like the R3000 and I believe it is a great way to enjoy taking your photography to the next level. Highly recommended.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rickiboston</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great photos, easy setup, big footprint!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My former Epson photo printer just outright died and I was desperate for something new and easy to use. After researching printers, I decided that I didn&apos;t need to go bigger and more expensive so chose the R3000. The setup was easy and I love the wifi option - the fewer cords the better. The only negative so far is the bigger footprint. It takes up more room than my previous Epson that printed the same size prints. Not sure why it has to be so big but...love the prints!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rick into Birds</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Color photos are astounding</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have just started doing photographs of birds and insects primarily flying or in motion. The color photographs I have produced so far have exceeded my expectations with the detail and subtle differences in colors and textures of the birds clearly and accurately reproduced. For the flying insects their intricate patterns of colors and textures and the richness of the flowers and vegetation they land on is vividly reproduced. For the money this is a great printer. Setup was quick with easy to follow directions; I was printing my first photo within an hour of unpacking the printer. As with most people&apos;s experience of this printer the biggest down side is the flushing of ink when changing to matte ink. I would definitely recommend this printer to anyone interested in producing display qualit ... y photographs.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Weatherman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy with R3000 with a few caviots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is my primary photo printer with photoshop 10. Got it because of perminant nature of pigment inks and reliability. After some set up issues, it is now working great. Had to figure out that that mode had to be set to ICM to get it to look like what I saw on my monitor. Wasted a lot of pictures before I figured that out. Certain colors of ink do run down faster and have to use Epson papers to get the quality I want. In the end the quality of the images are worth the fact that thge ink runs down faster than I would like.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very easy setup and wonderful prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a novice photographer who is picking up this previous hobby since I retired. I purchased a Canon EOS 60D camera and wanted a good printer. First let me say that it was simple to setup and use with wifi. The quality of the print exceeded my expectations and printing using different sizes of paper could not be any more straight forward. The only downside (if there is one) is the price of the ink. I am finding that I need to conserve on what I print so that I do not run down the ink. Overall, I love the printer and the quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kriptac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After having owned another similar photo printer by a different major manufacturer that was total garbage, I began my research on the internet with far more deliberation to find a replacement. It didn&apos;t take long in doing my homework before I soon discovered (from reviews and comments) that the Stylus Photo R3000 was the answer. Once I started honing in on everything written that I could find about this printer, I had no hesitation whatsoever in purchasing said printer. Once received, I could not have been more delighted with everything involving the R3000. Setup and software installation was a breeze... it could not have gone any easier. But my shear joy came once I started printing. The results were spectacular as the colors were brilliant, the detail was spectacular, and the overa ... ll operation was excellent. I was a computer tech for 25+ years and have watched the evolution of both the PC and printer since their infancy. I have worked on printers during that entire time and know I own a quality product that will give me many years of superb printing that will far exceed the disaster I recently experienced. Thank you Epson!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photographer wanna be</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Photo Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality Prints; Ease of installation; Wi fi is great

Cons: Very Heavy; Fairly expensive

I installed the printer without any glitches. 
I use it as wi fi set up and it works great, but sometimes, as expected, could run very slow.
Too bad it does not have option for printing envelopes.
Regular non-photo printing is not of good quality, too grey and not enough black. It could be a setting issue that I have not figured out yet.
Very little ink is provided with the printer as it comes in the box, it would be nice to get a bit more ink for the paid price.
Adorama&apos;s service was great. Placing order was easy, but I called in the order becasue I had questions. I received the package in less than a week from the time of order.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>El Fotero</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A fine machine and a terrible driver</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>First thing first. Color management in a tough coogie. If you believe that buying the best printer in the world will give wonderful color and B&amp;W pictures right out of the box you are ready for a big disappointment. Good color and B&amp;W pictures is a result of several factors, such as, a well calibrated monitor, lighting and even a viewing light that must be at least similar to the lighting condition under which the picture will be displayed. After several years I have settled for X-rite i1display Pro and Epson Ultra Premium Photo Paper Luster and Epson printer with pigmented ink. Before reviewing the printer, the bad things. I tried to install it for wireless use using the USB method. After three computers failed to install it I talked to the Tech Support, which is not a toll ... free number and the technician was as mystified as I was. Fortunately, the printer&apos;s screen provide another method of installation and this worked perfectly and flawlessly. Technical Support however could not solve it. To test the printer I used two pictures included in the driver CD ROM and the result were nothing short of amazing. However, I noticed that an old foe popped-up: Bronzing. Bronzing is a picture effect in which, if you tilt a paper picture in certain angle with respect to a light source, certain colors appear as a stain rather than being part of the image. It looks as if the color float on top of the image rather than being part of the image. When I called the technical support, they advised to bypass the entire Color Management technique to allow the printer to manage the color. This is astonishing! The whole concept of color management is to match the what you see on the screen with what you get out the printer. The printer is a peripheral and has no way to know what the monitor is showing you. The printer itself cannot decide what output will match your screen. I learned, way way back, that chasing color to match the screen and the printer can blow your cost out proportion. You waste the fine paper and your very, very very expensive inks pursuing a chance. That is one of the most important reasons to embrace Color Management. I followed the advise and, of course, the color was terrible off, and logically so. The technician could not explain the bronzing and how to mitigate it. This is still an issue. A more serious flaw is, however, the driver of the printer. A driver is a software element that is installed with the device to allow the computer to talk to the peripheral, in this case, the printer. Very few times have I&apos;ve seen such a careless driver. This is the list of issues that I found: The paper is mentioned twice in the same driver, with different name. In the front ed is called SPR 3000 premium luster, but deep in another submenu is called Ultrapremium Photo Paper Luster. This submenu is labeled Print Settings, but, if you try to go there to review the settings it tells you that the primer does not exist. The only way that I found to re-enter is by switching to another printer momentarily and then re-select the R3000 again. At that point I already lost all the setting and the driver by default goes back to matte paper. This driver remembers nothing. If I want to print two copies of the same picture, after the printer finishes the first, it already forgot that I ordered two. You can print a second one, of course, but the driver will also forget your color setting and you have to go back the same routine: Chose another printer because the driver does not recognize the printer the second time around, reselect the R3000 and you will need to re-enter all the color options. Every single copy is an exercise of patient. There are other less irritating issues, for example, I have found no way to erase a configuration that was wrong or I no longer need, the driver does not tell me how much ink do I have in the cartridges, etc. Of course, every time that you forget one of those little things the resulting color is completely off. Despite an irritating and cheap, cheap driver, my testing in...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr. Murphy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Pix, Beware the Ink Consumption</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This printer replaced a 2200 that I had used with pleasure for many years. Be advised that it is exclusively a photo printer, not a general purpose color printer. It produces much better quality prints than the 2200 and it is much easier to set up and use. I am happy with the purchase BUT... Get ready for a new dimension in ink consumption. The larger cartridges do not mean longer times between refills--they are large because you will simply use much more ink. Believe every word that other reviewers say when they complain about the ink consumption. It is immediately apparent even after producing the first few prints AND... Develop some patience because it takes noticeably more time for this model to cycle up and produce the first print than the 2200. NONETHELESS... This printer is certa ... inly the best value for moving up from lower-numbered Epson printers--if you want good quality photo prints. This is especially true if you print panoramas using roll paper because the next-up models only print sheets. 5 stars for the printer and 3 stars for the ink consumption makes this a 4 star rating.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JEO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow! Great Colors!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m not a professional photographer but wanted to print nicer photos and bigger ones then 8-1/2x11. I found out that you can only use Epson paper with this printer. I had another kind of high quality paper but it&apos;s weight is different &amp; as it comes out it scratches the right corner of the photo. The Epson paper makes a difference. Beautiful colors!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LT109</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s big, but it prints beautifully!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Large Footprint; A little pricey

I have this printer specifically for photos. I have limited experience with it so far, as I just got it. Having said that, I am excited by what I have seen so far. It was easy to setup wirelessly, with no issues. It is big, but if you have the room for it, it is worth it. Remember, you don&apos;t have to be wired to your computer to use it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Color and B&amp;W Prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Got this to replace my Epson 2200, very worthwhile upgrade. Setup done in less than 30 min., easily connected to my wireless network. Prints have been superb from the get-go, accurate rendition of display colors once I calibrated monitor and printer/paper. Produces neutral-toned B&amp;W (a bugaboo of the 2200) using the B&amp;W mode. Has been a joy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Robert Qi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Setup to use wireless, very easy and smooth. The CD/DVD printing function is very handy and important to me. Haven t used many features yet, but I believe it won t disappoint.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Riversher</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Quality Prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very happy with this product. Quality is outstanding, price is very competitive. Ease of use with a great design. I upgraded from an Epson 2200. It gives better prints than the 2200.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RaffaLUCE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Prints, Wasteful Ink</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>To be fair, this is my first printer of this level. It was down to this or Canon&apos;s 9500mkII. After tons of research, I got the Epson. I&apos;ve had it now for about 6 months. The prints are gorgeous - very impressive. Letting the printer manage color, with a little tweaking, actually works very well 90% of the time. Setup was pretty easy, and I love having the wi-fi instead of running yet another cable to my computer. It&apos;s about as big as expected but not overwhelming. Heavy but I was able to lift it from the box to table by myself without undue strain (I&apos;m 5&apos;7 female in reasonable but not epic shape). What I do NOT love, is the ink waste. And I don&apos;t mean while printing - that&apos;s acutally pretty good. On matte papers, I actually lower the ink density and use just the Quality setting now - d ... idn&apos;t see an appreciable difference from High Quality even looking very, very closely under bright light. Randomly (it seems) when I send a project to print it will spend about 7-10 minutes adjusting, whirring, and wasting ink. This is even if I&apos;ve used it recently and leaving it in standby mode. And no, not while changing from matte to glossy blacks. I&apos;ve watched ALL ink levels drop visibly when this happens. It is VERY frustrating watching $$$ disappear for no apparent reason. The nozzles can&apos;t possibly need that much cleaning! I called Epson with the issue to see if I needed to return/exchange the printer. He said the issue I described was not a known issue. He did his best to help, but ultimately, he didn&apos;t really have a specific solution to my concern (found more help on the dpreview forums) but did send a brand new set of inks to me without me having to ask. The problem seemed to subside for a while, but it&apos;s started doing it again today. Not sure if there&apos;s an external factor I&apos;m not aware of - temperature is pretty consistent in the room and it&apos;s not overly dry. I print anywhere from several times a day to every couple of weeks. BUT, when it isn&apos;t wasting ink on whatever it&apos;s doing for those 7-10 minutes, it&apos;s a great printer - the end result is really beautiful. I will note, too, though that it seems to struggle a little with highly saturated, deep blues, but I believe that may be something normal as blues can be difficult to reproduce in gamut. The reds are great though! Would I get another Epson? I can&apos;t say for sure. I&apos;d like to get a wide-format printer eventually, and who knows what will be available by the time I&apos;m actually able to buy one.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Indiana Cath</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No limits to your creativity</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Functionality; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Durable construction; Reliable

Cons: Price

Was fed up with bad color and media jams using cheaper printers, but didn&apos;t know if this pricey printer would be worth it. So far I&apos;m happy. This printer is easy to set up and has a ton of functionality. It has no problem handling strange paper sizes or thick card stock. The feed mechanism is awesome - when I choose a border around my print it is perfect. And the color is amazing. If I can imagine an end result, this printer can produce it. I have not used it long enough to comment on ink consumption, and have also not used the B&amp;W mode.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JohnT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer! Minor paper size problem</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Just replaced my Epson R2880 with the R3000. Over 90% of my printing is of photographs and never having to swap Photo and Matte Black ink cartridges when changing paper types is wonderful! Paper handling for thicker paper has improved. The larger ink cartridges are nice, but won&apos;t save you much money over the smaller R2880 cartridges. Printed images are superb, but that was true with the R2880 as well. I have a problem with Moab Entradalopes. The paper is 7 x 10 and the profile from Moab uses a Fine Art media type which forces the use of the front paper loader. The front paper loader has a minimum paper size of 8.27 x 11. My solution is to ask Moab support to suggest an alternate media type that uses the sheet feeder and I will make my own profile using a Colormunki when I hear bac ... k from them. Be aware that the minimum page size for media types that use the front paper loader is 8.27 x 11 and that you can&apos;t override where to load the paper as you could with the R2880. I would have given a five star rating if it wasn&apos;t for this limitation.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RR Ben</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Intro Pro Pinter</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Durable construction

Cons: Too much ink used

After extensive research and reading other reviews I chose this printer and I&apos;m not disappointed. The ability to connect via Wi-Fi was very important to me and the $150 rebate was an added incentive. It is a very sturdy well constructed and a very quiet printer, so quite you don&apos;t even know it is running. Setup was fast and easy.

I have used the Epson R3000 for a few weeks and a few dozen photos, it was easy to install and although the printer settings can easily be tweaked, the default settings work very well right out of the box. The quality in the color of my printed photographs is the best of any printer I&apos;ve ever owned. 

I love the ability to change from photo black to matte ... black. The only thing that chaps me about this printer is the amount of ink that gets lost due to switching from matte black to photo black or vice versa considering the high cost of the R3000 ink cartridges.

I am very happy with this purchase. It is a great printer and I would highly recommend it to anyone interested in a printer that prints very high quality photos.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bear</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far, Outstanding!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I ordered this printer on a Monday and it arrived Thursday. I have been researching ink jet printers for a year now and finally settled on the Epson R3000, for it&apos;s price and for all of the positive reviews I have read. I&apos;m particularly interested in its black and white capabilities so that I can print old negatives that I have scanned. It&apos;s still pretty early, as far as my experience with this printer but so far, I&apos;m pleased with its performance. I have spent quite a bit of time calibrating my monitor and making test prints. A little more tweaking of my image files and I believe I&apos;ll be there. Can&apos;t wait to print my color work!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cos</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb quality prints, uses o lot of ink</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the 3000 for large prints. The wireless feature is great and was easy to set up. The colors are rich and vibrant! The overall quality of the prints is superb!! The printer uses a lot of ink when transferring photo and matte black. I would recommend this printer</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Renzo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beautiful print quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Print quality; Durable construction; Easy To Use

Cons: Too much ink used

It&apos;s a pretty big unit and I was initially annoyed because the software cd did not include what I needed. If you have a mac with the latest version of lion operating system, you need to download drivers from epson&apos;s website, which is not entirely user-friendly. That also goes for the ICC profiles. Intersting that they don&apos;t have ICC profiles for all of their own papers. Also, epson&apos;s tech support is not available 24/7, so difficult for those of us with day jobs. I also read that it&apos;s heavy on the ink usage, but I haven&apos;t printed that much yet. I live in Arizona (dry) so I know I&apos;ll need to keep it on all the time and print at least weekly to keep nozzles clean. 
All that being said..... The prin ... ts are spectacular. I ordered a sampler of papers and the fine art papers are gorgeous (textures, whites, deep blacks, vivid colors). Despite epson&apos;s initial weaknesses, the prints are worth the experience.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Robi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent prosumer product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Durable construction; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

The printer is used essentially only for photo production. The ability to handle multiple paper types and sizes is a big plus. I set up for a MacPro OS 10.6.x with WiFi and really quite easy to get the printer entered to my Mac. The paper selection process when printing was not initially intuitive, but once understood, it was easy to select different papers. I print from Lightroom 1.2 and iPhoto; currently Lightroom&apos;s profiles produce a darker image, but I am working with Lightroom to correct that.

This is the printer for you if your focus is on photos. If you are looking to print color documents, I recommend a different Epson printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Catail409</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Going with the R3000</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Compact Design

Cons: Slow Print Time; Too much ink used

I like Epson printers. The Epson R3000 Printer is my fourth Epson Printer. I started out with a 1280 model, moved to a 1800 model (loved that glossy look) and then went to a 2880 because I wanted to do Black &amp; White, which I thought the 2880 did superbly. But my 2880 rear paper feed never really worked with any consistency and when the pump and other noises began to make me think that the old 2880 was on its last legs I decided to spring for the R3000 rather than take the risk that a new 2880 would simply have the same rear paper feed problems. Plus, Epson advertised that the R3000 offered better color, so I went for it.
Installation &amp; set up of the 3000 went well. There have been a ... few changes but nothing big and if you have used Epson printers previously you should not have any problems. Printing with the Top Sheet feeder is basically the same as the other Epson products. There has been a redesign in the way that thick &quot;Fine Art&quot; paper is installed. Rather than feed these papers through the rear as in previous designs, the Fine Art Paper is now inserted through a paper tray in the front where the printer grabs it, feeds it through to the rear where the machine aligns it prior to feeding the paper back into the printer it to make the print. I found the directions for this process rather opaque in the owner&apos;s manual and had to call Epson for explanation which Epson provided without any problem. Once you get the feel for the process things go fine, but the process requires you to follow explicit prompts on the screen in the front of the printer. This process takes time though, the machine is in control, it takes its time and you cannot hurry it. The good news is that there have no paper jams.
I have not yet decided on the print quality. I have printed everything on Level 4 Quality. The first prints I made on Cold Press paper seemed to have a little more vividness but it is hard to tell. The monochrome prints I have made do not seem to have the great tonal values that I got with the 2880, but that may be a case of me getting used to the machine. The negative comment I have is Ink Consumption. The R3000 seems to suck up ink like the desert sands absorb water. Ink consumption is definitely much higher with the R3000 than the 2880. My preliminary estimate is that consumption is up by as much as 50%. I am going to have to reduce the number of casual prints I make with this machine simply because of this increase in ink consumption. The prints are nice though. Except for the consumption issue I am pleased with my printer but if you are considering a purchase think about how you will be using the machine.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WBDesign</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love, Love, Love this printer!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I definitely recommend this printer to anyone who needs to print great quality prints! I am a graphic artist. I use my printer to send proofs to my customers. I have gotten many complements on the look of the proofs. I&apos;m also a mixed media artist and I use this printer for high quality prints to use in my artwork. Prints beautifully! Crisp and clear. Seems to work best on Epson papers. In my opinion this is the best printer you can buy for printing quality prints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cliff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Rich black and white prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>A great printer that was very easy to set up for wireless connection with my iMAC. I have been looking for a photo printer that would produce rich black and white photos and have not been disappointed. Scanned in some old black and white negatives and was very impressed with the output compared to the wet chemical prints I had made in a darkroom.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>C N Photo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Espon R3000</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Setup; Easy To Use

Cons: Too much ink used

The jury is still out. So far my prints look great. After only 7 5x7 prints the ink levels have dropped 30%. I was told this printer ships with full cartridges but maybe this isn&apos;t the case. I&apos;m hoping the ink meters on the front of the printer are not acurate. If they are I&apos;ll be investing another $300 in ink by the end of the week.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Inkjet printer for me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Reliable

Cons: Slow Print Time; Too much ink used

Great quality color prints on any paper! Absolutely great results! If you like the control of printing your own photos and controlling your time, this is a the best! My only complaint is the amount of black ink it consumes as it switches between Matte &amp; Photo black.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lucidinscriber</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My Pick for Perfect Prosumer Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>At school I&apos;ve been using an Epson Stylus Pro 3880 and have gotten kind of addicted to printing my photos. The R3000 is half the cost and almost exactly the same except for it&apos;s narrower 13 maximum print width (vs the 17 3880). Both use the UltraChrome K3 with Vivid Magenta ink set which is the same one used by almost all of Epson&apos;s Pro line of printers. Honestly, I don&apos;t know why the R3000 isn&apos;t in their Pro line since it could reasonably be used by a pro who never needed to print anything wider than 13.I printed some color test charts at the [@] photo lab (which should be reasonable quality since they actually calibrate their printers at least once a day and when they change paper rolls) and on my R3000, then compared them to an actual X-Rite produced ColorChecker chart, and the output f ... rom the R3000 significantly beats the output from [@] Fuji Frontier minilab photo printer. The Fuji Frontier print is noticeably duller with generally darker colors and a narrower range of saturated color reproduction. You don&apos;t have to be a color expert to see the difference.For the R3000 the ink cost is about $1/ml which comes out to about $0.01 per square inch if you get it at a discount (search for red river Cost of Inkjet Printing Epson R3000). That makes a borderless 8x10 cost about $0.80 in ink, and a borderless 8.5x11 cost about $1 in ink. A sheet of Epson Ultra Premium Photo paper costs as little as $0.60 if you get it at a discount, so printing a borderless 8.5x11 ends up costing as little as $1.60 in supplies. (Not to mention that you can get third-party paper that&apos;s just as good or better than Epson&apos;s official paper for less money.)The cheapest photo labs charge around $1.50 for an 8x10 (my local [@] currently charges $1.46). If we use a whole 8.5x11 sheet of official paper and a full 8x10 worth of ink to print an 8x10, we get $1.40 in supplies per 8x10 which is slightly cheaper than even [@] and significantly higher quality. Good third-party paper would be around $0.35/sheet meaning that you could also do as well as $1.15 per 8x10, maybe even better.Admittedly though that doesn&apos;t incorporate the cost of the printer, which you won&apos;t have to incur if you just use a photo lab. If you bought the printer for say $800 and you&apos;ve gotten your per-8x10 supply costs down to $1.15, then you&apos;d need to print about 2,580 8x10&apos;s before your total costs started to get lower than [@]&apos;s $1.46.When you get larger than 8x10 though then the printer really starts to pay off. One place online that isn&apos;t too expensive and has a good reputation charges $6.30 for a 12x18 on glossy photo paper printed with a photographic lab process. It&apos;s possible to get decent 13x19 gloss ink jet photo paper (same stuff that costs $0.35/sheet for the 8.5x11) for about $1.50/sheet. 12x18 of ink costs you $2.16 so total cost for a 12x18 on the R3000 with that paper is $3.66. At that price you need to print 300 or so of these large prints before your prints start costing less than $6.30, and again the ink jet prints may have better quality than the photographic process printer depending on who&apos;s doing the printing and with what.You also have the entire lifetime of the printer to make all these prints that we&apos;re talking about. If you make on average about 10 8x10 prints every week then it would take about 5 years to make this cost back, but if you made two of the 12x18 prints per week then it would take about 2.8 years to brake even compared to the lower quality photographic process prints ordered from most places online.But none of these estimates take into account the value of the convenience and additional quality you get from having a modern photo inkjet printer right in front of you. Add in costs like transportation to pick up photos, time spent driving, any sort of cost of inconvenience by having to wait for prints to arrive in the mail, the additional value of better color quality, and other hard to quantify things then the real savings may be better. Depending on how much these costs add to the cost of photo lab prints, a decent ink jet printer like this...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WinFirst</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer-great results!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Absolutely great results! If you like the control of printing your own photos and controlling your time, this is a great printer! No sending files off to wait for their return and hoping it&apos;s the look you want. Epson has done really well with providing ICC profiles so that there is next to no trial and error wasting paper and ink. It does use a lot of ink, but the results require this so it is not an issue. If I just want quick photos for friends to throw in a drawer or put on the fridge, use an inexpensive consumer item. But if you want stunning photos and realistic colors with breaking the bank too much then buy this printer!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>drjoe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The printer seems to work well, setup was easy and my initial prints look great. One issue is that the printer comes out of the box with the default setting on photoblack, and it is not easy to change this. A few blogs on the subject but I have not been able to figue it out on my IMAC. You can change the defaults on the front panel of the printer but they do not stay once the printer is turned off then on again.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Venz Studio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One of the Best Epson</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable; Compact Design; Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption

Printer is a one of the best epson printers. No problems and prints amazing photos. Wifi is easy to setup.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quality printer at an affordable price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this product to print 8x10&apos;s. I print between 10-20 per day and enjoy the right colors in the printouts. The R3000 consumes a fair amount of ink and requires the 5 star Epson paper to display glossy professional images.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fine Art Girl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Photos only</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this product to replace my old Epson 2200. I use the printer primarily to print note cards on cotton rag papers, and the image quality is very good. Before purchasing the printer I called Epson pre-sales support to see if the printer supported custom sizes for all paper selections, and I was told that it does. I now know that that affirmation was in error, and I have to trick the printer to print on my note card stock, just as I did on the 2200. No improvement there! Loading fine art paper in this printer is more difficult than it was with the 2200;another area where the new model is no improvement. I also used my Epson 2200 for general office printing: Letters, envelopes, labels, and etc. The R3000 does not print envelopes! This was a surprise, and a disappointm ... ent. Evidently Epson planned for this printer to be a photo printer only. The printer does nice B&amp;W prints, but changing black inks still wastes time and ink. I knew that going in, so no complaint other then the fact that Epson cannot seem to get this done efficiently. I rated the printer four stars because the print quality is very good, and I like the wireless connection. The B&amp;W is especially good. If you are looking for a photo printer only, the R3000 may be a good choice for you. If you need a printer that will primarily be used for photo prints, but also want to use it for general office printing you may want to look elsewhere. Although I would recommend this printer to a friend, I would do so only if they understood that this machine is for photos only.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nilou</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i use this printer for home photos,excellent results pictures are exactly the same as of it is on the computer. i have printed 8.5 by 11 and they are great i do not know about bigger size. it takes a while to warm up when i turn it on and little slow. other wise great printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Epson Fan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Results</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased the Epson R3000 to replace my aging R1800. The R1800 would produce great color prints but would fail on B&amp;W prints. I&apos;m happy to report that the R3000 produces exhibition quality B&amp;W prints that are neutral in tone which is exactly what I was looking for. I&apos;m somewhat missing the gloss optimizer ink from my R1800 that is not present in the R3000. The R3000 has both photo black and matte black ink cartridges that do not require physical swapping, but does require flushing. I recently did a print which required a switch between gloss and matte ink. In the print dialogue it will pop up an error telling you that black ink is incorrect which requires you to go to the printer&apos;s LCD menu interface to switch the black inks. Once flushing is complete (3 minutes or less) the prin ... ting will commence. There were some hickups with the R3000 not recognizing the the correct ink cartridges asking me to check the black cartridges so I had to pop them in and out which solved the problem. The correct cartridges were in the right place, so I&apos;m not sure if this is a bug with the the printer. The footprint is rather large but as other reviewers have pointed out, since it has wifi and is networkable you can place the printer in a different room.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KYRoadkill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Another Winner From Epason</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have not had the product long, but have used with normal luster paper, semi-gloss, exhibition fiber, and canvas. Once I read the directions on how to print, everything fell into place. Setup was simple and very straight forward. Only negative is the time and extra ink required for the printer to automatically change from photo black to matte black and back. If using different papers, it is better to plan ahead to save ink.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shauneen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Reliable Workhorse</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have a small commercial photography business and was tired of having good printers not up tp fairly routine tasks or failing after a few months. This printer charged out of the starting blocks and never looked back. It is easy to set up and operate. Customer service from the manufacturer is exceptional.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Suzy Q</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best printer I have ever used.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This printer works. It is a big, heavy serious printer and produces beautiful large prints. I have not had it very long, but I am really excited about the performance. It produces prints that have the look of those I used to make in the darkroom. Using the Epson Exhibition Fiber Paper, I have been amazed. It makes good prints on lesser papers as well. I have yet to use it with other of the Epson Pro Papers. It took a few minutes to set up the first time I printed but the directions are clear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>As advertised</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this printer to make archival photo prints. I usually print with Canson Photographique Rag and Canson Baryta papers. I&apos;m finding I prefer the rag for color and the baryta for black and white. The quality is great. I especially love the black and white. The only reason I give four stars instead of five is because of the switching that needs to take place between the photo black and matte black inks when switching paper types. It does seem to drink the ink, but that seems to be a common complaint with all of the high end pigment printers, and I knew of this before I bought it, so no unexpected surprises. If I could, I would rate it 4.5 stars. I&apos;m happy with the purchase and it&apos;s what I expected.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jlerviti</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The caveat here is that I&apos;ve only had this a short time- a couple of weeks- ergo I cannot speak to longevity. What this printer has done is produce some very lovely prints both on paper that Epson requires and other papers which I found to produce a print more to my liking. As far as ink usage,sure it uses ink but not any more than I would expect considering I&apos;m covering a letter size piece of paper with ink. I would not use this printer for everyday printing of text or other mundane material, photos only. Also, I experienced absolutely no problems using this printer wirelessly. My only negative comment is that the printer is unable to discern if paper is fed correctly and will print on nothing which creates a problem. However the fix there is to simply be careful and follow the instructi ... ons explicitly.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sekmet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use my R3000 to print CADS for apparel and accessiories, and it works great. Wonderful clear prints with outstanding vivid color. It is fast, and requires very little manual labor.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Michael</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

I bought this printer so that I could make good black and white photos. I have been very satisfied. Color is also excellent.

It was remarkably easy to set up and to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Perretta</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best small format printer ever!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been wanting to purchase a beautiful small format printer for my studio. Finally after seeing the R3000 at WPPI this year, I just had to have one! I print high quality prints for my fine art studio, the R3000 really prints clean, crisp and unparalleled quality right out of the box. I&apos;m just about to add some ICC profiles and I&apos;m finding that to be a slight bump but nothing major I&apos;m sure. I can&apos;t say anything negative on the product. Don&apos;t hesitate and it&apos;s priced way under for it&apos;s output.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Graphite artist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The Epson r3000 produces prints that are amazing in color and accuracy. The 13 x 19 paper is the perfect size for a fine art print and Epson offers a great selection of 100% rag fine art papers. This prints are fantastic!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DPA PHOTOGRAPHY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Compact Design; Durable construction

Cons: Too much ink used

I use the Epson R3000 primarily for printing photographs . Once you get the color profiles dialed in ( not to difficult ) the prints are of excellent quality. Printing panoramas from a roll is allot of fun and the results are awesome. It is an ink hog, especially if you switch between black inks. I recommend that you use the economy mode if you do allot of black switching which seems to help a little. I use a Mac Pro OS X Lion. Make sure you DO NOT use the install disc that came with the printer if you are using Lion. Go to the epson web site and follow their profile / driver install instructions. Over all I am very pleased with the printer and the prints. I just wish th ... e ink wasn&apos;t so darn expensive.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Studio B</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice upgrade from the R2400</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I like the wireless feature and the 9 cartridge slots. The icc profiles provide great correlation between my MacAir / Aperture and Epson Matte print. I did have trouble printing 13X 19 size and tracked this down to software / print settings. Be sure to use Super B size or A3+ size when printing 13X19. These metric settings are essentially equal to 13X19 paper and work in all cases. The 13X19 setting is problematic, depending upon OS, driver version, Aperture Version. Also, for LIon users: the installation instructions are confusing. Just plug the printer into the system and do a software update or printer install from the Apple website. There is a separate driver for USB and for 802.11</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MsBoss</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Prints but uses a lot of ink</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable

Cons: Slow Print Time; Too much ink used

This printer I great! I also love the option of printing directly on the compact disc! The print quality is also very beautiful given that you use the paper recommended for the printer. My only complaint would be print time and the ink! Every time you switch from Photo Black ink to Matte Black ink it waste alot of ink cleaning the nozzles.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ari</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>R3000</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>good print quality but LCD is useless and very poor resolution, why did they bother with putting an LcD? WiFi reciever is EXTREMELY poor. I lost lots of ink and 10 sheets of premium paper due to the printer dropping the connection after 90% of the print was complete. Epson took 5 months to send my rebate check. overall good print quality but terrible build quality, poor connectivity and poor interface. I should have gone with Canon</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jodi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great experience so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We purchased this printer for several reasons, one of them, to be able to print on CDs. Our CDs look professionally made, very happy. Had to make last minute business cards for something and it accepted a heavy card stock - the cards look great. Photos are fabulous. One drawback is the 9 ink cartridges at 33.00/piece. Didn&apos;t realize this till after we purchased. It could have been a deal breaker had we known but going to live with it now.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bumpy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Color Match to calibrated monitor</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Durable construction

Cons: Large Footprint

I have been fairly impressed at how well the printer image matches my monitor (after quite a bit of manual calibration work - I&apos;m too cheap and too infrequent use to pay for hardware calibration tool). Monitor is fairly good (HP ZR24w) so I&apos;d hoped for good match and overall am surprised at how well color calibration works. The printed image is just a little darker w/ a little less contrast vs. the screen, but colors look very accurate.

I use Lightroom and let LR manage color using Epson profile to match the paper I&apos;m using. I downloaded LR 4 with soft proof which looks like a great feature, the soft proof for printer/paper I use looks just a little darker and lower contrast so I&apos;m hoping t ... he result using soft proof will be even closer.

Pretty amazing for an amateur to get results this good (now if only my photos were better....).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nikonman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer from Epson</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to set up. Prints beautiful color and B&amp;W prints. Very nice printing on all paper including standard office paper and premium glossy. I have not tried any art papers as yet however I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll be pleased.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer and wireless too!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Printer gives beautiful detail, great color reproduction and many fine art paper options. However it is essential to update the printer driver and have the correct ICC profiles for the paper/media type.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Reliable; Fast Print Time; Low Ink Consumption; Durable construction; Easy To Set Up

Cons: None that I can find

The black &amp; whites that I&apos;m able to produce through this printer are spectacular. I like high contrast prints but I&apos;m amazed at the mid-tones that this printer can produce. The color prints are pretty spectacular too. I try to use Epson Exhibition Fibre paper for all my prints. I love the dated look to the paper and to acheive the best printing results make sure that you download the ICC paper profiles from Epson.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Previously had an Epson 2800 that bit the dust. It was an ink guzzler and we had to physically replace the photo black ink with matte black for some projects. The R3000 is a much better design and gives us beautiful prints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ahwange</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still Water Runs Deep</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I am still working to learn more about what this printer could do but I have been happy with its print quality so far. I still need get familiar with all the settins to get the optimal resuts. It runs quietly and has met my expection. With $200 rebate, that&apos;s a deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SIWC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy setup and start - very quiet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Semi-professional photographer. Have only used a few times to test quality. Blues and grays come out great, however, some photos show too much black and are too dark. Have tried with and without color management and results did not vary. Appears to use a fair amount of ink for even small size prints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big G</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Everything we expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The pictures we&apos;ve printed are professional-grade. Pictures are clear and totally true to the image on the screen. As warned, it prints slowly. Good things come to those who wait.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jorge</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent right out of the box</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been wanting to print my pictures after all these years. Used to develop and loved the creative aspects of getting to a great print. But after a while I would get a rash in my arms - allegies to the chemicals. Tried printing about twelve years ago but technology was not there. I am happy to report that it is there now - beautiful B&amp;W&apos;s, beautiful colors. And i just got started and trying to make time. Luckily I have many pictures which I took with a print in mind. Recommend Epson 3000 very highly if you like to create and give beautiful prints. The process for settings was a little confusing at first but no sweat. Thumbs up to Epson for the printers, papers, ink tech that allows such gorgeous results. Long live the print!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Helen K. Garber</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

wish ink wasn&apos;t so expensive, but this machine makes gorgeous prints.
I had still been using my 2000p, so a huge, huge difference.
would have opted for the larger machine if I realized it was on sale for less than $1000.00,
but this will do until the next generation or next large print sale</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best inkjet I&apos;ve ever used</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>While I use a lab for most of my printing, the desire has been growing on me to learn the ins and outs of inkjet printing, and the hefty rebate offered on the R3000 in November 2011 was the right incentive to buy. This printer comes with clear and easy-to-follow instructions for unpackaging and installing ink cartridges, and once that was done it was recognized without problems by my operating system (Ubuntu Linux 11.04). The ICC profiles provided by Canson for the paper I bought worked as expected. Colors are accurate, print quality is indistinguishable from silver-emulsion paper, and the Canson Infinity paper I chose was handled with no trouble at all. I&apos;m still figuring out the Advanced B&amp;W Photo mode; my initial attempts did not quite match the best silver prints I have, but I&apos;m ... sure that&apos;s merely a matter of experience. I look forward to much more printing with my R3000.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Valerie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stylus Photo R3000 Inkjet Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We have a small design/production studio on campus. This will be a great addition to our arsenal of printers. It fills the gap between color printers and our large format printers. Quality and color are great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr.B (www.bradhines.com)</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best printer for the money!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use

Cons: Too much ink used

My 2200 finally died and I replaced it with this. The print quality is much better and the K2 inks are archival so they won&apos;t fade over time. The machine is very large but it is whisper quiet and tack sharp. Best money I&apos;ve spent in a while.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jlarson21</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this printer to replace an Epson R1800. I use it for prints to hang on my wall as well as print greeting cards, etc. It was very easy to set up and I was printing in no time. It produces beautiful images, discernibly better than the 1800. My only complaint is the amount of black ink it consumes as it switches between Matte &amp; Photo black. Because of this I will be trying to limit my printing to matte paper as much as possible (my preference, anyway) to limit the usage.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gorgeous prints!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am suddenly making gorgeous 13x19 prints on art paper . They look like they&apos;ve been printed on a press. I&apos;ve been using a very old printer for years and had no idea what I was missing. I was able to set this printer up myself in a very short time and begin printing all sizes of prints right away. It is beautifully designed. I am worried about how often I&apos;ll need to replace cartridges and the cost, but for now, imagine it will be worth it. PV</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Frustrated User</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Waiting for Epson to replace my printer, the printer heads didn&apos;t work straight out of the box, after a week Epson will be replacing a brand new printer out of the box. Once I receive the new one maybe I&apos;ll write a better review. I will admit Epson reperasentatives have been very cooperative even when i haven&apos;t been easy to work with.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BevyJean</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Black and White Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a photographer who has now taken this hobby to the next level by printing my own work. I love black and white photography and the Epson Stylus R3000 is my answer. I had purchased a well known printer and was disappointed with its color as well as black and white. THe Epson gave me excellent black and white, shadows, contrasts and true to my photograph. I had to play around with the color pictures. I found the pictures were darker than my original pictures. At first I explored the monitor color settings but learned a PC has 2.2 gammas verses the MAC 1.8. I was told to contact HP to see if I could change the gamma to 1.8. Not sure if this is really the problem but will investigate. In the meantime, I allow Lightroom to be my source of color and turn off the color format for the ... Epson.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PaniktArt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Wonderful prints and Black &amp; White photographs. Great performance overall! The only inconvenience is that you need to change the setting for matt or glossy black which can affect your ink consumption.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Taubby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The printer is slow to print</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It is above average for the inkjet printers that are currently available. Probably inkjet printers that cost several thousand dollars would make my Epson R3000 printer look like a toy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PezzVT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to follow set up instructions. Using paper from my old, defunct printer company and the prints were excellent. Epson paper even better. Lives up to it&apos;s hype.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kerry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Mixed Emotions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love travel photography and this printer creates beautiful prints. It was extremely easy to set up and accomodates a wide variety of excellent papers. I just wish the Epson ink was more affordable. Even though the machine now houses both the photo black and matt black inks, when swtiching from one to the other, it appears that I lose about 1/4 of an ink tank (equates to about $6 ink loss) due to the feed line purge every time I switch inks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wearer of Many Hats</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for small business</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We justified spending what we did on this printer because in the long run, it will save us on outside printing costs when we can do most jobs in-house. Our first print job was on roll paper, it came out just as good as anything we could have gotten from professional print houses. We paid about thirty something for the roll paper and the one job would have cost us a hundred and twenty five to print at a print house. Within the next six months the printer will pay for itself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I am impressed by this printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As an amateur photographer and use this printer to make prints of my photography shoots, weddings, outdoor, family, nature and anything else that happens to pass in front of my camera. This printer produces some of the best prints that I have ever printed - outstanding! It was easy to set up and get running even for a technically challenged person like myself. I wouldn&apos;t hesitate to recommend the Epson R3000 Stylus Printer to anyone &amp; everyone</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Robert - SemiPro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Fantastic that makes great looking realistic prints. The printer is quite expensive, both in the purchase cost and the maintenance cost, which is primarily ink. I justified it with the time and energy I take in to taking the pictures and then adjusting in lightroom. I&apos;ve printed both color and B&amp;W, 4x6 Snapshots and 8x10s, Glossy and Matte with papers from Ilford, Epson, Moab and RedRiver and all of the prints turn out great. I recommend getting a monitor calibration device and then buying the sample packs of paper from Epson, Moab etc. printing a montage that represents your typical work with a good dynamic range and really test the printers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So happy with this printer...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Just beginning to dabble in digital art - coming from the darkroom. Will use for some alternative type of digital printing other than just photographs. Color is fabulous! And, easy to use when setting up a print. One thing I&apos;d like is to be able to use paper other that 13x19 when printing from the back. The printer will only let me use 13x19 poster board or what the printer deems is poster board. Other than that wonderful printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PhotoGal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love this printer. I upgraded from an older Epson 2200. It was so easy to set up (wirelessly). Paper profiles work perfectly out of the box with Photoshop for image printing. I highly recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dennis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beautiful prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m using the printer with a MacBook Pro and an HP PC. Canon 5Dii and L lenses and Colormunki. Unpacking and set up took only minutes. The instructions are clear, complete and easy to understand. The instructions can also be downloaded. This is my first professional grade printer, and only my second printer. The R3000 performed without a flaw or problem. The printing process seemed unusually quiet, and I believe there are some energy benefits to this printer. After reading the reviews in B+H and my research, I was torn between this and the SP 4900. They are both on the cutting edge of technology and both are Epsons. I came to the conclusion that there is no real wrong decision, just different. For financial reasons I chose the R3000, and the amount of printing I do. As for qua ... lity of the print, I can only compare it to the prints I got from my 2 1/4 film cameras. The prints are stunning. No remorse or regrets, I&apos;d buy it again. P.S. Buy extra ink because you&apos;ll love to print
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RetLaEnvEmp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Color Great - B&amp;W Exhibition Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Print wedding, family gathering, children event pictures. A lot of 5X7 prints. Quality of prints is a step up from other printer and photo services. Can easily see difference in prints; they are so much better. The black &amp; white increase in quality is shocking - it is exhibit show quality. Find myself now saving pictures by converting them to black &amp; white; you know the the good shots where there are too many contrasts (white dress/black tux/video camera lights/sun ray peeks out/ some clown waves his hand into a corner of your shot just when the shutter clicks/ half of the people in the picture are sunburned) - the kind of shots no camera can make but Lightroom and the R3000 can save, crop and capture in black &amp; white. This is a professional printer. It requires Epson ... paper or quality paper equal to Epson&apos;s recommended paper (what is on sale is not going to work very well - I tried it ). Reset my camera, computer, printer, drivers, Lightroom 3.4, I mean everything (?), to Adobe RBG colors; what I see is on my computer screen is what I print.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Must Have!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use the printer to print direct to DVD and CD as well as reproducing B/W photo scans. It&apos;s a great addition to my business with professional quality printing and a very user friendly operation.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Juan Z</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t Print Borderless</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>This printer prints awesome prints (hence the one star), but (1) cannot print borderless, and (2) paper has to be fed by hand, one page at a time, or else the paper gets misalligned. I only used the back paper feeder but was enough to made me send the printer back to B&amp;H for refund. I never had this problem with my old Epson 2200, which I had to replace because because Epson does not provide printer profiles, because the printer is old and the profiles are not updated to work with new computer software.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stacy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A High End Printer Without a High Pric</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had this printer for a little over a week now and I couldn&apos;t be happier with what I got for my money. It was really easy to install and the quality of the print is fantastic. I&apos;m a graphic designer and I bought this so I could proof my own jobs before they go to print. So far, I&apos;ve found my proofs to be incredibly accurate with very little effort. It was lower in cost than I expected to spend so I am very happy. I wouldn&apos;t have liked being able to print at 24 wide instead of 13 but the cost was over my budget. I haven&apos;t tried any specialty papers but that&apos;s not really what I bought it for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>calwldlfphotogarfer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Photo Printer!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is an extraordinary printer. My NEC monitor was callibrated and the Epson printer profiles added, and the images on Epson Hot Press Bright Smooth Matte are terrific! They match the monitor image perfectly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bob in MA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great prints, print cost &amp; econcomics</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this printer to make photos for gallery exhibits and for sale. The prints are vivid and sharp with fine gradations of color. I&apos;ve been tracking ink usage and I ran out of the yellow ink first after printing the equivalent of 25.5 12x18 prints. Estimating the amount of the other ink cartridges used, I estimate that $7.32 worth of ink was used for each 12x18 print. Adding the cost of paper, this means that the direct material cost of each 12x18 print is between $8 and $10 depending on the type of paper. While this cost may seem excessive, comparing the to the cost of having prints made at a professional printing company, which is from $35 to $50 per print, the breakeven point (including the cost of the R3000) where printing with the R3000 is less that the cost of having prints pro ... fessional printed is in the order of 20 to 30 12x18 prints.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far - great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I own a 1400 and r2400 and needed something a bit better. This will do borderless odd sizes and cards - the ink seems to go quickly, but perhaps it&apos;s just me messing with my new toy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photobymike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buy and you will not Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to setup out of the box. Great features including the ability to print on CDs and DVDs. Wireless setup was a breeze to setup and use. The color prints are fantastic!! BW look like it came from a darkroom. Also a straight thru path for thicker media like poster board.. Really nice build and quality feel, does not feel like cheap plastic printers of the past. Possibly the best Epson or any printer for 13 paper that can be purchased anywhere. In the past i have spent thousands on printers in the past.. with this purchase being the absolute best printer yet</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Art Girl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect prints with little hassle</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a painter and develop work from modified photographs that give me a sense of where I can take my paintings. I previously owned the R2400 which I loved until the day it died. The R3000 has a larger casing and an added ink well. The cartridges are larger and more expensive. I&apos;ve only been printing on this new printer for 1 1/2 weeks so time will tell more. The quality of the prints are excellent and I like the new features. The only comment that&apos;s less than a 5 star would be about the ink usage and cost of cartridges. I printed one 5x7 photo with a large expanse of black in the image using the Photo Black ink on glossy paper and the ink level indicator went down noticeably. So I&apos;m concerned about the expense and amount of ink used.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Technoholic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice printer but buggy driver</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Prints are beautiful once you get past the problems. Bug 1: On day one, printing from CS5, to the networked R3000, consistent Printer does not exist errors were becoming quite frustrating. A call to Epson support just added to the frustration when they told me they never heard of the problem. A Google search netted multiple hits and a workaround, just make the R3000 your default printer. If that bug is common knowledge on the net, why doesn&apos;t Epson support know about it? Bug 2: The driver defaults to 8.5 x 11 paper size. If you are not paying attention and have smaller paper loaded, the printer will happily feed the smaller paper and still print an 8.5 x 11 image spraying ink all over it&apos;s internals. No error is generated. This is the first Epson printer I have bought that didn&apos;t inclu ... de some paper samples. There also are no cables included. Only one size of roll paper is supported, 13 inch. Nevertheless, as stated earlier, the prints are quite nice and I do look forward to working with this printer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ttaleman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far, so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Fantastic prints right out of the box. The b/w printing is a massive improvement over the R1900. I can&apos;t wait to see what it&apos;s capable of when I&apos;ve created my own icc profiles. Still too soon to give 5 stars, but it&apos;s very close at this time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kristinmaynes</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This printer ROCKS!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought the Epson Stylus R3000 Printer to print my watercolor scans. I was worried they wouldn&apos;t be close enough to the original but I was wrong...it&apos;s so amazing, the first print I did (pictured below), my family couldn&apos;t tell the difference between the original and the print. Love, Love this!!It&apos;s so easy to setup and use...so easy!Originally, I was going to buy the R2880, because of the great reviews, but after researching a bit I found that the R3000 was wireless and had larger ink cartridges. I was sold. It was a bigger investment but with Epson&apos;s [$]rebate it was more affordable. (R2880 is [$]rebate)I do have to say the ink kinda scares me, it&apos;s [$]to replace all cartridges BUT not enough to scare me off. The quality is tooooo good to worry about ink costs.A note: This printer is BI ... G, make sure you have a place for it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photodan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You get what you pay for!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I paid a lot and got a lot. A printer that can print near perfect b and w prints in a wide format. I print fine art photos for salon sales. I had used a r2400 since 2006 and expect the r3000 to exceed the quality and durability. I am a happy Epson customer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Imagemaster</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My 6th Epson and still the best!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Two photographers use the R3000 via wireless with Mac and Windows operating systems. There are a total of five computers in the household at various locations and all are primarily used for digital imaging with Photoshop.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DW</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Superb Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My printer arrived at my home in great condition in the time limit given by B&amp;H. Although the printer is large and somewhat heavy, it took little effort to set my R3000 up and install the drivers and cartridges. I was able to start printing photos soon after installation and WOW, does it print beautiful photos or what!! I am having a little difficulty adjusting the photos for borderless appearance, but this will come as I get used to it. I feel like I will be spending more for ink, but in return I&apos;ll be producing beautiful prints. I have no regrets about purchasing this Epson printer, even though the learning curve is quite involved and complex. It does print slowly, but I&apos;m a patient person, and I can live with it-to get the kind of prints it produces.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>geep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great B&amp;W and color</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We bought this for the Black and White prints. Very happy with the results...except that it really uses up the ink, specially when changing from matt to photo black. Seems a bit slow when priinting fine images.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for double sided prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this printer to replace my R2400. The R3000 is a great printer that produces truly spectacular prints. However, I printed my portfolio book on this printer and was not satisfied with the results. My book has double sided Moab Lasal paper. When printing the front of the page all is great. When I flip the print over to print on the back the rollers in the printed leave two stripes on the front print. It is most obvious in the solid, dark areas but none-the-less the stripes are very noticable. When printing on my R2400 this is not an issue. Although the R3000 makes wonder prints and is very usuer friendly I returned the printer because of the issues with printing double sided paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>One happy camper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>EXCELLENT PRINTER FOR ART PRINTS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this primarily to make archival art prints of my wife&apos;s and my work. We have been doing this for over 10 years and previously used an Epson 2200. The R3000 is a huge improvement. The front feed feature is particularly useful when using relatively thick print stock.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Neeser</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I adore this printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I spend a lot of time and effort taking photographs and I wanted a printer that would provide profession quality prints for framing for both personal use and to give as gifts to friends and family. I love this printer. I couldn&apos;t ask for better print reproduction of my photos!! My previous printer did an okay job, but the results from this are truly amazing!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing From A Desktop Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I spent years in the traditional darkroom settings getting tones just the way I wanted them. Along comes digital and, whether your scanning film or printing straight from digital capture, this printer is capable of stunning output. Just make certain that your monitor is calabrated and you have quality output software (Lightroom is fantastic). My prints have been spot on with practically no trial and error. I have read other reviews (other sites) stating that the wireless capabilities are useless as the printer slows to a crawl. This is not the case at all. This printer is fast???even set to maximum resolution printing (although the spool time is extended a bit). Fast is a relative word, but in comparison to other printers I have owned this one is impressive. I have no reservations giving ... this product the highest of recommendations...Stunning, archival prints with nothing more than an iMac and the R3000.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anthony C.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The last photo printer I had was an HP 8750 and while good, it wasn&apos;t the best. This printer goes well beyond the HP in color fidelity and clarity. I&apos;m currently using Ilford Smooth Pearl paper and some others I haven&apos;t tried yet, but I&apos;ll be using the SP as my normal paper since I love the results. I&apos;ll be printing a ton with this thing and can&apos;t wait to try some of the fine art papers as I know the results will be outstanding.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>chemsaf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Right out of the box, this was excellent. I plugged it into a wireless printserver via an ethernet and installed the software. The software found the printer, even through a router to the printserver and it worked first time, perfectly. Used LightRoom 3 to control printing a 13x19 paper and it came out beautiful. heprint is being framed right now. If you need 11x17 or 13x19, this is the printer you want!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bobolink</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Truly Marvelous Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Reliable; Photo quality prints; Durable construction; Fast Print Time

Cons: Large Footprint

Had used an Epson R1800 for a long time with no problems. Read about the R3000&apos;s improvements and quality, so I gambled...and won. The R1800 was great, but the R3000 is superb! True, ink is more expensive, but cartridges contain three times more than those of the R1800 and show a marked difference in tone, intensity, and reproducing beautiful pictures!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>digitalshots6</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceeded expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up; Reliable

Changed over from an older printer that I thought I was happy with.....The R3000 blows me away with the clarity and color it prints. I can see a marked difference and the prints definitely look professional in quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Eric</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>the quality ....but the troubles too</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I don&apos;t have anything to say about the quality of my new R3000, replacing an excellent R1900 that was a nice printer also. But let&apos;s talk about the inks.On the third print, my printer get a message, cartridges red crossed blinking and asked to me to stop and restart the power, due to a bad paper insertion on the fine art path. Then it did a cleanup and drunk 60% of the ink ... Nice [$] print! i am just amazed that when we crash a paper, there is no issue on the software and that half of the ink just goes away. I just want that people know that it s not on the printer that they earn money but on this liquid gold... that is so nice about you Epson!And no the Fine Art path is not easy. If you follow the messages on the board, they neevr say t ... hat we must press back on the trail once the paper is positionned.NExt time i will see Canon solution or HP. Sorry but my last Epson. I wanna stop to feed the ones who are not enough careful with the users and hook them with the supplies.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>George</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is a good printer, however!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this printer as an all purpose unit like I did with my Canon i9900 which quit working as a photo printer after 7 years. It still worked as a plain paper printer but that wasn&apos;t enough. This Epson printer is slow compared to my old Canon printer for printing photographs but the quality is very good (better than the Canon). There is one issue however. Different types of media require you to switch from one type of black ink to another type which can become annoying after a while. Otherwise this printer is a joy to own.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ted W.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works Flawlessly</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>When my Epson R2400 died after 5 years of much use, I decided to move up to the R3000. The main reason I chose this printer was because both matte black and photo (glossy) black cartridges were in the printer lineup and you didn&apos;t have to switch them out every time you wanted to change papers. As for the printer itself it worked perfectly right out of the box, print quality is noticeably better than prints from the R2400, and I haven&apos;t even begun to customize settings. I also like the LED screen in front that tells you what&apos;s going on instead of having to guess.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>G-man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fan-tastic!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been printing on Red River Aurora Natural Rag paper for almost a month now. with almost no problems. Prints look gorgeous. Here are a few minor flaws: 1. The paper mentioned above will not auto feed in the autofeeder. not sure if I can fix that with some driver setting... right now i feed one sheet at a time through the autofeeder. 2. At first, there seemed to be quite a bit of adjusting by the printer. And I don&apos;t mean the ink-loading noises. even a few days after I started using it, there were quite a few pauses in output, accompanied by pump noises... The printer is now quiet. I hope there is nothing wrong with it.. A little more feedback on what it&apos;s doing would be nice. Overall, I am very happy with the prints and that&apos;s what matters!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>[@]</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Printer of Choice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Durable construction; Reliable; Easy To Set Up

I needed a second photo printer to complement, if not, to replace my Canon 9500 Mark II. The Epson Stylus R3000 is a great printer so far, I haven&apos;t had any problems yet. This printer has a good quality print and is somewhat quiet and fast. I use it for my photography business and is already the printer of choice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TMC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Recommended, yes. But, U need to READ</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After a few weeks; Great printer. However, you MUST learn about color management (what the difference between perceptual and relative colormetric is; what color space your camera is set to, what color space the printer is set to; how to calibrate your monitor, etc. If you don&apos;t take the time, you will be frustrated. Not something you can plug &amp; play with. Take the time to learn, and you will be happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paul the Skater</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I needed a smaller printer than my R3880 to have in my Florida condo. This really fits the bill and feels just like the 3880. The bonus is that it also uses roll paper for great panoramas which the 3880 does not. I love both of these printers and would recommend them to anyone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Everett</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy Set Up. High Quality Prints.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The R3000 is a snap to set up. I had it producing excellent prints in less than a hour. The feed seems to be improved over previous models. Makes beautiful professional prints that are every bit as good as the pro 3880. My only gripe is a familiar one - the ink consumption is rather high although due to the higher capacity cartridges I get a higher yield than with the 2880. If you produce and sell a lot of prints, you are better off with a 3880 if you can afford the initial cost.I have not tried the front loading feature yet but it looks like it will be more convenient than other models. Build features on the R3000 are excellent and the black &amp; white printing capability is outstanding although the interface is not as sophisticated as on the 3880. All in all the R3000 is a solid machine ... .
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daniel Maidman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>use for fine art printing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The printer works more or less precisely as advertised. I am using it in combination with the Moab Infinity 300 gsm inkjet-prepared whitened watercolor paper to produce giclee-grade fine art prints. I do not have any hesitation signing the output and selling it as giclee; color range and fidelity is extraordinarily high, contrast is excellent, and consistency of printing is reliable. The printer operates more quickly via USB than airport. Recommended as a good option for artists who don&apos;t need to print wider than 13 and want to be able to offer giclee prints without trekking back and forth to a print shop charging high rates to deploy the same technology in the wider-printing Epson pro line.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fantastic Frank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big, but it Prints Beautiful Large Print</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>When I received it, I thought my God, this thing is huge. But when I found a good place for it and set it up, it performed well. I had really old paper, so the prints were just OK, so I bought Epson Ultra Premium Photo Paper, 11.7 X 16.5, and the quality of the large prints knocked by socks off. It is wireless, which is a plus for me. It also handles 4X6 easily as well. The only complaint that I have and it may be a user learning curve issue is on the large prints, there was a slight miss on the borders - easily correctible through a paper cutter or a frame with a slightly smaller matte box.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t Handle Fine Art Paper</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Epson pre-sales tech told me the new R3000 solved the problems with the 2880 and 3880 not being able to handle fine art paper such as Hahnemuhle Museum Etching paper. Out of the box I&apos;ve now ruined six costly sheets trying to get the printer to feed. The special front slot for thick paper has no guides, and chews both the ends and sides of the paper and it invariably jams. Not a serious printer. I&apos;ll try the Canon 13.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dlisa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Finally, Good results!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The Epson Stylus Photo R3000 is the best photo printer I&apos;ve used by far. I wanted to duplicate a school photo of my 6 yr old niece. I had both a physical and email copy. The photo was originally done on a Luster type paper and I was able to duplicate it almost perfectly on Moab Fiber Satine. I&apos;ve never put so little effort in printing a photo before. Although the printer is a little slow (hence the 4 stars), it was well worth the wait.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gollum</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The next step in archival color printers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got this as a replacement for an Epson 2200. As such, it is a distinct improvement over the previous machine. The larger ink cartridges and color screen make it much easier to use. It is still not very fast but speed isn&apos;t why you chose a printer like this. The color rendition and resolution is excellent. Only time will tell about the color lasting but I susbect it will be good like the 2200.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>flash</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best printer i have had yet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable construction; Fast Print Time; Easy To Set Up; Compact Design; Easy To Use; Reliable; Great prints

Love this printer,easy to set up ,wireless is wonderful I can put it anywhere and it works ,it is very quiet and the prints are fantastic</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>G.R.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superior quality prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;d been using the Epson 2200 for about 9 years and, despite a recent overhaul by Epson, it was starting to show its age. The new Epson R3000 was the natural replacement and I ordered one from B&amp;H to see how technology has advanced in the approximately 10 years since the 2200 was introduced. The answer is, not surprisingly, a lot. Set-up was relatively easy. There&apos;s a considerable wait (about 10 minutes) while the printer primes itself with its first set of ink cartridges, but there&apos;s no work to do; the printer happily tends to itself in this regard. Driver installation (Windows 7, 64-bit) is straightforward. When printing the new R3000 is much quieter than the 2200; there&apos;s much less clatter and the printer sounds and feels much more solidly constructed. The overall impression is o ... f a very well-made printer. We&apos;ll see how it holds up with use. My biggest hope is that it&apos;s less prone to head clogging between uses. My printing is generally of large photographic prints for sale and exhibit. I&apos;ve found that for really critical printing it&apos;s best to use custom profiles, especially when using non-Epson papers. After making profiles for my preferred Ilford Gold Fibre Silk paper I ran a few test prints and the results were outstanding. Black and white printing, with the R3000&apos;s 3 black inks, is the best I&apos;ve seen from an inkjet. The only glitch so far is what appears to be a head strike towards the end of one 13 x 19 print. Perhaps this is due to the thickness of the Gold Fibre Silk paper and using the front-load system for the paper will cure it but I didn&apos;t think the Ilford paper was really thick enough to require this. Further testing will tell.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photodude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The images almost jump off the page!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The Epson R3000 replaced an over-the-hill Epson R2400. The R3000 will be used primarily for photos. Although some ink will be lost from glossy to matte, I like having all of the K3 inks available without cartridge swaps. I print all my images from Lightroom 3; the color management is very straightforward. I am really looking forward to printing a 13 X 19 or larger image. I recommend the Epson R3000.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zone X</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have made about 6 prints with this printer and am very impressed. I am especially impressed with it&apos;s ability to produce full range b&amp;w prints. Now I know 6 prints isn&apos;t very many so this is a first impressions review. I showed a couple of these prints to a digital printer I know and he was impressed as well. Set up was quite easy and intuitive. As far as printing goes, make sure you specify the correct paper before printing (glossy, luster, etc.). My main reason for buying this printer was to print b&amp;w and it looks like I won&apos;t be disappointed. It does go through a long warm up cycle when I turn it on which begs the question, How much ink it is wasting? I haven&apos;t found an answer to this question yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have just upgraded from the R2400 printer, which I was very happy with. The problem was that I had difficulty using Velvet Fine Arts paper. The R3000 has resolved that problem and now I&apos;m even more happy. It is excellent for both B&amp;W and color printing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Feed up with Epson.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had my Epson R3000 for about a month. This was a replacement for my Epson R2400 which had given me inconsistent results. Indeed, an Epson rep confided to me that the R2400 was rushed to market and gave many people troubles in printing. My R3000 was intended as a replacemnt. Initially, I had good quality prints and then out of the blue began to have problems with it. I&apos;ve spent hours on the phone with Epson technical support trouble shooting and going through color management process. I may not be a computer genuis but I feel I am smart enough to get this product to work. It doesn&apos;t, and I am ending my long unhappy relationship with Epson and will replace with a Cannon which I should have done long ago.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>R3000 inkjet printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Use at home for printing photographs and some other general printing. I have had the printer a month and everything is great so far. Delivery was right on time with all the paper work for the rebate. Installation could not have been easier. I am using the wireless connection on multi computers. It was very easy and has not failed once. So far nothing to complain about. Thanks</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photodave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Like being back in the darkroom!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve only had the R3000 for two weeks, but have already found that it has me remembering what fun it was being in the darkroom and being able to handle a photographic project from inception to final print. I had held out purchasing an ink-jet printer for many years until I recently had some prints made on an Epson at a local gallery. I was very impressed with the quality and decided to take the plunge. I am SO happy I did. I love the complete control over my images. The Epson produces wonderful results. I have been matting and framing them for an upcoming art show and know that they will be a hit!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>leicaman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An AMAZING printer for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This ink jet printer incorporates advanced technology that produces high quality prints. This printer uses 9 inks and produces finer droplet sizes which enables the printer to create better tonal gradations and color nuances.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mark</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Initial Review of Epson Photo R 3000 Ptr</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve only had this a short while. I bought it as a replacement for my aging HP Photosmart 7960. The color is great and with some calibrating (Datacolor Spyder3 Studio SR)got great color match results. It would be rated a five but it goes through ink like a race horse drinking water in the desert, and at $233 + to replace all the cartridges it can be an expensive aquisition.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>A disappointed user</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not as good as the R1900</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I regret to have upgraded my printer from the R1900 to the R3000. With the R1900, I did not have to worry about the kind of black ink I was using, the printer took care of that without me noticing or having to do anything, the printer selected the black ink, photo or matt according to the media used. With the R3000 you get a message asking you if you want to change the ink, then after lot of noises and time, you will notice how the printer drinks the black ink before you print anything. The software is not as good as in the R1900, it is more directed to non-thinking minds. Being the R3000 just below the pro line, the software should be more targeted for people with mind that enjoy the photographic experience from taking the photo to printing it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Appalachian Trail Hiker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer from Epson</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Moved up from one of the all in one printers from Epson to this large format printer. [...], the software installation took a few minutes, calibration of the monitor, and later my first test print - all fast and the printer output is exceptional. Configured printer for USB interface and the printer has been working flawlessly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>xelent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>All that I wanted and more</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this printer because I was having problems matching the color as viewed on the screen as to what I was getting printed. I have 2other HP&apos;s and another epson. I set the printer up and printed a photograph using windows. The color matched perfectly and I was able to finish my project that day. I highly recommend the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson R3000 - great wide format printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have only had this printer for a short time. I&apos;m moving from an Epson R800. Looking forward to the wide format capability. [...] Set-up was easy. I am waiting for some high-end paper sample packs from Epson and Red River for more testing. The prints that I have made so far (on Epson Premium Photo Paper (Glossy)) are very nice. I used the printer managed color so far. I have not done any B&amp;W prints yet, but am looking forward to them.As I get some more prints done I will update my review.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No regrets</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Upgraded my HP PhotoSmart to the R3000 and am very happy with the results. Even low-res image look great at 11 x 14. Subtle color and punchy B&amp;W. I feel like I&apos;m back the darkroom watching each image with excitement as it trundles out of the printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fotag</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer but....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Awesome printer especially with the wireless capability. The ink consumption for switching between photo and matt black seems excessive. Epson should work on the black ink issue since this is a comment from many users.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A very good printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am an amature photographer and stepped up to quality pro equipment. The print quality is really fantastic on the few things I have printed so far. I really like the black and white feature of the printer, that is my main reason for the purchase of this printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Weekend shooter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Do You Really Need B&amp;W?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For anybody that is upgrading from the R1800/R1900 - I would caution that they think things thru very carefully whether the R2000 (vice R3000) is more suitable for them. Make no mistake - the R3000 prints beautiful color (glossy) photos! The issue is the amount of ink you waste in switching to do B&amp;W - and then switching back. If you are a predominantly color (glossy) user - the R3000 is probably not the best choice. For occasional (and non-exhibition grade) B&amp;W printing, I recommend the R2000 (it can switch between photo/matte black inks without flushing/charging the black ink line because it has dedicated separate lines for each). Two small gripes: (1)if you forget to open up the print output door in front - the printer keeps right on pushing the paper thru until it scrunches u ... p the paper inside and ruins the print. (2) Epson should have designed the printer with separate ink lines for black matte/photo to prevent significant ink wastage in flushing out and then charging the single line. You will definitely NOT want to switch back-and-forth!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It just works</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Works out of the box; Easy To Use; Excellent Print Quality

Cons: Pricey Replacement Ink; Hard Setup

I bought this when my HP wide format printer would no longer print jobs sent through our Ethernet network. The Epson has a built-in Ethernet port and worked right out of the box with the network. Setting up the printer was a bit more work than some. The printer is huge. The ink tanks are quite small so it will require fairly frequent replacement. All in all I&apos;m quite satisfied.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mikeCtv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t think twice about buying this!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this printer for my photography and my artwork and I can&apos;t be more pleased. In-line photo black and matte black ink switching is a BIG deal for me. The only complaint I have is Epson designed this to except poster-board up to 1.22mm thick but they don&apos;t make the poster-board. I called Epson three times and searched on line and no one in the paper business makes a 13 x 19 poster-board (I need to make signage from time to time it would be nice). You will be blown away with the output from the Epson R3000 don&apos;t think twice if your in the market for a new or upgrade desktop printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Earl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This printer replaced my Epson 2000 which worked well for 10 years. This printer is fast, great color, and does borderless prints in a variety of sizes. I printed several large prints using the multi-page option. I was amazed that I could create a 4-foot by 6-foot picture using 16 Super-B borderless prints with no cutting, the pannels fit together perfectly. The first few ink cartridges ran out after about 25 Super-B prints (13 by 19).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Q</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

I mostly use the printer for home use and some display purposes, it will fit the bill perfectly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Setup; Durable construction; Easy To Use

Cons: None

This is a great printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wahu Willie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beautiful Prints, drinks ink like water</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Printed 17 8 x 10s, they were beautiful. Ink cartridges are showing low ink. [$] a cartridge will cost a small fortune.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Har</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great color photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Brilliant colors but seems to use a lot of ink</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MATUREFUN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GOOD PRINTER REPLACED MY R2400</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>LOVE THIS PRINTER AND VERY EASY TO SET UP. THE PRINTS SEEM TO EVEN BETTER THEN MY R2400, WHICH IS PERFECT.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lanyard</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far very happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Wifi setup very easy,the whole setup from unpacking to printing took about 45 min.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>June</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good product for black and white</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time

easy to use</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tbutler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great photo printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use this printer to print everything up to 13x 19. Great quality color prints on any paper!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tony</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Easy To Use; Durable construction

Prints color and B&amp;W prints very well. Amazing results</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bnapfel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again and again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to set up. Great printing photos</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>flashblub</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Firsf Class</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Every thing easy to set up, great prints out of the gate. Only problem was removing roll paper when changing to sheet paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Michele</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Prints beautifully Beautiful Doesn&apos;t take up too much space Love that it&apos;s wireless easy to use easy to set up</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Duce</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Photos only, much better than the 810 dye printer a bit slower but colors are greatly improved.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Riley</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Epson. Need I say more</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a professional photographer printing 5 x 7 ~ 11 x 14. This printer was not only easy to set up but very economical.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Capt.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great for printing images for my anglers</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>155</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Thor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product! What i come to expect!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Once you get everything set to ones liking works just as advertised.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>156</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Charlie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Professional Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Print like a professional. Excellent Quality Prints</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>157</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wally</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High Quality printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: High quality prints Large ink tanks Well built. Cons: Software did not work with Mac 10.6.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>158</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dallvr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer, but uses a lot of ink</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the printer to make smaller prints than are practical with my 24 wide format printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>159</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wes</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pleased with the product and B&amp;H</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve used an Epson 1280, two of them, a 2400 and two C88+ photo printers. They&apos;re all great, but this is the best ever.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>160</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photo Fanatic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredible Photos!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love the print quality on this printer. The only thing is I wish the ink wasn&apos;t so expensive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>161</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>artist activist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fabulous colors!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For greeting cards or art gallery prints, this can&apos;t be matched as far as I can tell. Slow and noisy but I don&apos;t care.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>162</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Barto10</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I expect this product to outlive me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Setup; Reliable; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

Great for panoramas</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>163</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Surreal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>nice looking prints ink not cheap</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>164</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chrysalis Archaeology</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Setup; Easy To Use

Cons: Large Footprint

As an archaeological firm, the large format printing is excellent for map making!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>165</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>barto10</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Top for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast Print Time; Easy To Setup; Compact Design; Reliable; Durable construction; Easy To Use

[...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>166</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ad-man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Used to print photos, docs, banners and posters. Works great but I don&apos;t like how I manually have to change black printer inks based on the item being printed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>167</ID>
     <Item>Epson Stylus Photo R3000 Color Ink-jet printer - 120 sheets</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10571255283768463687/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1015&amp;bih=613&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.95&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=o6mRUJ27Ocrm2QXV6oHIBQ&amp;ved=0CM8BEPQCMAQ4Mg</URL>
     <Reviewer>its the light stupid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>wish i could auto feed fine art paper</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Use for small amateur photography business. Beautiful photographs. Has the same problem that I had with my R1800 - cannot auto feed fine art paper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

