<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>DustyGut</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Printer, Cheap Ink, Great Deal</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking to replace my old Canon 500 printer. Price of ink was a killer with 3 kids in school and ALWAYS printing something. Decided to go with the Kodak Hero 9.1. It got good reviews and their ink is cheapest around. I was impressed with ink quality of printed docs and pictures. It was easy to setup and configure. It took me 2 tries to setup the wireless but totally my fault 1st time through. Need to know your modem type and I was wrong. I am very happy with the price versus features and functionality of the printer. Already used the duplex, fax, copy and photo print features.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>JohnJackRalph</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Meets All Expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of setup and photo print quality.

Cons: Nothing that I&apos;ve encountered.

I&apos;ve replaced my last HP printer. Prior to purchase, I read reviews from several sites. Most reviews were positive and some friends have a Kodak printer that they are very happy with. So I decided to make the purchase. The printer was also on sale. It was very easy to setup. I followed all directions and in a relatively short time I had printed, scanned, copied and faxed. I printed both color and B/W documents. I&apos;ve printed both 4 x 6 and 5 x 7 pictures on Kodak and non Kodak photo paper. All prints were excellent. I especially like the picture edit and print menu. It has some nice features. This is a top quality printer at a reasonable price. I haven&apos;t owned the printer very long, but the ink s ... upply seems to be lasting and it&apos;s much less expensive to purchase. I&apos;m glad that I decided to switch from my third HP printer to a Kodak.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>DeanO7</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Printer, but ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great printer. Picture quality is great

Cons: Not a great scanner

As I said in the summary, it is a great printer. The picture quality is good and the price of new printer cartridges is better than with hp. As for the scanner part, it works okay, but the resolution is not very good. I have not use the fax portion. I have used the cloud print feature, it works very well. I have run into problems with remotely logging into the printer, I forgot my password. There is no way to reset the administrative password from the printer itself. I had to restore the printer to its factory defaults. When connecting wirelessly, I recommend using the WiFi protected setup feature, if your wireless router supports it. It makes it very easy to connect. Otherwise, I had problems connecting ... wirelessly by using my wireless network key. I guess I wasn&apos;t patient enough. Not sure what the future holds with Kodak seeing bankruptcy protection. I hope they continue to make the printer cartridges. In summary, it is a great printer for the price. Best Buy had a great sale price for it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>cal2000fb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great price for everything that it does

Cons: Haven&apos;t found anything wrong as of yet?

This printer is awesome! I&apos;ve had this printer for at least 2 months now. I use it for my everyday use. haven&apos;t had to change any ink catridges yet and its easy to work. The setup was easy to do and it took no time. I got it at a great price. The original price was $250 and I got on sale for $150. A week later it was on sale for $125 so I got a price match for that. Great deal! I have only printed one photo picture and it looked great. It also has the capability to print in 3D which I have never heard before. I printed an example of that and it looked nice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>TreoGuy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features, Cost, Value, Quality

Cons: Speed

I&apos;ve owned a Canon and HP printer and I have to say that this one tops the others I&apos;ve owned.

The first and probably most important is the photo quality. The photo prints are almost no different from lab quality and the printer is relatively quick to print 4x6&apos;s. The best part is the ink is cheap and simple to replace. Even though the colors are all one cartridge, even if you run low on one color, the odds are the other colors aren&apos;t far behind and with the low cost on ink, you really wouldn&apos;t be saving much to replace just that color unless you were printing large volumes of pictures all the time.

The regular document prints could be faster but if I were after a high volume fast color printer I would consider a l ... aser printer over any inkjet printer anyway.

One of the features that really impressed me was related to this printer&apos;s connectivity with the internet. After setting up the wifi this printer actually has the ability to scan directly to an email address you pre-define, scan to a network drive or scan to a computer specifically on your network.

You can also send faxes to this printer from your computer and with it being connected to the Google Cloud Print service, I&apos;m able to print from my phone or other computer away from home.

Another unique feature was the printer&apos;s built-in forms. It&apos;s able to print a wide/narrow rule notebook, grocery list. grid paper, without even turning on the computer.

Overall, I&apos;m impressed with this printer&apos;s features and so far haven&apos;t found any cons to this purchase. The only drawbacks I could really have with it relate to speed where it might not be as fast as others out there and it not having the ability to have individual colors replaced. Those drawbacks in my opinion are outweighed by it&apos;s other features and low cost ink.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>ERJedi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Like it...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good buy for the money

This is my first Kodak printer. I&apos;ve had horrible experiences with HP and heard a lot of good things from coworkers about Kodak. To be honest I was a little nervous at first, I&apos;m a big believer in checking reviews before I buy and I was i reading a bunch of bad reviews regarding this particular model in terms of mechanical failed and print quality. All I can say is that I have had nothing but good experiences with the printer so far and I&apos;m happy I made the purchase, (which is a pretty good compliment for you Kodak, since I&apos;m not easily impressed to begin with, in fact this is the first review I&apos;ve ever written, lol.)

Photo Quality:
I own a Sony Alpha camera, and the pictures that the Kodak printer produce do the camera justice. In fact I compa ... red a photo that I printed at home with the Kodak to one from the photo store on the chemical printer and could not tell the difference. Picture paper may offset the cost of this advantage but it is still cheaper nonetheless. Very satisfied with the photo quality.

Print Speed:
Didn&apos;t find it to be quicker than any other printer I&apos;ve used but I wash;t expecting it to be lighting. It prints as fast as it advertises, (Rough guess, I didn&apos;t sit there with a stop watch, and people that do need to get out more.) It isn&apos;t slow but if speed is what you&apos;re going for, perhaps inkjet overall isn&apos;t what you should consider. For my purposes, it is great.

Document Printing Quality:
Printed 200 wedding invitations, reply cards, and their envelopes. Not one single hang up despite the unusual document sizes. My HP would jam every 3 pages if I was lucky. Has a generous bin for paper. Also it &quot;re-inked&quot; itself appropriately (Didn&apos;t print low ink invitations before it re-inked, which I was hoping for.)

Print from Mobile Phone:
Yes! ok, I was totally stoked to see this. The printer has a separate tray for photo paper, so whenever you want to print a picture, you don&apos;t have to take out your plain paper and load photo paper and switch back when ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>IMaMama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent for Wireless Printing for ENTIRE Fam!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wireless, Cost of Ink, Quality of Docs and Pics!

Cons: Finding Compartment to Remove a Random Paper Jam

Easy &quot;out-of-the-box&quot; set up for immediate WIRELESS use! Very few paper jams, and they were easy to unjam (once locating the inconspic compartment at the back). Only tsk tsk is there is no visible &quot;where to place the paper&quot; marker. Kinda want it to be a quick, no-brainer time saver, so I put piece of yellow tape to mark the spot for paper edge placement. Don&apos;t be afraid to try the added features for printing and pics, they are all great. Still a big plus.....THE INK IS THE CHEAPEST AND BEST STUFF OUT THERE!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rodney</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BEST PRINTER ON THE MARKET FOR PHOTOGRAPS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It produces excellent prints without much effort

Cons: I haven&apos;t found any shortcomings yet

This is my second Kodak printer and it is even better than my Kodak 5500. I assist a large number of people with their computers and printers and most people are not able to achieve the print quality with their HP&apos;s etc that you can get with the Kodak 9.1. The Picture Perfect Program enhances photos to the extent that they are as good if not better than you can get a Kodak processing lab. The 9.1 was very easy to install on my Apple Mac and I can mass produce prints at a fraction of the cost of other printers. The lexmark also has economical ink but the picture quality is not as good as the Kodak 9.1. The metallized dyes use in the Kodak 10 cartridges is also a bonus feature for ... long term print stability.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sutor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I just love my new printer. I bought it primarily for home use - printing, copying, scanning. I haven&apos;t used it much yet, but love what I have done so far. This printer has many features and I can&apos;t wait to use all of them. I already bought extra ink so I won&apos;t run out. The price of the ink is cheaper than what I had expected. This printer was also easy to setup, and easy to use. This is my first wireless printer, and I couldn&apos;t be happier.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>LNantt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Keeps me at home with kids rather than having to run to the office to scan or fax something...

Cons: If it goes to &quot;sleep&quot; I have to run downstairs to touch the on button - very minor for me...

Bought this printer on Black Friday, so price was drastically reduced - LOVE LOVE LOVE this printer. Easy to set up - Google Cloud is easy to use with it, it prints Great Photos and documents. I print photos from my cell phone from wherever I am and don&apos;t have to worry about changing out the paper as there is a place for regular paper and one for 4 X 6 photo paper. I use the document feeder a lot because I print and scan and re-email a lot from home... Love the touch screen - I haven&apos;t faxed with it, but don&apos;t have to really because of the scanner and email - I would recommend th ... is to anyone needing a great work printer or a home printer that is needed for the occasional (or in my case, perpetual) working from home. I would gladly pay the full price for it if I had to.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>mel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kodak Hero 9.1</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up

Cons: Large Footprint

I think it is a little complicated to operate. When you want a 4x6 photo you have to go into your control panel and change it. Should be automatic.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>JoeHockey</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Value - Love Wireless Printing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy Wireless Use/Setup

Cons: A little pricey upfront, but value is realized over time.

No cords, easy to connect to multiple devices via Wi-Fi. Ink is much less expensive than competitors - overall, very pleased.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>GovanGirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great deal from QVC! Easy to set up, only drawback is that it sounds a bit clunky in use! Apart from that does everything a home used could want, really pleased with it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My new printer,a big improvement over my old one!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We got our new Kodak printer this week,and we are very pleased with it!
Easy to set up,even the Wi-Fi,(on our three computers),it&apos;s easy to use,and the prints are very good as well!
Our other printer was three years old,and,and as I had recently treated my husband to the excellent Fuji Hs30EXR,a previous TSV,and all he needed now was a modern printer.
This seemed to fit the bill,was a good price,and we seems solid,and well made.
Cartridges are long lasting,very reasonable,and readily available,so it should be cheap to run as well.
As the Fuji can take 3D images,and this printer can now print them out(Kodak even supply 3D glasses),it will be fun to try them out!
All in all,a good buy!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>bus4355</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excelent printer for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have tried a number of different printers none have given results to match my old printer (epson R340) always had flat blacks until now. Hero 9.1 gives superb colour and vivid blacks Easy to setup and connect to WI FI setup only downside no disk printing but can use R340 for that</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ricky Smacks</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>First Impression Good, waiting to see</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low cost for ink; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Flimsy Construction

Product appears fine. Cannot set up to automatically detect incoming fax or turn off ringer. Seems to go through a lot on start up, parts moving around, concerned about lasting beyond warranty period.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jules11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good quality printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The printer has lots of good functions, and is cheap to replace the ink. Printer is of good design and quality, only downside is that it has a large footprint, so takes up a fair space. Hence only 4 stars.
If you have the space, printer is a good buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Less than expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Efficient; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Inefficient

Bought this to replace my HP8600, go wireless. and reduce my ink cost. I should have saved my money and continued to pay the highrer price for the HP ink. The HP was so much better and better made.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Darlene206</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Printer used mainly for documents</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: nothing

Cons: corlor printing &amp; touch screen pad

This printer is AWFUL for the amount of money it cost. Touch screen pad was extremely hard to use - had to use a stylus pen to maneuver between options &amp; different screes. Color pictures/documents never printed correctly. Took it back after 2 weeks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>N12KA16</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>East to get up and running on wireless network</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of up and running wireless and easy cartridge change.

Cons: Glossy finish attracts dus. Didnt buy it for t he color/t

Crisp character definition aand vey good photo printing,
Shipping tabs to access printer carriage were not easy to pull on.
Everything else was freat. Using computers and printers since 1972.
(yep, before pc&apos;s).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mitzi25</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I got this printer on sale right before christmas..The wifi works wonderful, very easy to setup. I print a lot and still have the ink that came with it for over a month. Better then the old HP I had..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>biker4595</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent printer for documents &amp; photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up &amp; operate

I like the design on this printer &amp; the wireless operation. The touch screen operation of this printer is excellent. I do not have any regrets in my purchase of this printer the Kodak Hero 9.1 All-In-One-Printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Perplemom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great home printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to set up, EXCELLENT price

The Kodak Hero 9.1 printer is awesome! It&apos;s fast, and easy to use. It&apos;s more compact than my last Kodak printer, yet uses the same cartridges, so that I didn&apos;t waste my supply on hand. Excellent machine and a great buy for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Laney223</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Printer for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, quality of pics, &amp; reasonable cost of ink

Cons: Haven&apos;t had any issues thus far

I had a Kodak printer prior to this one and so I wanted another one. I adopted my daughter and send her mother pictures every couple of months and so quality of pictures is important for me. I also am able to print great pictures for scrapbooking projects. The best thing is that the print cartridges are reasonable and easy to install. I really love my printer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tequila George</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Practical, useful, &amp; it works.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Strong price performer; Great telephone support; Compact Design

Cons: PDA config not intuitive

Nice that it can print email from PDA. Wish it was able to be identified as an Apple &quot;Air Printer&quot;. If it can, it is certainly not intuitive. The price for the performance still makes this a nice value.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sharon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reliable; Compact Design; Quiet; Easy To Use; Easy To Set Up

Set-up was very easy. Print quality is good, color is not as sharp as I would prefer but it is acceptable. Replacing ink cartridges is a little tricky, seems fragile.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>gojets2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice printer, better then average quality prints</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Double sided printing, copies and faxes

Cons: Works best with Kodak paper

Bought this because my HP photosmart 7660 paper feeder started messing up, feeding two sheets at a time. The photo print quality is not quite as good as the hp but it&apos;s adequate. Does have improved quality features when used with Kodak paper. The reason the ink is so cheap is you don&apos;t have to buy a new print head every time you buy a cartridge as is the case with most inkjets. Had this once before with an Epson Photo Stylus 700 printer, but when the print head got clogged the printer was trash, my fault because I hadn&apos;t used it in awhile and the ink dried up in the head. Fortunately the print head in this one is replaceable and has a maintenance cleaning feature. A replacement head is available f ... or $45, reviews claim it lasts 2 - 3 years so sounds like an economical solution if you only have to replace it a couple times if at all, during the life of the printer.

Only complaint is photo printing must be used in best mode to avoid streaking and it seems you can&apos;t do borderless when printing with &quot;kodak offset dot mode&quot; or at least couldn&apos;t figure out how to do it.

The automatic image enhancement software can do more damage than good depending upon the image contents, worth experimenting with and the &quot;negative&quot; effects are visible on the preview so if you don&apos;t like it you wont waste the paper or ink.

Has an automatic duplexer for double sided printing but doesn&apos;t do double sided copying, that must be done manually to single sided. Automatic document feeder seems to work well. Copies are clear and accurate, can be done in either color or b/w modes.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim02351</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Cost of ink, easy to set up and use.

Had to replace HP Photosmart Premium 309. Sent back for exchange/repair twice in 2 years it had decided to die once more, this time permanently. What sold me on this was not only the price to buy, but the price of ink. Five ink cartridges in the HP meant over $100 every time they ran out. The Kodak had all of the same features as the high end HP printer and cost less. Turned out it works equally as well, operates quieter, and the ink cartridges last at least twice as long.

Using half the ink saves me the cost of this unit over a period of 2-3 months and as a small business owner and in today&apos;s time, every buck counts. As for the 4 star rating, I dropped it one star because I don&apos;t know how long the print head is going to last. Other ... than that, it&apos;s 5 stars all of the way. So far, I can pat myself on the back for making a wise decision.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pogo1946</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, features, ease of use.

Cons: What&apos;s not to like?

Easy setup, great features, low price. Touchscreen control makes this a dream to setup and use in all modes. As a small business owner transitioning to a paperless office the easy to use scan function is a real bonus-it&apos;s fast, efficient, and all selections are touchscreen menu driven.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cap1929</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality and cost of replacement cartridges

Cons: Nothing so far

We purchased this printer a week ago and it has been awesome. It was very easy to install via our wireless network router. We are running Windows Vista &amp; Windows 7 operating systems and the printer was easy to load on both computers. The quality of the printing is outstanding and the printer has great features.

Our last printer was an HP 7400, and after about 4 years of service it started to go out. Not to mention, we were spending about $90 every two months on cartridge replacements (value pack at Sams). We are really looking forward to spending much less on cartridge replacements with our new Kodak Hero.

A+++++</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJL1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent purchaswe</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>very quick delivery.very easy and quick set up had it up and working within 5 minutes.great picture and printing quality. best printer i have ever purchased and i have had quite a lot.dont know why i didnt buy it earlier</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Staples customer never again</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Staples Refuses to Stand By This One</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Inefficient; Flimsy Construction; Unreliable

The only thing worse than this printer is the TERRIBLE RUN AROUND BY STAPLES, when it comes to rectifying a problem. We bought this printer less than a month ago. The printer stopped printing the color blue then started jamming every other paper then the print head jammed completely rendering the printer completely useless After several phone calls and emails we were told they only have a 14 day money back guarantee and since we bought the two year extended program we had to call other 800 numbers. Which we got the busy signal. So We had to run out and buy another printer to keep our company up and running while The Staples crew tried to figure a way to stall us or ignore us till we went away.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>tekky1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent purchase Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve just bought this printer after seeing it on air, and can I just say what a printer !!!!!! what a amazing price !!!!!!!!!!. I had a standard Lexmark before this purchase and I was looking to upgrade. I did some research online looking at both its functions/pricing,extras and for me QVC came out the best in value on this item,and it has everything I&apos;m looking for. It caters for all my printing needs. It does it all and a lot more which is a added bonus. Setting it up is very easy about 5/10 minutes, load the disc into your computer follow the on screen instructions and off you go. I have so far printed some pictures (1st class print quality very clear) used the copy function, and printed off some emails. It does all this at great ease and speed. If you looking to upgrade choose this gre ... at printer you won&apos;t be disappointed trust me. Thank you QVC for a great buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>navair</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great purchase</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>this printer is well suited for my needs. i use the wired network option and i can print from any computer on my network. ink is very reasonable priced. it is a bit slow on the network print. and the interface software could be a bit more user friendly.but overall a great product. i have been looking for a new printer for over a year and kept coming back to the Kodak. the auto feeder for faxing and copying is excellent. overall..printer great design,software needs some tweaking.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>randyb9671</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kodak Hero 9.1</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Positives: Cheap cost of ink Reasonable cost of printer itself Works great and duplex is much fast than my HP 8500. The ink drys faster making the print on both sides page creation faster. This printer prints beautiful photos and can can determine what tray to use based on what you are printing. Negatives: One color ink cartridge instead of separate cartridges for each color. Consequently, when one ink runs out, you must replace the entire color cartridge. The cheap cost of ink makes up for this deficiency.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lost Again</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>OK to own</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The set to automatic double side print is great. Photo scan is improved and photos from SD (etc) is super with the touch screen. Many features available. Still have a tray for keeping 4X6 or 5X7 photo paper on board. Can work with 14 paper. A wee slow but worth it. Over the years, my 3rd update printer. Never put drug store ink in a Kodak!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mikeyl72</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Poor Tech Support</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Tech Support

Purchased my Hero 9.1 on Dec 27, 2011. Used it with the Ethernet connection. On Jan 29, 2012 the printer stopped working. After many phone calls, e-mails and broken promises someone would call me back they are sending me a new printer. It is now Feb. 2, 2012 and the printer is due her next week.

I cannot speak to the quality of the printer, other than to say it overrides the default printer setting anytime you turn it on – I have 2 other printers in my network. Technical support is extremely poor and has no understanding of how the printer functions. If they cannot read it on their computer screen they cannot help you. One Tech blamed my router, one tech blamed the power cord, and one tech said it was not her job. Truth is the “motherboard” of the printer o ... r the firmware is corrupted. Also the accent of the techs was so strong I had a very difficult time understanding them. I would NOT recommend this to anyone, and doubt I will every by Kodak again. Next time it will be another Epson or maybe a Brother.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>pflute</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great printer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up...great print quality

I got this printer to replace 3 other miscellaneous printers/copiers that had accumulated in my office. It&apos;s compact, easy to set up, puts out great print pictures and documents, and I really, REALLY love it! Of course, the lower ink usage is a HUGE plus!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Holley777</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Looks great on paper but features are HORRIBLE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ink price is cheap

Cons: See comments!!

2nd Kodak printer I&apos;ve had. Many problems with it. But this printer looked to be EXACTLY what I need. I&apos;ve had it less than a month &amp; so far: Wi-Fi features turns itself off all the time, double sided print feature jams the printer, 1/2 of the time paper prints and cuts off words at the bottom &amp; top of the page; colors are off on pictures like ink is low (which is not), prints MUCH slower than states. I don&apos;t care how much cheaper the ink costs which is the only plus with Kodak printers, I will NEVER buy another one. I guess you get what you pay for. I just thought I would give them another try. Kicking myself for it now!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>doug1234geek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great printer.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: initial cost

Great printer. It does everything. Kodak&apos;s ink is great (and cheap). Prints are great, touch screen is convenient, and the fax function also works from pc.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>westrider</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Product Did not work!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low ink cost

Cons: Durability questions.

Purchased new Kodak Hero and it did not work. Called Kodak and they sent me a new printer within three days. New printer is working fine. However had to box up the printer I originally purchased and returned it to Kodak. This is not the first time that I have purchased a new Kodak printer only to have it not work. This will probably be the last Kodak printer I buy so when this one breaks I will find something else. However I do like the lower ink cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>griff45</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I LOVE this printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The quality.... it is a winner

Cons: mmmm can&apos;t think of anything at the moment

I have never had a printer that I have liked more in the 30 years I have been buying computers and accessories. The ease of the setup right out of the box, the networking of my other 3 laptops in the house, instant success, but most of all the cost and the quality are next to none. I have had every brand of printer you can imagine and when this one went on sale I was first in line. Even with Kodak going into chapter 11 I would rush out and get a backup if I thought they wouldn&apos;t make it out. I have the Hero 9.1 so am enjoying all the extras. PHOTOS look just like they came from a photo shop. I can&apos;t imagine anyone being disappointed especially if you buy your ink on Wednesday&apos;s ;-) 20% off</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joser147</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good value for price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: value-price, ink &amp; features

Cons: print quality only OK

This printer is my second Kodak. The main reason for this purchase is the value based on ink and features on this model. I had an earlier version that died on me but luckily I had purchased a warranty from BB and it was replaced but I upgraded and paid the difference.

The print quality is average. I haven&apos;t printed photos and I would hope it is better. All in all, it&apos;s a good machine for document printing and its reasonably priced with good prices for ink.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>TWSorlando</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best ink cost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: low cost ink-Great printing

Cons: When I find something, I&apos;ll let you know.

This is my 3rd Kodak printer. I gave my son my first one...still going strong at his house. I gave my daughter my second...wireless WiFi...can print from anywhere in her house. I have a third chance to buy any printer. I bought another Kodak!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>SweetDevil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Prints Great Pictures and Easy to Set Up</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Print Quality; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy To Use; Quiet

Easy wireless set up and easy to use. Prints great pictures. Much quieter then my old HP printer. So far so good!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>John</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No warranty</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Unreliable

Please be advised Kodak does not honor its one year warranty. Horrible customer service if you can call it that. Don&apos;t go here!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>pHiLlP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>printer came thursday so easy to set up excellent quality would recomend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kim the  Baker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>&quot;Nothing to get excited about&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Easy To Set Up

Cons: Unreliable

Average, but as they say you get what you pay for. What you save in ink, you lose in reliability.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>G. Winters</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hero 9.1</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Setting up instructions could be more clear for wireless. But once set up it is as promised.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>blitz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>QVC</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>worst purchase ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Iwas led to understand this kodak printer could do all but make a cup of tea believe me there is more chance of it making a cup of tea than printing a photo.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lynda719</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is a great printer for everything</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It prints fast and well. Great pictures, fast documents and seems to hardly use any ink. The ink cartridges last a long time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Kodak HERO 9.1 All-in-One Color Ink-jet - Fax / copier / printer / scanner</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/12328936959780198714/reviews?q=printers%20and%20copiers&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.85&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=8KiRULO3POmY2AXSzoDwBQ&amp;ved=0CO8BEPQCMAU</URL>
     <Reviewer>SimR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good printer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Inks are inexpensive compared to other brands

The wireless feature is excellent and installation is a snap.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

