<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Apple iPad 2 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile, backlit color touch screen, smooth, quick page turns, robust iBooks store, works with all major e-bookstores and free sources, runs apps, including Kindle for iPad, lighter, thinner, faster than predecessor

Cons: Screen is hard to read in bright sunlight or overhead lights, still bigger and heavier than most e-readers, relatively short battery life, 3G wireless costs extra, unlike Kindle, expensive, even after a price cut, lower-resolution screen than current generation Apple iPad

While the new Apple iPad has drawn lots of attention, the Apple iPad 2 tablet remains available and, thanks to a $100 price cut, a little more affordable. For those interested in using an iPad as an e-book reader, the most significant difference is the new iPad&apos;s high-resolution Ret ... ina display that does wonders for illustrations and for text, though the display used by the iPad 2 has plenty of pluses -- and a few minuses -- in its own right. ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>17 out of 19 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bestcovery.com Expert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Bestcovery</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ranked Second in Best Budget Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The 16GB iPad 2 remains in Apple&apos;s product line, but is much more budget-friendly thanks to its $100 price cut. As Apple is keen to point out, the iPad 2 is just as impressive as it was before the latest iPad was announced. Old model or not, the iPad 2 is still a wholly legitimate proposition. The dual-core A5 processor provides plenty of...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jlppimb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not my cup of tea!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, battery life

Cons: Graphics, video quality

Bought an iPad2 after the recomendation of the BB employee. It works fine and the battery life is great as most people say. It is easy to use as with most Apple products. The sound is also not great, especially the volume, but i wasnt expecting a blaring sound system so it may be fine for most people. I am in know means impressed with the graphics! Watching CNN streamed is horrible, any movement and its impossible to know what you are watching. The HBO GO app is great, but again the video quality is poor. The app store has almost anything you could want to use on a tablet. All in all, I would not recommend this to anyone looking for a tablet at this price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HyperFC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Continually surprised by the utility</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery Life, overall speed and performance, portability, ease of use

Cons: Wifi sometimes stays &quot;asleep&quot; after sleep, Some pay apps you must buy twice between iPad and iPod/iPhone

I purchased the iPad 2 to be used as a work/home mixed use device. I waited for the second generation knowing Apple goes on a (usually) yearly refresh cycle. I did get to use the first iPad thanks to friends who had one, and am glad I waited.
I have a 32 gig white wifi. I thought the white finish might be distracting for video at first but even in bright light I have no problems. Wifi signal holds well in all areas of my work/home but I find sometimes I must turn wifi on and off if device has been sleeping to &quot;wake&quot; the connection.
As an e-reader I think it works well with the screen br ... ightness very low. While not as easy on the eyes as my wife&apos;s Nook, I still don&apos;t feel the eye fatigue I thought I would from the screen with brightness down low. It does work with Nashville&apos;s library system, but only for ePub books via Overdrive app.
The screen looks great and battery life thus far has been excellent. Form factor of the thinner edges and lighter weight is noticeable and makes the device easier to handle.
The ability to toggle the switch on the side from a mute to an orientation lock is fantastic and a wonderful idea. If you hold the down volume longer than a second, it goes straight to mute. Sometimes that’s not what I want but you quickly adapt to multiple clicks for down volume and holding it down for mute.
The sound from the speaker is very good and has some punch, but it’s still a tiny mono speaker so don’t expect incredible things.
I haven’t used the cameras much and probably will only really use then if I use facetime, which right now I don’t really utilize. I can’t imagine taking a lot of pictures with the iPad.
The device does seem measurably faster for the apps I’ve used between the two versions, and the upgraded graphics ability is a big part of that.
I was not sure how I’d feel about the on-screen keyboard, and let’s just say I’m not going to type any novels on it any time soon. But you do adjust to the fact that there’s nothing to touch other than the scr ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sam1313</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BEST TABLET OUT THERE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: its fast, it has great screen quality, its design, great for school, battery life.

Cons: needs a case, glitches sometimes, no adobe flash player, camera quality

i got the apple ipad 16 gb right before school started over the summer and i love it! it has everything i wanted and needed, its great for school projects and also its fun to play games when im home! The internet is lightning fast, although it glitches sometimes. it has great screen resolution and it feels great in the hand. it doesn&apos;t have flash player, but you can get an app that supports it which is good. sound quality is fairly good but can sound a little fuzzy when its on high volume. The ipad 2 is portable so you can take it on the go. The picture quality is better in the front, for the camera in the back ... which is pix-elated. it scratches easily, but they don&apos;t show up on the white as much as the black so i prefer to get the white one. the black one is also known to overheat and it looks bigger. the white one looks more sheik and expensive. apple did a great overall job
now im waiting form my iphone 4
- apple for life(:
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DrMeerkat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s the category defining experience</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great screen and battery life, the leading ecosystem of software and media.

Cons: Admittedly pricey, a luxury item for sure. Must have a case - kids are drawn to it like flies!

There is a reason that this defines the tablet experience - it is simple to use, well constructed, attractive design, and great battery life. The software and hardware are designed around each other, so there is consistent, predictable and reliable performance. The ecosystem of services makes the package though - integration with all the stuff from iPods or iPhones, and this is just magnified if you use macs. The thing just works &quot;right.&quot;. Just be careful with it because every child with the ability to reach it will become fixated on the thing, and there is no included case,</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>fireman01</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Was a great buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very flexable, easy to use, good quality

Cons: Price

The IPAD2 was very expensive, but the price was the only minus. We love it and are finding more apps to use on it all the time. My Wife, and twin boys use it all the time and the battery seems to last forever. We recently bought an IPAD dock with an audio jack and nice speakers. That added an additional sound system to our house. We use it for instant email, weather, news, face time, texting, netflicks, photos, videos, and more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Svenn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s an iPad, what&apos;s not to like?!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Intuitive, portable, great app&apos;s available, accurate graphics.

Cons: It&apos;s more expensive than a tablet.

It&apos;s an iPad. They&apos;re intuitive, easy to set up. Portability is perfect for sittin&apos; on the sofa or hanging out on the back patio. Graphics are crisp and plenty bright. Plenty of app&apos;s to download. Don&apos;t mean to sound like an advertisement, but it&apos;s nice having one around the house.

Sales person was helpful.

Downsides - not as cheap as a tablet. Also, because of size advise getting a case. Seems too easy to drop otherwise.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bubby888</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Time To Buy An iPad And Save Money Too!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sleek, fast, portable, long battery life- on sale!

Cons: iTunes

I was about due for a new netbook, but since I wanted the comfort of surfing from a prone position, I gave the iPad a serious look. The iPad 3 was about to be released, and, after comparing specs, I decided I didn&apos;t need the highly touted &quot;retina display&quot;- I wouldn&apos;t miss something I never had. My understanding was, and still is, the core processor in the 2 and 3 are basically the same.

After the iPad 3 was released, Best Buy had a sale on their remaining stock of the iPad 2; some returned items were much cheaper than the sale price. Unfortunately, the returned items were selling out quickly, so I bought the 16 gig iPad 2 at about 20% off.

Right out of the box, the Pad was partially charged, a ... nd I was able to play with it a bit. But first, I had to register to get an Apple I.D, and have access to iCloud (the online area where you can back some data up to).

I found the screen quite large, and the virtual keyboard quite easy to navigate; almost as easy as a real keyboard. The screen is quite bright, but adjustable.

I use the iPad mostly to surf the &apos;net. This is only possible while near a wi-fi hotspot with the model I have, which is fine with me, as I don&apos;t intend to travel much with it (I have an iPhone). I&apos;ve loaded books, and purchased a season of Breaking Bad to view. I personally find the picture quality excellent. I also stream Netflix movies to the Pad.

The built in applications aren&apos;t bad, but we should have the option of deleting those we don&apos;t want entirely. Even after learning how to group icons, the screen can get quite crowded.

I wasn&apos;t a fan of iTunes in its first iteration, and still not now. I understand that Apple, for proprietary reasons, wishes to control its content through iTunes. However, I still prefer the drag and drop method for moving, or deleting data. Creating playlists, adding content- most everything has to go through iTunes. For that alone, I hate it- but not enough to return it.

The iPad is very thin and sleek, and seems fragile ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Movin2pokie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superfun!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use with clear graphics and great sound quality.

Cons: I really miss using flash and I am not satisfied with their storage choices of photos and videos.

The ipad2 is a wonderful product and I highly recommend it. I use it for many hours per day, which I did not foresee. I do not play games on it. I use it for getting information on starting a new business, communication, taking and viewing video along with Facebook and email. I have more than a dozen grandchildren, so it&apos;s very valuable for staying in touch with family.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>NortheastOhioCustomer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One amazing device that does it all</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great battery life, overall reliability, and ease of use.

Cons: Accessories such as cases and adapters can be somewhat expensive

The reliability of the iPad 2 is absolutely amazing. I never have issues with viruses, ease of use, or freezing up. The iPad never has an issue slowing down and runs flawlessly no matter how many programs I have running.
(jrw)
The display is crystal clear with great graphics and high quality when zooming in. Every image on the display is crystal clear.
(jrw)
The iPad 2 battery last 10 hours. I watch 4-5 full length movies on it before it needs recharging. Additionally it can play music for at least 10 hours before needing to be recharged.
(jrw)
This device amazes me with everything that it does and the investment in it is wor ... th every penny.
(jrw)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SteveFTW</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed, screen resolution, ease of use

Cons: No USB port, Must use iTunes to sync, Doesn&apos;t support Amazon Cloud

I actually bought the iPad 2 for my mother as a book reader. She hasn&apos;t hardly gotten to use it yet because I fell in love with it! For books it&apos;s perfect because of the battery life. The speed and choices for apps is outstanding also. It&apos;s easy to use but takes some getting used too the 1 button design. I would recommend it to anyone but with three caveats; First, It doesn&apos;t play well with Amazon&apos;s cloud. I wanted to download the music I had purchased through Amazon and there wasn&apos;t an option. I couldn&apos;t even stream it from the cloud. Not a huge deal because you can download the songs on the PC and then sync them to the iPad from your pc. Second, I wish it had ... a USB port to be able to add or remove music, videos, books, etc... Third, although the speaker on the iPad is clear and sufficient, they should have put two speakers on it. I knew when I purchased the iPad it would have limitations so I&apos;ve accepted them. It&apos;s still an amazing product and in my opionion well worth getting.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>N4Sir</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overall, good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Overall usefulness.

Cons: Cost.

I originally was looking to purchase an ereader.when my daughter showed me her iPad. I was intrigued with what all it could do. I decided I wanted one for my birthday, and what do you know, I got one.Not so subtle hints work well.

I am not overly critical of any device. It is easy to nitpick anything. And, for the sake of the readers attention span, I will be brief.

It is a great ereader and is easy to download reader apps such as Kindle and Nook. It comes with eBooks. I have wi-fi access almost anywhere I go, so it is easy to stay connected with my email and Internet. Typing on the screen&apos;s keyboard is a breeze. The screen is the perfect size for me and overall it isn&apos;t too heavy. There are plenty of useful and fun apps tha ... t are available. The iPad is very easy to setup via iTunes.

On the other hand, some of the apps, such as Facebook, crash for no apparent reason. That gets aggravating. Not having a flash player plain stinks. Apple really needs to come up off of some of the proprietary limitations. Furthermore, apps that are free on Android devices are not on Apple devices. some of the programs take getting used to as they do not look like the familiar Windows applications. The external speaker sound is mediocre.

Overall, I&apos;m enjoying it a lot
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RaceCityEd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, speed, picture quality, value.

Cons: Nothing so far.

I have only had my iPad for a few days and already LOVE it! It does everything I need it for. I am sure it does a great deal more but I mainly use it for email, surfing the web, and with the Apple TV I also purchased. I like the design, picture quality and the screen size is just right. The other reason I bought it was for travel. My laptop is bulky and heavy, the iPad is not. So far I have not found anything to complain about. Way to go Apple!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sammyd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Another quality Apple product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portability,Quality,Easy set up,

Cons: ?? price

Since buying my 1st apple product several years ago and specifically switching from the PC to MAC I&apos;ve had nothing but good experiences. The IPAD2 has been no exception so far. I recently bought a MACBOOK PRO and thought I would have no use for an IPAD so purchasing one was more of a dream. Luckily someone close to me was listening when I said how cool it would be to have one. It was a merry x-mas. What&apos;s great about the IPAD2 is the portability and easy of use. The graphics are second to none, pictures fill the full screen in amazing clarity. With ICLOUD you can link all your apple products sharing apps, files ect. It truly is a tablet, even thinner than the IPAD1, which makes it so easy to bring just about anywhere.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ekn412</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, lighting fast

Cons: No chat on Facebook

I just got my iPad the other day and I&apos;m very satisfied with it. It has great screen quality and the sound is great. The part I don&apos;t like, is that on Facebook I cannot get on to chat. The price was a bit high, but I managed it. I got a screen protector and a cover for it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ravenx2012</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Almost perfect, but....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight, battery life, ease of use, not as easy to jailbreak as iphones and original ipad.

Cons: resolution, flash support (ehh...no biggie)

Apple is trying to drive the future of product development with putting pressure on their desires of the industry to accept apple as the leader. This is a battle that has been going on sometime since the iphone came out. No flash support. That being said like the wars with BETA over VHS, one adult industry sealed the deal on the battle, and VHS finally emerged as the only format. Now APple wants the security of HTML5 over flash. Therefore they won&apos;t use flash. That same adult industry is starting to code websites specific to html5. Other internet companies are feeling the pressure of Apple&apos;s market shares, and going to HTML5. ... Will the next 3 - 5 years see the same chain of events as VHS? Most likely, if Apple does not change their stance. So lack of Flash ... minus 1 star? Outside of that, fixed memory size, &quot;locked&quot; system unless you jailbreak. A few downers.

But, on the upside. You have one incredible tablet with a tone of applications that are very easy to use. The device integrates seamlessly with other apple products in the house. I used to be a power gamer building my own PCs regularly. I now own an Iphone, Imac, Inano, and Ipad... Back in the days of Macs vs PCs, before MAcs became intel based .. there was no questions as to who was on top. Now today the battle is Micrsoft vs apple. Or maybe even google vs apple, as desktop computers are becoming outdated, and everything is moving mobile.

Competition has recently released tablets with higher resolution and flash support. When ipad 2 was released, no one had better. Others only added these features to try and take something from ipad. Ipads next gen, will have more features, and higher resolutions. then, th compition will listen to whatever complaints they hear about ipad 3 and try to add those into their units.

Long story much shorter.... Apple is leading the industry and setting the standard. Everything else out there is a copy of the iPad and simply trying to catch a small piece of the pie all ready larg ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ChicagoNESE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I was expecting AMAZING but recieved GOOD</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The mobility, easy to use, price point is good, sleek design

Cons: Just doesn&apos;t turn enuff tricks with out FLASH!

I purchased the IPAD 2 in July in order to commicate with my family while I was on vacation over seas. The video quality was not that great. However, I was able to do facetime in the spots that were WIFI ready. I have had a total of 4 IPAD 2&apos;s due to exchanges. Random scratches right out of the box, to the home button not working and lastly, the sound not working at all. Once they exchanged my device that was scratch free with sound quality, I realized... I need more...something else! Kinda sad that flash doesn&apos;t work on it. And the whole Itunes cloud is a great concept, but when my credit card was stolen and account closed, I didn&apos;t get another card which m ... ade using my purchased apps, an impossibility. Bottom line is, I&apos;m going to try the Motorola Xoom. I think I will have better luck with the things that I need an tablet for. I&apos;m trying NOT to purchase a laptop.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>phnick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Product - looked at others too</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The design, screen, batery life, app store

Cons: No flash support, price, storage size the camera quality

I recently decided I wanted a tablet. I did lots of research on the competing products. I checked out the xoom, galaxy and several others. I am not an apple fanboy, though I love their products. This is simply an amazing tablet. The design is smooth and beautiful. It feels good to hold, has a beautiful bright display and very, very smooth scrolling.

THE GOOD: I didn&apos;t think I really needed an iPad, so I looked at many others. I love the wide variety of cheap, beautiful apps available. That is the obvious advantage Apple has. But the device performs very well, no crashes. I also love that I can easily add corporate email accounts. All of the other tablets requ ... ire tons of settings in different places. The ipad is just easy to use.

THE BAD: I really do wish it had Flash support. Furthermore, the quality of the cameras is below par for the price. They work fine, but there is a noticeable quality difference.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>esenior</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>First iPad ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The product name only sold me.

Cons: nothing right now.

I never bought first generation, but I did buy iPod Touch 3rd generation. There I was sold. I love my iPad 2. I played around with first generation of iPads and I come to like the it. Graphics, clarity is a fantastic on the iPad2. if you digital comic reader you&apos;re going to LOVE IT!!!. Photos: its depends on the lighting. Bad lighting bad pictures. Digitial copies are great. surfing the net good, unfortunate you still can&apos;t use Flash player yet, but overall I think iPad2 is great. Oh I got WiFi only, don&apos;t need a other bill... lol PS: Battery life is awesome. I charged it on 03/12/11 and it finally went below 50% on 03/16/11. Yes I was on it every day after work.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jones102</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect tablet so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The tablet has met my expectations completely so far. Not owning the previous iPad, this is an all new experience. Having a USB port would be nice but knowing that it didn&apos;t have one buying it, I can&apos;t really complain. It is very fast and I plan on using this probably more often than my actual computer. The graphics are great and playing games are good. It has not crashed or had any problems yet. The battery life is amazing! A wireless keyboard to go along with it would be a good investment. The cameras were a good edition and they are fine quality for the average person. I would probably stay away if I was looking for high quality photo taking. Downloads apps and music is a little slow but nothing to complain about. Wifi does not use that battery. I have used Netflix a good deal and altho ... ugh it is nowhere near as clearvas the computer, I am still satisfied. I would highly recommend this product!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PCCare247</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Gadget for a techie</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Widescreen and its touch is great.

Cons: The price. Quite Expensive

The Widescreen and the picture quality is superb. The Dual camera feature is nice. Battery life could have been improved. But overall a good gadget.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>QueenRN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I am very pleased with my I pad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, user friendly to navigate, and you can read everything without increasing font size

Cons: There is no USB port

I love my I Pad 2. I purchased the 16 GB which is enough space for my use . Pictures are clear and no this isn&apos;t the retina image. I did not see the need since we have a digital camera. I have downloaded several books to read. I even take it to church and read the Bible with much ease. You will not go wrong with the I Pad 2.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chachar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use from opening the box, great battery life.

Cons: We didn&apos;t purchase the model with the data coverage.

I received this as a birthday gift from my husband (by my request). We went with this model to try it out and see how much we use it. We have 3 kids (13, 10, &amp; 4) and knew that they&apos;d try to use it often and think of it as their own, but had heard the horror stories of kids dropping iPads and the repair was more expensive than the replacement cost. (I just institute the rule for my 4 year old he&apos;s not allowed to walk with it ....anywhere! Just sit!) I purchased a durable case for it to protect it a bit, and of course a screen cover is a MUST. In hindsight, I wished we&apos;d gotten the next model, with a data package. We mainly use this inside our home, but ta ... king this to the summer lake cottage, sports fields, and use in the car would have been more convenient with the data coverage option. I&apos;m sure we&apos;ll invest in another one over the next few years so it was a good starter iPad to try and determine if we liked it. I&apos;d say our family consensus is &quot;love&quot;.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PAJ74</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent for on the go people.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use and battery.

Cons: Price is always a concern.

This iPad is very fast and stylish. It is great for when I am on the go, which is all the time. Apple makes a great product and very user friendly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Creokutie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love my Ipad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to use

Cons: Keyboard is not so great for alot of typimg

I abso love the new sleek design of the Ipad 2!! Very easy to use and the screen clarity is awesome. Great travel companion.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Breesfan1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing screen quality. All around great tablet.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to set up &amp; it&apos;s always something different I learn about it every time I pick it up.

Cons: Can&apos;t really come up with anything. A little pricey; but you have to remember the quality of the product Apple puts out

I bought a Kindle Fire when they 1st came out. Then my best friend had to have one. I love electronics period. I always said I would never spend the money that some of my other friends were spending on the I-Pad. I loved the Kindle Fire. Nothing at all wrong with Amazon&apos;s new tablet. I had it for a year &amp; my cousin was wanting to buy a Kindle Fire. I decided to sell her mine for $150.00 &amp; look at some other tablets. I knew I had my desktop &amp; 2 laptops, so I was in no hurry for another tablet.

My Aunt had just bought an I-pad so m ... y Mom &amp; I decided to go to Best Buy just to look a couple of months later. I told the salesman about the Kindle Fire I owned before &amp; then I told him right off I wasn&apos;t spending the money on the new I-Pad; but I told him if he could take the time &amp; give me some reasons why I should buy the I-Pad 2 instead of one of the cheaper tablets; that I would purchase one from him before we left Best Buy. He didn&apos;t act like your regular salesman does. This guy stood there &amp; told me almost everything there was to know about the I-Pad 2.

After about 30 min. of he &amp; I talking; I walked out of Best Buy with a new I-Pad 2. That was 2 months ago &amp; I have never regretted by this Apple product. The only other thing I&apos;d like to add is if you aren&apos;t sure about which tablet to purchase; just remember this. If you have the extra money to spend it&apos;s well worth it to pay the extra &amp; know that you have purchased the better product. I had always said I&apos;d never buy an I-Pad but I can say now that it&apos;s absolutely the best. By the way. The battery life is simply amazing on this thing. Thanks for a great product; Apple.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>saint04</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for light class work</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portability, quality build, apple software productivity suite (pages), battery life

Cons: Screen resolution is acceptable, but not the best. Speakers located on one side.

I purchased my iPad 2 primarily for course work while working on my masters. In class I use an apple Bluetooth keyboard to take notes with Pages. What&apos;s really cool about pages is that it now sinks with OSX Mountain Lion (I use a Mac-mini). I don&apos;t bother carrying around binders any more which is great. All I really need to keep are folders for printed out and graded course work for home/personal use. I also use a tablet pen with pen ultimate for any free hand notes I may need to take. So when it&apos;s time for class I just take my Targus shoulder bag with me containing my iPad pen, Bluetooth keyboard, hdm ... i cable, hdmi to dvi adapter, headphones and iPad hdmi adapter. I carry the adapters for giving presentations from my iPad to an external monitor/projector and I also use the iPad for my note outlines when giving speeches, Bible studies or Sermons. I also use the kindle app to read my course books. Not having to carry heavy course books was one of my largest factors in deciding to purchase an iPad. I carry little to nothing now with this great tool.

I originally purchased the New iPad, but have found that I prefer the longer battery life and shorter recharge time of the iPad 2. I also like that this unit runs much cooler than the iPad 2. What&apos;s also pretty cool about my particular model is that it&apos;s an iPad 2,4. The iPad 2,4 has the newest A5 processor utilizing new types of materials at the 32nm process vs Apple&apos;s current 45nm. This translates to 15 to 30% longer battery life getting me 11 to 15 hours under normal use and watching video. Most people have not heard about this upgrade but it can be googled and anandtech (website) provides a much more indepth article of what I&apos;m talking about. So technically the iPad 2,4 is more advanced in regards to power efficiency than the new iPad processor (not in comparison to graphics; just processor efficiency). Apple released this new hardware (SoC-system on a chip) discretely. The new iPad does not offer this although it woul ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>CJMR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Abundant functions are worth the money.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact and easy to use. Great value.

Cons: Sound qualtiy

My husband wanted to buy me a tablet to read books on, but decided to get me the ipad 2 so that I could also use it for other functions like accessing the internet, facetime, games, pictures and so much more. It is well worth the money compared to buying a tablet with only one function. Apple products are so easy to use. The sound quality is somewhat limited, but good for such a compact product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>evyonnec</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love my Ipad2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy, convenient, my &quot;mini laptop&quot;!

Cons: Camera could be better.

I love my IPad2. Easy to use, small, light weight and I am able to do everything I do on my computer. Very sharp and clear and battery life is great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AppGizmo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t beat iPad from any aspect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The screen, the apps and the cameras

Cons: no SD card storage

There are umpteen tablets in the market in 10&quot; category but it is hard to beat apple. The style icon attached to it, the battery life, the screen resolution and specially the apps, make this iPad 2 the best in the lot. It&apos;s even a sweeter deal since you are getting almost everything iPad 3 offers at $100 less. Love this product...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AgentGee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The iPad 2 is great.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: battery life, easy to do things, and really fun.

Cons: Price, cameras.

The iPad 2 was a very useful product to me. I use it everywhere, whether it&apos;s in the car, at home, or at the airport. I like the battery life; it&apos;s really long... It survived a 9 hour trip to New Orleans, while being used most of the time (after being fully charged) and still had some battery left (around 20%).
What I didn&apos;t like was the price; it was pretty expensive and the 5 megapixel back camera seemed like 2 megapixels. The front camera was average.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MunnyRow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The only Tablet worth Owning</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Flawless performance and graphics

Cons: Battery could last a little longer and charge faster...

Can&apos;t wait for the new iTV. If it performs like this iPad and my iPhone, I&apos;ll definitely be a buyer. Apple has quality and innovation pegged.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jcs45</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent tablet for wifi use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set-up and use.

Cons: nothing so far

First time purchasing a apple product and needless to say I am very impressed. Screen resolution is great and ease of use is excellent along with speed of this tablet. I am not a electronics guru, however, this tablet is much better then previously owned tablets. The price of the ipad2 was less expensive as the ipad3 and figured that the ipad2 is a good start for a beginner. Overall: I am very happy with my ipad and might purchase a iphone in the not too distant future.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alana03</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Cons: Flash not supported

I bought the iPad 2 after the 3 came out. I did some research and found that the 16g was definitely a good choice for me. My main purpose was for surfing the web and apps. Videos take up all the space and u can put them on and take them off when your finished. The size comparison is Not a big deal but the iPad 2 is smaller. Not to mention the cost! I bought one that was returned and still had apple care for a year it was $250. That&apos;s a steal!!! I also of course got the black protection which is ALWAYS a good idea on electronics. If you are in the market for a tablet like your smart phone but bigger, this is definitely the one to get. I love it! And the battery life rocks!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Narcissis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price

Cons: Nothing

Easy to set-up, use, long battery life. So much easier than pulling out the laptop. Perfect for keeping my girl satisfied no matter where we are.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dunkhighlander</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent size and easy to use.

Cons: Wifi connectivity

I am an APPLE NUT! However, I was extremely disappointed that the iPad 2 had such poor reception with Wifi connections. It really is the only thing that I have an issue with overall. Otherwise... I love it!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>lynbryd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Satisfied Customer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love our new iPad2. Looked at 16GB but was happy to find the 32GB. Battery life is amazing. Worth the extra cost. Plenty of storage. Also Great customer service at B&amp;H. Fast transaction &amp; fast shipping.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MKbrw</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Machine! I rate it a 10!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything! Value, Ease of Use, and Beautiful!

Cons: Nothing to report.

My iPad is everything it is advertised to be, and then some. So easy to use. The battery lasts so long, I can&apos;t believe it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TGal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice purchase for an Apple &quot;newbie&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sleek looking

Cons: no SD slot

Not ever owning an Apple product, I am very pleased with this purchase. The overall looks is beautiful! It is so easy to use if you&apos;ve had any kind of computer experience. The sound from it is amazing and is loud enough when playing games and/or just listening to music. Bought this iPad 2 just a few days before the &quot;newer iPad&quot; was introduced to the public. Didn&apos;t see the need to go for the advanced retina display or other features since this will mainly be our ty-in to the internet when travelling.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>senatorbl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Would&apos;ve Been Nice to Know iPad3 Was Coming</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pretty easy to use, great apps and screen size

Cons: Technology moves so fast will be obsolete fairly soon

The iPad itself is a great tool. Bought it for my wife who is now pretty much addicted to it.

The only issue I really had was that I purchased the iPad2 a couple of weeks before the release of the iPad3. I don&apos;t follow technology very closely, so I was unaware that the iPad3 was that close to launch. I imagine that the associates at BestBuy knew that this would happen, but I was never advised. I certainly would have held out and bought the iPad3 had I known. Disappointed in the customer service.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jboooog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love our Ipad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Its Apple you cant go wrong

Cons: nothing!

Waited for the ipad 3 to come out so that they lower the price for the ipad 2. Saved me a hundred bucks :). I really don&apos;t need the new one when this one does just fine for me and my family. Love everything about it and so does my son who is four. Easy to use, long battery life, and more convienent to use then our laptop.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>tydek07</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use and reliable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, build quality, available applications

Cons: Some would say &quot;the price&quot; but you get what you pay for.

As much as I would like to use an Android tablet... they are just not &quot;there&quot; yet. I have tried many Android tablets, none of which were as stable and easy to use at the iPad. This tablet is very stable and very easy to use. There are so many apps out there for iOS, you are bound to find the one you are looking for. It is build strong and can withstand normal wear-and-tear by the average user. If you are looking to get a tablet for the first time, this is the way to go. You will enjoy it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Turp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Freaking sweet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything save the price

Cons: Price is on the high-end

What can you say? The iPad 2 is pretty awesome. Screen and graphics are gorgeous, TONS of apps to explore, it&apos;s almost like having a handy computer that&apos;s just a swipe away from using instantly.

Used mainly for web-browsing, social apps, expense tracking, etc. All of which the iPad 2 is perfectly suited for. Keep in mind, the speakers are fair at best. You may want to purchase headphones, or external speakers if you&apos;re using it for media.

Only big downside is the BASE version is FIVE HUNDRED freaking DOLLARS. And that&apos;s the start! Add in tax and a keyboard (which comes in handy) and you&apos;re looking at $600-$650 easy. That&apos;s kind of steep.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jmaillet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, no age limit.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Almost everything, battery life

Cons: Screen resolution

I&apos;m using it to type this, haha! Anyways, it really is an incredible piece of technology. As the title says, no age limit. My younger cousin who&apos;s 5 plays with it and navigates it like a professional. I myself, an eighth grader, also use it incredibly well. I use it for schoolwork, personal use, and I share it with family. My grandfather uses it just as well as I do, and he&apos;s 70! It has flaws, like the screen resolution, but it&apos;s still incredibly clear, there are just times where I wish it were better. I LOVE the speakers on it. They play so loud and clear, you can hear close to every instrument in the song. It&apos;s also incredibly fast and responsive, which is helpful when I&apos;m playing games. I would definitely recomm ... end this to ANYONE!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PKicker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I wish I had waited 6 weeks to save</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Apps, and the new price.

Cons: N/A

I wish I had waited 6 weeks to save $100. It is a great product and easy to use. I could have had the new IPad that just came out for the same price I paid for this one. So now I&apos;m just kicking myself for not waiting, but it was a birthday gift and I couldn&apos;t push that back 6 weeks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big Hec, BPS Productions Front Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What more can you say, its an iPad!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this iPad primaly to display images to clients in high resolution. Easy to navigate, long battery life and a gazillion apps all at your fingertips. Highly recommended!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>COLady</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light weight and Very easy to use.

Cons: Nothing.

I love the IPad2. It&apos;s one of the best investments I&apos;ve made. Great battery life. I can do everything on this device and I don&apos;t go anywhere without it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>thatotherdude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BUY ONE OF THESE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: light weight, user friendly, apps apps apps, long battery life

Cons: price, need a screen protector and case

I am very satisfied with my purchase. Good stuff. If I would change anything I think it should either be cheaper by about $100 or come with a screen protector and case (both of which are pretty much needed to protect your investment).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent for my first apple product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good price, great size, easy to use!

Cons: Didn&apos;t come with instructions on how to turn on and off

I have been a pc user for over 20 years, and never thought I would use an apple product, but I&apos;m so happy I decided to expand my world and buy and ipad 2. It has been so wonderful, so easy to use, makes a lot of sense, much more than the pc. It&apos;s a great product and I would recommend it highly to everyone!! Very happy customer!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>THEGENRAL01</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>iPad2 is good, but not for everyone.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: design, appearance, screen, camera, apps

Cons: functionality, removable storage, customization, price, flash, performance

Bought an iPad2 a few months ago, with high expectations. Unfortunately, they have not all been met. Certainly many reasons for its success, and hats off to apple for a great piece of technology. But, its got a long list of shortcomings that, in my personal opinion, are unacceptable for such advanced, expensive equipment.
Pros-
Phenomenal design. Truly a good looking, sexy product. Slim, light, powerful. Really great screen, fantastic camera. excellent app variety.
Cons-
No removable memory, un- upgradable (more ram/storage/battery V difficult). No flash? How hard is that to include?? Restrictive customization. Forced to use all apple (eg ... . itunes) products.
Dang expensive.
Summary-
For this kind of money, there really should be less shortcomings. My $350 laptop can do way more. Its not as portable, but I guess that leads me to my conclusion: The iPad is a product that seems to appeal to folks who value appearance over functionality. Sorry fanboys, but this is a yuppy toy for people not really tech savvy. Good to browse the web, read a book, play a game or watch a video. Its not good enough to compete with a real computer just yet. Maybe in a few years, I&apos;ll try again.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnno99</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for ease of access and use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use and set up.

Cons: Printer availability, better battery life would be desirable.

Easy to start using right out of the box. No special download requirements. Good size screen for viewing pictures and e mails. Easy touch screen keyboard response. Only thing to be careful about is to be sure you get an Airprint certified printer for wireless printing. Apps are at the App store but are troublesome for printers if the printer does not come equipped from the maufacturer for Apple.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TrustNoOne181</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fun Savvy Toy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, great screen, fast, and battery life

Cons: No usb connection and price of the IPAD

Over-all Review of this product is a thumbs up. It has everything you could have asked for in a Tablet. Great screen, good battery life... I could go on and on.

Only draw backs of course are no USB connections and price $$$.
So popular in demand.. no reason for Apple to drop the price. And People will pay for it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HappyRetiree</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome companion to full fuction desktops/laptops</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size/weight/portability

Cons: Does not support Adobe Flash Player

Love the iPad2 for size and ease of use when sitting and surfing in the evening. It is wonderfully easy to use (touch screen), extremely portable, and goes for extended periods without having to recharge the battery. It cannot be considered a replacement for a desktop or laptop, and it does have some limitations even using it as most people probably do (i.e., checking email, surfing): Obviously, typing lengthy emails are a bit tedious on a small hunt-and-peck keyboard. Also, and more frustrating for me, is that the iPad2 does not support Adobe Flash Player, so some videos and photos are not accessible which is a sort of serious drawback for some news sites and some eBay item photos. If there is a work aro ... und for this, I am unaware (but I&apos;m also not an IT guru either). All in all, the iPad2 is a great purchase and I love it even when a bit frustrated with the Adobe Flash issue.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JSquil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Display</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set up. Easy to use. Looks great!

Cons: High price tag

I&apos;ve recently become a fan of Apple having owned an iPod touch and an iPhone. The iPad2 is pretty much a large iPod touch with tremendous screen clarity. It is alot more expensive than Android OS competitor products and this is like buying a BMW instead of a Kia. The product is just sleek, intuitive and easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrG11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Enjoying my iPad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed, Ease of use, Apps available

I looked at several tablets before buying the iPad. What brought me to choosing the iPad over others was the availability of apps and the smoothness of operation of the iPad. I guess my second pick would be the Samsung products. I&apos;ve been using an iPod Touch second generation for several years. So many of the apps run on the iPad as well. But apps designed specifically for the iPad work best. I don&apos;t use the cameras much. They&apos;re best suited for video, under good lighting. I use the iPad everyday for email, weather reports, news, and games. My two year old granddaughter even enjoys playing the kids games and educational apps that I have. Its amazing how a young child can operate this device so easily. Battery life is great. I also have an App ... le TV. The integration between these devices is impressive.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roho</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Nothing

Bought this for my wife two weeks ago. She was apprehensive at first. But with easy setup and a few days of surfing and getting to know her new iPad: she now loves it! Just wish the price was a bit lower. Purchased otter box to put it in. Does make it heavier but removes all worries of scratching the screen and damage to the ipad. The battery life is unreal. Eight hours of use and still had 30 percent battery life. Using the maps/navigation app to plan our summer vacation trip was a snap. Much quicker than using computer. And linking it up to our wireless HP printer thru our Verizon wireless wi-fi was a breeze. The cameras ( front and rear) are great. Crisp clear and fast. No hesitation from when you push the button and when pic is taken. Don&apos;t ... make the mistake I made.....don&apos;t wait so long before getting your own iPad.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom202</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Best but still lacking</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Perfect size for internet and movies when traveling. Fast and easy to look up on the internet while watching TV

Cons: No Flash. Not easily expandable

Still needs Flash. Tired of hearing that Flash will be going the way of the dinosaur. Still needs SD storage or USB storage rather than buying 64 model. Want to be able to carry more pictures and movies on my extended trips. Other than that, still the best there is. More screen resolution? How good is good enough? Let me whip out my ipad to take a picture! Honestly?</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hookkem81</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, but too pricey</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, set-up, battery life

Cons: Price, can&apos;t sync older iPods wirelessly

I love everything about my iPad2. However, for nearly $800 out the door with taxes and a case, just too pricey to receive 5 stars. Also, iCloud sync does not work with 1st and 2nd generation iPods. You still have to use your primary PC to sync your iPod.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mrandmrsp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Best!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, sound, picture, and quality

Cons: Needs adobe flash player

My husband bought me this for my birthday &amp; I love it! I play games, surf the Internet, take pictures, read ibooks and video. It&apos;s a must have! I would recommend this to everyone! My company uses iPads and its great for business too. Great product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>lsufan076</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good addition to my Apple arsenal</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy of use

Cons: Nothing, its all good.

The IPad is a good addition to any computer users bag. As a proud owner of a Macbook Pro, IPod Classic (160gb) and Apple TV the addition of this IPad was a good fit. With light weight and small form factor makes it great for trips. Very easy to set up and use for someone who has never touched an IPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dw12</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>As expected - Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, quick to startup, long battery life

Cons: Wireless range is not so great

More convenient than a net book for close to the same price. We bought during the black Friday weekend when we got 10% off. Great battery life--it does last 6-10 hours. Really appreciate the quick start-up time, even when completely powered down. We mostly keep it in the normal/hibernate mode.

The weakness of this device would probably be its wireless range. You&apos;ll see devices show up then disappear. The range isn&apos;t the greatest. We&apos;ve noticed this at places we&apos;ve stayed and restaurants visited. That is the only minus I can grip about. Otherwise, this is a great product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>fmchog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Is all that I had heard</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight and portable

Cons: Will not accept Shockwave and Java applications.

I really enjoy my iPad. I had no problem getting on Wi-Fi when we traveled recently and changed locations. It has great graphics. It is light weight and fits in my purse. When we traveled via airplane, It was very easy to get through security. I took it out of my purse, laid it in the pan, and put it back at the end. I downloaded an application that lets me listen to my Sirius programs on the iPad. Many other applications and games are available and cheaper than downloads for PCs. I also use it to access my email and Facebook. In our travels, I rarely had to use my husbands laptop. My only complaint is that I cannot play my FB games on it as it will not download Shockwave or Java application ... s due to Apple issues. Therefore, I do have to use my husband&apos;s laptop to keep up with my games which is a disappointment to me. One reason I bought the iPad was to keep from having to travel with my laptop.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ipadlover88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME!!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great games and price

Cons: battery life isnt 10 hours like it says. 8 at the most

this device is awesome!!!! graphics are great. so many apps. games r great. battery life is pretty good. at least 8 hours.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Drewskiie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than I expected..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed, lightweight &amp; reliable..

Cons: Not a lot of free full version apps.

I had played with the acer iconia and toshiba thrive, I found them very good for the price.. My sister covinced me to get the iPad 2. And there was a big difference. Very easy to get use to and really fast. Now, I don&apos;t get anywhere without it. Only thing I don&apos;t like is you have to pay for full versions of apps that you can get free on the android market. Great battery life, went a full day of constant use without dying.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>bestbuyreview2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great and easy to view</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to read books/apps with screen size

Cons: A little heavy when reading a book for extended time

I received as a gift and have been very happy. Was impressed with battery life on vacation as I was reading a book. Smart cover is nice feature (but a little bit expensive) to quickly shut down and preserve the battery.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>LDub1965</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Addicted to my iPad2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Price

I am very happy with my purchase of the ipad2. Ivey had it about a month and already my laptop is tucked away in a drawer. It&apos;s light, sleek and very easy to use. The speed is quicker than my notebook. I have even started reading again using iBooks. I wish apple would get more in line with its competitor as far as pricing but that would be my only problem with the purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kja3dzign</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Mixed feelings about the IPAD 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: A lot of things...

Cons: A lot of things...

I recently bought the IPAD 2 about a month ago. I enjoy it, so don&apos;t get me wrong. The games are good quality in regards to graphics. Doesn&apos;t beat my PS3 by any stretch of imagination! The Apps. are of value, but more on a business aspect. I am a Graphic Designer and I also use an Intuos Tablet for illustration / Animation graphics and Design, however, the IPAD 2 has a small amount of artistic illustration apps. which is horrible! The touch screen is great, but I use the Bamboo Stylus Pen because I don&apos;t like smudges on the screen, but the Stylus Pens are too big! It&apos;s like using a crayon on the screen. I don&apos;t like the fact that the IPAD 2 doesn&apos;t support Flash. It&apos;s ridiculous, everything is done with a flash interface these ... days so why not include it? I don&apos;t like that you cant customize your app icons, or your interface. Most apps cost money but don&apos;t necessarily do as well as the free ones. I here a lot of people bashing the Samsung Galaxy and giving praise to what they think is a Godly tablet, the IPAD 2 is not! It&apos;s a simple tool for business owners and or web browsers with limited capability. I would recommend this product to others, but if you are looking for more options, customization, browser ability, business ability, and artistic ability, I would also recommend a Samsung Galaxy. For some, they said the Galaxy lost power after a couple hours, well that&apos;s because the batteries for any electronic device are never fully charged out of the factory, and ALL forms of platforms are subject to factory defect, if that&apos;s the case, take it back n swap it out for a new one. If you don&apos;t know how to use it, don&apos;t even bother with it, it&apos;s too advanced for you. Anyway, the IPAD 2 with all of it&apos;s personal faults is still a good play around gadget, I would also recommend the Galaxy. Happy hunting and God Bless.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SwedishChic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing 1080 screen resolution!

Cons: It could have better sound quality, but you could always hook it up to speakers.

This is the first Apple item I have purchased. I must say it is much more user friendly than PC&apos;s. You just charge it up and go, it was so easy! It is great because it is so light and portable. It is just the right size not to cause eye strain, such as using a cell phone would. I love my first Apple device. I am a fan! I paid $499 and have already received my investment back, due to it&apos;s lightweight and take it anywhere capability. The 1080 screen is amazing! The IPad2 is small enough to put into a purse, even if inside a case! I am currently job seeking (like so many other people), and find this device to be quite advantageous. This baby gets 5 stars f ... rom me! Love it!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nissi67</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful product, wonderful price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Best value for money, a number of devices in one.

Cons: Does not come with instructions, Best Buy store employees are horrible at explaining things.

This product is wonderful! I am sure we can use it for more than what we do, but this is great! We were looking for a new laptop and to find that this is a phone, camera; Still and video, a computer, all wrapped in one. The value is excellent. Great addition to our home as far as electronics. It is also fast, lightweight and long battery life. We are able to control household devices, use with the wireless printer and with our beautiful big screen Aquos television. It took 4 Best Buy employees to help us turn it on------ very curt, know nothing, non customer service oriented employees. Thanks to 1 VERY, communicative, profe ... ssional young man with common sense to help us with our first Apple product.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Elhoosier</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What an excellent product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight and portability.

Cons: The price.

After having our Ipad for 2 weeks I&apos;m already happy I didn&apos;t wait for the 3rd generation to come out. This is such a light weight device and with the extended battery time there is little to no need to carry the charger to wifi hot spots.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ETSN87</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Yet another great Apple product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It works exactly as well as I thought it would, the only drawback is the price commanded for the brand. The dual-core processor and multi-touch screen make for an exceptional experience. I would suggest getting a good pair of headphones, as the built-in speaker isn&apos;t the greatest. The battery life is fantastic! On a cross-country flight, I watched a movie and spent the rest of the time browsing the web and still had over half the battery left.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>iddles</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love the size and how easy it is to travel with

Cons: fingerprints on the screen

So easy to use and great apps for everything. Nice to travel with. A laptop is to bulky and a pain to have to unpack to go through security. Light weight and great price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>maggotbrain</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nothing special, returned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery life, portability

Cons: Price, lacking basic functionality

I got the iPad for testing purposes for my business. It&apos;s a nice tablet, but not worth $500 in my opinion. The battery life was great, animations and transitions were smooth, and it integrated well with my email and remote desktop environments. The small size and portability were definitely nice features.

Features that should be free, like printing, cost a fee to buy the print application. I might have used it like a laptop to write and send emails, but there should be more functionality built in for it to be able to fill that role. It became frustrating as I felt like I was being nickel &amp; dimed to get beyond the device&apos;s basic capabilities, which should be included at a price of $500. I can e ... asily afford it but the principle value is not worth it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>George2319</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really enjoy it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen, speed, quality, battery life, apps

Cons: Price, no flash

I love this thing and all it can do. I do really miss the flash and wish Apple was not so stuck on themselves, but I am learning to deal with that. The quality and screen are awesome. It is easy to use and the apps to choose from are amazing as well. It is pretty fast on internet, but I was surprised it seemed the same speed as the HTC flyer that I returned to get this Ipad 2. I guess I though it would be faster with a dual core and the HTC running on Gingerbread. It is more than I wanted to spend, but by far is the best quality and bang for the buck. I like the 5.0 update and instant messaging. Now I text my daughter when I am out of town on business and she can text on her ipod and she thinks that is coo ... l. I hope Apple can continue putting out as good of products without Steve.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AJ13</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet availavle</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, great battery life

Cons: Price

Was shopping between Android tablets and the iPad 2. Decided to go with iPad because it is easy to use, has millions of apps, and will work with my existing iTunes library and account.

Also, it was hard to decide between the many different Android tablets because they have different features and I have seen both positive and negative reviews for almost all of them.

I would recommend the iPad to anyone who wants an easy to use tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DirtyDogg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Welcome to the Pad Wars</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease and portability.

Cons: Price is a little high.

Another winner from Apple. Love the screen size and remarkably easy to use. Kids love to play games on it and gives me the opportunity to catch up on my email with out having to plant myself in front of a computer for hours on end. Outstanding!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kibbles</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exactly what we needed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, useful

Cons: Expensive

We needed this for out son, who has autism, and cannot speak. The apps for kids with disabilities are FANTASTIC. Does more than the medical devices that cost thousands more. Works great, battery power is great, and for someone with the cognitive difficulties he has, it&apos;s been so intuitive for him to use. A real game changer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mikedqt2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for all my business and leisure needs</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The compactness, power and camera

Cons: keyboard which is ok after practice

I&apos;ve only had this a few short months but it&apos;s been a great value for me. It sure beats hauling around a 7# laptop. The camera and video have amazing clarity. I vacationed in Italy in July and between myself and my daughter we took over 1200 pictures and several videos. Everyone that we showed them to could not believe the quality and all of them said &quot;you took the pictures with that&quot;. If there are any drawbacks with the camera is that it does get blurry and grainy when trying to use the zoom or in a dimly lit room. The keyboard takes some getting use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrTdawg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ipad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: screen size, lots of apps, battery life, ease of use

Cons: price, no micro SD card slot for expandable memory.

The ipad 2 is my first tablet and i must say i shopper around for awhile before i bought it. The first thing i must say about it is that the batter life is excellent. I think i get very close to if not the full 9 hours of heavy usage on a full charge. There are only 2 downsides to this product: the lack of a micro SD card slot and of course the price. Other than that i would highly recommend the ipad 2 to anyone in the market for a tablet with the cash to spare.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>srszee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, needs more apps</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, battery has a long charge life.

Cons: Price, needs more apps available.

I LOVE this iPad! However, the set up instructions are vague or non-existent. You have to sync it to your computer to get iTunes, etc., and I wouldn&apos;t have known that if my son hadn&apos;t told me. Also, it needs more apps, especially for games. I have a lot of games on my iPhone, like Bejeweled and several card games and none of them are available for the iPad. I wish it was less expensive. I keep thinking for $600, I could have gotten a laptop or desktop with more capabilities (not a Mac, though).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>rc310</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overall good solid product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Solid Performance

Cons: Camera picture quality, no back button

Another overall good solid product from apple.
My only complaints are the cameras produce sub par picture quality, at this price point I would expect a quality camera. Also I wish there was a dedicated back button.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>OMICRONIX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Portability and technology</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: EVERYTHING

Cons: PRICE - THCIKNESS

Battery last for 1 day 1/2 of constant use with our baby ( videos ) . Easy to use interface, lot of apps of any kind.
Great Pictures...
Great for Books..
Great for IT ( Support online ( teamviewer, remotedesktop ) )

Disappointing on : No Flash, No HDMI, No USB,
But its Its a Great device .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>KYReviewer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome product that needs to be widescreen!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, easy to use and set up, convenient, very portable, sturdy, extreme battery life, and MUCH MUCH MORE!

Cons: Fullscreen ratio instead of widescreen

This is an absolute great buy. The product does everything expected and more. I have put this little machine to the test; running tons of apps and it just doesn&apos;t slow down or lock up! The iPad 2 is definitely efficient. Of all things, my favorite feature is the mail client. I check all four of my e-mail addresses now because of it . . . Constantly checking them because it is made so conveniently. On top of this, the battery life is freaking insane! I use the iPad heavily, such as playing movies and games, and it always gets 10 or more hours.

My only problem with the iPad 2 is that it has a 4:3 ratio (full screen ... ). HD Widescreen is what is the most practical and this product should have such that. Apple really dropped the ball on this feature.

However, the negativity ends here. I love using my iPad 2 (64 gb)! It&apos;s the most fun and convenient device I own! I used my laptop all the time and my iPod was practically connected to me, but now my iPad 2 takes the place of both. The others have landed on the back burner, iPod in the car most of the time and the laptop to sync the iPad and type school documents.

The iPad 2 is definitely worth the price paid!!! :)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ehvee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for non-techie people!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: So easy to use and fabulous picture quality. Long lasting battery.

Cons: No complaints so far but then &quot;I&quot; haven&apos;t really had much opportunity to use it. :)

Bought this for my husband. He is NOT tech savvy. He loves it!!! He has barely put it down since I bought it. I mean that literally.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Free1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The iPad 2 is an excellent tablet and easy to use!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use and great value for the price.

I was interested in a tablet to use as an electronic reader and looked at all of the tablets. I decided on the iPad2 because of its outstanding features including its high resolution, size and weight. I highly recommend it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>childatplay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ability to grab wireless signal disappointing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: limited ability to hold wireless signal

Cute machine. Great screen clarity and color. Long battery life. But I anticipated a main use would be to stream from netflix in bed. The ipad can&apos;t seem to hold the signal from there. My laptop has no trouble. Disappointed. So much so that I would return it if I could.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SDThinker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen size, weight, functionality, easy to use, great battery

Cons: The Screen gets dirty quickly, thats about it...

Being an average consumer of Apple ie. iPod Classic, iPod Nano, iPod Touch, I decided to try something bigger, since I wasn&apos;t ready to get a 2 year contract on an iPhone, I decided to keep my Android and get an iPad. This is perfect for browsing the internet, emailing, seeing images as well as a variety of Applications (I mainly use the free ones). If you already have a desktop and want something mobile, this is the solution for you. This by no way will substitute a desktop or a laptop as it does not have the funtions of saving in external thumb drives nor does it have a CD Drive. If you can email anything with WIFI then this can be your solution. Would ... I buy this again? Yes, no matter what the competition says the style and quality of Apple is not reached.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>gman192</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I enjoy my IPad2!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Style, ease of use, user interface

Cons: A bit pricey, but it is an Apple product and that means the best.

I hesitated paying the $499 for my IPad 2 at first, but I love the flawless integration with my Macbook Pro and IPhone4. Everything works so smoothly together. I am anxiously awaiting the IPad3. If you are on the line between the IPad2 and another tablet computer then go with the IPad2. The operating system is superior to any android tablet on the market. The user interface is very user friendly for the beginner and the novice alike. I love the size, portability, style and relevant usefulness of the IPad2. I have friends with other tabs such as the Samsung Galaxy tab (Android) and my IPad2 outperforms it in every area.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>GBaldwin3821</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not Bad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Software, Graphics, Speed, Apps, Battery life(10hr)

Cons: App store prices, Charging time

Just bought my first IPad and for the most part I&apos;m impressed. The only thing I have found to be a problem is the apps. I found almost every app for the iPad is great but almost every app for the iPad cost money. Other then that the graphics and incredable and the running software. I think it is a little over priced but well worth the money. I would not suggest buying this if you are planning to use for extreme business stuff and matters of that sort but other then that it&apos;s great for travel and school/college. But likewise I think apple hasnt done half bad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>edxfs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Tried every tablet...iPad2 is the BEST!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sleek, stylish, easy to use, apps and more!!!

Cons: Price! And I hope not to see iPad3 soon!! Grrr!

I tried HP, Asus, Motorola and Acer tablets, returned all and settled to iPad2. Apple perfected the wonders of owning a tablet!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Love to travel 18</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Glad I Waited....................</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>to buy the Ipad 2. I loved the Ipad when it came out; played with it in the store and contemplated buying it then. But I held back, as the first model of a new item tends to be buggy, and the price was outrageous.So, when the Ipad 2 came out, I decided to go for it. The price had come down somewhat, and it was getting rave reviews. Like many others have mentioned, this almost replaces my netbook. (Don&apos;t have a laptop; just a desk top.)In fact, I am deciding whether to take this to Europe in October on a pleasure trip and leave the netbook behind. It&apos;s that good.Super fast response from one application to another. Pictures I downloaded made me gasp. They look like you&apos;re actually standing a few feet from the object in the photograph. Battery life time is great; I spent a whole day playing w ... ith it and didn&apos;t need to recharge. And, as mentioned, it&apos;s thinner and lighter. There are many stands out there, but I haven&apos;t found a need for one. It also does not generate the heat that a laptop or netbook do, so you can truly use it on your lap.Yes, it does show fingerprints. However, I keep nearby a small micofiber cloth wipe (the kind that comes with many pairs of eyeglasses) and just wipe it down as needed.My only complaint is email. It was difficult to load my primary account, as it is not a prominent company, and had to use the Other designation and fiddle with it for awhile. And even though Apple says that all emails will be synced and delivered at the same time, I have found that I have to click on to that account to get that email. A minor annoyance, but even so. If I hadn&apos;t had the problem with the email, I would have given this product five stars.And, of course, the Apple apps!!! What&apos; not to love?!? Thousands, and they will sync with your Iphone (which I don&apos;t own =(( . I had one regret--that I owned a Kindle and now would need both that *and* the Ipad (Apple pushes its&apos; Ibooks format.) But, low and behold........I search the apps and found Kindle!!! It seamlessly downloaded all of my former purchases, and offered me three free books to try out! So, shall I sell my Kindle? Hmmmm......I am extremely happy with the 32GB, which is plenty of memory for me. I don&apos;t download videos or do business work on the Ipad. You may want to switch to the 64 GB if you do that kind of work. [...]I have been happy with the Wi-Fi only. There are so many internet cafes these days, both here and abroad.Another concern I have re: bringing this to Europe is that it is so new and probably has a greater than normal chance of being stolen. It *is* registered to me, with a password, and an autolock after five minutes of nonuse. But hey, thieves are not the smartest people alive!!!Unless you think that Apple will come out with another version in a year (wow!! that was fast!) I would definatly purchase this item right now.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SemperFidelis11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Meh</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Graphics, easy to use, and amazingly fast.

Cons: the camera, no flash player, and no usb inputs.

i think that the ipad is great, but due to some hiccups, i have come to regret buying it.. the camera could definitely be alot better, and could come with a flash. and also the flash players really need to be avalible to really function everything on the internet. other than those three problems, i think its great, and if your really just looking for something to use for business, not for complete internet usage, or videos on youtube. this is a great buy. its incredibly fast, the graphics are better than my HD tv, and its multitasking system is great. it also doesnt take up alot of bandwith on your wifi connection that would normally make everything else slow. its easy to wo ... rk and great sound quality. i think that you should maybe look at laptops or other tablets first until your commitment is solid. and make sure your willing to spend big bucks.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ipodfan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Another Great product from Apple</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, good price for it&apos;s size

Cons: Most I-touch apps (games) don&apos;t fill up the screen.

I&apos;ve been on the fence about the i-pad2 for awhile because I use my laptop primarily but with my friend&apos;s opinion, the Best Buy and Apple sales staff I couldn&apos;t pass it up. The screen is clear and the set-up is just like the i-pod touch. Surfing the web is easier to do than an i-pod touch and playing the games are much better (because of the size of the screen). The only minor complaint I have is the games I bought for the i-pod touch come out the same size (3 inch viewing screen)to play on the i-pad. The games are playable but it looks like you&apos;re playing on an i-touch. So I bought the i-pad version or HD games to get use of the full screen.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>norgester</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome, yet not quite the cat&apos;s meow</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Display quality,speed, slick design, apps

Cons: No Flash support, hard to browse apps

Absolutely beautiful display, highly responsive and versatile.
Netflix and Xfinity run flawlessly with great picture quality.
Taking some time to get used to the OS, have to close a program to open another. Does&apos;t multitask very well. The apps are fantastic so far, but the Android market is much easier to browse than the AppStore. Their problem is they make so few apps for tablets. (Which is why I went with the iPad) Seems like you have to know exactly what you&apos;re looking for to find it at Apple. But how do you really know without seeing everything? Also the WiFi reception is weaker than than the Xoom. Had to buy a range extender to get a signal in parts of my house, where the Xo ... om had no issues. Lack of Flash support makes absolutely no sense to me. What is Apple afraid of, being perfect?
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>gk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good but not great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The product is good. But not powerful. I would prefer a laptop as I am still not comfortable using tablets. I play games and read news on it. Its sleek, small and light, and the battery is fine. very flimsy..scared that it might break. Apps are great but if u wanna buy a lot of deem, shell out a lotof money</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ShiftTab</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Abt</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MC979LLA - Apple iPad 2 With Wi-Fi 16GB In White review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Display,Sound,fun,App store,Simple,Sleek,Easy to Browse,Size

This is a must buy. The reason why it&apos;s not available anywhere is it&apos;s because it&apos;s in such high demand. Yes the camera is kinda minimal, but for standard video chat, it&apos;s not bad at all. I&apos;ve had it for over 3 weeks and can say that it&apos;s not bad. This is what the iPad 1 should have been and I&apos;m glad I waited a year so that I could purchase the 2nd gen.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechMan2010</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>iPad 2 = Revolutionary, Magical, Slim, Speed X2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Dual Core Speed, Display, Graphics, New Design, Slim, Smart Covers!

Cons: Camera; otherwise nothing!

iPad 2 is a definite buy and here&apos;s why:
Speed times 2 over the 1st generation iPad. iPad 2 beats everything my iPad did when side by side tests were compared.
Iron Man 2, the most intensive game I have, loads slowly on iPad but not on iPad 2! Dual core really makes the difference.
Graphics are definitely improved in EVERYTHING! May not have retina display but very close. Everything is brighter and more colorful.
Slim size!! iPad 2 is incredibly slim compared to the already slim iPad.
New design! The new design not only makes iPad 2 more attractive but also easier to hold in any orientation. New design and combined lighter weight equals a much more fun exp ... erience.
New color. The iPad 2 is awesome in white (you may think differently).
Safari has definitely been improved and is extremely snappy, as is everything on the iPad 2. Of course a slow internet connection might not help you see many differences. Fast internet and the new iPad 2 is definitely a good combination.
Camera is the only downfall to the iPad 2, but I really don&apos;t think many people will be pulling out the iPad 2 to take pictures because they already have something they use. Camera is just a small enhancement that makes your experience better. Serves its purpose.
iPad 2 has Facetime if you didn&apos;t know.
Smart cover and the iPad 2 were meant for one another!! Check out my review under the blue polyurethane smart cover for an extremely detailed review.
My opinion, Apple has made revolutionary changes to the original iPad and they will stay ahead of the market.
Definitely worth upgrading from 1st generation and if you are on the fence now is the time to buy.
Demo one today at Best Buy!
GREAT FOR HIGH SCHOOL OR COLLEGE STUDENTS!! GET KEYNOTE, PAGES, &amp; NUMBERS! (Equivalent of Microsoft Powerpoint, Word, and Excel)

A side note: flash is not supported. This is not new news!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AniOSDeveloper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>iPad 2, from a developer perspective</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: faster, lighter and more capable than the first iPad

Cons: camera&apos;s tend to be grainy in low light conditions. A flash would have been a big help here.

I purchased the iPad 2 on friday the 11th not because I wanted it but, because I needed it to be sure my iOS apps would work as expected
on the new device.

I was not disappointed. The iPad 2 out performs the original iPad
by a wide margin. Nearly 200% greater execution speed, double
the available RAM, a built-in gyroscope and dual camera&apos;s are major
improvements over the first iPad which I also own.

The thinner design and more flattened back are nice but the real
benefit of this new design is the improved audio quality from the
built-in speakers. It sounds more life like, more bass than th ... e
previous iPad.

So, why only 4 stars?

Apple said that the multi-touch gestures 4 and 5 finger gestures, would not appear in this version of iOS nor the new iPad 2. Unfortunately, that turned out not to be true. Those gestures are present and will be troubling for users who leave them on with some apps. Such as Garage Band, where it is common to use multiple fingers at once. Swipe up with 4 fingers and the task pane shows. stopping your app. Swipe left or right accidentally with those same 4 fingers and it switches between apps. Great right? maybe, unless you were in the middle of something and not expecting the change:)

For those constantly harping on not supporting Flash, get a clue
people, Flash is old technology that never worked reliably. Adobe
has NEVER delivered a fully functional mobile version of Flash and
likely never will.

All in all, Apple has hit a home run again. Great design, great implementation and managed to maintain the same price point.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrGameItUp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The ipad 2 is amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Slim profile, amazing design, great price, battery, Fun Fun Fun

Cons: needs better cameras

The new ipad 2 is simply amazing. The new ipad is so slim and appealing. This device looks cool and sleek. The added cameras are great additions although the do look grainy on the ipad&apos;s large screen. The photos do look pretty good when you print them. The A5 processor is so fast. Facetime is really cool and is a great feature to have on an ipad. I think everyone could use an ipad and enjoy owning one. Great Job Apple!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>bettercameras</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I think I will wait.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Rear case, overall design, feel.

Cons: CAMERAS, size, no SD slot, speaker (should be speakers)

OK, I am not an owner, I do own an I pod Touch 4G. I did spend a lot of time using the I pad 2 and comparing it side by side with the original I pad at Best Buy. Cameras are the biggest disappointment. Front camera was good enough for the job it is for, at least for the Face Time sender. I could not compare what it would be like on the Face Time receiver with another I pad 2, probably very grainy on the full screen. The rear camera was a big disappointment, especially on stills. Very grainy, of course I realize it is not meant to be used as a stand alone camera, with mega mega pixels, but the pics are so bad, I wouldn&apos;t even want to show them to someone standing next to me, le ... t alone print them! The video is better and I could accept that, but if they ever improve the still, surely they would also improve video. Again, I know it is not meant to be a great camera, but why even have one on the rear if it is gonna be as bad as a $15 web camera. You don&apos;t need a rear camera for Face Time. Everything else is a nice improvement over the original, i.e., speed, weight, thickness, etc. Even with the thickness and weight reduction, which is very obvious when compared side by side, I would prefer a smaller version, say a 7&quot; diagonal, a lot bigger than I pod touch, and a little smaller than I pad with a much improved camera, front and rear, and an SD slot (not for storage, but for maybe moving those improved camera stills and videos). The back cover is a work of art! Perhaps some of my wishes will come true in the Ipad 3, which I am willing to pass on this one and wait for the next one in September!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>thebread</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Enjoyable Little Friend</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simple

Cons: I would have loved to see that HDMI input get built in on this version! Darn.

I love my iPad 2. The reason why I love it, is because of the simplicity of the operating system.

I went into this purchase understanding and knowing that what I was about to buy, was not a computer at all. I knew that it wasn&apos;t even pretending to be a computer (like the competitors).

When you look at the specifications of the iPad and place them against any other tablet, you&apos;ll find that the others seem to be more impressive. What you don&apos;t see right away, is the functionality portion. Apple didn&apos;t put a touch panel over the top of a complex Windows 7 or even Leopard OS. They engineered a new way to compute altogether and succeeded. Plus it is extremely light weight ... for the 10 hours of battery life it holds.

Apple does not want the iPad to replace your computer (that is why you need iTunes to activate it). They simply want to make this a fun and interactive way to maintain your productivity at the moment in time that you need it.

With all of that said...the average iPad user will most likely use this lovely piece of machine to watch Netflix in bed or read an iBook while they fall asleep, but not before they check their Facebook! :)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lumax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No regrets!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality of apps, very fast response, safe app store/ iTunes, real light weight and easy to hold

Cons: Cameras, speakers

I love my iPad 2! I bought the Motorola Xoom last week because on paper it sounded pretty amazing. When I got it I was extremely disappointed. The apps force closed all the time and it had more glitches than you can imagine. I returned it and waited for iPad 2 to come out and I have no regrets at all. The quality of the apps are way better than the Xoom, and the iPad 2 is very easy to use. As you may have already heard the cameras really aren&apos;t that good, but who really buys a tablet for it&apos;s cameras? They are just nice to have. I also think they could have added better speakers. But overall I love it! The iPad 2 is still King of the tablets!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dddavis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>iPad 2 serves a purpose</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to set up and operate.

Cons: A bit cumbersome to deal with large documents.

Not as good as everybody thinks, but better than nothing. Next time I will probably buy an android, they are more cost effective. Parenthetically, Best Buy did not give me credit on my Best Buy Rewards for this purchase, which is quite a bit. Keep a close eye on Best Buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>wstone8800</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the iPad no matter what generation</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: So handy!

Cons: I only wish I had bought the built in wireless...

I love iPads no matter what generation. Handy and easy to use, I originally purchased it for home use and didn&apos;t buy it with the built in wireless. That was a mistake! If you are going to purchase one, spend the extra money on the built in wireless-it makes a difference!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Adam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is an truly amazing product. I had this for my wife, a computer idiot, and she enjoys using it everyday. It powers on immediately, long battery life, and easy to use. The only regret that Ihave is that I did not order a mode with at least 32 G to store more stuff. Thank you very much, Steve Jobs!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kate1968</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sometimes very stubborn to accept touch signals.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to coordinate all mailboxes.

Cons: Almost everything you might want to add will cost you.

I still prefer my laptop and my e-reader to the IPad 2.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>tbowers</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The iPad is great. My wife loves it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, easy to carry, tons of apps for it.

Cons: A bit pricey.

What&apos;s left to say that hasn&apos;t already been said? Apple products are trend setting and innovative. Easy of use is the best in the industry and their quality is up there too. Their products are a bit more pricey than others, but as they say &apos;you get what you pay for&apos;.

The iPad is a great substitute for performing computer tasks like checking email, browsing the web, and playing some games. It is light, the size of a book, so it is easy to take with you almost anywhere.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>borzoiowner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great, I should have bought it 2 years ago.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Take it on trips instead of laptop, long battery &amp; versitile

Cons: nothing

Purchased to replace Nook for reading but it does so much more. Search the web, emails, games, weather, maps and so much more. Long battery time makes it great for trips. Easier to use than a PC. My next computer will be a Mac.. The price is the same everywhere but with BestBuy you get rewards points.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fashionista925</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing product for an outstanding price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use, portability, screen resolution, battery life

Cons: Nothing - It couldn&apos;t be more perfect!

Just bought this about a month ago and haven&apos;t been able to put it down since! I got rid of my 6.5 year old iMac for this since I&apos;m in graduate school and it has definitely served me well. While I miss having a desktop, I haven&apos;t missed a beat thanks to the iPad. I chose the iPad 2 over the new iPad because the small differences of camera resolution and screen resolution just aren&apos;t enough to justify the additional cost for the new iPad in my book. But, I am so happy with my purchase! Among the first of my app purchases was Pages, Numbers and Keynote. I totally don&apos;t miss Word, Excel or PowerPoint as I have nearly the same functionality, without all the toolbar clutter ... . I rarely have to charge my iPad unless I&apos;m using it heavily to keep up with text readings and articles or working on homework. For casual use (gaming, watching movies on Netflix), I usually have more than sufficient battery life. Like a mother with a new baby, I&apos;ve gone crazy purchasing covers for this thing - I love it just that much! Crazy, I know, but Apple products are just that good!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kikgal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Clarity of the screen

Cons: n/a

I wasn&apos;t sure if I wanted to spend the money on the ipad, especially since I already had a laptop. Was I glad I did!
The features of the ipad are great! Easy to use and understand and so easy to take with you. Wish I would have bought one sooner.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>LesleyG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love, love, love.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, can take it anywhere like Itay for 2 weeks, can print from it.

Cons: Breakable.

This is ny 2nd iPad, I dropped the first and it broke. This time I bought a Square Trade Warranty on-line which covers breakages, unlike other warranties. Price of warranty is reasonable. I just love the ease f using the iPad and the portability. I use it several times a day. Easier than trying to read the small print on my iPhone. Got Square Trade Warranty on iPhone too and my Canon camera, laptop and printer all bought at Best Buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>queences2002</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awesome device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: ease of use, great value

This device is awesome! It is a great addition for anybody who owns an iPhone, a Mac or any Apple product. It is easy to use and provides a great tool for student or any adults who need help.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SouthernGenie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the iPad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use

Cons: nothing yet

Had the iPad2 for 2 months and am loving it! Easy to use, great to integrate with my iPod even though I&apos;m not a geek. Love the apps. Great resolution. Great value for the $$. Decided not to go with iPad 3 and spend extra for 3G since I didn&apos;t want a data package anyway. Am happy with the resolution even though it is not the new retina display. Am very happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bigbike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does everything I need it to do</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to use

It&apos;s a lot of fun to use and taking pics and videos are simple. The only problem I have is that my rewards weren&apos;t credited for this purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SHAKEBAKE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Granddaughter loves the i pad2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to learn how to operate. Keeps my 7 year old granddaughter busy for hours.She has taught me so much.

I am very happy with the i pad 2 it keeps my granddaughter busy for hours. Takes great pictures, lots of apps. light weight and easy to navigate. We went on vacation from San Antonio to New York and i wanted something to keep her busy and what a great surprise , she stayed busy while traveling on the planes. She is very pleased with it and so am I. Nice gift for her</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MAB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to Use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: light and user-friendly

Cons: there is no back button, what&apos;s up with that? and No flash on the camera

This is a great for everyone because it&apos;s easy to use, lasts for hours with a charge. Light and easy to carry. Many of the apps are free although I find sometimes just going to a website is easier than the ap. I find it weird that there is no back button, I looked and looked and looked than found out that yes it does not have a back button, well unless you erase everything. Also I was very excited about the camera only to learn that it does not have a flash and many pictures come out blurry unless in just the right light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bucknutty24</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great family device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to setup and use

Cons: Nothing

Our family loves the iPad 2. Everyone can use the device. Our 4 year old son is able to use the learning apps without confusion. It&apos;s just an overall great device. The battery life is really good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great product that is very versatile.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: A clear, bright screen. Ample battery life.

Cons: I haven&apos;t noticed anything negative.

The I-pad 2 is such a great product because it can do so much,just like a laptop computer. It is light and easy to carry. You can travel with it and find what ever you are looking for. Kids can play games on it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Genabug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to download Apps

Cons: Longer battery life desirable

Very pleased with product overall. Lightweight, easy to transport. Chose over laptop computer and am very happy with the decision.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mavelin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Absolutely love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Value, lightweight, easy to use, very useful

Cons: Wish it had more memory for the cost

Love the iPad 2. Can&apos;t complain. Wife and I both have one and haven&apos;t had one issue. Great piece of technology.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ChipperDi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the I-Pad 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use and light weight for people with bad hands!

Cons: Nothing i can think of other than my husband plays Angry Birds for Hours!

was easy to learn and use from the minute we took it out of the box. Sales person was wonderful and helped make sure that i was informed concerning everything about it. Took the time to explain everything in detail and was patient with me with all the questions i had.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Apple iPad 2 Wi-Fi 16 GB - Black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/8109144915694416954/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.11&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=yoCRULbVO8bXqgHOr4DYBA&amp;ved0CKUBEPQCMAA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Heat2004</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: ease of use / long battery life

Product is easy to use and requires no computer knowledge or directions. It is great as it allows quick access to check emails or access to the internet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

