<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EDUTablet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>More bang for your buck!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We bought this product to test against other tablets for use in education. We were looking for something light weight, responsive and easy to use. This tablet excelled in all 3 areas. The absence of Market was ok, as the AppsLib had most of the apps we needed. And Market was easily added when needed. The battery was better than average against the other tablets we tested. Sitting at idle for 8 with WiFi on, battery usage has only been 24%. Using WiFi on the device was simple and we never had a problem with signal strength. The tablet has Android 2.2.1, so web browsing good, especially when you add on flash. The storage on the device was good for our application. But the included microSD slot is a plus for personal use. Some of the cons were the lack of USB port for connectin ... g devices, like some of the larger tablets had. The screen size was good, the picture was crisp, but there was a glare when used in direct lighting, as to be expected. We never had any freezing issues, but it can be laggy at times when opening apps. Over all this is a very good device for the price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>6 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Smangione</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An economical, durable tablet that functions well.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>An excellent value for a durable piece of technology.

Battery Life

Battery lasts 8 hours with heavy usage. With the sleep mode, the battery can last 12-14 hours.

Processing Speed

Surprisingly fast for the price of this tablet.

Weight

Lightweight for portability. 

App Availability

Android compatible so you are able to download many Apps.

Design

Simple and elegant. 

Durability

Durability is excellent as the main user of this tablet is my 12-year old son. It passes all that he thows at it from a durability, ease of use and processing aspect. Highly recommend this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>npv76</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Fast, convenient, stylish. The sympathetic screen. The powerful battery. Support USB-host. (It is possible to connect the mouse, the keyboard, an USB-disk). Perfectly approaches for viewing of films. A loud and pure sound. A convenient folding support...
In general - the balanced product of the European quality at the price of the Chinese anonymous products.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pachydermus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic tab and media powerhouse</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought two of these, one for myself and one for my wife. I opened the first one and upgraded the firmware right away. Big mistake. It got into a reboot loop. Returned it but kept the second one. Still haven&apos;t upgraded the firmware on it, and it runs like a dream. I love that it has 250 gigs of space for a decent multimedia library on the go. And it can handle any format. A far cry from the Ipad 2 I let my kid play with. It also works brilliantly as a UPnP media server on the LAN. It prints wirelessly (get an app to do it from the Android marketplace). It works great on HDMI out with another Android phone as a remote (Archos app on the Android store). I have a VPN running on it. It streams Netflix and YouTube out to the TV. I Remote Desktop into my machines on the LAN. I stream media in ... to it from another UPnP server at home. It connects to my network shares. You get the idea - I get a lot done out of this little bunny. The size of the screen is ideal as an eReader (I&apos;ve got around 8000 books on it across Kindle and ePub). The colour screen is perfect as comic book reader (I&apos;ve loaded around 1000 comic book archives). Battery life is decent. I get around 6-7 hours on it watching movies and surfing the web. Screen resolution is the bare minimum for decent viewing. Don&apos;t go by the fanboy nutcases who think you need an aircraft grade aluminium body to qualify as solid build - My kid&apos;s dropped the &apos;other tablet&apos; a couple of times and given it dings in all the corners. This machine feels solid when you hold it. But don&apos;t drop it - it has a hard drive that could break. Looks very cute. USB host mode works brilliantly. I&apos;ve attached other hard drives (with external power) to it and they work like a charm. Haven&apos;t tried HIDs, so can&apos;t say if that cheap keyboard leather case on that popular auction site will work on it. Front camera quality is embarrassingly bad, but until there&apos;s a good Facetime equivalent on Android, it is irrelevant. Lack of rear camera doesn&apos;t bother me. I use a DSLR. Do I care about Android 2.2 vs. Honeycomb? Not really. I wish Android would step up their game on the apps in the market, rather than worry about the OS version. All in all, keeps me entertained and informed on the go. Integrates with various devices on my home network and entertainment centre. Love it. Can&apos;t imagine how I did without it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sdew42</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 250gb Internet Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I recently purchased the generation 8 Archos 70 Android tablet and am initially pleased with the performance of the product. The price, combined with the 250gb of storage, made this the perfect option for carrying all my media- music, videos, photos, ebooks on one device. After reading the Archos forums and getting the full Google market working, customzing and downloading apps works flawlessly. The tablet multi-tasks pretty good with some slight lag jumping between apps, you can feel a slight vibration from the HD as it is retrieving the app data. The battery life is around 6 hours of typical use. The device is pretty slim and light considering it has a hard drive. I will admit I was torn between the 250gb and 8gb flash/sd version, but for me it was more cost effective to get the hard ... drive version and have all my media in one manageable place.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>spatch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 Shines with Android</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been an Archos fan for a few years, going back to the Gen6 line-up. While Archos has always been renowned for making great media players, previous devices could never be described as sleek, internet-connected tablets. All this changes with the new Gen8 range of Android slates, and in my opinion the Archos 70 is the pick of the bunch. I was growing weary of the iPad&apos;s size &amp; weight as my primary, everyday device, and the Archos 70 has arrived as my saviour. It is light as a feather and I am able to hold it in one hand for a very comfortable viewing experience. With an expansive 32GB memory card onboard, I have been enjoying the larger capacity for movies &amp; TV shows available to me for my bus rides to &amp; from work. This 7-inch form factor really hits the sweet spot in ter ... ms of screen real estate -- perfect for casual browsing &amp; email, ideal for everyday media needs. Archos has really benefitted from the open-source Android platform, creating an almost stock Android experience with their own custom media capabilities added to the already impressive mix. Video &amp; music playback is superb, with full 1080p playback available and an HDMI out port to connect with your HDTV or projector. If you don&apos;t like the built-in functionality, there&apos;s the wealth of apps available to try in the Market, many of them free. For the first time, Archos has equipped it&apos;s high-end models (the 70 &amp; 101) with capacitive screens, and while not quite as slick as the iPad, the responsiveness is impressive. Recent updates to the firmware have really tightened things up, and now the hardware is truly allowed to show it&apos;s potential. If you&apos;re familiar with how Android smartphones respond to touch &amp; swipe gestures, you&apos;ll be familiar with the Archos screen. The only downsides for this product relate to power. Android is by default always connected, and unless you carefully manage your running apps the battery will run down in about 7 hours with moderate use. I have to keep WiFi &amp; Bluetooth off when not in use, and an app kill switch downloaded from the Market has helped greatly reduce power consumption. In addition, the device cannot charge via USB -- it must be connected to the mains using the supplied power cable. This is not a deal breaker, but it can be a problem if I&apos;m at work and running low on juice. Finally, the position of the power button (used for on/off &amp; sleep) has often caused me to press it by mistake. Not too bad if I&apos;m browsing the web, but disastrous in mid-video or gameplay. If you hold the device like a mobile phone it makes perfect sense, but is illogical when held in landscape like a tablet should be held. Despite these minor deficiencies, I cannot recommend this device highly enough. Even those friends of mine who are disciples of all things Apple have been impressed with the Archos 70 due to it&apos;s lightweight appeal, and all agree that the 7-inch screen is the perfect size for everyday portability and general use. At this price point, it is hard to argue that this is the best value Android tablet available today.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Android Fan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Update immediately</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Compatibility; Easy To Read; Compact Design; Attractive Design; Good Screen Quality

Cons: Poor Software Bundle; Short Battery Life

This tablet is not for the faint of heart. If you are techie, this can be a wonderful tablet. You can back up a whole computer on it to take with you. But, do not buy this if you think it will be a wonderful product straight out of the box.

It is flakey. You need to immediately up date it. It doesn&apos;t have initial access to the full android market. You will have to side load the market if you want it. It also has serious battery drainage issues. Some people believe the last update fixed it. But, it didn&apos;t fix mine. Mine finally started rebooting itself for fun. I&apos;ve mailed it in for warranty service. While I haven&apos;t rec ... eived it back yet, they claim they are replacing it.

I would not discourage someone from getting it if they find a wonderful price. But, have a realistic expectation.

I am putting &quot;no, I would not recommend this product to a friend&quot; simply because I don&apos;t think most of my friends would know how to deal with it. But if you are a techie in search of a new toy, go for it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BrewTonyA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Machine</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a very nice machine. The display is great. The one of its problems is the microSD slot is on the side of the machine and is too easy to eject by mistake. I would also like a little longer battery life. On the whole it is well worth the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Linda</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It ain&apos;t Windows</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I naively assumed this would work like Windows. BOY oh boy, was I wrong. BADLY wrong. This fights at every step. Some of it of course is operator error. I am familiar with Windows - not Android. I am pretty good with computers, but not with this. Okay, with that said, let me try to be fair. I really like the small size. Easily fits into my purse and will fit into my camera backpack when I travel. I HATE the Archos customer non-service. They have ignored any written requests for help. Their on-line chat was hugely inadequate. And the unit did NOT come with a converter from mini-USB to full size USB. What the ???? This is unbelievable. Now I have to go out and get a part to allow me to do the main thing I bought it for. Not Archos fault, but another hugely annoying fac ... tor is music I legitimately purchased from ITUNES won&apos;t transfer to MP3 and thus to this player. Grrr. I can pay to have them converted, but I paid to buy it for my personal use. This is also for my personal use. Having a very difficult time figuring out how it works. How do I get my documents over there so I can read them when I am away from home (and away from wi-fi). I tried Google Docs. What a waste of time (and it loaded them Z to A instead of A to Z. Tried another Docs program, but can&apos;t get the docs over to the tablet - yet. When I do play music, the sound is just fine. Far better than I would expect. Battery life seems poor - but this is par for the course with tablets. I guess if you are familiar with Android you could possibly like this. I DO NOT.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this tablet to replace my broken iPod Touch that I&apos;ve had for almost 2 years now. I was originally looking at getting one of the 4th gen touches but after a little bit of shopping I came across this for the exact same price, there was no competition. Just the right size to fit in a guy&apos;s jean pocket, and still a 7 inch 16:9 display for movies. Also, the kickstand may seem unimportant, but trust me, you will use it. The battery life is AMAZING, lasts all day. On occasion it will start to slow down if you run 10+ processes on it, but that is expected. Unbeatable for the price. Buy it, you wont regret it. Putting on Google Market is a piece of cake.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good enough for me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Once received the product was impressed by the speed of it. Graphics, touch screen, and updating was easy. The only complaint is the web cam, not the best picture. Once you put the android market on, the friendlier everything is to use ( have an android phone). Battery life is good if you put the brightness on low. Trying to get an adopter to see if the usb will work with camera and things. Would recommed anyone to buy one if looking for at an Apple ipad for half the price and tons more memory.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jamestown Judy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I really like this tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I really like this. It is so much better than the other brand I bought and sent back. There definitly is a difference in tablets! This is easy to use and program. The picture is clear and there are lots of apps to chose from. My email come through great. It picks up the internet signal from my network easily. I really recommend this if you don&apos;t want to spend a fortune for the expensive ones and don&apos;t want to have to sign up for cell service!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Hammer!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exactly what I was looking!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The ARCHOS 70 Internet Tablet was excatly what I looking at a reasonable price. The size is perfect for holding onto, it&apos;s not to heavy and the images are displayed super clear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mom of Teens</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not impressed with this product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design

Cons: Difficult To Set Up

I bought these for my teenagers and these did not do anything that was discribed they could do. They would not load up apps at all. We sent ours back as both teens were unhappy with them. Sellar is great and returned them in a timely manner.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JR, not Ewing</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos Support Bad, B&amp;H Support Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I do like the tablet overall for the functionality and storage. I intend to use it to store digital movies for my son when we travel. However, the bad part is that on the second day of use, it stopped booting up. Upon pressing the power button, the splash screen displays for 3 seconds, then the power cycles on it and the process repeats. I tried getting an RMA through Archos, the manufacturer, but they are very slow to respond, ask the same questions multiple times and do not read your feedback when you inform them of what the results are from your troubleshooting steps. The good part of this is that B&amp;H is VERY responsive and offered up their RMA service immediately to do an even exchange. Within 5 minutes after the call, I had an RMA form and shipping label to print out. I am ... hoping that the replacement will work as it should so I don&apos;t have to deal with Archos again. The only reason that I am not recommending this product is due to the poor customer service of the manufacturer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Urlilkitten</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I specifically bought this Archos because I hate lugging a laptop through the airport. The size &amp; weight are convenient. There are many apps available and the 250 GB really sold me. The iPads don&apos;t even have that much GB and they cost 4 times what I paid for my Archos. I can download and read my e-books on the plane, or listen to my downloaded music, and still keep up with e-mails from work when I get to my destination. Great product and an awesome price that I couldn&apos;t find anywhere else.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Eaglewarrior</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Grreat Device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the device To hear Music Watch Videos Surf The web Play Games Great to manage The Battery life is not good battery power drain very fast. Speakers sounds Great Sound HDMI video output is great to watch my videos and play games on my HD TV</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Allen the traveler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This thing rocks. The 250MB storage + Droid OS is phenomenal. With the nook software and lots of ripped movies, the archos is the best traveling companion you could ask for. I can&apos;t say it completely replaces a laptop...just not enough horsepower but the battery life, great screen, and ridiculous amount of apps makes it a great alternative. The 7&apos;&apos; screen and a kickstand make it a godsend for international flights. It&apos;s a little pricey but well worth it. It&apos;s pretty much the same screen size as a kindle (roughly the size of a steno pad). I did drop mine off my desk and it survived the 3&apos; impact with no bruises or performance issues, so plenty rugged. If you have a Droid phone, there is no learning curve, the menus are exactly the same. My only issue (minor as it is) with the archos ... is that the droid app lib program (application market) is horribly slow and freezes too many times. Unfortunately you have to live with this glitchy proggy if you want droid apps. Other than that, roses.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Diamond</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One of the best device out there.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s one of the best tablet on the market out there at the present. If Archos improves the battery life, weight, and the CPU of this device, not to mention its external access/ports, I would upgrade to its future version. For now it is one of the best tablet out there.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Julius</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You can&apos;t go wrong.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The first Archos 70 I got serves it purpose. I needed something that is light enough for me to hold on to for an hour or so to check something quickly (while lying in bed, getting dressed, etc.) like emails, facebook or even read documents (you need to download an app) without paying for an ipad price point, then this device is for you. I do have a desktop, laptop and a smartphone, but sometimes, you gotta have something in between those and this is the one that borders the smartphone&apos;s portability and a laptop&apos;s functionality. This is also the first Android based device that I own but I must say its not that hard transitioning from Apple OS to this one. I tried it out with video streaming within my network from my WHS and I&apos;m quite impressed. I thought a device this small would choke ... down but it beats my expectations. It does have its own drawbacks too like occasional slowness and flash crashes or slows down considerably. Overall though I&apos;m satisfied with my purchase and for the purpose that I need, so much that I bought a second one for my wife. It&apos;s not an ipad nor a galaxy tab but with its low end price I&apos;m sticking with what makes sense and does exactly the same thing. Besides, after a few months, new devices will come out and I will most likely buy a new one. At least I saved some more money to buy a new and better product. Things I like: - HDMI out - expansion slot - mini USB - decent battery life Not so great but satisfied nonetheless: - Slow to respond at times.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ASLgirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had this tablet for over a week and i am very impressed. The sound quality is amazing. The storage capacity is more than i should ever need. I use it mainly to watch videos in american sign language and the built in kickstand is great for allowing multiple people to view the screen. Sometimes i notice a little lag in the processing speed as the hard drive revs up but it hasn&apos;t been a problem. There is a very slight vibration from the hard drive that is picked up by the webcam. The battery life could be better but so far it hasn&apos;t died on me when i needed it. Otherwise i can&apos;t think of anything negative to include in this review.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Alternative to IPad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Runs on Android 2.2 (Froyo) and has access to the Android Market. Allows Flash content, IPad dose not! Like the 7 inch size better than the 10.1 inch IPad. Has a front facing camera good for Skyping. Uses WiFi connections a/b/g/n but does not utilize the 3G or 4G. Capacitive touch screen is sensitive and the resolution is nice. For the price this is a great value and so far a solid performer for me with internet browsing and answering my emails and watching videos. Hook it to your computer with the included USB cable and it comes up like another drive and you can easily add your own content, like music and movies. Can expand the 8GB by adding another 32GB via the Micro SD card slot.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Reggie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This tablet is great! Everything I have tried to do on it has worked. I have watched video on youtube, played a avi movie, installed google apps, downloaded and played numerous games. I have used as a book reader using the nook and kindle apps without a problem. I have had a occassional problem dropping my wifi signal at home but did not have that problem at my son&apos;s house. Overall u cant go wrong buying this tablet. It is the best value out there.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JmSeattle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>ARCHOS 70 250GB 7 MULTI TOUCH SCREEN</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to use, very powerful, lots of storage in the 250GB hard drive. Connects fast and easy with the web, automatically retrieves your emails, is good with games, sound good with earphones or plugged into an amplifier. The picture and video screen quality is amazing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim E</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Got what I was hoping for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My tablet experience started with a Nook Color, that experience lasted about 3 hours. I then realized that the Nook Color was not a full tablet like was advertised. I returned it and bought this tablet (Archos 70 IT) after about a 1/2 hour I knew I found what I was looking for. It is a full Android tablet. Google Play accessible. Every app imaginable in your hands. Online video quality varies. Processing speed can be a little slow due to programs running in background. I still have some things to learn. Camera quality is below average, I don&apos;t use it anyways. I use this tablet for browsing the web, checking email, and reading the news. It does all these perfectly. I still have to try the HDMI connection to HDTV. Hoping that will be a huge bonus. Battery life is great. 32GB storage card is ... huge for music and videos. Overall a great buy for me, very pleased. Glad I went through B&amp;H to buy this product. Great timely service and dependability.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>oldtimer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I am very computer illiterate and the user manual does a very poor job of explaining how to use the unit and what different symbols on the screen mean. I was hoping to be able to watch video clips on sites like ESPN or You Tube but have not been able to and can&apos;t figure out if I even can on this unit.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Clyde The Glide</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for a reasonable price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have had mine for about six months now. I take it almost everywhere I go. It has a fairly large screen but is still small enough to fit in your coat pocket. Can&apos;t do that with an iPad! It also has an incredible amount of memory, four times as much as a top-of-the-line iPad. I find it great for web browsing, e-mailing, book reading, etc. while on the go. If you are not near a wi-fi spot, you can bluetooth it to your cellphone and use your cellphone as a modem (of course service charges will apply for this method of web access). I have downloaded an app called Office Suite Pro to it which allows me to work on MS Word, Excel and Powerpoint files while on the go. It sure beats lugging a bulky laptop computer around all the time. Only one flaw with this tablet. I have found when usin ... g the Sound Recorder tool, the recorder picks up the intermittent whirring noise of the hard disk drive spooling up and down. This can be rather annoying when you review the recordings. This wouldn&apos;t happen on a solid state drive tablet. The iPad does have an advantage in this regard. Overall this is a very good tablet and it&apos;s the ideal size. By the way, I&apos;ve written this review using my Archos 7o tablet.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SGT Martinez, Alfredo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70it 250gb review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this product for listening to music,watch movies, research parts for my job (being in the military and deployed it comes in handy with technical manuals) and of course games. All of which i have had no problems. The 7in display is amazing i would say perfect size. The 250gb hdd is great limitless for everything. It is not bulky or to heavy. And being that it is android there are so many ways to customize it. I honestly have nothing to say on the not so great side. Just be patient with your product with a little research and tinkering you can do just about anything. Thanks Again SGT Martinez</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Promangan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>one of the best tablets in the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This tablet is lightweight with long battery and good touchscreen and does not get hot. There is no Arabic language on the system. A bit slow when many tasks are on. Better to close all tasks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pbeaumont</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this with a very specific idea: backup of my pictures while travelling. The capacity offered is incredible, and the price really interesting! And you even get access to Wifi while on the go! Only drawback: The USB port is not a standard USB, but micro USB. Therefore, I needed to buy a USB host cable (very cheap) to be able to connect my camera, card reader and external HDD. I will leave in a couple of weeks, but I am very enthusiast as I feel this will soon replace my Laptop/Lonely Planet guide/Mp3 player combination!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>justjill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Android Function Great, Battery Terrible</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I want to love this device, but the battery life is so terrible I can not use it enough to do so. As far as I can see the Android Tablet function of the Archos 70 (250GB) is great, responsive screen/keyboard, everything you could want, especially at this price point. However... The battery life is TERRIBLE. I have yet to be able to set it aside in standby and come back later to be able to turn it on and use it without having to charge it again. I have to micro-manage wifi use to save battery life and am constantly watching the battery monitor icon plummet. If I can do basic wifi (non-video) access for an hour, that would be a looong session. So far I have had to pretty much use it plugged in. I&apos;m considering returning it only because of very poor battery life.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Grama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for everything I do</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Not a problem with the pad, just frustrating when I can&apos;t pick up a WIFI connection. Battery has a short life....can&apos;t use it more than a few hours at a time without recharging. Enough G&apos;s to download everything I can think of!! Surprisingly good sound system. More apps than I could ever want. Wish it had Mah jongg dimensions...my favorite game.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daniel2126</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Internet Table</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After comparing all devices on the same price range I made a good selection. The screen is responsive and the Android application are fantastic. I&apos;ve downloaded as many as I wanted at no cost and uninstall is pretty easy. Very handy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dan the Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bought it for daughter now I want one!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We were looking at e-readers for my daugter (who loves to read) when we came across this. Pros- Great Price! Cheaper than Nook Color. Android 2.2 OS. Does everything! Plays many different formats of video including .mp4 and .mkv. Front facing camera for web chats, doesn&apos;t come with &apos;Android Market&apos; but can be added very easily so then you have access to every &apos;app&apos; imaginable! So now my daughter can install any e-reader program she wants and not be limited (Nook, Kobo, Kindle, etc). Has Bluetooth and Wifi so you can stream video through home network and can connect to your cell phone to access the internet anywhere! Cons - Space is a bit limited, it&apos;s expandable via SD drive but I gave it 4 out of 5 stars due to the fact that there is another version of this tablet that comes with a bui ... lt in 250gb HD, (more $$ but you&apos;d have to go buy an 8-16 gb micro SD for this one anyways). My daughter filled the internal storage with apps quite quickly, surprisingly quick actually.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Weasel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This one has everything you need</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The price on this tablet from B&amp;H Photo was to good to be true. The Archos 70 internet tablet with 250GB has more storage then the average person would ever need in a tablet and the apps available for a Android system are terrific. I feel like I&apos;m sitting at my desktop computer. From the ability to load my movies on the hard drive to being able to show them on my friends and families TV sets it has it all. The best part is I can put it in my pocket and it&apos;s have tabelt will travel. I don&apos;t usually write reviews but this product deserves it. Couldn&apos;t be happier</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Capt. Brewha</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You Won&apos;t Regret Having 250GB of Storage</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Nice unit, not without its flaws, but solid and a good value. The standout is the 250GB; you can carry your entire music collection, coded at high bit rate and still have space for lots of movies and books. And with this player, movies are worth having. The web community is good for help and info; check out forum dot archosfans dot com. This unit is best described as a super iPod touch, without the ease of iTunes or Apple jail. More screen, more storage and full Froyo support. Be prepared to do some workarounds. Some computer literacy is needed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ralph</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cool Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Well first thing i must say is thank you B&amp;H...great prices, ease of access [...] I received my ARCHOS 70 INTERNET TABLET in perfect condition. I mostly want it for entertainmet purposes, Video, Music, Internet etc... I got it out of the box and turned it on. It started right up and in a few minutes i went thru the set up wizard and it was ready for use. Wifi worked great, internet pages loaded pretty fast. I checked the Firmware and it did need the update to 2.2 FROYO. I went into settings...FIRMWARE UPDATE and DONE in minutes. I been using it for everyday now for about a week and its great. APP Market works great, great 7 screen and videos play just fine. Touch screen is responsive and switches from landscape to portrait just fine.The front web cam works fine. Apps download fast and ... i even set up my private email and my GMail.Fring works and i was able to Video Chat with a friend. Once i downloaded Flash player it worked great. Webpages with flash content can be viewed with no problem. Great device....Great price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ladyoak</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>just what i needed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i needed a product that has lots of memory. this was perfect since i have to use quite a few different American Sign Language videos. I was able to download without a problem. Easy to use, with excellent video quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daviator</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t believe all you read from Archos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>This was a great idea... a tablet with a decent screen AND a hard drive and USB connectivity to connect directly to your camera. But... You must buy the USB host cable separately to connect USB devices. It is NOT a standard USB cable and is NOT sold by Archos U.S. In addition, USB devices will only connect if they are low or self-powered. Does not charge via USB port either. Also, RAW files cannot be seen/copied from digital cameras. Archos claims dual boot out of the box. Not true. Plus, if you download and install that option from Archos it will void your warranty. Bluetooth tethering does NOT work on most phones. The latest firmware has caused battery issues for my A70 and has actually fried some USB ports on some A101 tablets.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You can take it anywhere... almost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I initially got this product to use as an e-reader for PDF documents, but before long I found that its just as powerful as my laptop and a whole lot lighter. The size is just right for reading and seems to have all the bangs and whistles. The really great thing is the ability to research what I&apos;m reading without having to go to a computer. Although, I haven&apos;t spent a lot of time with all the apps available, all that I have installed work well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Swtgaks</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy and fun to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>this tablet is really good for the price

Battery Life

Wish the battery would stay charged longer , but when i&apos;m around a plug i just plug it in ..

Processing Speed

seems to load fast enough for me and my books load fast on it 

Weight

weight is very good , light enough to be convient but havy enough to be sturdy 

App Availability

love the amount of apps it has in google play ,i have found many that i enjoy using .and all for free so far

Design

the design is good just one thing would make it better ..place the camera in the middle of the framing somewhere

Durability

have had no problems with the durability...i use a soft tipped stylus most the time so have no scratches at all on my screen</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>normsy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not bad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>This is decent: It does what my Android phone does, but on a larger real estate. And yet, it&apos;s light and thin. But the hardware can&apos;t handle the sofware, and so it often freezes up. It also loses the WiFi signal easily. And the bezel gets easily discolored from the oil on your hands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: little sluggish, no Android market, battery life just barely adequate, screen resolution could be better, doesn&apos;t charge via USB. Pros: 250gb (!!!), light, excellent form factor for long commute, Android, any video format. In my book pros beat cons hands down. And did I mention the price? Got it as a birthday present from my wife. As soon as I showed it to her - I saw so much excitement in her eyes, I just had to give it up. Now she is pretty happy watching movies and reading books on the long bus commute. Now I am waiting for her birthday to get one too. R.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WAHOO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use the archos 250gb to store sign language dvd&apos;s great and easy to down load information. great easy ways to search for products on the net. at this time it will NOT play videos on youtube,there are no drivers for flash video. the camera amd video are good items on the archos as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MnM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos Tablet a hit!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It does everything we want. We like the size more than the iPad. We are still getting to know the device (and tablets in general). The list of quibbles below may have as much to do with our lack of familiarity with tablets as with the device itself. *The music player is unintuitive. our main impetus to buy this was to replace a dead mp3 player. It would be nice to have a more logical music program on the device. Perhaps we can download a different player that will suit us better. *What&apos;s up with the apps library? What&apos;s the point of not having direct access to the Google Android Market, let alone other markets? We have already learned of a few apps (google sky map, e.g.) that we cannot find in the only apps marketplace we have access to. *wi-fi range could be better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GHan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos has raised the bar with this one!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The tablet give you total portability around the house browsing the web. The display is very good. The resolution is sufficient for most web content. It suffers a little when viewing small text but not a deal killer. Would like the memory to be a bit more - 512 as opposed to 256. Loading pictures and thumbnails seems to be a little bit on the slow side.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kazuma</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Having purchased Archos 70, I&apos;m using mainly web surfing in my home. Very comfortable and smooth. It&apos;s tough thing taking time for the gallery app(pre-installed) to read some pictures on SD card. Battery is not provided though USB cable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kosovo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice for music movies and games</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Web Browsing; Operating System; WiFi; Easy To Customize

Cons: Battery Life; Button Configuration

is good but appslip is useless i had to Download google play 

good for Downloaded movies (Downloaded bv pc )

heats up fast</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cujo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My Best Purchase Of The YEAR...!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Best product for the BUCK...!!! Needed the 250 GB storage because I&apos;m a music buff and have over 40G of owned music alone. Can&apos;t always count on WI-FI: Travel alot and needed to have music and movies ALWAYS available</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MaggieB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for my use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I decided on the Archos 70 tablet because a)I didn&apos;t want to fork out $500+ for a tablet; b)I knew I wouldn&apos;t be using it for gaming ..other than word games; c) needed a tablet to take with me on a trip to Australia for 2 months and d) needed something to replace my old palm pilot for contacts and calendar. I&apos;m delighted with it..and am thinking I may use it for more purposes than originally thought. I have limited technical knowledge but was able to sync up very easily with google calendar and contacts. Getting Android marketplace downloaded was time consuming..but very easy once I found out on line how to do it. This is really beneficial as the apps from AppsLib loaded on the tablet are pretty limited. I did buy a case with keyboard as I found the on screen keyboard rather cumbersom. ... ..I have longish nails and so this may factor into the awkwardness.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>foyrbye99</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love,Hate affair with Archos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Operating System; Easy To Customize; Web Browsing; WiFi; Screen

Cons: Difficult To Customize; Accerometer; Battery Life

This is not a table.It is a Media Player ,first.
Like I said with Archos it&apos;s a love,hate relationship. I had the Archos 504,5,5IT,and now the 70.So I think I have some say on Archos. With every new Archos there is a learning curve to operate.There seems to be no uniformity in the Archos models operations. They do the same things,but differently. Maybe it&apos;s because the&apos;re improved. But what is the same,from the Archos 5,5IT and 70,is how bad the accelerometeor works.When you rotate from horizontal to vertigo.They need to improve this a lot!Also album art display is bad on there units.What&apos;s up with that!I never had this problem with other MP3 player ... s,why with Archos!
I have used all my Archos for media mainly,and this is it strength.This beats having a bunch of DVD&apos;s along traveling. Also the hard drive storage is a big plus! Archos 5IT 500gbs. and Archos 70 250gbs,wish the 70 had 500gbs. Apple can&apos;t beat that!It seems with every newer model the web browsing gets better,a plus,also.So it&apos;s not all bad.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>archos 70 8G</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought Archos 70 for my daughter. This tab is very good for my daugther,fast and good screen,she use the tab mostly for video. Finally, the services is Amazing,It took three days to get a tab from the USA to Iceland.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cesdaa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>IT´S A PROBLEM</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: NONE.

Cons: THE SELLER IT´S A GHOST

I PURCHASED THIS TABLET IN NOVEMBER 2011 BY MARKETPLACE IN THE BESTBUY WEB PAGE AND RECEIVED ONE WEEK AGO . IN THE WEBPAGE SHOW , 250GB IN HARD DRIVE AND 16 GB IN MEMORY FLASH TOO IN THE BOX SHOW THIS, BUT WHEN I TURN ON THIS TABLET DON´T FOUND THE HARD DRIVE ANYWHERE AND THE MEMORY FLASH ONLY SHOW 1.5 GB . THEN I GO AT THE BEST BUY STORE AND THEY CAN´T HEL ME BECAUSE I USE ONLINE SERVICE BUT THE GEEK SQUAD CHECK THE TABLET AND CONFIRM , THE TABLET HAVEN´T HARD DRIVE , NO MEMORY FLASH OF 16 GB ONLY 1.5 GB . AND DON´T CONECT WHIT COMPUTER BY USB DON´T WORK THE CONECTION.
I WRITE AT ANTONLINE AND FILL A FORM AND THEN THEY ANSWER ME CANT´REFUND THIS TABLET BECAUSE I INSTALLED OR ACTIVATED THE SOFTWARE , BUT I ONLY TURN ON, AND WHAT SO ... FTWARE I CAN INSTALLED IN ONLY 1.5 GB, I CAN´T INSTALL THE UPDATE FOR ENOUGH SPACE. TOO THEY CHECK AND TELLME THE ITEM IT´S THE CORRECT ANY TO DO ,AND . I TRY REGISTER THE TABLET IN THE WEB PAGE OF ARCHOS BUT THE SERIAL NUMBER DON´T MATCH WHIT THE KEY PRODUCT. AND THEN I PAY 279 USD FOR A TABLET WHIT 250 GB IN HARD DRIVE AND 16 GB IN MEMORY FLASH AND I HAVE ONE TABLET WHIT ANY GB AND ONLY 1.5 GB IN MEMORY FLASH. BEST BUY CAN´T HELP ME , ANTONLINE DONT´WAN´T HELP ME . I DON´T KNOW TO DO.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HeavenzSapphire</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A excellent tablet for what is needed.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: No problems; Have the apps I need; WiFi; App Availablity; Web Browsing; Operating System; Works great; Fast

Cons: Could use improvement; Good but not great; Speaker Quality; Battery Life

The unit is a great addition to my learning about tablets. I have worked with computers for a number of years but only recently started becoming familiar with tablets. I am a fast learner and want to be able to enjoy whatever I have taken time to invest in. This unit basically provides all that I am looking for, it&apos;s not a PC but provides a base for me to use to load up on movies and music, that being the large hard drive. Moves a little slow, but after working with computers I realize that it is the amount of stuff added that does that. The ram could have been better, but overall, this ... is a doable unit that I am pleased with.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>daydream337</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stay away from it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight

Cons: Fragile screen

I liked this unit but never even got to explore it&apos;s uses because it broke after one week of having it. It wasn&apos;t dropped or hit, the screen just cracked and is not covered by warranty.Buyer beware the lcd screens are not covered at all and cost almost as much as buying another unit to replace. Zero stars for this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>marcoperla</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great easy to use product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Let&apos;s start of that I am a big fan of Archos products. This is great because it allows you to connect to other devices and it also allows you to connect to flash drives so that you can work on your documents portably.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MLB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t want ipad - Great Tablet!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great tablet. It does what you want it to do. I use it for ASL videos and it works great. Has a lot of apps to choose from as well. It&apos;s not an ipad, but it runs real close to it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>scg66</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We purchased 9 of the Archos 70 Internet tablets for use at our medical facility. Our clients enter information into a web form for a short survey. The units have worked perfectly and the bigger screen has made it much more friendly to our consumers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jeanj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is ok</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>It is ok but I was shocked to find I could have purchased an Archos internet tablet, just as nice but a different model for $100 cheaper at Best Buy. I was not happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LFP guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Device for the Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have a Droid so getting use to the android interface was very easy. The device is very slick, thin, well lit. Connecting to wifi was effortless. I have not be able to enable tethering through my phone though it works well with my laptop. Lots of forum on Archos to help. For the money i would definitly recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>blueb0ttle2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good value for money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have handled ipads quite often, and I find this device is just as capable, and more portable. It suits my needs well, and is excellent for browsing.Advice: Download flash 10, and look for the Google Marketplace app on [@], since appslib is somewhat limited.Also, get realplayer for android.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>chibiko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great: this product has every function</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Used for social contact including web browsing Unlike other tablet products curently in the market, archos 70 internet tablet puts all means of communication and human activities in a nut shell with their applications almost free to download.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lucentsteve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not what I hoped for...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>First off, I think it&apos;s a nice product and it&apos;s well constructed with some good features. But after having it a few days I realized I had to return it. Main reasons being that it couldn&apos;t access my yahoo e-mail account (it actually has a warning message that it cannot access all yahoo accounts when you try it set-up your e-mail) and second I couldn&apos;t access my website because it doesn&apos;t support Flash Player 10. I&apos;m sure it would be a nice addition if you&apos;re just looking to surf the web and play movies, but I wanted just a little more out of it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Not quick to Buy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Little Device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great for checking emails, and the perfect device for traveling. More than enough space for all your music and movies. Great play back quality. External speakers not great, but do the job.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>David</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple to Set up and use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The pad was simple to get going, mostly because I already have a droid phone, one suggestion to users would be to load the main android store if you want access beyond just the Archos listed apps</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I Like it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I searched a long time to find a tablet device that didn&apos;t require a montly fee, had WiFi, could work as a reader and had access to apps. I haven&apos;t figure out everything yet but so far, I&apos;m really pleased with it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DaRyZe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Loving my Archos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love the 250g hard drive and all the space it allows for my photos, video&apos;s and music. I also love that is has a usb port so that I may easily transfer anything to and from my computer. I love that I can have the market and android apps on it as well. It does more than any other tablet I&apos;ve seen and I love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>abee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best budget tablet ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i start using this product just 1 week ago.just to let you know i already have samsung galaxy tab,apple ipad and notion ink&apos;s Adm tablets too. but this tablet is the one which i use most out of all,reason its cheap,its fast enough,its loaded with latest android OS(2.2.1) and battery back up is very good too. i use it very rough may be bcos its cheaper than all other tables.its bearing all my misuse and still going fine.its in my bag with out case.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Justin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 is worth the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great tablet for everyday use and as an ereader. I added the real goggle marketplace and installed all the missing apps. It is slow at times due to the lack of system memory. Just have to kill apps running in the background to get back the speed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jgnsc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this for my son for Christmas and he loves it! I only gave it four stars because it only has a camera in the front so its hard to take a pic of something. Haven&apos;t figured out how to download skype,it says it cant support it,and we haven&apos;t found a texting app yet. Other than that no complaints. I would love one for myself! ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Peaches</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Light-weight powerhouse</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As an IT Manager I have used and supported many handheld devices over the years, but this is the one I bought for ME. It is small enough to fit comfortably in a woman&apos;s hands and yet stores all our music, pictures, and a load of android apps. It boots quickly and videos/music load fast. It does take a while to catalog all my music files and the hard drive hums a but when it spins up. The capacitive screen is responsive. The soft keys do take up a bit of the screen lessening the display space, but it&apos;s still big and bright...even compared to my Droid X. Wireless connecting and internet usage is a breeze. One major drawback is that firmware upgrades (to 2.2 Froyo) wipe all applications and setups...wish I had known that before I loaded every app imaginable from the market (I installed the ... Google market first thing). Also, it would be nice to have a slot for an SD card. It can be a pain to connect to my computer in order to transfer music or pictures. All in all a great product, and I am pleased with my Christmas present to me. FWIW, this was written using the Archos.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sparky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>half-baked</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Instant-onFast web surfingCapacitive touch screenGreat as online photo viewerGood potential to be a google tv PC after acquiring usb host adapter, wireless keyboard &amp; mouse set and mini HDMI cable for direct hookup to flat screen TVUsb host adapter has to be sourced from foreign merchants, not available from manufacturer (major oversight from ARCHOS)Apps lib keeps on losing connection/crashing after installing latest firmware update (NOTE: wifi is stable)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jpminard</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Android tablets are getting better...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>This is not a tablet that will make you forget about an iPad, but it certainly is a step in the right direction, especially after you update to Froyo (Android 2.2).  There are a great many things to like about it (especially the price) but in order to get the full usability out of it you have to side load the regular Android macketplace.  It takes all of about five minutes to get to that point, but if you aren&apos;t a techie or savvy user then this device probably isn&apos;t your cup of tea.  The video playback is top notch, the capacitive touch screen is darned responsive (though once again, you wouldn&apos;t want to put it head-to-head with an iPad, but it is half the price) and once you get the Marketplace on it you can go nuts with the applications. I&apos;d say that if you were a tech person you&apos;d be pl ... eased as could be with in twenty minutes of opening and even happier as you don&apos;t have to connect it to a PC to start using it, it has several ways of loading data or connecting it to a machine and its a pretty fun device.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My husband uses the Archos 70 internet tablet for video, music and web browsing. It is faster than expected. The touchscreen is very receptive. An occasional delay after coming out of sleep mode. But overall, very impressed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>navydotz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great ipad/galaxy alternative</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>love the portability!!! fits right n2 my purse to carry around when running errands when in the waiting areas just whip out &amp; check email, play angry birds, check twitter instead of just twiddling thumbs wasting time</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KCS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 Internet Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The tablet is top of the line. Easy to use, quick, and meets the needs of a book reader with the functionality of a PC. This is a great tablet for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hpc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Good Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very easy to use. There is nothing bad to say about this tablet. It would be nice if it had a better camera. Otherwise it works great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Adam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 Tablet(250 GB)</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Overall good tablet for the price, not having a newer vers. of Android does limit the apps market.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roosterbyrd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for the Money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Easy way to tote stuff

Works fine for the low price</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lake forest joe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this tablet a lot..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Easy to use and understand Android OS and has a help app Every thing is great about it</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Be Kool</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet Ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful; Quality Display; Long Battery Life; Comfortable Keyboard; Quiet; Fast; Lightweight

One of the best tablet I have ever own.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymouse</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos - Good Tablet Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Good value for tablet. Read Android forums for support. Arctools helps with Android Marketplace.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>berniewood</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Although I am used to a Windows format, I find the product easy to use. There seems to be plenty of apps available and the wi-fi works good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CPOPEREZ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>FANTASTIC TABLET</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a fantastic tablet, not just for watching movies, you can surf the web without problems, it??s fast and has and appropiate size.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Vlad43</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Use more than a month. Works great battery long enough to travel.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Adrian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good afortable tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Good tablet for the price, android 2.2 pretty nice, screen respond really good</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tthace</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Cheap, Android, Looks good, has great battery life. Just remember that it does not have a usb hole so you need to buy a cable that allows you to seperately.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Criton</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Has a 250 Gig Harddrive

Cons: None

Best tablet besides the IPad</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>franks mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>we use it everyday for everything. So user friendly our 4 yr old uses it all the time for learning games and more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>moe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>250gigs in such a small body is amazing. I love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tablet Newb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Advice: Save some money and go for either the 10 Inch Version, or the 250GB Model, just your preference.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>robertadisessa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again and again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I like so much!!!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pepe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>very good product, i like, ai recoment i</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i use to streaming video, flash works great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>margirat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Some free apps bring pop-up ads with them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Moran</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>referbg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great product, great service!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MeatMan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great For Playing Games And Other Apps From Google Market (Once Downloaded) or Browsing Internet</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Android interface is great and very responsive. Only complaint is having to go through setup again after loading 2.2</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Archos 70 Internet Tablet 8 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/2056536557841999780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.17&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=mIKRUMObEMHIyQHysoCgCw&amp;ved=0CLIBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SilverSurfer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Archos 70 is awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The tablet is fun to use, stable, fast, and has met every expectation I had when I ordered it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

