<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ike58</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome business tool !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to learn. Intuitive. Quality machine.

Cons: No skype or spotify yet.

Love it! If you&apos;re mostly going to use a tablet for gaming, skyping, or spotify, (for now) stick with the ipad. But for $300. I got a smaller, more portable 64gb beast, which browses faster and organizes downloads better. The new os2 makes it easier to check email than my laptop, and it now supports android apps.

Graphics are awesome! Takes nice clean photos and HD videos. Sound quality is superb. I&apos;ve linked it to my home stereo system which takes it to a new level. Easily synced with my laptop to download Excel files. Easy to combine similar apps into folders on the home screen.

I prefer using the rapid charger (sold separately) as it has it&apos;s own
magnetic port which saves wear ... &amp; tear on the micro usb. Depending on what I&apos;m doing, the charge will last from 8-10 hours.
I put it on standby when not in use so the long boot-up is a
non-issue. Both online and call-in customer support is very good.
I had a battery issue with the 1st one I purchased, no prob exchanging it that week &amp; the new one worked like a champ.

I would like to be able to skype &amp; I&apos;m not sure that will happen any time soon. In the meantime, I can video call to my wife&apos;s playbook
when I&apos;m on the road.

This is really a business tablet that you can have a lot of fun with.
YouTube, Amazon, E-readers, Facebook are all supported. It has an
accelerometer for smooth gaming. I haven&apos;t even scratched the surface of what this is capable of !!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ralph0722</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: BB qnx and new 2.0 software

Cons: Power button failure , location of ports and buttons

This is my second tablet. Back in Feb I bought a Acer Iconia A200. Now in May I bought my PlayBook as a bday gift from me to me. BlackBerry did a amazing job with the PlayBook. The hardware is sexy and sleek, quality materials used, superb fit and finish, and feels great to hold. The new software 2.0 was immediately uploaded as soon as I started to configure the tablet. Qnx is amazing! Battery life is very good. Browser is super fast, speakers and super loud and clear. Screen resolution is crisp clear and sharp. App market is well behind the curb. No good apps at all. Now for the negative, this is actually my second PlayBook since the first one failed at the second day of ownership. T ... he power button and charging port stopped working. Got it exchange so I&apos;m hoping this one doesn&apos;t fail. Power and volume buttons are poorly located and they feel cheap in my opinion. Charging port is not in the best location also. So to wrap it up, the BlackBerry PlayBook is an amazing device. Smooth and fluid software, quality feel, superior browser, and sharp screen. But I&apos;m a bit wary about the buttons and ports not being reliable and prone to fail. I&apos;m very happy with my purchase and I will recommend this product to a friend.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>EDD28</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Get it before you regret it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Performance, Look, Easy to work with.

Cons: No memory card expansion slot.

I bought this for my wife birthday. I just play with it a little bit and i&apos;m impressed. Very fast tablet, good looking. For $199 you can&apos;t go wrong (Half Price of an Ipad and it is a good competitor). It has dual cameras, 1080P HD, GPS, WiFi.

To be honest, I was about to buy a kindle, but this unit does a lot more than just a reader. You can open word, excel, pdf, ebooks and whole lot more formats. The browser is good and you can see flash images and videos quite well. It does not have a lot of apps, but the average person just installed a few of them. Every day they include more and more apps (you can sideload some androids apps too).

Are you In the mood for playing games? y ... ou got it, because this device has a dual core 1GHZ processor of and one 1GB memory, more than many others devices.

If you own a blackberry phone this is even better, because you can use as remote control for presentations, as a keyboard and mouse for your playbook, also get internet everywhere through a process call Tethering using your data plan. All of this thanks to Bluetooth technology. For business people, you can open your emails, calendar and contacts from your phone with this unit using the bridge application.

It also have an HDMI port so you can watch videos, pictures and movies in your TV.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Flatscape</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Apple lover purchased and likes.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portability

Cons: Popular Apps

Get one. This is the most underrated tablet I&apos;ve used. It&apos;s size is perfect. Screen resolution is crisp. Lack of popular apps is Ok if you&apos;ve got an I-phone or hem-DROID. This is my first blackberry purchase and I like it. It&apos;s perfect for Web content consumption on a wireless network. Can&apos;t beat it for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jack03290</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does the job</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I can even edit Word and Excel Documents

Cons: Battery life could be better, more apps would be nice.

I looked at playbooks last fall and had a hard time justifying the price. Not because I didn&apos;t think that the product was worth it, but because I am frugal. So when I saw the sale (32 GB - 249.00) I went right to Best Buy and got the last one they had. I am not disappointed in the least. The picture quality, sound and ease of use are amazing. So was set-up. I took it out of the box, turned it on and typed in my WiFi password and it downloaded updates and then set itself up! I bought the tablet primarily for the four days a week that I spend a hour at a time on the treadmill and I dont want to watch the gym&apos;s TV. Unfortunately, as you&apos;ve heard, Netflix, XFinity and Hulu ... are not supporting the OS. However, I downloaded an app called &quot;Tablet TV&quot; and have found that there ae many sites out there that I can veiw TV Shows and movies. The promise of Android Player is encouraging. The OS update was a step in the right direction too.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>lungpai</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great hardware; bad software</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Hardware

Cons: everything else

I bought this tablet beccause I thought it would be a good buy vs a compararble 200 android tablet.

The good: great hardware. The screen is beautiful, and the build quality is strong. The resolution is wonderfull, battery life is pretty good, and the sound...is probably the best thing about this tablet. It has two front facing speakers which provide incredible sound for a tablet. The rear is some sort of matte finish plastic which could have been metal and it would have been better. The cameras are nice, and beat most android tablets in quality in this price range. The use of the bezel is unique and a nice touch. You actually use the bezel as a touchbotton by swiping.

Let me start by noting that blackberry users I have seen i ... n forums rave about this tablet and are able to overlook it&apos;s major flaws. This is either because they have not used a real smartphone/tablet or because they are blindly loyal to RIM.

Also, we got this during Christmas and I was under the false impression that the 2.0 OS was coming soon and would fix my gripes. I waited until today for that to happen (today the OS 2.0 was released).

The bad:
Hardware: while I have said that this tablet is very well built I need to clarify that it is well built for a $200 tablet. It beats the Pantech Digitals of the tablet world. That&apos;s not much of a barrier to break. Two major downfalls to the hardware are the powerbutton and the usb plug. They are very small and very weak and look like they would be the first things to physically fail this tablet. (We have used the interactive menu instead of the power botton just to avoid this problem.)

Software:
The OS 2.0 was released today and the ig news is: email and calendar. I know. Almost a year to get what should have been delievered in the first place. Other than some small graphic changes there isn&apos;t much to say about the new OS that I can see. The supposed &apos;android&apos; apps that were so promised are sparse and overpriced.

The OS is smooth and nice to use so this ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Keebler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Impressive tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The screen is beautiful, sharp and responsive. Nice overall size, and just a good balance between a small handheld device, and a laptop. Swiping from the outer screen perimeter is a smart and handy ability. Adobe Flash compatible which is nice, for those select sites that contain Flash content. Very easy and handy to transfer files to/from a computer in USB mode. I use that very often. Multitasking is terrific, and visually easy to manage. Very much looking forward to OS version 2, and hope that RIM and various other game/app developers continue supporting and moving forward. Overall...Very nice tablet and great deal Cons: battery life is pretty good... but could be better. And wish there were more Apps.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>amacrgv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Playbook great product when correct price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use and light weight

Cons: touch screen could improve

the first week i used it i felt like returning it. I felt it wasn&apos;t as responsive as i was hoping for. Now I have gotten more used to how to use it, including how to turn it on and off. If offers a lot when you can get it for $200. $500 seems way too high, for that an ipad would be the choice. I understand it is almost the only tablet that uses flash so you can see the internet like you do on a computer. 3 years ago i had a black jack smart phone with the fake internet, i did not like that at all. I like the touch to enlarge. The picture quality is very impressive. the games play very well, with moving the tablet to drive a car in one game. Sim city does not play as well as on a regular computer, but really n ... ot too bad. my kids love to use it, but i use it more then they do. It is really nice to hold while reading or in bed as it is not so heavy like a laptop. Strongly recommend for the right price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>littlejjam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice OS, quality display, and great speakers.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality product especially when BB had it for $199. :-)

Cons: If anything... lack of mindless apps... and no micro sd slot.

Great:
- Display quality (HD playback)
- Authentic windows explorer experience (not mobile explorer)
- Multi-tasking power
- Great (good lighting) video
- best speakers on any tablet I&apos;ve heard. Not just loud, but quality output and clarity. Mid - Mid-high bass got some meat to it.
- OS that just makes sense.
Good:
- Perfomace is on par with other Duel Core tablets
- Internet performance / speed on a N-router is good, not great. Wifi range is suffiecient, no drops or signal loss once in place.
Not so good:
- Limited to on board Memory only
- Less apps to chose from... not like android market or IPad app stores. ... r&gt;- No 9&quot; or 10&quot; version.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrGround</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product for use with BB</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Meets all my needs, great form factor/performance/hardware

Cons: Limited support by app developers.

If you are looking for a 7&quot; tablet and have a BB phone this is an amazing product. Yes, it does not have native email, but using BB bridge with a BB phone makes that totally unecessary. The size is perfect for holding in your hand, and the feel and performance of the device is outstanding. Some have complained that the power button is difficult to activate, and that is true - but using swipes there really is no need for a power button anyway. Even without OS 2 this product meets my needs, but the additional features coming this Feb will just make it that much better. Not a ton of apps available right now, but it does what I need/want it to do. By the way the video/sound i ... s incredible.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>NicholasMM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>very nice tab but falls way short on apps</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Performance, portability

Cons: very few apps, camera

Playbook is a great little tablet, the screen is very nice, UI is very easy to learn. I didn&apos;t notice any stutter and hang up while scrolling through screen/browser and has very smooth transition between apps(I think Playbook OS is better than android OS). it feels really solid yet light enough to be in your coat or jacket pocket. Music app makes it easy for me to import my library from itunes but no option for videos and its video player doesn&apos;t play DRM vids from itunes :( also the camera is not worth using at all. it takes very grainy, dark pictures and the colors are very dull and unsaturated. the main reason I only gave this tablet 3 stars is because there really aren&apos;t any apps in BB appsworld and the one ... s they have are expensive ie. there is no skype app, Googletalk, Netflix, pandora, espn, just to name a few. And what decent apps they have had cost me between 99 cents and $ 7.99. I would not recommend this product unless you have a BB phone because BB has a feature called BB bridge feature where it gives you free internet tethering with playbook and it also has a build-in BB face to face talk app such as skype and gtalk which works only with other BB devices.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tester1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Connection</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the Playbook!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been reviewing both the iPad2 and the Playbook. The Playbook is easily the better device, hands down.

The feel of the device is much better, more compact and easier to handle. The iPad2 just feels clunky and heavy. The Playbook will fit in the pocket of your jacket or such. No way that is going to happen with the bigger, heavier iPad2.

As for the screen and touch use, the Playbook is brighter, sharper and the control is much better. The one word I hear when I show comparisons is how much smoother the Playbook works.

The Playbook is much more intuitive. There isn&apos;t any real guessing about what to do. Everything you need will be from the pull down top screen, while apps are controlled with a touch on the bottom of the screen. No hunt-n-peck of where or what to do ... with the iPad2 - Touch the middle, the side or the top, maybe the bottom?

Setup of the Playbook is much easier too. Whether it’s the Bluetooth, Wireless, tethering, USB, etc., all easy to set up through the Settings menu at the top right. Best of all, you are free to do whatever you like and not hampered by iTunes.

Battery life is equal to the iPad2, no issues there.

Then there is the price. Why would anyone spend the money for an iPad2, when you can get an equally set up Playbook for $200 less?

The BlackBerry Playbook is the iPad2 killer. Period.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dubdub</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Surprisingly good for 1st generation</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen, speakers, size, inventive design

Cons: Software, lack of accessories at Best Buy

This is my first tablet purchase but I do have experience using iPads. I really wanted the power of a tablet with the size of an eReader and the Playbook fits that perfectly. The software is surprisingly reliable for being a 1.0 version but it is lacking features you would expect such as built in email and calendar apps (said to be coming this summer). The number of apps in App World seems to be growing quicker than I expected but we are waiting on bigger names to show up (Kindle by the end of May, Skype hopefully soon).

Pros: Amazing screen color and clarity. If you use a Playbook for some time and then look at an iPad screen you will notice that the iPad looks fuzzy because ... of the lower pixel density. Speakers are great for such a small device. The feel of the device in your hand is very solid. Battery life is pretty good. Flash runs well but could use some improvement. Bezel gestures are great once you get used to them.

Cons: Software needs some polish (mentioned before its 1.0), still waiting on some big name apps, waiting on the Android app emulator coming this summer, waiting on the email and calendar apps. Really all of the cons are around software, which can be improved with updates.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SouthLA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Hardware and OS, waiting a few apps.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Hardware, OS, Form Factor, Interface

Cons: Waiting some apps

I have been using my PB for a week, and I love it. The form factor is perfect. I was worried it would be too small, not the case (and I have middle aged eyes). The screen is awesome. The navigation very intuitive. The OS is responsive and solid. Let&apos;s talk about the supposed negatives. No email client. First there are ways to get your email. The bridge works well enough, and I am on AT&amp;T. Just because they don&apos;t support it, doesn&apos;t mean it won&apos;t work. I got the app from another source and it works perfectly on my AT&amp;T Torch. The Bridge Browser is very slow, but I blame AT&amp;T&apos;s horrible 3G network as much as anything else. It is really a farce in this area. Secondly, Outlook Web Access works perfectl ... y as well. So I have two methods of getting my corporate email. Those of you who are real blackberry users will realize that the BES server only allows one device per user. Creating a solution for that is in my opinion is the reason for the delay in an email client. Apps, yes there is a lack of apps. That will change. I am not a big apps user, but there are 3 or 4 that I would like to see ported to the Playbook. As an early adopter, I am used to waiting for perfection. Battery Life, it is not all day if you are using the radios, but I have never reached 50% in my daily (intermittant) use. No 3G, this is a real complaint, but it doesn&apos;t affect me. Until the carriers allow you to pool data like they do minutes, I am using a MIFI (Verizon) due to having multiple devices. If I had a contract on each, it would cost hundreds of dollars per month, with the MIFI, $50. Finally, if you are a &quot;Blackberry User&quot;, a &quot;Power User&quot;, or a &quot;Tech Nerd&quot;, you will probably like this device. If you are an Iphone user, a tech illiterate, or live for apps, it may not be for you.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RaycFL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good but not ready for primetime just yet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Blackberry phone integration, user interface, browsing

Cons: Lack of apps, expensive, unique charger

I have been mulling over tablets for some time. Considered the Ipad, Xoom, Viewpad, Netvertibles - looked into them all. They each have their own pros/cons but I decided to try out the Playbook (primarily because BestBuy had one in stock or else I probably would have gone with an Ipad 2).

Here&apos;s my assessment so far of the Playbook:
PROS
- Blackberry phone integration. This is a MUST. If you do not have a BB phone then THIS TABLET IS NOT FOR YOU. The Blackberry Bridge functionality is an excellent feature. Being able to use the BB phone 3G data at no charge is a huge plus. Also, I can see my purchased apps from Blackberry App world so I am assuming that you ... can eventually install them on the playbook w/o paying for them all over again (once Playbook versions become available - see Con below).
- Browsing experience. People complain that there is no built in email, calendar, etc but the BB bridge feature plus excellent internet browsing on this tablet overshadows those limitations. Browser works great and who wants yet another device to store email.
- User interface. Crisp, responsive and intuitive. I&apos;ve played around with Androids and the simple swipe up for main menu and swipe down for settings on the playbook blows away Androids in terms of simplicity.
- Battery life. Only have had it for a day but so far so good.

CONS
- Availability of apps. I read about this complaint and wrote it off that people were just being picky. Let me clarify for everyone - THERE ARE NO APPS YET FOR THIS THING. I mistakenly thought my existing BB phone apps would work - WRONG. Even the basic apps like Pandora, Skype, etc are not available yet for the Playbook. RIM says the Apps are coming but they better live up to this promise ASAP if they want to be a contender in this market.
- Size. The screen could be a tad bigger. Also feels solid, perhaps a bit heavy in relation to its size.
- Charging adapter. One of the reasons I bought it is that it has a micro USB charging port like my phone. ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brucetech</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Super easy, fast and very durable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: speed, price, flash

I read many reviews on this Playbook, I must say its the most underrated tablet in the world. It puts the other tablets to shame, The weight and quality are the best. Battery life is great and colors rock !. And it plays Flash.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>nickname27</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, easy, simple

Cons: Nothing that I know of

I had it for 2 weeks now and it is going great. This is a great product for a steal 200 bucks. It is fast, easy to use and a very low price. Fast Internet Speed and great camera quality. Great for all multi taskers. This also has great speaker quality. I would recommend to all. This is almost like an ipad but smaller. Best 200bucks I ever spend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JM21</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet for a good Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Graphics, Flash ready

Cons: Not great for beginners, limited Apps

I purchased this for the reason that it&apos;s very affordable. The first time I saw this, I fell in love with it. The resolution is really clear. Sounds are fantastic. And it can read Flash websites too. But I have to admit it&apos;s not really great for beginners. If this will be your first tablet and you didn&apos;t have any before, I recommend to buy Apple iPad instead. The interface of the Playbook is somehow confusing sometimes. And the Apps from the App World are not so many. There&apos;s no Yahoo! Messenger, there&apos;s no Skype. I dunno what else are not in there.

I gave 4 stars to this for the graphics, price, sounds and able to read flash websites (that iPads can&apos;t). Could have been 5-stars if they have ... Yahoo! Messenger and Skype. Hope this is helpful.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PlaybookEnthusiast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent piece of equipment!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything works and works well.

Cons: Nothing

Since purchase, the Playbook has become my most useful piece of digital equipment. It&apos;s the perfect size to carry around, and I use it for everything. It had a lot of nice apps installed when I first got it, and everyday they are adding more. The OS is beautifully designed (elegant) and a joy to use. I recently added an in-expensive app that allows me access to my home computer from any WiFi connection. I have a larger Android tablet, but I prefer the size of Playbook. It&apos;s easy to carry, and feels like a pocket book. I had to contact Blackberry technical support when I first got it, and they were great to work with, knowledgeable and patient. I am thinking that I would like to change my cell phone to a Blackberry so that I ... can take advantage of the Blackberry Bridge. The Blackberry phones will integrate with the Playbook. No Netflix (yet!), but everything else is perfect. The speakers are loud enough to watch streaming video without headsets - so it&apos;s great to use in bed for other streaming audio and video content. They have the best online support I have ever seen - you can watch an entire set of well made videos that explain every detail and feature of the unit. So it&apos;s learn how to get the most out of it. There&apos;s even a little free app that makes access to these inflectional videos part of your system.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>unclegigi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: performance, OS stability, battery life, did i mention performance

Cons: nothing so far

i purchased a kindle fire and boy was i upset with the device. slow, sluggish, stop. totally worthless. amazon needs to stop advertising it as a tablet. it is a reader. returned it and all my complaints vanished because i purchased playbook. what an amazing device!! superfast and picks up wi-fi no matter how weak the signal. apps all work just fine and with the recent addition of angry birds, i may have to buy one more for my daughter. the document handling capabilities are tremendous and the email client is superb as well as the calendar. it handles multiple browser tabs like nobody&apos;s business. i have owned android tablets and ipads as well, and i have to say for performance for the ... business world, this is the best choice anyone could make. If you want an overpriced toy, buy an ipad or galaxy tab. if you want a fully functional business device, buy the playbook.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great deal on Playbook</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Got a great price; not being tech-no savvy, still trying to figure how to bluetooth it to my blackberry. WIFI is fast though, and the screen resolution and performance are great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>badassbob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality and responsiveness.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, screen responsiveness.

Cons: Lack of apps/games available, app prices too high.

The BlackBerry PlayBook has a feel of high quality. The screen picture quality is impressive. Both cameras work very well, providing there is enough lighting. Indoor photos and video may be a bit grainy if there isn&apos;t enough light. Outdoor video and photo quality is amazing. The touch screen is fast and responsive.

The AppWorld store could use a whole lot more apps and games. The prices are a bit high.

At the sale price that I paid, this is a real bargain. At full price - maybe not so much.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>eraser08</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome tab</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price and really good to use.

Cons: Battery

It&apos;s much more convenient then the ipad and much smaller to carry around. A++++ and the graphics are more clearly defined.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mackee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent playbook</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good price

Cons: not too many free apps.

I love my playbook its because the price is too cheap but i will sure to you its nice and good tablet... The speaker is very loud, HD screen, the battery is great... The only thing i hate here is not too many free apps here... So when it comes to apps, Android is better... But other than that 4 Star for this playbook:)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>KTG2012</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent product for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I also own an IPAD 2, but for the price, functionality and features the playbook is definitely worth the money. It has mini-USB, mini-HDMI it supports flash and, if you&apos;re saavy enough, it can also be rooted to use Android-supported apps. Occassionally my browsing window will close unexpectedly though - not that often, but enough to be an annoyance. Sound quality and video are excellent. It also comes equipped with Word and Excel reader. I use it for work and for personal use. Lightweight and portable (almost fits in my back pocket). Plus, I&apos;d rather my daughter play with this tablet as opposed to my IPAD in the event she drops it due to the lower cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>route87</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good hardware, unstable software</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Value, sound, recording quality, interface, battery life

Cons: Unstable, memory leaks

This was on sale for $200.00 at a local Best Buy, and I was sold on it.

There is a tremendous amount of potential in this tablet.

The picture quality was so crisp and clear that it took a bit of getting used to. The sound is very sharp through headphones or the two built in stereo speakers. I don&apos;t miss my old SB Live! Card. It takes up to 1080p HD video with the back mounted camera. It also has a lesser camera on the front. I managed to get around a half hour of 1080p video out of it before it filled up all the 16 GB of memory. The sound recording quality is probably one of its best features, as it records in stereo! It picks up every little sound, and is good where you ... want to capture the overall ambiance of an event or concert.

I spent some time with the AppWorld program that came with it looking for any interesting apps I could come across. I was not happy there that there aren&apos;t any synthesizer apps yet like you can get on the Ipad and Android operating systems. But this is just the beginning, and I have heard that Android apps will be available for the Playbook soon.

The interface is great, and responsive to your finger&apos;s touch in less than 5 milliseconds most likely. Toggling through photos in real time is a breeze.

You can set up all your email accounts to automatically be checked on intervals by your Playbook. A little red blinking light will blink when you&apos;ve received new messages. This would be good for someone who is running an e-business, or needs immediate correspondence on the go.

I had a lot of fun with this the first two weeks or so I&apos;ve had it. But I&apos;ve noticed it slowly become less stable. I will check my email and the browser will crash. Overall, it acts like a computer that has a bad memory leak after a while, and I have to restart it for it to act normally again. Sometimes it will still be a little unstable after that with multiple apps open. This is a big disappointment and deal breaker for me, and would be reason for me to return it and ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mrsbib</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything, especially the price

Cons: can&apos;t think of anything

I&apos;m a mother of 8 year old twins. They are doing extremely well in school, so my husband and I decided to surprise each of them with a tablet. I compared the Samsung Galaxy, Ipad, and Blackberry Playbook. Price was a factor in our decision since we had to buy 2 tablets. I was surprised to find the Blackberry Playbook on sale for 199.99 so we purchased them and I will say that I could never be happier with our decision. Not only were they a great buy, but we are having a blast with them, hubby and I included. The picture and video quality are awesome and easy to post on Facebook. Video Chat is cool. The list goes on and on. Everyday we learn something new about the Playbook and literally can&apos;t put it down. Be ... st deal ever!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JohnK1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love my Playbook!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: compact, quality screen resolution, loud stereo speakers, HDMI port/cable to connect it to my TV

Solid, quality product. I bought 2, one as a gift, after buying myself one.
I love the high quality screen, loud stereo speakers, 2 cameras (front/back), &amp; HDMI port (so I can connect it to the TV, to view movies, etc., from the internet). The wifi internet connection is even better (stonger connection) than my Toshiba laptop. Highly recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>showbox</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for business travel</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size for traveling, BB bridge, Price, simle setup

Cons: Jury is still out on battery life during long flights.

I had been looking for a 7&quot; tablet to use on planes as I travel frequently for business. With the release of OS 2.0 and the reduction in price to $199 this was a no brainer. The new video store allows me to rent and download movies directly to the device to watch when I don&apos;t have an internet connection at airports and on planes. I am currently using the standard Kobo reader app for books and it works great. The fact that I have a Blackberry phone for work really sealed the deal. The blackberry bridge is perfect and allows me to wirelessly use the data connection off my phone if I need something and do not have access to wifi and also allows me to transfe ... r work email to the playbook to view attachments on the fly without breaking out my laptop.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>buffandsweet33</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>multitasking powerhouse</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: speed, elegance, hdmi port, os 2.0 multi tasking powerhouse

Cons: first unit was shipped faulty

beautiful hd screen. dual front and rear hd cameras. new playbook os 2.0 2/21/12. hdmi port for connection to your hdtv! sleek design. i have the 16gb version and originally i was shipped a faulty unit from shopblackberry.com blackberry paid shipping to get it fixed and now i&apos;m loving my playbook. pleanty of accesories available like silicone cases, zip sleeves, and funky envelopes. best 7 inch tablet in the market. price is out of this world for blackberry quality and 1gz dual core processor!!speakers are very loud!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>EB123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, easy to use, lot&apos;s of apps, ability to use Internet with the blackberry bridge

Cons: Haters will hate

We bought 2 of these for Christmas. The wife and I love them. Any issues previously mentioned have been fixed with the latest OS release. Tons of apps added and now there is an email client.
Love the fact that I can still use the Internet when there is no wi-fi available using blackberry bridge.
Can&apos;t go wrong at this price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Slayrider</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Deal for the Price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Performance, Very Easy to Use, Sound, and Display

Cons: Touch screen seems unresponsive or finicky at times. Document organization.

Video-resolution fantastic.
Processors-quick, reliable, can easily multitask.
Touchscreen-still getting the hang of this (my first device with one). Most primary links respond well, but I have trouble with some secondary ones.
Apps-not an IPAD or Android selection, but I have the basics I need to listen to online radio/video streams, record HD videos, and take/edit pictures.
Overall build-solid, good feel.

I have a blackberry bold which is always with me, so the bridge feature works fine for accessing and using smart phone content like emails. It does have gmail and similar apps, but I don&apos;t use them.

The 2.0 OS is ... supposed to come out in February, which would:
1. Make it Android compatible and open up the number of available apps.
2. Allow better organization of files, as right now documents seem to lump together in Word to Go.
3. Make it possible to transfer files directly by flash drive. Right now it can be done through email or by synching with the computer using the BlackBerry Desktop Software.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>EH4860</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love it!...can&apos;t wait til the update next month</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen, sound quality, battery size.

Cons: Very limited app choice vs Apple and Android...but android apps are coming!

The playbook is a solid performer for web surfing. The screen is awesome. I have a 10&quot; Android tablet as well. I like the size of the Playbook for carrying it around. The battery life is very good as well. I find myself wishing that the Android tab could work like the QNX software on the playbook. It&apos;s very convenient for switching between apps.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rudog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No Android Apps-No Skype-No Netflix! Useless!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Design! Compact size! Dual Camera! Sale Price!

Cons: Not enough free Apps, like Android! No Skype! No Netflix!

I bought this tablet when it went sale online for $199.00, and thought it would be a great buy to have when traveling. I was totally disappointed when I received it, and returned it to the the store 4 days later!
Although Blackberry claimms they are in the process of adding similar apps found on Android sometime in February, I just didn&apos;t see the benefits of owning this tablet just mostly to check email &amp; surf the web!
I&apos;ve an Acer Iconia A500 10&quot; Tablet, and I love it besides being able to add a multitude of free Android Apps!
Sorry Blackberry, nice product design but hardly any worthwhile free Apps running only OS sytem!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BuddyBoyNC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good for businessmen with Blackberrys

Cons: Set up

I could not pass up the sale on the Playbook and I am glad I made the purchase. I primarily use it for business and use the Blackberry Bridge app to connect it to my phone via Bluetooth. It is much, much easier to go through and answer e-mails rather than using the small phone. The pop-up keyboard is just the right size and very easy to use for my fat fingers. The browser is great and graphics are unreal.

My beefs with it are #1 Set Up - what a pain in the tuckus. Took more than a day and the worst part was getting my desktop to recognize the Playbook. Not sure if this was the trick or not, but after trying and trying decided to turn off the internet connection and that finally did it. My #2 beef is that the Citr ... ix app could be much better. It pretty much runs on the Playbook very similar than what it does on a desktop but that is the problem - desktops and tablets are different animals used in different ways and it is harder to navigate. I just hope that this is just a case of getting used to it and it becomes easier as time moves on.

I bought a case with Bluetooth keyboard separately and, although a wee bit bulky, was a great purchase. My goal was to be able to take this on one or two day business trips without lugging around my laptop and this does the trick.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have had a playbook for about 2 months and like it more and more. With tablet s you have to figure out how to customize, and with the playbook you can pretty much do what ever you want. I use it for both business and personal. The playbook is built great, very fast, and wifi and blue tooth work very well with a great range( better than anything I have used. The bridge feature is great. Anything that is on your phone you have on your playbook. You can transfer files, pics, videos, ect... all over bluetooth. With the new software coming out the phone will work as a remote for the playbook as well as many other inhancements. The size of the playbook is perfect. 7in tablet is portable yet give you a user interface that is that of a lapto. I would definitely recommend the playbook.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tennisfox</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great performance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and image quality.

Cons: Lack of access to applications.

I have had the 16G version for a couple of weeks and am very happy with it. It&apos;s the right size, fast, super graphics, and when OS 2 is released in February it should be a complete package. However I am caused by the lack of activeX which causes the Playbook to be unable to connect to some sites that reqire internet explorer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HiRajeev</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Value for Money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I recently bought the 32 GB Palybook at the promotional price of USD 249. Compared to the regular price of USD 599, this was a deal hard to resist. The overall built quality is extremely professional in line with blackberry products. The size is just fit and makes it very easy to hold as well as take it with you anywhere. Screen is razor sharp and works flawlessly for touch operations. Yes, the apps options are limited and I am still to get the apps for even basic yahoo/gtalk.. If you are looking for a tablet mainly for surfing, videos/music, this is the best you will get. Also, if you have a blackberry phone, this becomes an extended phone and you can access emails, calendars etc. Also, you can use your phone 3G services to access internet in playbook if the wifi is not available.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>NielsK2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best of three - iPad, Android, Playbook</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Link with Blackberry phone, great price, and great interface

Cons: Somewhat limited apps currently (but that&apos;s improving)

My kids both have iPads, and I just got a Sony S Android tablet and a Blackberry Playbook for Christmas. While the iPad is clearly an exceptional product and easy to use, I&apos;m not personally a big fan of it because it is a bit too simplistic with just pages of rows of icons. That is why I got the Sony S Tablet. I like the Sony tablet and it seems to do everything well, and it seems to be able to get nearly every app that I&apos;ve heard about for the iPad, so no big loss there. I also like the flexibility to add widgets and customize it more.

Finally, I got the Playbook because it was a great deal with the reduced pricing and because I use a blackbe ... rry phone and liked that they could easily sync with each other. However, what I&apos;m finding is that I use the Playbook the most of the three. The interface is unique from the iPad and Android, but it is very intuitive and works exceptionally well as an interface. It&apos;s easy t oswitch around between applications and I love the connection with my cell phone. I can see all my mail and calendar much easier given the much larger screen versus my phone and the integration is seemless. I also like that I can get full web access even when I&apos;m remote and it doesn&apos;t cost any more than my standard data plan that I had for the phone already. There are clearly less apps for the Playbook than the other two tablets, but there are still a ton of apps to choose from and that list is still growing well (I just looked at data on that in an article), so developers are still doing more and more on it. And, while I couldn&apos;t always find the same apps I&apos;d find on the iPad or Android, I could nearly always find very similar ones for the same purpose. Finally, the image quality on the screen is excellent. I like it the best of the three tablets.

So, if you use a Blackberry phone, I highly recommend getting a Playbook to go with it. For what you get and the now reduced current prices, all Blackberry users should have one! Even if you don&apos;t have a Blackbe ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hankzilla</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Loved it at first.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed, size, image, design, and features.

Cons: No backers on apps and battery buldge

Blackberry Playbook is a fast compact tablet which was almost worth keeping for $199.99. Good things about this tablet was speed and the amount of apps you can run at once, flash player worked excellent, sound, video, design, and features are all great. Here&apos;s the downside to this tablet, not enough apps or backers for this tablet which I really wanted skype on this for video chat which you can only use there playbook app with other playbook owners, apps that are available for there phones are not available for playbook. I almost kept the playbook but what made me return it was the battery buldge, after charging it for about 6hrs. the device buldged a bit on the back and bothered me th ... at much. Great device but has more negatives then positives.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jecsc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wait if you can....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Cons: Limited Applications

I am BB proponent and could not pass up on the price for the playbook.

Likes - Clarity/Ease of Use/Size
Dislikes - Limited number of Apps in comparison to other systems.
Limited online 3rd party video functionality. No email client.

I had an extremely difficult time bridging between PB and phone.

As you can see my dislikes outnumber my likes. I understand that a Feb release will adress several of my dislikes. For this price it is not a bad purchase, but my daughter is getting more out of her new kindle then I am from the PB...matter of fact i purchased her a PB and she has given it away.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>blackberryman82</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: superb quality, high end product for a great price

Cons: lacking long term development without android OS

The playbook is an awesome value for the price, considering everything you get from a quality perspective. For starters, Although the playbook does not run on Android OS, the user interface is very well laid out. The clarity of the HD screen, sound quality, and the front and back cameras are some of the best in the tablet market! even better than an i pad. Not to mention that you can take full HD 1080p video which is far better than the stand 720p found in other tablets. This may not be a $500 tablet, but for $199 its a steal! if you want something to go online with and use for multi media and games, this is right up your allley! if you have a blackberry phone, the ... bridge option makes the playbook even better!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Petete</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very, Very good tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Graphics, size, sound

Cons: Browser could be improved a little bit

I&apos;ve had it for three days and I love it. I don&apos;t think you can find anything better for $200. Plenty of Apps tp choose from, amazing HD image resolution, ease of use. The web browser could be a bit faster (reason why I didn&apos;t give 5 stars). Sound is good for such a thin tablet. Those who complaint about not many apps, sound quality, etc are insane, they either do not know how to search for apps or are dreaming they can get Bose sound quality in a $200 tablet. I am VERY satisfied, and it synchs beautifully with m Torch.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MISSsweetiePIE2u</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product at a great price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture, sound, price, speed, ease of use, good battery life, appearance, dual cameras

For $200, this Playbook CANNOT BE BEAT! I did a ton of research before investing in another tablet. My first one was horrible (I will withhold brand name). The Kindle Fire was my top choice.... until I saw the Playbook price dropped. Blackberry is a name I trust, so it immediately spiked my interest. Doing a side-by-side comparison of this and all other tablets, including ones double the price, I realized this product could not be beat.
I have only had it a couple of days, but I am HOOKED. The picture/video quality is outstanding, the speed is superb, .... well, I could keep going all night about the greatness of it, but I will try to refrain.
I do not understand what the big deal is a ... bout the power button. Yes, it is small, but it sticks up high enough to easily reach. The only problem I have had with it is sometimes when I chose &quot;Standby&quot; mode, it restarts. Buuuuut, all I have to do is quickly press the power button and it will automatically go in standby.
BOTTOM LINE: this is a wonderful product that I already have and will continue to recommend to others.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Vijender</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BlackBerry Playbook beautiful and faster</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Usability, great hardware, simillar UI of webOS, cameras, price ($189) and useful apps

Cons: screen size should have been between 7.5&quot; and 8.5&quot;.

I&apos;m great fan of webOS, when I looked at Blackberry playbook OS, it is also as good as webOS.

Hardware is Superb &amp; Build quality is excellent. Screen brightness not comparable with any other pads.

Have good number of USEFUL apps. I don&apos;t need millions of apps in other brands like apple or andorid - most of them are JUNK or Buggy.

I got it for $189. It has beautiful cameras.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jadepearl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got mine on Saturday for $199. I absolutely love my new BB play Book! It is very fast, easy to operate, excellent HD screen resolution, great front and back camera, perfect size and more importantly it is reasonably priced. Just some friendly advise, be gentle with the small on/off button because it is very delicate. Just push it down gently and you should not have any problem. I highly recommend this tablet to anyone. Go get one now before they&apos;re sold out.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Waferman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceeds expectations for $299</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought the BPB 32GB as an impulse buy; I took the floor model for a test drive and found it to be more smooth and faster than the other tablets in the $300 and under price range. I had a feeling that the low price offer was ending soon, so I called on the last night and had them reserve the last unit for me. I&apos;m very glad I did!

This is my first tablet. I was worried about the lack of applications from the blackerry store, and I&apos;m still hoping to see more apps added in the rumored big February release, but out of the box it has everything I need! Instead of Pandora for streaming music, it has Slacker radio. It has Facebook as a pre-loaded app, or you can log on to your normal account and view it as on a PC. WiFi reception is fine. Once I synced to my laptop, I could literally drag ... and drop my music from Itunes!! I can&apos;t even do that with my Iphone on another computer! It has a Kobo book reader app, which had any book that I typed in by author or title, so it should be pretty inclusive.

I bought an HDMI cable and plugged it into my Plasma TV. Wow, fantastic picture! I only have a 720P TV so there was some degredation in picture, but still it looked fantastic. I don&apos;t have cable so I download TV shows like Dexter, etc and used to put them on a re-writable disk, which can skip and make an episode unwatchable- now I can move them onto the playbook and watch them that way. The sound is top notch from this thing! I also played the inclued race game that came with the Playbook, and even though games are the last thing I would think of doing on a tablet (I would rather have a keyboard and mouse over even a console) it was way cool to see it on the 42&quot; plasma. Of course, I can do that with my PSP also.

Battery is fine. I&apos;ve been listening to Slacker radio for 3hrs now, and the battery life has gone from 65% to 52%- very nice. This thing fits my needs out of the box, but I will still be interested in seeing what the Android market can do for the playbook. The only thing ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>eldogg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small, but packs a punch</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very powerful and very inexpensive

Cons: No auto-focus on the cameras

It&apos;s fast, powerful, just the right size, and at just the right price. This can do everything other tablets can do, and it also has a better native browser and better Microsoft Office integration than iPads and other tablets. Definitely a must-have for an Blackberry user.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MarcoWhoElse</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>For me, best tablet on the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: BlackBerry Bridge, sound quality, size, screen, OS, build quality, HDMI

Cons: lack of apps

I&apos;ve been anxiously waiting for the PlayBook&apos;s release ever since it was announced and now having it for some time, I can say that for me, there is no better option than this tablet.

The quality of the tablet is amazing. It is solidly built with no creaks or anything. It&apos;s the perfect size, allowing me to take it anywhere and it even fits in my back pocket! The speakers are crisp and loud, the display vibrant and the cameras decent.

I love the operating system, it multi-tasks well and doesn&apos;t lag. There are no buttons on the PlayBook used for navigation; it is gesture controlled and it works great because gestures are intuitive.

The one thing that separates th ... is tablet from others is BlackBerry Bridge. You can use your existing BlackBerry data plan and use it to tether your PlayBook at no additional charge. You can also exchange files, BBM and reply to emails on the PlayBook, and take notes on the tablet and have them saved to your BlackBerry phone. This feature can save someone a lot of money like it did for me for about a month I didn&apos;t have internet access at home. And when you wanna go out and there are no hotspots, you still have internet access.

Overall, the PlayBook&apos;s great. Android apps and native email are coming soon which will add to the tablet&apos;s great features. The only thing is there aren&apos;t many apps in App World, but it is a new OS, in time more apps will be developed but it&apos;s not a big deal as the browser on the PlayBook is one of the best.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ruwi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gr8 product to say the least.....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen clarity, UI and functions, the Cameras, Speed.

Cons: Nothing found so far.

After reading a few expert reviews, I finally went ahead and purchased a Playbook 2 weekends ago.

And I am so glad that I did so. The screen and the UI is amazing. It&apos;s incredibly fast and the functionality is so natural and simplistic.

Tethering to my BB phone was easy and the manuals are very straight forward.

What&apos;s more the Cameras are awesome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Centaurita</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome little tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Waiting on more Apps.

I have had my Playbook for about three weeks now and I have to say, it is everything I had hoped for. Some of my favorite things about it so far.

Screen/ graphics - Stunning HD video and the pictures I have taken so far look crisp and clear. Shot a quick test video and it looks very nice also, with great sound. The touch screen is also very responsive and the &apos;swipe-from-bezel-to-wake&apos; feature is cool, as is swiping from the bezel to minimize programs. Typing on the screen keyboard is easy enough and I have yet to hit the wrong keys.

Organization of screen icons/ programs and ease of use - Easy to navigate to whatever I want from the home screen and moving from program to program is totally intuitive. Quick links to S ... ettings, Bluetooth, WiFi, Battery, Bridge, Orientation Lock are all in the upper right corner. Email message notifications (received and stored on my BB phone- accessible via bridge) are in the upper left.Time and Date top center.

Connections -The Bridge to my Blackberry Tour email and content is seamless and fast. I have also found that my phone does not not even need to be close for it to work. I can surf to an email link with no problem, and the Bridge browser does not require WiFi. Turning the Bluetooth and WiFi on and off (to conserve battery) could not be simpler. WiFi is fast and strong and both the bridge connection and the WiFi work throughout my home and yard. Picking up free WiFi connections when out and about works great.

MISC.
-The Browser and online content rendering is great. I have had no issues so far and having Flash is definitely a big plus.
-Excellent calculator, with Standard &amp; Scientific modes, as well as a Unit converter and Tip calculator. My son used the scientific calculator for his Geometry final and said he preferred it over the TI-84 Silver Edition.
-The Kobo Books eReader is good enough for my needs as I prefer most of my books in hard-copy. I have however downloaded several for when I am stuck waiting somewhere with no ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jram5555</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unexpectedly nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Blackberry quality (no compromise)

Cons: nothing stands out to me as a shortcomming yet.

I own a Blackberry phone, so I waited for the Playbook to be released before I purchased a tablet. I just purchased the 16Gb version from BestBuy (local store) this weekend. I couldn&apos;t be happier with it. It is bright and easy to handle (the size is just right for a tablet). The user interface is very smooth and responsive. I created a bridge to my BB 8530 and it is working nicely. There is no learning curve to contend with. The user interface is well thought out and seems to work naturally. I haven&apos;t had to read a manual yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>cybersunshine</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is by far the best tablet available. I own a I pad, ipad2, a motorola xoom and a playbook. I was hesitant about buying the playbook because of the pre launch reviews. I&apos;m so glad that I ignored the bad reviews. Setup was easy and fast. It was great before I bridged it to my blackberry. It&apos;s faster than all of my other tablets. Nothing about it is confusing or complicated. The size and weight make it easy to operate and comfortable to hold. There are tons of useful apps. Animations, movies, videos are smooth, do not hang up and no long wait while they load. The browser is lightening fast. I only have one complaint and that is the power button. It&apos;s small and hard to push if you have the case on. I use it for business. I bought a second playbook for family use (that&apos;s a first). It is. Q ... uickly taking the place of our desk top, laptops and net books. My little boy is autistic and he uses it with ease after showing him how to use the touch screen. I love my motorola xoom but it has taken a back seat since I bought my playbook. We are getting 10 hours of battery life with constant use. Another big plus is that I can charge my blackberry with my playbook. Too bad it doesn&apos;t have a printer. You can&apos;t :-) go wrong with a playbook!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fletch23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Things Come To Those Who Wait</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful, Responsive, Strong Battery Life, 1080p Video Recording

Cons: Lack of apps (though not for long!!)

After a few days of playing with my new BlackBerry Playbook, I can say for sure that it is INCREDIBLE! The one thing I thought I&apos;d complain about, or have issues with, was the screen size. I have not once found it to be a problem. I can type 50 wpm on it, which should give you a good idea of the size/usage ratio. The interface is flawless, fluid, and the ability to multi-task heavy apps, without performance issues, is insane.

Another thing I am completely blown away by, is the 1080p/720p/480p options for recording. I hooked it up via HDMI to my 1080p 50&quot; LCD, and it is stunning! It offers everything one would/should look for from a tablet, and then some. It ... syncs with your BlackBerry, even to tether your cellular data network.

Now, the reason behind my title. It is already equal to the iPad in terms of functionality. But it&apos;s greatness lies in future updates and app additions. (Which BlackBerry is saying will arrive every few weeks). I&apos;ve had it for just one week, and I&apos;ve already gotten the video chat app, native Facebook app, and BBM. I can assure you however, that the games are mind-blowing. Way better than anything I&apos;ve seen on any of Apple&apos;s products. Oh, and I heard somewhere today they announced Angry Birds for the PlayBook?

GET ONE NOW, SO YOU CAN BE THAT GUY/GIRL WHO&apos;S AHEAD OF THE CURVE. I&apos;m confident that I won&apos;t have to buy a PlayBook 2 anytime soon. How bout you Apple tweeps?
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>finally a real tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: hardware, OS, size, very well built

Cons: other than waiting on next round of updates;-)

i bought my playbook on launch day. i have been very pleased with the overall feel and performance. the new OS is smooth and simple to use. the browser is exceptional and i love the size and portability. i have used the video camera and works great. everyone i have shown my playbook has been impressed. i cant wait for upcoming updates and more functionality. i love the bridge app. my best advice is get one and give it a try, you may be surprised. i typed this review on my playbook :-)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kjclouden</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid Device that does what i need on the go</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Web browsing, size, speed, build quality, the vibrant screen, battery life, cool gestures

Cons: current lack of third party apps, no auto correction, lack of native email and calendar clients

Week one has been great so far. I love the interface. It&apos;s smooth, it&apos;s quick, it&apos;s pretty. This has one of the fastest browsers I&apos;ve used on a mobile device. Being able to load full websites, flash and all is great.
The build quality is solid. Does not feel plasticy or cheap at all. Takes great pics and video..in decent lighting conditions. The battery can last two days with moderate use. I&apos;ve yet to run out of juice on a full days use.
It&apos;s the perfect size for portability. can slip it into your pocket and not feel awkward pulling it out in public.
Multi tasking like a p ... ro. This thing can run 9 plus apps simultaneously without slowdown. Video playback is awesome. I&apos;ve downloaded some music vids from youtube and they look great
The downside is yes, there aren&apos;t alot of apps in as it stands right now.
No native email for those that don&apos;t just go to gmail.
No auto correct when typing.
These can all be remedied with software updates. Hopefully sooner than later.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>GAChicago</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Expensive browser and IPOD</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen resolution &amp; sound

Cons: Lots - Cant&apos;t sync with BB smartphone, can&apos;t stream Netflix

AT&amp;T Wireless customers BEWARE. AT&amp;T has not approved the BlackBerry Bridge software which you must have in order to sync your BlackBerry smartphone with the PlayBook. You need to download the Bridge software onto your smartphone through BB Apps, however, you get an error message from BB that the Bridge Download is not available to you from your carrier. BB Tech Support confirmed this issue. The main reason I bought the Playbook was so I could read emails and attachments on the PlayBook&apos;s larger screen that I received on my smartphone. Also you cannot live stream movies or TV shows from Netflix on the PlayBook like you can on IPAD. Netflix gave me an error message tha ... t the operating system of my device (PlayBook) was incompatible with live streaming.

On the positive side; I did load my music on the Playbook and the speakers have outstanding sound. Also, screen resolution is excellent when browsing the web, just wish I could view videos besides You Tube.

Not sure why BlackBerry introduced this device, have been a BlackBerry user for over 10 years and AT&amp;T for over 5 years, this is very disappointing and a waste of over $900 with accessories -- will be returning all and converting to an IPhone and IPAD on Verizon.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>hotmcihaelbi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Playbook is the best tablet on the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: none

Excellent design with strong performance! It is really an IPAD killer!!!. IPAD2 has nothing to compare with this device, except apps. However, the most of the apps are trash anyway!!! When the app world grows, it will be the best tablet ever made. The audio quality is very close to best stereo. Ipad2&apos;s audio sucks!!! I sold my IPAD2 on ebay !!! I love playbook and use it for my business and entertainment.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PNAIR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Finally!! A worthy challenger to the iPad!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, build, ease of use, sound, screen quality

Cons: Not a huge negative - but they could&apos;ve had atleast 10 good apps at launch.

I&apos;ve been using this for the past 12 hours straight with the Blackberry Bridge setup. My intent was solely to check how easy it was to accustom oneself to the tablet and whether I was hitting a balance between &quot;sacrificing&quot; features or hit the ground running using whats available. I&apos;m an iPad 2 owner as well - so I knew that the expectations to be set are high though it still needed me to be reasonable.

Results:

Those complaining about lack of native email client - agree that its lacking - but you are free to use the killer web browser to check all your email (even MS Exchange).

RIM has confirmed they&apos;ll launch native ema ... il clients within the month or next - and I&apos;d be glad to wait.

Emails on Bridge - The Playbook shows email from your BB in a relatively neat layout. Deleting / Replying / forwarding emails from the PB work like a charm. Ive been a BB user for 4 years...but my iPhone loving wife wishes her iPhone/iPad had the same capabilities as my BB/PB.

Multitasking - the capability to &quot;tile&quot; your applications and have them all running (or paused - your choice) is very useful and truly a PC like feature that will be welcomed by many users.

Gestures - you get used to them fairly quickly. True Story - I swiped across my iPad thinkin it&apos;ll kill an app and then went back to pressing the button to get it done. Oh wait - I need to press it twice and then launch multi-taskin to kill it.

Where the iPad wins (for now) is that it has clearly made a head start that gives users an option to have many apps. But keep in mind that both Android and RIM are catchin up fast. (Remember - Apple had to play the catch up game a few years ago ... its cyclic)

Speakers - LOUD. CLEAR. PERIOD.

Display - 1080p HD - Clear videos, Clear pictures. Enuff said.

Any bugs - yes - Bringin the PB back from sleep needs a bit of random swiping. The browser has crashed on me once in the past 12 hours.

You can see the App World is being updated with new apps each day. I&apos;m sure we&apos;ll have a goo ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Operating System</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: OS, Security, Price, Simplicity

Cons: So far, nothing!

I had no hesitation buying the playbook, it&apos;s a &quot;Blackberry&quot; product afterall. I saw other tablets on display, but in the end, what matters most to me is not the popularity of the tablet but rather reliability and security. Reliability in the sense of smooth operation of the OS, and functionality. It doesn&apos;t have all the cool apps of the other tablets, but really, i did not care so much about those. I needed my tablet for serious work and this playbook has delivered on that. The battery life is great, several days on minimal use. Although, it takes a few minutes to power on, but i&apos;m sort of used to that already with my blackberry phone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Luxe0316</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love it!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great tablet! You get more gigs for the price of an 8g tablet.The Internet browser is so crisp n clear and is like browsing on a desktop, love the fact it reads flash...a big must have! Battery life is super long ..about 9hrs! It feels really durable and very sleek looking . Comes with YouTube,FB, twitter, n docs to go. App world doesn&apos;t have very many apps and it doesnt play Netflix would probably bother some, but I really don&apos;t even use the apps on my iPhone + you can side load android apps, but I haven&apos;t tried yet and if I do watch Netflix its on a tv. If you can get passed that, then you will find its other qualities is worth the money. Awesome product! Ps- kudos to OD on super fast shipping!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>CMed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for price, Poor quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: quality &amp; workmanship

I bought this tablet back in December mainly to use for work with by BB phone. For that purpose it did it&apos;s job very well. Writing e-mails much faster with the tablet than on the phone. Easier to look at and edit Excel and PPT files, etc... I won&apos;t complain at all about those features of this tablet.
My complaints lie in the build quality and workmanship of the product itself. It was about 3 months after purchasing that the USB charger jack on the tablet became deformed and mis-shapen that you could no longer plug in the standard charger to recharge. I could overlook this and went ahead and bought one of the rapid chargers instead to recharge. Well on August 1st the whole tablet just died. I&apos;ve called RIM customer service a ... nd the warranty is over, 3 months only so they can&apos;t really help. I could send it in to them to look over and possibly fix, but most likely will be cheaper to buy a new tablet.
That&apos;s exactly what I plan to do. However, it won&apos;t be from RIM. I&apos;ve been using the wife&apos;s IPad 2 lately and love it so I&apos;ll be getting one of those also.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>nerdowell</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent hardware and fast os</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Well done tablet and easy navigation

Cons: Would like an sd card slot

Everyone is bashing Blackberry but they&apos;ve always had good hardware and the new OS - soon to be OS10 at the end of the year for the new phones, is great. (same as used in the Playbook now). Everyone says there aren&apos;t enough apps and granted there are fewer than Apple and Android but 99% of those are terrible and really, the Playbook is geared more for adults and business. I&apos;ve got Kindle loaded, can access my work via Citrix Receiver along with a few really good games. The display is wonderful with 1080 out. When the price was lowered -$249 for the 32g, I jumped on it. If you have a blackberry phone, the added bonus is using the bridge feature to use it as a touchpad and/or remote.
I refuse to buy ... the into the Apple koolade, and Android is fragmented and has some scary security issues.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BlackBerryfan100</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t go wrong at this price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Bought the BlackBerry Playbook based on years of using BlackBerry smartphones for personal and business use. Smaller screen size is nice compared to the iPad as it is easier to carry. Features are identical except for number of apps which is not important to me to spend the extra $300. At $199 for the 16 gb model, you cannot go wrong with this tablet. Have been using mine for a month and have had no issues with it at all.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>pcfixer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty Good Tablet For The Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It&apos;s fast, has a great screen, easy to use and figure out from the first time using it.

Cons: Too many of the favorite Apps are not free like they are with Android devices.

Great tablet over-all for the price. Really good for business applications, but not so good for the games unless you have money to burn downloading Apps..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>t</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great product! Very responsive. Easy set up out of the box. I figured how to load android apps on it so it is even better now. Great screen resolution. Limited availability of apps, but for the price its definitely worth it. This tablet is very portable, which is very nice because you can pretty much carry it everywhere with you. I would definitely recommend this tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>FastRouter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t waste your money on the I-Pad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy Setup, Great HD Graphics, Killer Price, ease of use

Cons: Nothing comes to mind

I went into Best Buy to purchase an i-pad. And very nearly pulled the trigger on one. Call it the bad publicity that Blackberry has been recieving lately or the fact that almost everyone seems to be raving about i-pads - but whatever. I decided to do a back to back comparisson against the i-Pad. And I am glad I took the time. The Blackberry Playbook is better in so many ways it&apos;s just not funny.

I&apos;m beginning to wonder if the folks that are buying the i-pad have just drunk the koolaid. The blackberry simply runs rings around the ipad.

If you want to pay the extra $500 to buy into the marketing hype by all means buy an i-pad. But if you want a grown up tablet with great gra ... phics at a decent price get the playbook.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Technology83</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My business Helper!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, fast, intuitivity

Cons: no sd card slot, but i love it.!!!!

this tablet is my helper during my work gives me the possibility to connect my blackberry phone and use my data without having to pay an extra charge.
On the other hand also offers speed when I&apos;m on the net, I&apos;m happy with this tablet.
as all know the Blackberry platform was not created for media why there are not many applications, but the truth to me is not a problem. I use it for business and personal use.
also the price this tablet seems to me correct, and hopefully that&apos;s the price of the other tablets.
I recommend it to all who are looking for a tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Flavio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent display, and decent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Display is excellent, and camera is decent: that s a pity Skype has not been ported on PlayBook. Text in mail can be formatted (bold, color, highlight...) and predictive words are sometimes useful. Browser is quite good. It comes with Tetris preinstalled and you can download Asphalt 6 and Modern Combat for free. Battery life is a little less than iPad (with fair use you need to recharge almost every day...). Good deal for this price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BD81</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent hardware but lacking software</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Build quality, size, weight

Cons: Poor app availability

Even with a $199 price tag this is not a best buy. The hardware is great. The build quality is superb. The size and the wight are perfect for a tablet. Multitasking works great. Very fast and responsive OS. The latest 2.0 software update adds some features. So why only 2 stars?

While the flash support is available, this tablet lacks so many &apos;must have&apos; apps. You can not stream Netflix since there is no Netflix app available and ever worse, Netflix has stated they will not be developing one for the Playbook. You can not read your Kindle books because Kindle app does not exist (I would be really surprised if Amazon ever develops one). If you want to use Skype you need to look elsewhere since, you guessed it, S ... kype app does not exist.

The good news is there are ways to &apos;side-load&apos; some Android apps and get them to work (google it and you can find fairly easy how-to instructions online). RIM also seems to be making some Android apps available (like Dolphin Browser HD). But for $199 I don&apos;t want to work to get the apps I need. Also keep in mind that with any non supported apps you will get absolutely no support from RIM. BTW it seems that RIM will be disabling side-loading with the next (2.1) update so if you own this tablet I recommend not to update from 2.0.

I simply can not recommend this tablet to anyone other than Blackberry phone users and fans that have strictly business needs. If you want to buy a tablet I recommend getting Samsung Tab 2 7&quot; version and it&apos;s only $50 more. No messing with apps and getting them to work. They are available and ready from the get go.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MCMF</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Poor Customer Service</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Cheap price but goes the same with the service

Cons: Very Poor Customer Service

I sent my Blackberry tablet for repair to RMA last first week week of March, 2012. When I followed up on March 24, 2012 they said they sent it back to me and gave me a Fedex tracking number. After a week of not receiving my tablet I called customer service almost everyday since then. I received hundreds of apologies and &quot;I will get back to you&quot; promises but not a single one did give me updates including supervisors. Just tonight, after the agonizing wait and repetetive calls to the customer service they finally said they sent MY tablet to the WRONG COUNTRY and WRONG PERSON. And when I asked what their plan is after the blunder they made they said they still have to discuss it .What kind of s ... ervice are they giving? This may be the cheaper tablet but the customer service goes with the price too.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>michellerm1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Android Tablet with ICS Upgrade</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: compact size with all the features I need.

Cons: Battery life is just as bad as all the other tablets.

Dual processor, 1gb ram, 8gb onbard memory. I added a 32gb micro sd card and now have 40gb. Tablet fits in my jacket pocket and gives the portability I didn&apos;t have with the 10&quot; tabs which are huge by comparison. Android Ice Cream Sandwich will be available this month. Then I&apos;ll have it all. All this for just over $250!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Buttons252</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I hate blackberries but love my playbook</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, features, quality

Cons: rear facing camera has no autofocus

**My review is with newest OS update**

I was in the market for a 7&quot; tablet to replace books. I dont understand the purpose of 9-10&quot; tablets. They are to big and heavy to be used as an e-reader. They are difficult to type on and if you sync a keyboard to one, why didnt you just buy a laptop?

the 7&quot; is ideal for e-readers, the playbook has a very bright and crisp display. Its very snappy, and after you master the user interface gestures the playbook offers a great user experience. The front and rear camera arent very good but a lot better then the kindles complete lack of camera. Everything plays extremely smooth on the playbook except the facebook app seems to lack hardware acceleration, so s ... crolling through posts is somewhat choppy. For my intended purposes and the price paid I am extremely pleased with the playbook (same price as kindle fire)

I think its superior to the kindle in user interface and feature set, plus you can even sideload android apps to it. When priced same as kindle fire its a no brainer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MeanDude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s cool - but they really need more apps!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price to Performance

Cons: Application Availability

Yeah, it&apos;s kind of like the title says - but here&apos;s the thing. For the price, I was going to get either a playbook or an Android tablet that couldn&apos;t use market - so, I&apos;m one ahead as at least there are a smattering of applications available for my Blackberry. Still, I want more applications, so I can&apos;t muster up that final star.

Funcationality? It rocks! Hasn&apos;t crashed or locked up yet. Seems to perform smoothly with video.. nothing to gripe about here - especially for that $200 ticket priced. If you are looking for something in this price range, this is the beast.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>letitsnow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love this device, top build quality, nothing cheap or flimsy. I&apos;ve had it 2 weeks and just keep loving it more. I find the 7&quot; size to be more handy for on the go over the Ipad size. I absolutely love the gesture based OS, I didn&apos;t think I would, but it just works beautifully. MY single complaint is Netflix surpressing use of the device for streaming, my kids would like more apps. Ipads are certainly nice, but this tablet is more than 90% for $200 if you don&apos;t mind the 7&quot; size; I think it is truly a bargain at that price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sultana</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceeded my expectation in every way</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>at $199 price point I will compare it with Kindle fire as I own both the device. Though I&apos;m using fire for months and playbook for only a couple of weeks, I guess my experience with playbook is worth mentioning.

Pros:
1. Display is excellent. Fire and playbook both have 1024X600 pixels, but pixel only tell you partial story of quality. The display panel on playbook is superior and you have to see it yourself.
2. The OS 2.0 is stable and is more intuitive than android in almost every way. I&apos;m using ICS 4.0 (CM9) on my cell phone and ( Amazon skinned) 2.3 on fire. Even ICS can not come close.
3. It has 1GB RAM compared to 512MB RAM of fire. Multitasking is phenomenal on playbook. This is hands down the best multitasking implementation on the market. Everthing is snappy.
4. ... It has two cameras in comparison to none on fire. Even the front facing camera shoot 1080p video. Though the quality isn&apos;t outstanding, its doable and of course better than having none.
5. The build quality of the tablet is also extremely good. It seems solid and have a quality feel to it.

Cons:
1. the offered contents are not very good. The appworld is missing a lot of applications. But fortunately I found most of the apps as .bar file and able to run on playbook since playbook can run android apps.
2. I would like it to be lighter. Its not heavy at 425g but a i expected less.
3. Battery life is around 6 hrs. I am really happy with it. But people who used iPad before might notice this as an important down side.

Finally, I would like to mention that the multitasking on playbook, the intuitive interface and ability to play multiple graphics intensive games simultaneously this device has exceeded my expectations. at only $199, this is a steal. People who do not like constant tinkering, would love playbook.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Geotracker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this Machine</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: definitely worth it

Cons: no external sd card slot

i have used this for a few weeks and i am loving it. very simple to grasp and go right at it without much knowledge. fast processor and really can do multiple tasks no problem. why did i give it a 4star instead of a five. well 1, there isnt an optional sd card slot so you are stuck with the gigs you buy but price was amazingly low so worth price. 2. the app network it runs under isnt that tight but they still have a good selections. 3. the startup is a bit lengthy it does take about 90 sec before finally getting started</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gloria51</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Difficult to set up.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this for my husband&apos;s birthday and after 5 days of frustration, he has boxed it up and I will be returning it. His primary complaints were slow responsiveness to his touch and difficulty adjusting to smaller screen size.
I think it had great potential for him when working on the road and the compact size makes it easy to transport.
I would recommend it for a younger more tech savvy person.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ChocolateGin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to setup, Price

Cons: Slow to start

The Blackberry Playbook is a great starter tablet and for $199.99 it beats Apple anyday. The features are awesome. The only negative I have is the startup is very slow but one on its no stopping what you can do with this tablet. Awesome buy!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>thewalmartguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Devs need to support it, but a good tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact, snappy and multi-tasking

Cons: Netflix, hulu and Kindle are not available

I&apos;ve had my playbook for over a month before thinking of writing a review. It has also been updated to OS 2 (which is where most of what I discuss is based).

I love the multi-tasking. This is not for everyone, but I tend to do a lot at once on any device that I own and use. I found the web browser to be a little laggy on some sites, but it has loaded html5, youtube and all sites I have visited just fine.

I love the size. Other tablets were too big for me and not comfortable to hold or carry around. I wanted a portable tablet, and the 7&quot; screen size works for that (the PlayBook fits in my back pocket). I haven&apos;t had a hard time reading on the screen (touble-tap to zoom, or pi ... nch)

The gestures are pretty simple to learn and become second nature. It is similar to the HP TouchPad in some ways, but has been improved upon. My wife and seven year old daughter were able to learn them pretty quickly and finds them natural.

Blackberry Bridge is the main thing I was looking forward to. It allows me to open and edit any file I have stored on my cell phone (9810), handle emails and BBM from the tablet and use my phone&apos;s data connection when I am not around Wi-Fi. A new feature to the bride in OS 2 was the remote control. This allows me to hook my Playbook up to a TV and use my phone to control it (similar to the touch pads on laptops) along with letting me type from my phone. All of the gestures work the same, including the bezel ones. I found this handy for video, pictures, web browsing and spreadsheets. I can sit anywhere and control the device, answer emails and messages and even use my phone for non-bridged apps at the same time.

My biggest complaint has little to do with the device. Services like Netflix, Hulu and even Kindle have not supported natively on the playbook. This annoys me because they support other tablets. Netflix said they have no plans and Amazon promised a Kindle app over a year ago. Since this is not RIM&apos;s fault, I cannot fault the tablet (it can run ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JoeKY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Size is just right for me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Speakers, Camera, Battery life

Cons: No flash

For most people that already own a laptop, this tablet will be a very good purchase. I like everything about it. The size for me is just right when you are using it while still on bed in the morning, or when you are sitting in the toilet playing angry birds. It doesn&apos;t have card reader, usb port and other extra ports found on other Android Tabs, but in reality you don&apos;t really need it on the tablet because you already have a laptop to do that. Thank you BB for the $50 gift card. I know Apple Ipad is nice but this one is perfect for my needs and I do not have any feeling of buying another tablet. It has a very good speakers. Its loud and perfectly setup. Good Camera too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>zookeeper88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet if you already have Blackberry items</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It was a great sale price at $200

Cons: Everything else about it.

I took this tablet back. I bought it for my mom and could not put the traditional apps on it like Nook and Kindle. You have to have everything in the blackberry version, which they of course charge you for every little thing. It was also difficult to download blackberry apps and the website was not particularly helpful. Would not recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jsjacobson1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than a reader but it&apos;s no iPad.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The price during the $199 sale.

Cons: Lack of apps, unresponsive to touch at times

I bought the Playbook for my wife primarily as an e-reader, since it was the same price as a Kindle Fire. I&apos;m used to an iPhone and was disappointed by the lack of good applications. And the ones that are available are generally more expensive. I&apos;m also concerned that often the touch screen does not respond to touch, that it does not have a Skype app or a good radio app like Pandora. And since my wife&apos;s eyesight is not the best, I was looking for a provision to increase the font size. I hope my experience improves with time and that Android apps become available soon.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just as Good As any Tablet out there.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Tablet size is perfect, never feels too big and bulky!

Cons: Waiting for OS update, but patience will pay off in the long run.

As with any tablet the first iteration is not going to be the best, but as with Android Tablets, the updates will come and soon enough people can quit wishing for Netflix and Native Email and Calendar. Battery life is excellent and the screen is very nice and vibrant. Surfing the web is the best out there on a tablet and you will find it hard to crank up the laptop if you do not have to type alot (of course you could always buy and add- on keyboard if you needed to) Best of all is the price that no other (real) tablet can compete. Stop hesitating and purchase and start enjoying the convience of a great peice of hardware.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>seemsixty7</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredible Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Size, Specs and Quality

Cons: The lack of recognition of this incredible tablet.

I am a huge fan of this Tablet. The multitasking aspect is far superior to any other tablet. Soon the 2.0 OS will come out for it and make it even better. The Size is perfect. I was able to take this tablet with me for a backpacking trip through Scotland. The Videos an pictures I took were amazing. The durability and size make it perfect for everyday everywhere use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>whapo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice But Limited</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size &amp; ease of use

Cons: Very limited available app

I purchased the BlackBerry PlayBook Tablet with 32GB Memory because of the price ($299) and the BlackBerry brand.

It was very easy to use, my 7 &amp; 9 year olds learned its functionality within minutes. I like the size, look and feel.

However, it has a VERY limited selection of apps, no Kindle, no Nook, book reader apps. Few business apps that were useful for me. Overall it was a disappointment because it lacked the needed applications for my work &amp; life. Had those been available I would still have it and be happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zapt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love it...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: flash, sound, and camera quality

Cons: weight... kinda heavy...

i love this playbook... can play most of the vid and can play flash on website too :D

i cant wait for 2.0 OS :D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>siroz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy set up and fast loads web pages quick.

Cons: Nothing

Well, i was debating for a while before getting the Blackberry playbook. I must say i am very happy with this product and was able to get it at the 199.99 price, what a steal. Its fast and i can do everthing i need to do and then some.I get to all my emails including work,all websites and they load fast. If your thinking about this don&apos;t think anymore just go get it. The size is perfect the price was right and the tablet is awesome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>shrink479</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>underated</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size function look

Cons: battery life isnt as good as the ipads

i have been enjoying the playbook for a few months now and i love it. i have two ipad 2s and i believe this to be the superior tablet. ipads have better apps, although playbook is working on that, but when it comes to real use and functionality and multi tasking this playbook is terrific. my children 2 and 3 years old received one each for xmas, the apps for them are great. i use it for business and life management. also just browsing the web and socializing. great tablet. Go RIM.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>blankblank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good deal for the 199 sale amount</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Blackberry Bridge, Files, HD screen and good sound. Good speed.

Cons: Read the comments

The Playbook is a good deal for the 199 sale amount. May consider an Apple if paying full price. Playbook works great and fast enough. Have zero issues with operating, sync, wifi access, etc. Good video and pictures if outside. Overall, I&apos;m happy with my purchase. Pros; Can bridge with BB cell and have internet access anywhere for no cost! Can download files Excel,Word, PP etc. Access to files w/o internet. Downsides; BB has a limited number of apps compatible w/playbook. Files download into general access and you cannot create additional folders for seperating specific files. (Still better than ipod, where you must have internet to access files). Will not accept any type of addition ... al USB file storage. Sometimes hitting the correct email or icon on the touchpad is difficult if you have larger fingers, but I still like the smaller size than iPad. Note-there is an OS update coming in Feb, which is suppossed to fix the majority of wants and needs.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Taklbry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Decent Tablet for the Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, OS

Cons: Lack of removable storage

My idea of a tablet is something bigger than a phone, but smaller than a notebook; something highly portable. I prefer the 7&quot; format for these reasons. The Playbook is a solid tablet from a hardware perspective and the QNX OS is very stable ans secure. The biggest shortfall is the lack of a SDHC slot cuz 16MB is not that much when it comes to storing photos and music. I am anxiously awaiting the OS upgrade from Blackberry next month which should give the Playbook the ability to use android apps. There are apps currently available through the BB website but nothing compared to android apps. The Samsung Galaxy Tab 7+ is the only other tablet I considered, but it is nearly twice the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>reggie123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very good price

Cons: Maybe if they offered a choice in different screen sizes.

The Blackberry Playbook is a great compact tablet. It&apos;s fast and easy to use. I have had mine for a couple of weeks now and I am very satisfied with it. I would recommend the Playbook to anyone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mpharos</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still needs a lot of improvement</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen and sound quality

Cons: Not much apps, no manual and sunk on/off switch

The Playbook is average in my opinion. It still needs a lot of support, apps and improvement. I do not not why, RIM did not provide a hard copy manual with the tablet, every time you try to know something about it you will have to go on line. I&apos;ve it for about three month now and still do not know a lot about its functions I/P ports and more. When I first bought it it was dropping the internet connection alot and I had to call the company for that, it is not doing it as much now. The On/Off switch is too bad and you&apos;ll have to have a sharp finger nails to get it to work as it is sunk in the frame. There is no a solid answer if this tablet has a GPS or not. Also, sometimes it freezes and refus ... es to work till it takes its time or you re-boot it. I got this tablet on sale during the thanksgiving time for $199 and I think that this should be the price always and not higher. In summary I think RIM was in a harry to put this toy on the market while it still needs some work.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>shaji</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great all-rounder!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very Fluid and responsive..

Bought this two weeks ago.Its awesome. The UI is simply superb and so very fluid. The multi tasking works flawlessly. I mostly use the Browser and its simply superb, handles all the flash content with ease. The NFS game is an added attraction. I dont mind less apps available thing, whatz d use of so many apps when u cant run &apos;em without sayin &apos;augh!!&apos; as with Android devices..also battery runs good...Final verdict is this absolutely great tablet!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechMaster101</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Except For A Few Things</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen, Camera, Multi Tasking etc.

Cons: Not real good app world, and no Netflix.

I have had this tablet for 2 months. Love it! I get atleast 7 hours of battery life which is amazing compared to my 45 minute ipod touch&apos;s battery life! (2nd Gen). The screen is amazing! The touch sensitive sides are handy but sometimes can be a little annoying. The operating system is easy to use and is uberly handy! The app world does pretty much suck. Some good apps but the app world is getting better. Oh, and NO Netflix! I am surprised because iPad does not support flash and this tablet does, yet you can watch Netflix on iPad but not on here! But it should be available soon. Overall, this is a great tablet if you dont mind waiting a while to get alot of apps and Netflix. :) Oh, and the ... speakers are AMAZING!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TWDESQ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Built for Business...Portable and Powerful</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great business tablet

Cons: Found nothing wrong yet

I already own the 64 GB Playbook and recently purchased my fiancee the 16 GB for Christmas. We both have Blackberry phones for security purposes and the Playbook&apos;s Blackberry Bridge allows us to browse the internet without WiFi and tethering (extra cost) when we are in remote locations. It also syncs with our phones and we can update calendars, memos, and contacts as well as read/delete email messages from our phones by using the Playbook. It has Word to Go, an Excel program, and a Powerpoint program pre-installed. Its size lets me carry it anywhere and is even discreet enough to carry into business meetings when it is housed in its leather cover. If you are serious about business applications and security, then this i ... s the best tablet on the market. If you just want a toy to play games on, then get an IPAD2 or Android tablet. Although...the Playbook does have many games (Angry Birds, Dead Space, Monopoly, etc.) if you need a break from work and the graphics and sound are great.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kansaspipeliner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, blackberry operating platform is easy to navigate

the 7 inch screen is perfect, can hold in hands and type easily. the operating layout is better than ipad, to navigate u just slide your finger on different areas of the screen, unlike the ipad where u push home sceen button then select. perfect for online shopping, emails, surfing the web.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>wikiwikirulz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Blackberry Playbook is Increadible</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Performance, Screen res, Batt life, easy to use

Cons: Balckberry to Balckberry only Video Chat

I got thisBlackberry 16G Playbook as a Christmas gift from my wife and son. This thing is increadible. The laser beam quick performance out-does our brand new DELL Home PC. The Video chat app states blackberry ID to Blackberry ID... I hope to figure a way around it w/ some online research...or wait for skype to get the new app for the blackberry playbook. It has Blackberry Market apps that I am not too familiar with yet but seem in-line w/ the android market. The screen res was fantastic. The Battery finally died after about 9 or so hours of use... which is increadible to me. Also, it has fantastic sound from its micro speakers. Even w/ video chat to blackberry ID Blackberrys ... only... still give it a 5 star.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>millsa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Setup, Price, Power

Cons: Nothing yet

I bought this tablet for my business. I loved it so much I bought one for my daughter, wife and 75yo mother. My mother loves it. She even takes it to bingo to play games in between sections. I have looked at some others and for size and power. I believe its the best.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kupitero</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best 7&quot; tablet out there - No regrets</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For users with Blackberry phones with data plans, this is the best tablet to buy. Period.

Of course, there will be Apple &amp; rabid iPad fans, but, some of them are totally missing the big picture. Apple doesn&apos;t always deliver the best product in the best interest of consumers.

So, who wants to pay extra monthly fees if you&apos;re already paying big bucks for your data plan on your iPhone? Pay another data plan for the iPad. Not me.

Thanks to Blackberry PlayBook &amp; the BB Bridge software plus my data plan on my BB Bold. I have the best tablet in the planet today.

The 7&quot; screen is just the right size. The iPad looks like a dinosaur.
Movies, eBooks, my mail and the glorious web are rendered so much faster on the PlayBook than the iPad.

It&apos;s so unbelievab ... ly fast &amp; sleek that I&apos;m buying a second one for my wife during this &quot;sale&quot; by Blackberry again!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>rstack75</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Steal of a Deal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The price.

Cons: Non use of sim cards

I purchased the blackberry Wednesday for express delivery and it arrived the very next day, WoW! I couldn&apos;t wait to begin playing with it. The tablet is very sleek and well built which is not surprising being made by BlackBerry. It&apos;s definately user friendly for someone like myself who is a first time tablet user. I&apos;m still trying to figure out how to use my xfinity and neflix to watch movies, but nevertheless I&apos;m enjoying the use of it. Can&apos;t wait until more apps become available even though there&apos;s plenty of apps currently available on it. I&apos;m ordering one for my husband today. I will be recommending it to my family and friends. And one more thing, the sound on this table is phenominal!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BigOso</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An Amazing Tablet...as long as you know...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Elegant, Fast, Unrivaled Browsing Experience

Cons: Lack of apps (for now)

I have never written a review before, but I felt compelled to tell you a story. The story of the best purchase I have ever made. That being said, I will be FAIR and point out from the beginning that the PlayBook is NOT for everybody.

Some things to know about me:

- I own an IPAD 2
- I have never owned anything from Blackberry
- I love Android and its extensive market
- I like long walks on the beach....oh wait, I digress....
- This review hinges on the price remaining close to $200

If you are like me, you are reading this review because you were being diligent and doing your research to make sure the Playbook is the right fit for you. This won&apos;t be the only review ... you read, but let&apos;s start off with all the negatives you will undoubtedly come across:

- Lack of Apps: This isn&apos;t an IPAD or Android based tablet, so you won&apos;t have access to the THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS of apps on those systems. If you are an app junkie, walk away right now.
- Lack of built in Email/Calendar: I don&apos;t know how a company called Research in Motion didn&apos;t do any research into every other tablet ever made because they would have found that the lack of a native Email program/Calendar is an embarrassing oversight
- Power Button is really small
- Some people are bothered by its size
- Camera does NOT have LED flash

Ok now let&apos;s get to the good stuff:

- This thing multitasks better than my PC! LOL, for reals, it&apos;s amazing how you can run 5 or 6 different apps without skipping a beat. The OS on the PlayBook is simply superb in that respect.
- The screen is OUT OF THIS WORLD! Seriously, I have an Ipad 2 and the clarity, brightness, and colors are AT LEAST on par with it.
- While some people have complained about the size (Seriously, people, did you NOT look at the specs before you bought it? How do you even sleep at night after writing a review and complaining about the size when the rest of us are sitting here wondering what you thought you were buying?), I find the size perfect.
- It feels so ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ZebraCapb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price, easy to use, works amazing!

Cons: the iPad exists and people think its chocolate on a stick

This tablets hardware and software is about 50 times better than the iPad and more than 50% cheaper! The world is wasting its time focusing on the iPad while great tablets like this fall to the wayside. Please be an educated buyer and you will realize you get more for your money if you buy this instead of the iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kabir</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, great touch screen, runs very fast

Cons: App World

This is one of the best products I own. This product is is very easy to use and set up. The touch screen works great and it&apos;s very responsive. It has a front and rear camera, however the camera does not have a flash but that doesn&apos;t really matter to me. This device does have adobe flash so you can go on any site and it will look just like it would on a regular desktop or laptop. You can also watch videos on sites like youtube and megavideo. However hulu and netflix does not support blackberry yet. Also there are not many apps available to this device yet but it is fairly new and new apps are being introduced everyday. I bought it when it was on sale but it is definitely worth the price it is right now. I pr ... efer this over the iPad because of it&apos;s flash support. If you want a good tablet that is easy to use with many great and advanced features this is it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Playbook 32 gb tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I m really happy with my Playbook. I bought it during their sale recently. I read quite a few reviews on other sites before I bought it, and the main criticisms are the size and not enough apps. As far as the size, you know what you are buying ahead of time, and the picture is really excellent. I guess it depends on what size you prefer. I m not sure how many apps anyone needs, but it seems to have plenty. No Angry Birds though, which my kids want, and I would like a Skype app. The word on other sites is that an upgrade due out in Feb. 2012 will enable it to get more apps. The camera works great. The picture is excellent. The operating system is seemless. For the sale price, I think it was a great buy. Now if it was full price, I might want something with a large screen, and a usb port or ... micro sd port for storage.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not at all a good buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I am a veteran iPad user and a blackberry user for the past several years. I purchased Blackberry playbook based upon the reviews which I think were posted by RIM. I have had a terrible experience with the Playbook and found it totally useless unless one wants to use it to play video games.

Its on/off button is very hard. Battery shall drain away when its on the standby mode. NO EMAIL. Not many applications.

Conclusion: Not a good buy even for $100.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Totally excellent surprise!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Can t believe how cool this playbook turned out to be. Blackberry hit a homerun, and the shame is, no one knows. It was priced too high before, but after the big drop, a total steal! I ve had it for two weeks and I can honestly say I love it. Best part is the form factor, perfect to hold in your hands for typing, and the operating system blows iOS and Android right out of the water. The browser is like having a full sized laptop. Highly recommend at the $199 price point. Typed this review from my playbook, sitting on the couch!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>BlackBerry PlayBook 16 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/5640733186255610780/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.15&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=YYGRUMrDH4ivqAG6v4G4BA&amp;ved=0CJwCEPQCMAk4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dennis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet out of the Box</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It s easy to use out of box. Connected to my wireless network easily. Customer support helped me to upload and download files from my desktop using WIFI (fast, knowledgeable and courteous). The USB cable connection works just as well. Online videos and manuals are very helpful getting up to speed. I m completely satisfied after 1 week.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

