<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Redsox Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet, great price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fun; Portable; Engaging; Easy to Use; Attractive Design; Durable

We gave this tablet to our son for his birthday. I downloaded games and apps for him to have. For the price, it was a great investment. It works well and we have had no problems. The battery life isn&apos;t great, but that&apos;s no different than for any of the smartphones I have owned.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Champ&apos;s Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Battery life WAY TOO SHORT...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Fun; Portable; Engaging

Cons: Drains Batteries

BOUGHT THIS FOR MY 7-YEAR OLD, which is just fine -- used for math, spelling, Netflix, Angry Birds, Kindle Books, Nook Books, and whatever the Android Market offers. Had it since November -- testing it myself -- and gave it to my son on Christmas. I wouldn&apos;t recommend this for an adult who would use this tablet frequently, as the battery life is terrible (not more than 3-4 hours). It&apos;s heavier than other tablets in its class, and has a &quot;soft&quot; metal casing rather than a hard plastic. After rebate, price reduction, and replacement warranty, still paid UNDER $190 FOR all. You do get what you pay for -- out of the box there&apos;s no access to the Android Market, and no real useful apps pre-installed. However, (as ... a workaround) because you can connect your tablet to a computer using the USB connection, you can copy &amp; install &quot;apk&quot; files that enable you to get access to the Android Market, Netflix, and all those goodies -- without &quot;rooting&quot; the device and voiding the manufacturer&apos;s warranty (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BrWSC2uiAg). But hey, buy the Toys R Us replacement warranty, and you&apos;re good. So, yes, I love the USB port, and HDMI output. If you&apos;re up to installing the necessary files to gain access to the Android Market, you will save a lot of money. The MAJOR drawback is the battery life. Even with the WiFi turned off the battery doesn&apos;t last long. May have to root the device to reconfigure the settings to extend the battery life -- or consider returning it if my son&apos;s use of the tablet necessitates a better battery life. For myself, I bought the Novo 7 Advanced for $155, and am in heaven. Battery lasts for DAYS! And, it has the &quot;feel&quot; of an IPad (which I have thru my job) which is really great. The Customer Support is GREAT! However, if you need that extended &quot;bumper to bumper&quot; warranty consider paying that extra $100 to $150 and look to the Kindle Fire or Nook Color with the pre-installed apps &amp; buying ToysRUs extended warranty. Those are also great tablets -- less flexibility to manually install apps, but worth it if you&apos;re not a technical person.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NewAndroid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Toy for the $$$</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Inexpensive, good design, screen.

Cons: Battery life, Sleep Mode.

I have the 7022 for 2 weeks now. It is a great product for the price. Please note that you will have to invest some time to make it great. Install Market, Netflix, JuiceDefender..... etc. The tablet is responsive to touch, screen is easy to look at for hours. Only the two issues which prevented it from getting 5 stars. Battery life (only about 5 hrs) and tablet sometime will not wake up from sleep mode (reset button is in the back). 7022, a smart entry into the tablet experience.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bdub</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lasted less than a year</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable; Fun; Easy to Use

Cons: Drains Batteries; Poor Quality

I purchased the MID7022 from TRU in July 2011. It froze up in April 2012. Lasted less then a year. For the most part I liked this entry level lower cost tablet. My main reason for buying it was the inputs/outputs it had.

Pros
I could watch digital movies on TV via the HDMI output.
Angry Birds was fun to play.
Surfing the internet was fine.

Cons
Battery life wasn&apos;t that great.
Couldn&apos;t keep a constant wifi lock.
Resolution was subpar, words weren&apos;t sharp

I&apos;m glad I purchased the replacement plan. I received my gift card in less then a week.

Now I&apos;m torn. Do I take a chance and by the new Coby 10&quot; Kyros if TRU sells it or get something else. If I buy anothe ... r Coby from TRU I&apos;ll defintely purchase the replacement plan again.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jayswife</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would not buy this</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design

Cons: Difficult to Use

I purchased this as a Christmas gift for my husband. We have had a terrible time downloading any apps. The AppsLib does not work, it keeps coming up that there is server maintenance and that it is not compatible with the device. We also tried to get the android market on here since it does not come standard, this also did not work. So what we are left with is a small tablet for browsing the internet, definitely not worth the hassle. It is being returned today.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ron</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good bang for the buck</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight; Expandable memory; Front-facing Camera; VALUE; Adequate Storage; USB port; HDMI port

Cons: Poor Battery Life; Cannot View TIFF images; Needs a firmware update

I purchased this around Thanksgiving, on sale, and was surprisingly also given a gift card with my purchase. Considering the price and features the Mid7022 offers, it&apos;s probably the best value out there. It has a microSD card slot for up to 32Gb of memory expansion, allowing you to load lots of photos, videos or music onto the unit. This is a feature even the iPad doesn&apos;t offer. There is also an HDMI port, and mini USB port to connect it to your computer, for file transfer. Unfortunately, the Coby will not charge through the USB port; you have to use the included AC adapter. The screen is capacitive, ... rather than resistive, which supports multi-touch gestures, such as zooming. The screen&apos;s resolution could be better, although it is adequate for most non-critical applications. To my disappointment, I was not able to view my TIFF image files, which is how I store most of my photos. JPEGs worked fine, though. Battery life seems mediocre, which is apparently cause by the unit searching for cell service. The battery usage indicator shows &quot;cell standby&quot; battery usage at 77%. If Coby would get on the ball, and offer a firmware update to correct this problem, battery life would no longer be an issue. Coby, are you listening?? If you purchase a leather case online for the Coby, beware of the corner retainers covering up the home/menu and power buttons. All in all, I&apos;m quite satisfied with my purchase.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s A Steal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Fast; Quality Display; Easy to install apps; Well-built

Cons: Short Battery Life; No rear camera; Heavy; Only 3 megapixels

With a desktop, a notebook and a smartphone the last thing I needed was a tablet, but you know boys and their toys. Could not justify the cost of an iPad, and really didn&apos;t want anything that big, so the Kyros MID7022 seemed to be a good alternative. I had originally ordered the MID7125, and then started to investigate, and realized that a resistive touch screen was the wrong way to go, so I cancelled it and ordered the MID7022. 

Have been playing with it all day today, and I really can&apos;t find anything major enough to complain about. The screen is just about ideally sized, and the display is nice and sensitive. It seems to be well buil ... t, and easy to handle.

I have installed Android Market, Adobe Flash and a number of other apps. All went smoothly. If I have any complaints, the battery life could be better, and I wish it weighed a tad less. Other than that, I tink I am going to enjoy this little toy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chuck336</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Coby Tablet 7022-4G A Real Winner!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Outstanding Price for it&apos;s features and capabilities

I ordered the COBY 7022-4G from Best Buy’s Outlet store and it arrived under a week.

The 7022-4G in my opinion is an advance second generation tablet with a capacitive screen, which runs on Android 2.3, which in my view is the best for tablets until it gets further upgraded in the future; all this for under $180!

I have installed Flash 10, Android market and Netflix with no problem; as far as Hulu, some folks have been able to configure Hulu to run

I have installed Skype and Google phone, and they work with no problems for making phone calls through the tablet’s built-in microphone and speaker via WIFI.

I am using all my e-mail accounts and it provides a nice phone tone ring alert when you receive ... mail.

I installed several apps including CNN, FOX NBC, ABC and Amazon Kindle. I have also installed a power saver app for saving battery usage by turning off some applications. The unit now runs about 7-8 hours on its battery. The strangest thing about the tablet is that it identifies the biggest battery user as being the “Cell phone”, although it does not come with any cell phone capability. Who knows what’s inside this tablet, could be a built-in feature that would eventually be enabled in the future?

I purchased a nice carrying case for 7” tablets that came with a small 8” wide keyboard, with a leg support to hold the tablet up in front of the keyboard, all for under $20. You can also purchase an ultra mini USB hub and connect a mouse to the unit aside with the keyboard (try to do that with you IPAD).

The tablet’s 7” size is perfect for carry. It feels solid and has rounded corners to slip nicely into a pants pocket without jagging or for that matter a purse.

Overall, the 7” size sure beats the large 10” errs out there for convenience or for that matter the 4” phones for viewing.

I feel that COBY has a real winner here, and I am really surprise that Best Buy sells it only through its Outlet Store.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>maylea</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Entry Level/Price for 3 year old</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price; Screen; Simplicity

Cons: Wake issues; Weight; Quirky sensor

There is nothing else available with these specs at this price, period. This is a great tablet for those who have been using android for a while and know how to modify it for their own personal preferences. Plays any movie I throw at it using rock player. This was purchased for my 3 year old for her educational games and videos after I caught her squinting at her ipod touch. After a few adjustments to the settings, the battery life is good and the screen is bright and responsive. She has already learned the controls and asks for it instead of the ipod. Is this a Galaxy Tab or Ipad. No. Do you need to be somewhat literate in android. Yes. Is it worth the time and effort to learn how to get the mo ... st out of this sub 200 tab? Most definitely. For us on a budget, this is wonderful and cheap enough to buy another tablet when needed.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>playnex</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Device for college!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything!!!! Android 2.3 Gingerbread people!!!!

Cons: ummmm......only comes in 1 size i guess...

im one of those people who study a device before they even think about buying it. One of those people who know every last spec. about the device. One of those people who know the name of the device from beginning to end. Im a Electronic nerd. lol Anywho.... I rate this device 4 1/2 out of 5. Thats becuase nothing in the world is perfect. There are 3 main reasons i chose this tablet over competiting netbooks, laptops, tablets. 1rst. Price. It offers a great amount of utilites for a price of just 179.99 which adds up to 202.00 after tax and standard shipping. 2nd, It looks sexy. sleek black finish and a nice webcam intergration. 3rd, Android 2.3 Gingerbread!!! Thats all you ... need. 512 (ram). Most netbooks have that. Do you people see how great of an investment this is??? Anywho. Being as though i go to college, I need something that is book bag friendly, can keep up with my constant facebook I.M.ing, Word typing and battery saving lifestyle. I attend 2 writing classes. I bought a keyboard carrying case usb extention for this tablet. It works great and i recomemend it for anyone who needs to have that pysical keyboard. And dont let it not having a physical keyboard change your mind. It has a great on screen keyboard. And even if you do happen to spend that 40 dollars to buy the physical keyboard carrying case. Your still spending under 400 hundred on a great study tablet. Anyways!!! I rate this 4 1/2 out 5.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kgirl555</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>If you do it, but the best buy warranty!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, great for a kids first tablet

Cons: dealing with Coby Support!

NIGHTMARE!!!!

Bought this for my 12 year old for her birthday in February, last week the screen froze and you couldn&apos;t unlock using the unlock pattern or power off. Let it completely die and recharged hoping that would reset it....nope! Finally called Coby support. WASTED 1 hour of my life on HOLD waiting for someone to answer. Finally someone answered and he was a complete JERK! Yes, spoke English...American East Coast Support, but total jerk! Gave me an attitude and treated me like a moron even though I have a degree in Computer Networking and am well versed in computer technology.

So he tells me how to do a hard power off/reboot on this device. Got to the root menu and tells me ... to wipe it, but failed to mention that doing so, (as with most computers) will wipe any data off the system. Most consumers would like to know ahead of time right??? Anyway, got that done and got it to the home screen, but screen still not responding properly to touch. So he tells me he needs to give me the warranty information. Not only do I have to pay for a trackable shipping to send it back to them, but I also need to include a $15 money order for them to ship a new one back to me. I said 3 months ago I paid $200 for this thing now I have to pay over $20 to exchange something I don&apos;t even want anymore??? He said &quot;yup&quot;. Gave me all the info and says he&apos;ll transfer me to the address information, which is basically a recording of their address so he doesn&apos;t have to give it to me with his own mouth. NEVER ONCE did he say Thank you, or sorry, or anything. I WILL NEVER BUY A COBY PRODUCT AGAIN NO MATTER WHAT GREAT TECHNOLOGICAL STRIDES THEY MAKE!

Additionally, it did work fine for my daughter and she loved it, but I think it was too expensive for 3 months of use and the Coby support and Manufacturer warranty shipping fees are ridiculous!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>frustrated</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>*****DO NOT BUY THIS PRODUCT*****</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Poor Quality

Purchased this item for my 5 year old at Christmas. We experienced trouble connecting to the wifi upon set-up. Tried to reach Coby customer support multiple times and never heard back. Even sent an email to them once I finally connected after the help of an IT Manager I work with and asked Coby how to remove the naked women applications. While I realize this item may not be intended for a 5 year old I certaintly would not expect naked women to be loaded on something purchased from Toys R Us. The email was sent to Coby in January, it is now March, and no reply. After about 6 times using the tablet the screen locked up. I had to let the power drain for the item to shut off. Thankfully, I purchased the extended warrenty for TRU. I called Coby and was told to mail a $ ... 15.00 money order along with the product. It&apos;s now been close to 3 weeks in which Coby has had the product back in their warehouse per my USPS tracking #. I called to check status and was told to check back in early April. I started to complain and state this is unacceptable and the csr hung up on me. I called Coby headquarters and the &quot;operator&quot; was busy and requested I leave a message. Are you kidding me, does this company really think customer service is a joke? Well guess what, I will never buy another item in my lifetime with the Coby brand and I sure would not recommend anyone else ever buy from this manufacturer. I have been on the phone since the csr hung up on me trying to get a supervisor and the lines are so busy that it hangs up on me and requests I try back at a later time. I would not recommend anyone ever by this product.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable; Attractive Design; Portable; Easy to Use; Fun

I brought this so my husband would have a tablet. I have an iPad. This was so very surprisingly just about as good! Really easy .but turn off the rotator until u get use to it.if you&apos;ve never had a tablet .watch videos on coby website and utube to find out how to use. I am impressed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Like Technology</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Problem solved</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fun; Portable; Attractive Design; Easy to Use; Engaging

Cons: Not durable for one

I purchased 3 Coby&apos;s @ [$]each. I received them in good time for Christmas and opened each one, charged it, set it up for wireless and all worked fine. On Christmas, one of the three choose that moment to stop working. We took it back to the local Toys R Us and they fortunately had one in stock and replaced it immediately. The new one works fine and everyone was happy. Slightly inconvenient but all worked out in the end.I also purchased the 2 year extended warranty so hopefully, if anything else happens it will be just that easy to get them fixed. Thank you.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Scooter74</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Price POOR Design Features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Priced at [$] When I purchased it, it seemed like a good deal. Reviews were fair but suggested some caution. REVIEWS didn&apos;t go far enough.Basic design flaw that is HORRIBLE - Back, Menu and Home are BUTTONs. First unit Home button lasted less than 1 day. Back button (Silver Button below Screen) is noisy. First Unit also has one bad pixel that stands out like a sore thumb as it is always one (Blue white dot)Waiting for 2nd unit to arrive - will not hesitate to request refund/different product if this one has any issues.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price &amp; Quality

Cons: Wish it had GPS and bluetooth.

No other Tablet PC will match the perfomance of this device for the price you will pay. As other reviews have noted, you can easily update it to Android Market Place (search Kyros mid-7022 on U-tube for step by step instructions and links to the needed softeware...I have included a link at the bottom of this review) and add Adobe Flash Player 10.3 to make this tablet equal to others that are priced hundreds of dollars more.

Coby has other tablets for sale, but this is the only one I have found that has the multi-touch capacitive touch screen just like the iPad.

If you get a mini-hdmi chord you can attach the Coby Kyros to your HD television and watch movies in 1080 HD. I had a mini-hdmi chord from my ... HD Camcorder that works perfectly. The only problem you will find is that the sound comes out of the Kyros speakers and the tv. To get around this problem, just plug in head-phones into your Kyros.

Get a 32g micro-sd card. You can find one for around $40 on Bestbuy and other web sites. With 36 gb total storage, HDMI out, and a price tag around $200 (with the micro-sd card)... kinda makes the more expensive tablets look stupid.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>zamale</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good prodct but....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight

Cons: Short Battery Life

Bought this for my 4 year old for his birthday to keep him off of our iPads. Had to return the first one because after one day 1/3 of the touch screen stopped working. The new one works perfectly, so I guess we just got a bad one the first time. 

As for the product itself. The battery life is pretty short, the apps are very limited. It looks and works just like my Droid X phone, only bigger. I am a little ticked off I can&apos;t get a Netflix app for it or flash (both of which I have on my phone so I know they exisit!)

It is a great product for the price though. My 4 year old loves it and can play all his little games, like Angry Birds. I am thinking about getting one for my 85 year old grandma because she keeps taking my mo ... m&apos;s iPad. It is not for a tech savvy person who wants or needs everything, but it is great for beginers, especially at that price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PipingMasterExpert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What more can you ask for &lt;$175?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price and ease of use

Cons: Volume Level, WIFI speed

1) The screen definitely needs some getting used to but after a while it ceases to be a problem

2) Google search &quot;how to install Android Market on Coby Mid7022&quot; and there is a step-by-step guide on how to get it setup. Takes about 10 mintues max.

3) The internet is not as fast as IPAD and Galaxy but what do you expect for 65% less in price?

4) The volume is not loud enough. That&apos;s my main complaint</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Passionate tech maven</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great 7&quot; Android tablet for under $200</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Current Operating System; HDMI USB and WiFi; Multi-touch screen; Lightweight; Powerful; Fast; Quality Display

Cons: Doesn&apos;t make me coffee; Wakes up on its own

To find a 7&quot; capacitive (multi-touch) screen, 1GHz processor, 512MB of RAM, with both USB and HDMI for under $200 is a great deal. Not only that, but it comes with Android 2.3.4.
You do not have to root this device to make it work well. If you have any other Android phone or tablet, it is easy to backup the Android market and any apps, upload them to Dropbox (for free) and install them on this. YouTube has easy to follow videos to do whatever you want with it.
We watch Netflix movies, run any app, and mirror it on a TV at 1080p.
For the price, this &quot;can do&quot; device is unmatched. It&apos;s just like the Sam ... sung Galaxy Tab for half the price.
I&apos;m very pleased with the purchase.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Barbie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well worth it....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality Display; Fast; Capacitive screen

Love, Love, LOVE this tablet. I was looking for something comparable to my hubby&apos;s Samsung Galaxy but for a much cheaper price. I shopped around and only saw this tablet with a restrictive screen at other major retailers but was so excited when I saw that this one is capacitive. It is very easy to navigate and an easy transition if you have a droid phone. I mainly wanted it for internet, games, music and skype. Everything works great except for skype (I had to download it from an outside site bc it doesnt come with it). Its definitely worth the money. I have yet to find another capacitative tablet with 512 RAM for under $200. Great deal...you should get it :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>busymom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love/hate</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Fun; Engaging; Portable

Cons: Poor Quality

I had this tablet for 9 lovely months. My kids LOVED it, it was easy to use and never let me down... then it just stopped working. I went to turn it on and it stayed on the &quot;COBY&quot; screen. I tried EVERYTHING to fix it but there is nothing that can be done. It is dead :( It will be missed! BTW this was my second tablet, I returned the first after 2 weeks when the speakers stopped working... my next tablet will NOT be a Coby!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>oblio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth every penny with some work.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As is, out of the box this tablet is pretty useless. If you are willing to do a little research and a little modification you can easily get the full android market and flash installed. Once you make a few ajustments to the tablet it rivals anything on the market for the price (by the way, wait for it to be on sale). The only true and accurate critcism is the battery life is not the greatest but if you are spending more than 3-4 hours on a tablet you have bigger issues in your life ;).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>isdept</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Meh...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Wanted to try an Android tablet and figured an inexpensive Gingerbread device was a good place to start. Mistake.
Surfing, streaming video from a nas box, copying files from a microsd card have all been painful.
It plays Angry Birds well (make sure to set volume before running game).
If left for a few days, the battery will be dead.
So far, me no likey :(</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>luvnll414</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not worth it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design

Cons: Poor Quality

If your looking for a tablet that does absolutely nothing this is perfect. The market is VERY limited as it is not the full android market. It wont load most internet pages bc it wouldnt accept adobe flash. It was just useless. We traded it in for the KIndle Fire and for a little more $$ it was totally worth it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tears on Christmas Morning</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Terrible Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Difficult to Use; Poor Quality

The Coby would not connect to the APP Store although we had access to the internet. I spent the entire Christmas day with my son, trying to figure this out. With tears in his eyes, he asked me to see if Santa could get him a new one. I took the Coby back and bought a Kindle Fire. Nothing but succcess since then. This product is not good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>riozavarce</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hesitant About Coby Tablets</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: No Money Back Policy; Bad Experience with Coby; Poor Quality

I bought two of the MID7012 models as Christmas presents for my son&apos;s Godparents and after they opened their presents and tried the tablets, I was so embarrassed about the tablets&apos; performance and quality that I took them back to returned them to the store. To my surprise, I couldn&apos;t get my money back because the store&apos;s policy is no money back; only the same product and sometimes they can make an exception and give you store credit. So, now, I&apos;m stuck with a [$] gift card that I&apos;ll use the next Christmas, I guess.It was a mistake buying at Toy R US. Very aggravating experience. I couldn&apos;t get my money back to go to another store to buy another present.I also called Coby for tech support and their lines were very con ... gested and when somebody finally picked up my call, she said that she could only take my information and open a ticket and somebody would call me back within 48 hours. No way!Moral: Don&apos;t buy Coby Tablets unless you test them yourself. Don&apos;t buy at Toys R US unless it&apos;s a product that you&apos;re sure about because Toys R US doesn&apos;t return your money.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Parent Shopper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Shopping Parent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small and portable

Cons: Drains Batteries

This product is very user friendly and a good start first tablet pc. I bought for my son and he love&apos;s it. I would strongly recommend this product for parents with children in middle, and high school.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Annoyed!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Product, But No more Toys R Us!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use

Cons: Toys R Us will Not Refund

The product is nice, everything I expected, however, I wanted to return it (oh, and I bought 2) because our children changed their minds on what they wanted for Christmas only to find out that online items returned to the store recieve store credit only!!!!!! Even with receipt!!!!! Buyers beware!!!! If you are unsure you want to purchase from Toys R Us online I would seriously think about it. They own your money once you purchase online regardless of reciept or not!!!!! My business now belongs to [@]. Sorry Toys R Us you have to do better than this to keep my business!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>binarybro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My granddaughters love them!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Long Battery Life; Quality Display

Granddaughters are 9 and 7 years old. Battery life has not been an issue. After about two weeks of use the tablets still function fine. There&apos;s a youtube video that guides a person in force feeding flash to the tablets allowing additional internet content to be viewed. Granddaughters use them to surf the web, receive email, listen to music, watch youtube videos etc.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>IT Pro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful; Fast; Comfortable Keyboard; Quiet; Quality Display; Lightweight

Cons: Short Battery Life

This is a very nice and solidly built tablet. With a few mods, you can get the full Android Market. Haven&apos;t found an app that I couldn&apos;t make work yet. Only problem is battery life. Looks like the firmware is looking for cell activity, which the tablet does not have. This is a major drain on the battery. With WiFi on, I only get a little over 3 hours. Aside from that, it&apos;s great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Butch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Quality Display

Cons: Short Battery Life

Overall it&apos;s a good tablet for the price, a capacitive touch for less than 200 with a 1 gig processor, android 2.3. Cons, battery life is poor, wi-fi will occasionally drop out, need to re-boot to get it working..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would like it better if it worked.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I bought the tablet about a month ago. For the first several weeks it worked well. Recently it began having problems. From power on to the home screen was normal but touching an icon does nothing and touching the launcher screen button produces 5 small white squares instead of the launcher screen. The reset button doesn&apos;t help. Power off and restart doesn&apos;t help. Finally factory reset doesn&apos;t help. I called Coby tech support and they said to return it. So I exchanged it for a new one. I charged up the new tablet and powered it up. This new tablet was having exactly the same problem. About one time it 10 it will correctly go to the application but the other times will not. So either I happen to be extremely unlucky and have found the only two tablets that have problems or the problem is ... very widespread. I would suggest all potential buyers think about this carefully [...]
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Vance</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Coby cpapcitive mid7022</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Exc hackability; Lots of 3rd party support; Inexpensive but well mad

Cons: Not for the non-techy

This Android tablet is not bad out of the box, given the capacitive touch screen (as opposed to a resistive screen, which depends on actual pressure to activate icons, etc.). Gingerbread 2.3.3 is a decent OS, and the Coby&apos;s specs are pretty good.I like it for the hacks. I&apos;ve installed full Google market, ClockworkMOD for backups and ROM installations, and various other kina techy goodness.It&apos;s a bargain at [$]. I suppose there will be other, better tablets coming down the road, but that&apos;s how it goes with technology. However, it&apos;s not an iPad. It can give you an excellent tablet experience if you keep your expectations in the sub-$200 bracket. You get 85% of the capability a ... t 33% of the price.Not bad. Not bad at all....
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Entry level tablet has good features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality Display; Lightweight; Fast

Cons: Short Battery Life

Getting aviation weather forecasts, checking e-mail, getting news. Boots up and shuts down quickly and gets WI-FI easily. Needs much better manual, nothing on-line for this model MID7022. e-mail is limited.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TO Deb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Deal</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Quality Display

This is the only place that sells this newer version of this tablet. Bought for my 4 year old Grandson so he would leave my iphone alone to play Angry Birds. He loves it and already knows how to turn it on and use the screen to get to Angry Birds. It has a very clear screen great grahics, it is a steal for the price, get one before they are gone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechnoGeek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for everyone...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Well Worth the Money; Fast; Powerful; Lightweight

Cons: Can&apos;t Upgrade; No Bluetooth; No Android Market; Short Battery Life

I have been using this device for about three days and the more I use it the more I like it. If you want a tablet that just works then you may want to look else where... If you are a do-it-yourselfer then you may find this tablet very interesting. The first thing I strongly recommend you do is install Android Market! I followed the advice of an earlier post and searched for &quot;kyros 7022 market&quot;, I discovered it was very easy to install. Some of the apps I installed with Appslib and [...] Appstore either would not install or would crash when started. The same apps from Android Market installed and worked just fine. If you want to watch videos you will ... have to install one of the free video players like Mobo player.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>marvinwv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>tech nerd review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality Display; Powerful; Long Battery Life; Lightweight; Capacitive multi-touch; Fast

Cons: 32gb microSD format time

i have had this about 24 hrs and it seems great. i loaded adobe flash player from freewarelovers com/android with no issues. 
i had a 32gb microSD on hand and if you are going to use it be ready to give it time to get the card ready to use. while it is doing this the tablet will lock up but when it is done it is ready to go so let it sit while you do other things. other smaller cards like a 2gb will be ready in seconds.
the kobo ereader covers work well enough if you are interested.
you can also get kindle or nook from other sites like the one above. i tried the installed appslib and they want to access my paypal which isnt a prob it is tha ... t they want to set up a payment of $200.00 with a 1000 time refill rate??? odd so i didnt do it.
system has been working great and i got one for my wife instead of an ebook reader and one for me. i am downloading a movie from solarmovies so that will be ready later.. 
very fast loading system and great apps.. angry birds works great as well lol
GREAT DEAL FOR THE MONEY!!! BTW CAPACITIVE SCREEN IS AWSOME!! if you dont know what that means then basically it is a screen like the ipad with multi touch.. otherwise you would be stuck with a resistive screen which is less responsive.. 
I cant wait to try the HDMI out port as well.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>juju8409</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best in Class</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Powerful; Lightweight; Quiet; Quality Display

Cons: Short Battery Life

I have been looking for a budget tablet months now but the resistive screen was a HUGE turnoff.
When i heard of this new tablet from Coby I rushed to buy one.
Its fast and fun... my only complaints are battery life and some apps force close.
Overall, i love it and recommend! I wasnt expecting an iPad but i am more than happy with this!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cstarr728</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW-best tablet out there under $200!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Capacitive Touch Screen; Fast; Powerful; Quality Display

We purchased this Coby mid7022 7 inch tablet for our son&apos;s 5th birthday. He wanted something like a iPad. After researching tablets under $250 this was the best I could find for what it does. It has the multi/ capacitive touch screen which is like using a iPad or iPod. The resistive touch pads are difficult to maneuver so I wanted to definitely get a table with the capacitive touch. I like that it came installed with 2.3 android. After getting this table home &amp; trying it out we all were amazed at how fast it was. Installing games, 3d wallpapers, looking at [...] it quickly flies through the pages and quickly downloads. Surprised me considering most tablets i&apos;ve used are slower, this runs like a dream. ... The screen brightness looks great outdoors and indoors. It comes preinstalled with several great apps already and lots of games on the app store loaded on the tablet. My son had no problem working it as soon as he got it right out of the box he was downloading Angry Birds (which is FREE in the app store!) Watching movies, playing games, surfing the web-you name it, it basically does it all. We love that it takes micro sd cards up to 32 gig. The tablet feels sturdy and not cheap made at all. Its screen navigates easily with the flick or touch of the pad of your finger and its almost impossible to put this tablet down once you play on it. My oldest son, my Hubby and myself are now all wanting one for our ownselves! Oh and before I forget Toys R Us were the only store that we could find that had this specific model plus they had a deal going to receive a $25 gift card with the purchase! My 5 year old has yet to want to put this tablet down he says it was the best birthday ever!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buggy and not worth it to me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Cons: Low resolution screen; Freezes Up; Wireless issues

This thing locked up on me a few times. The wireless slows down extremely after it sleeps and the web pages didn&apos;t look too great at that resolution. I got rid of it and bought a nook color. I rooted that and made it my tablet and I&apos;m soooo glad I did.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alaska99801</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great steal andvalue for options and price...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Capacitive screen; Android 2.3

Cons: Nothing so far

I bought this tablet just to check it out. I am surprised that it is not mentioned at the Coby Kyros website.
At the Kyros site the closest to this is the MID7024-4G, but there are differences between the two.
The 7022-4G selling at Best Buy has all the options and memory of the 7024, but it has one thing going for it that was the catalyst that made me buy it.
At this price level, all Android tablets come with a resistive screen. You have to push hard with your nails or with a stylus. This one, MID7022-4G has a capacitive screen, you just have to swipe it softly. Just like the iPad (it is not an iPad, look at the price), the Samsung Galaxy Tab, but at one half the price and you pretty much can do everything th ... e Galaxy Tab can do, again, at a much cheaper price.
Of course, the built is not as quality as the Samsung (not mentioning the iPad because that is a different type of device. I mention the Samsung because both are running Android), but the Samsung runs Android 2.2, and the 7022-4G runs Android 2.3, which has been improved quite a bit to run better on tablets and bigger screens.

I have had it for two weeks and no problems so far. It is the only Android tablet I know below $200 that has a capacitive screen, android 2.3 and a 1GHZ processor (most tablets in this price range come with processors running at 800MGHz or less) ,with 512GB of ram. That put this inexpensive tablet up there with other androids costing two or three times as much.
Having this fast processor will allow you to play the games that you could not play with tablets having low powered processors. It plays Angry Birds (if you care about that) very smoothly and any other one you throw at it.
Some people will complaint that it does not have the official Android Market. But who needs it today? It comes with the Appslib store, you can also load the Amazon appstore, you can bookmark in your browser this site, freewarelovers.com, and with those three you will have all the apps you will need.

So, for t ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TOOL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>NOT TO BAD....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Inexpensive

this is a decent little tab. it does all the basics &amp; then some. Features the &quot;non google&quot; android market which is not bad at all. Thousands of app&apos;s &amp; games are avaiable. Does not come with &quot;flash&quot; installed however the dl is out there, find it, install it &amp; your good to go. Does just about everything, if not everything that the other do, but at almost half the cost. It has a reset button on the back, good thing because you&apos;ll need it. [...] i say give this tab a try. You&apos;ll be happy you did &amp; even more happy that you didnt eND you blowing a few more hundread on AN IPAD for example.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Engaging; Easy to Use; Fun; Portable; Durable; Attractive Design; 411 Jelly Bean Update

Cons: Drains Batteries

For being a low-end device, this tablet comes with a 4.1.1 Jelly Bean update. What else does it need? It&apos;s a great tablet for starters. The touch-screen is responsive to every touch.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sorry I purchased this device</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Do not purchase</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design; Small

Cons: Lack out download areas; Battery last about 30min; Drains Batteries; Poor Quality

The person who I purchased the gift for does not like it because it is not very user friendly, nad the battery does not allow long time use, unless you are sitting next to a plug. Especially since the power cord is really short.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rick3418</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good unit but lacking a bit</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: wifi, browsing, email

Cons: generic androd operating system. limits on what app you can use

Netflix doesn&apos;t work on this unit, Its a good unit, does most things but it does get frustrating that its not totally compatible. Google play is a pain to down load but you learn most apps don&apos;t work on this tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>thenurse</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for me!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Honestly, nothing

Cons: Android apps not available

Was very disappointed with this product. Returned it to Best Buy for a refund (less my $8.99 shipping). The return was really easy and I have no complaints there. I tried several times to get Android apps which apparently aren&apos;t compatible with this device according to the on-screen message. Could view Facebook, but couldn&apos;t post or comment. I could get to my email inbox but couldn&apos;t open emails. This is probably suitable for someone more tech savvy who knows how to work around these issues. I don&apos;t have the knowledge, time or patience for that. Trusted the reviews before my purchase but it didn&apos;t take long to realize that I&apos;d made a big mistake!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wito</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>PIECE OF JUNK</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: NOTHING IS GREAT ABOUT IT.

Cons: NOT GREAT AT ALL JUST JUNK.

I purchased two of this Coby Kyros Tablet for my kids. What piece of junk this is not even good to keep the kids happy. I can&apos;t believe people have rate this as good becasue it&apos;s not please believe me. I wish I would of NEVER purchased this so mad becasue I can&apos;t even return it. Stuck with something that NO ONE wants to use. What a waste of my hard earn MONEY.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kitty witty</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>this thing is so stupied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable

Cons: Drains Batteries; Difficult to Use; Flimsy; Boring; Poor Quality

this thing is stupied i got it for christmas 2 years ago it worked for 2 days and then the screan would not work and it took 2 weeks to get the return slip and i just got the gift card for a new one today.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>COBY Tablet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DO NOT BUY</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Poor Quality

DO NOT BUY THIS TABLET. First of all is not upgradeable. This Android tablet cannot be update to the latest OS. Also, I purchased this tablet because it had a camera and wanted to use it for Skype but Skype cannot be used on this OS. Also, I&apos;ve only had this since November 2001 and now IT STOPPED WORKING!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty good for the $$$</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Purchased this tablet for my son.

He loves all the games and the ability to surf the net. I added an additional 4 GB of ram.

WiFi is great has a good 250-300 foot range.
Plays Mp3 and Mp4 very well and their are tons of apps that work on this 4/5 apps work.

Even Skype works on it so he can call his mother or me from home or school.

Does consume some power but if you de-activate WiFi while reading an E-Book its good.

Doesnt support Macromdia flash, but youtube videos and all the sorts run great.

Overall i was impresed after reading a few bad reviews on this unit i think for the money this is a great little bundle.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gulten</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>horrible</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Bought it for my son.Horrible tablet.You can&apos;t get any good android game.All the games are not easy to play except angry bird.I can&apos;t afford [$] angry bird game.So decided to return it,but they said any open electronic cannot be returned.I wanted to upgrade to kindle fire but they don&apos;t have it.So they didn&apos;t give me a store credit either.I will never buy anything from toysrus again.[@] has the same things at a cheaper price and their return policy is alot flexible.Toysrus failed in customer service.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not what I expected for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Fun; Portable

Cons: Poor Quality; Drains Batteries; Bulky

PROS: Easy to useCONS: The battery life is horrible compare to the [@]Fire which is only $30 more. The batter is drain after 2-3 hours of use.No Android Market. I had to download it and install it myself, but most of the apps are not compatible with the chip.Screen is blurry compare to the [@]Fire.Can&apos;t turn off the cellular feature to save battery since the unit doesn&apos;t support calls.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Disappointed Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Poor Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design

Cons: Difficult to Use; Poor Quality

This thing was not worth the money..The only reason I even gave 3 stars is because of the excellent customer service I received at the Asheville, NC store when I returned it. They graciously took the item back even though it was an opened electronics item. They were only able to do merchandise credit as stated on the website for online returns in store. I was fine with that as it gave my 5 yr old a Toys R Us shopping spree. Thank you Toys R Us of Asheville.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>did not work</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Poor Quality

purchased as a christmas gift did not work, returned it to toys r us would not refund money because it was opened, in order to know it does not work must be opened gave store gift credit which we purchased a kindle fire that is excellent, whch i will be urchasing another one but not from toys r us. At the time of returniing item four other people were returning same item for same reason. I had purchased an extended warranty and would not refund the [$] what a racket. I will never purchase another item from toys r us again. Store manager very nasty to customers</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fwqlaweg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>i don&apos;t like it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>you gave me really horrible thing
sometimes its touchpad is wrong
I can&apos;t unlock and use it
and I can&apos;t even use the internet
because it is so slow
ah. .. I really regret my stupid behavior
I could buy much better thing</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Barb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not worth it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: None

Cons: Poor Quality

Bought this for my 9 year old for Christmas after reading all the good reviews. I was very disappointed to say the least. Could not get apps. to download. The only thing my son could do basically is use the camera. We asked someone from Geek Squad to see if we could find out what we need to do to get it up and running. Their first question was - &quot;Did you buy this used?&quot; We replied: &quot;No, bought it on line from ToysRUs.&quot; They said it was obviously a used tablet and we would not be able to download any apps. because of what had been done to it. We tried to exchange it at Toys R Us, but they were out of stock. Tried to get my money back, but since I bought it on line, they would not give a refund. Needless to say, Toys R Us has lost my busi ... ness.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Really really mad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Horrible Online Shopping Experience!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>i tried to buy this for my husband for Christmas. Toys R Us said it was available for store pickup, and stupid me thought it was like other store&apos;s &quot;ship to store&quot; option, which i thought was safer than delivering to my house. Well, i placed the order with no problem, only to get an email 20 minutes later saying my order had been cancelled, no explanation given. i called customer service and was on hold for 25 minutes, and when i finally got to speak to someone i was told that the item wasn&apos;t available in the store i had chosen for pickup, so my order was cancelled. Why couldn&apos;t they have called or sent an email asking if i wanted to change my shipping my option, instead of automatically cancelling it?? So the customer service rep goes on to say how i won&apos;t be charged- but TOO BAD TOYS R ... US ALREADY PROCESSED THE ACH HOLD. So now i have to wait 5 business days for the money to be put back in my account before i can afford to order another one, and the way these things are selling out everywhere i will be very surprised if i can find one. i can tell you this, it WON&apos;T be from Toys R Us!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TroyH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great specs but poor implementation</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Freezes Up; Slow; Too Hot

I was looking for a sub $200 tablet when I found the Coby MID7022 at Toys &apos;R Us for [$] gift card. The specs on it were great. I bought it in July 2011. However, it wasn&apos;t long until I wished I had anted up the extra dough for a different tablet (especially with Toys &apos;R Us&apos; return policy on electronics (you open it, it&apos;s yours). And there was not one in the store to test drive. Though the specs looked great, the screen was not as crystal clear as it should have been. Just to get past the lock screen, I had to swype it 2-4 times. The wi-fi was extremely slow and/or dropped. It locked up &amp; I had to reset it many times. No, I didn&apos;t root it or modify it. The last straw was last week when the top 1.5 inches of the screen stopped responding. Lucki ... ly, I had purchased the product replacement plan. They&apos;re taking it back and sending me a gift card for Toys &apos;R Us. I&apos;m now the proud owner of a Nook Tablet.If you want to use it as an e-reader or entry tablet for a child, this will suffice. Other than that, look around and try out a few others first.Be wary of the return policy!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>my kids mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Defective Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Wifi doesn&apos;t work

Tried it before giving as a gift. Doesn&apos;t work. Turns on but not much else. Called help line and took to local store they determined that the wifi card is bad in it. Sent back for replacement, waiting............
Glad I tried it before giving as a gift.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jerry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Android Table for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I got Market, Facebook and Netflix working on it with minor effort. It&apos;s the best sub [$] tablet you&apos;ll find for the specs, especially the multitouch capacitive screen. Works great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>patrick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>very good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This one comes with a capacitive screen-that is the only type you should buy. The resistive type screen is awkward to use-not very responsive. I had a Coby 7015 with the resistive type-it works-but you&apos;ll get frustrated if you use it much.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>corona tech</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bang for your buck tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful; Fast

I have owned this product for a week with no problems. It is as advertised. Fast, hackable, and most of all, cheap. I was not expecting an iPAD. I would recommend this to anyone on a budget but desires a quality tablet. They are going fast so get them while you can.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mecinoid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice unit for the price...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast start up, ease of use and it takes care of most of my daily needs.

Cons: Screen in bright sunlight. However it does have brightness control. It works better if you have some shade.

Very pleased with this device. It allows me to quickly log into my email, watch a movie via device or on my 50&quot; Plasma 1080 TV with real clarity, play MP3 music, surf the internet anywhere there is wifi coverage etc...

Very nice unit. The quality is good.
I did not want to carry a 10&quot; tablet and this 7&quot; is just about right in my opinion for using every day. The screen is big enough to see a song playing of the MP3 player while heading down the road in my car. It only takes a split second to read just like a radio face would allow you to do. I like the fact that I can read word ... or excel docs with additional free application that you get through applib that comes installed.

I have no need for 3 or 4GLTE service at $50-80 monthly so that wasn&apos;t a need for me. Maybe when service fees come down I&apos;ll buy a wifi mobile hot spot and it will give me connection to up to 5 wireless devices like this one to surf the net. However, finding open wifi is easier and easier these days so, why pay the fees?
I&apos;d like to write again on how happy I am with start up speed and shutdown speed. I hate booting up my laptop all the time to just check emails etc.. So, this device really helps me save time everyday. I like the fact that Android 2.3 allows you to delete email as you go. That really helps me clearing out my email box quickly.

I heard about this through college students online.
It works to listen. ;-)

Tech seems to get better and better.

The only thing that would make this better for me is a portfolio cover with built in keyboard. Touch screen keyboard can be slow with my fat fingers at times and a film keyboard would be really nice.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TayMay27</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Its a nice product for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Nothing...yet

This is a very useful tablet, and you could install android market from the web! But for hulu and Netflix, you have to use third party apps for those two. But other wise, its great, and the only tablet below $300 with a capative touch screen.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ktakis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet overall</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight; Quality Display; Comfortable Keyboard; Long Battery Life; Fast; Powerful; Best tablet for the buck

Cons: none

The MID7022 is the sucessor of the MID7015, there is no tablet on the market in this price range that does what this tablet does. 

With a little modification you can run full flash on this tablet, and fast, 3D games, office, everything. Its zip speed fast, if i had the choice i rather get 5 of these then 1 of the other expensive brands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jon Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You Get What You Pay For</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Android 23; Battery

Cons: No Back Camera; Small Memory; No Android Market

This is great for any kid, but for an adult, you don&apos;t have much memory on this, only a front camera, and no android market. Also there&apos;s not a lot of after market items for this such as leather cases, accessories.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KVarth</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Coby doesn&apos;t know they make it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>The touch screen isn&apos;t quite right and when we turned it off the password ended up something we hadn&apos;t put in. No prob just reset, nothing on web site, or in paperwork, the customer service don&apos;t recognize they make this product. After 2 weeks of constant we&apos;ll get back in 2 days (they don&apos;t) they finally today 7/18 had someone who recognized the product, and the reset doesn&apos;t work on this unit, though several coby employess claimed their might not be a reset. Now they want another 3 weeks to ship it back for them to repair (we used it for two hours and have been fighting with Coby ever since), Not good customer service if there is a problem. And honestly how can resetting be a problem!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Concord dad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Warning DON&apos;T BUY THIS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Slow.....
Hard to use touch screen. (its ok if you have small fingers)
not able to download anything 

.........Please do not buy this...........</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>i would buy again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Adequate Memory; Good Battery Life; Good Display Screen; Lightweight; Fast Web Browsing; WiFi

GREAT PRODUCT JUST WHAT I WANTED</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doug....best dad ever!!!!!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Tablet!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Quality Display; Lightweight; Long Battery Life

Bought this for my 10 yr old..... she LOVES it!!!I am now officially the BEST DAD EVER!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>gg</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight

Cons: Short Battery Life

great device</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tompilot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>SWEET...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Just as effective as the iFruit version. The Samsung core chipset is really quick!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Charly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>it;s not worth it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Poor Quality

Tooooo Slowwwww!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mommie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bad Christmas gift.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable

Cons: Poor Quality

Froze up after a week.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>very busy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>did not perform as expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>did not perform as expected</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>upset father</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Learn how to ship</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I put the order in and it did NOT ship for 10 days.
I an NOT a happy camper!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>COBY Kyros Internet Tablet MID7022 4 GB</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/9609149515948814546/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=J4ORUN6yDPLiyAHPjoHIDw&amp;ved=0CNQBEPQCMAQ4Wg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bre</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Toys&quot;R&quot;Us</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>By far the best tablet I have found for under $200.00.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

