<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Petwils</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I like the HP touchpad mostly because it accesses almost all sites. It can access flash and java which I had trouble accessing on an Ipad. It is user friendly and quick. With program upgrades it has made this an adroid tablet as well which has made it an awesome tablet to own for the price it was sold at. It is a bit heavy and unfortunately they chose to cover it with a plastic back that is easy to crack. 

Battery Life

My kids can use this forever before needing to charge. It seems to run several hours with no problem.

Processing Speed

It loads quickly and I haven&apos;t had problems with it pulling anything up.

Weight

It is a bit heavy but not so much that a person can complain. 

App Availability

Apps are good and there is a suffici ... ent amount now that it has android

Design

The design is well and sleek. Overall pleasing and easy on the eyes

Durability

My peeve is the casing. It is plastic and cracked easily with a small bump to the side.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>devexityspace</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad is a fun tablet for a low budget</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I managed to pick up the 32GB Touchpad w/ Case, Docking Station, and wireless keyboard (bundled) for $149.99, and it was money well spent. 

It may not be as fast or great as the iPad 2 or Samsung Galaxy 10.1 Tablet, but for the price it&apos;s amazing. The HP O/S has much need for improvement, but current Android Root Project has an amazing beta that puts the HP Touchpads stats to good use.

Battery Life

I can&apos;t complain about battery life. I watched 2 full length NetFlix movies on it without it needing a charge. That was a moot point however (just to see battery life), as the docking station it has charges it and props it up perfectly for movie watching. Very pleased however with the power consumption overall.

Processing Speed

With a 1.2 GHz Qualcomm Snap ... dragon dual-core APQ8060 processor, it is definitely beastly! While it is not quite as fast as the Galaxy 10.1 or the iPad2, it can be reached by overclocking it to 1.4GHZ (which can be done rather easily via a quick Google Search). 

I know what you&apos;re thinking though, the iPad 2 only has a 1GHz dual-core as opposed to a 1.2GHz. It&apos;s the fact that A5 processor the iPad2 has is far more efficient. However once you up your speed on your hp touchpad to 1.4GHz it rivals the iPad 2.

Weight

the HP Touchpad (32GB) is 726grams. Which is 225 grams more than the iPad2. However it is not a &quot;brick&quot; by any means. Still light enough to enjoy your day to day tablet use. I don&apos;t know if I would want to hold 1.6lbs for 2 hours watching a movie, but that is what the docking station is for. For that I rated the weight 4/5 stars.

App Availability

I am rating this 4/5 for the simple fact that you have options. You can use HP O/S apps (many of which have been made free after HP discontinued the HP Touchpad), or you can root your device and turn it into an Android Tablet which has a lot more apps from either Android App Market or Amazon App Store.

Design

Simplicity is good when it comes to Tablets, and HP nailed it on the head. Large 9.7&apos;&apos; screen that is crisp with a great resolution, and the screen is 95% of the front face. A+ for design.

Durability

Just like any other Touchpad I have played with (Except the XOOM which feels like a flimsy piece of plastic), this seems to be tough enough to withstand some tossing and dropping. Just the same make sure you take advantage of the HP brand fold case for both protection &amp; convenience.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>arty4u37</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It Get&apos;s The Job Done!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s a great starter tablet when you can&apos;t afford the apple ipad. Perfect for those who just want something to check email and surf the web quickly and easily. Great for traveling on airplanes or road trips. Easy to use and easy to find apps for this product. Though limited, apps for purchase for reasonable price to even free. I&apos;d suggest a case is a must have for this device. But don&apos;t overspend for a case. In most cases, I have found that an inexpensive ipad case will fit this HP Touchpad and some are less expensive than an official HP Touchpad case.

Battery Life

Only downfall is that there aren&apos;t many apps to choose from and so far the apps that are available aren&apos;t compatible with android os systems. 

Processing Speed

Great.....No Problems...

Weight ... r&gt;
I have the 32GB tablet and the screen size is perfect to watch downloaded videos or streamed movies. 

App Availability

Not bad but could be more.

Design

Very stylish and very easy to use. Even a stylus pen can be used with this product if you have a hard time touching the pad with your fingers. 

Durability

No problems so far. I am very pleased with this product.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sscopp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good quality at an affordable price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It does has all the function I need at a reasonable price.

Battery Life

The battery last a long time and the battery dock is a conveinent addition.

Processing Speed

Not the fastest but fine for my needs.

Weight

It is a little heavy, I do have a cover on it that makes it a little heavier to carry

App Availability

not as many available as Ipad, but I have found many useful apps to suit my needs.

Design

easy to use and nice big screen

Durability

Has taken all the knocks and misuse I have delived to it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>zrenee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple use, not much apps for you to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s cheap when I bought them, I bought 3 of them. One for kitchen, just listen to Pandora and check recipes which is mounted under the kitchen cabinet. Another one is for my daughter to use it in the car, like watch Dora and play games. The pictures&apos; quality is really good. The design for unlock the screen and how to close windows which are pretty cool. Surprise me that HP is still doing updates once in awhile. The sound quality is good since it&apos;s just a tablet. 

Now let me talk about the bad thing about this tablet. Not good if you want to use other language on this. I would like to type Chinese on it, but there is no way I can do that.
Their apps are not many to choose from either. Really limited.
If you have a cover to protect the tablet, the cover will block the sensor on ... the tablet and make the screen darker automatically.

So far I just remember these, I will update more later. For the cheap price, if you want to use something like reading books, watch movies, do simple things on this tablet, that&apos;s possibly good enough. If not, I don&apos;t recommend this product.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sozi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best bang for buck, great way to surf the web!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up with out using a computer, awesome bang for buck!

Cons: Battery life &amp; putting pics/videos on it isn&apos;t that easy

Obviously this product doesn&apos;t go pound for pound with the iPad. But for $99, it&apos;s awesome! I think it&apos;s worth $250! I love it, it looks great, sounds great, and has a really sharp display with nice graphics. I&apos;m a Mac guy but I really do enjoy seeing a different layout than the typical iPhone app screen. So having multi-search engine box to type whatever you want is really nice. Skype comes built right in. What I like most about this TouchPad is that I could combine all my email addresses, for some reason one of my gmail accounts doesn&apos;t sync with my Macbook Pro or iPhone, but it worked like a charm with this tablet! I&apos;d expect the battery ... life to be a little better and I noticed that placing videos/pictures on the device was a little difficult. Other than that, I recommend this to everyone I know!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>greenlake</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent gadget</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I found this HP Touchpad 32G to be an excellent gadget. I love the design and features provided through the touchpad. Very easy to setup and use. Good battery performance. Here are some drawbacks I found in this touchpad, 1) starting process is kind of slow, 2) cannot process popular files, including word, ppt and pdf (ready only, but I think it is a common problem to similar products), 3) short of convenient application softwares, and 4) no operation system manual. But I still love this product very much. Strongly recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>shdw03</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great OS, but bad execution/launch</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: WebOS

Cons: Fingerprint hungry, SLOW!!!, no app support

My current situation. I am an owner of an Acer Iconia A500 and my company recently offered a $300 tablet credit for a few qualifying tabs. Being that I had my Iconia, and daughter has an ipad2, figure that I would try the webOS HP. Went to BB this weekend, at the end of the $100 price drop sale. Played with the (limited) demo unit and was actually impressed. So I purchased the 16gig unit.

The Good:
I like the UI of webOS. Such a simple layout and design that I feel best suites tablets. Gestures would ok for the most part and I like the &quot;Cards&quot; that you can cancel with a flick of the finger. Unit feels good, easy to hold, but an exact copy of the OLD ipad. Accessing the different apps from the laucher is e ... asy to find, execute. VERY EASY to switch between apps or &quot;CARDS&quot;, with their processes costantly running till they are cancelled. One HUGE highlight to me was the 50gig of free box.net storage. With that much space, who needs a expansion slot? pretty good battery time.

The Bad:
As mentioned earlier, this tablet was designed to compete with the Ipad, what HP forgot to do was design it to BEAT the ipad... then along comes the Ipad2 and the other slated of Andriod tabs. if this was a year ago, this tab may have had a chance. Its too bulky, heavy and the piano finish loves my prints! Boot times are horrible as well, 3 minutes or so, thought my tab was frozen. along with the bad boot times, launching some apps take forever to load. Just today, DL the iheartradio app, and the first attempt to launch never work, froze. the second attempt worked just fine though. The touch interface lags with some apps and at time even unresponsive. The kicker for me was that quickoffice app, pre-installed, is NOT fully opperational. Read only, no write, edit or create.

Wrap-up:
If this there was more app support for webOS, and if HP could fix the lag issues, this could have been a better tab. I installed the update last night as well, but still laggy/buggy. HP should have held off laun ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>skater425</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP touchpad is great product for great price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>it is a great product. HP is great. I am not a fan of the battery life. The functionality is great. Great keyboard. I wish that I had the ability to drag and drop on the touchpad . It is a great size. The price was so much better than the iPad. Sometimes it freezes. But this very rare. Wish there were more apps available for HP. Wish it at least had an android operating system. It has a great e-reader. In fact, it has amazon kindle beta. Great product for the price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NadiaHughes</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE THIS PRODUCT!!!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got the touchpad as a gift I originally wanted and ipad, but after getting the touchpad and comparing them I&apos;m happy I chose the touchpad. It&apos;s cheaper than the ipad, but it dooes the exact same thing that the ipad does and it have less glitches in the system. I take this thing every where. It&apos;s been a great help and I don&apos;t have to drag my laptop with me every where and that&apos;s a big plus.

Battery Life

The battery life great I could charge it and work for at least 4 or 5 hours without having to put it on it&apos;s charger.

Processing Speed

I think the processing speed depends on what type of service you have. If I took it to the library it was kind of slow, but when I had it at home or at my friend&apos;s house and connected it via wifi it was extremely fast.

Wei ... ght

The touchpad has a good weight to it, its not extremely heavy at all which is one of the qualities that I like about it. You can put it in your purse or an over sized bag and it won&apos;t weigh it down.

App Availability

The app store for the touchpad is great! It&apos;s easy to use and it has apps for everything. I love to cook and learn new lanuages and had a variety of apps to choose from. My son also love to use the touchpad so I downloaded alot of educational apps from him to use.

Design

I like the desing of the touchpad it reminds me of a little writing tablet, but the screen is big enough so you can read books and other materials online without hurting your eyes.

Durability

This thing was built to last I love the hard exterior that&apos;s on it. My son has dropped it a few times and it hadn&apos;t affected it at all, although I wouldn&apos;t recommend dropping it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bTi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The HP TouchPad is a quality tablet to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The HP TouchPad seems to have gained a second wind with HP making WebOS open sourced for hackers to turn it into an even better product. However, even with its proprietary WebOS, the TouchPad is a tablet that can stand its own.

Battery Life

The Battery Life with WebOS is pretty good, with on and off usage. I haven&apos;t measured it exactly but I have gotten more than 3 hours of usage with it.

Processing Speed

This tablet is pretty fast. At a 1.2GHz Snapdragon processor, it can handle having multiple tasks opened at the same time. 

Weight

At about 1 lb., 4 oz., it&apos;s slightly heavy, but nothing that would break your back. I have other tablets and while the TouchPad is slightly heavy, it gives a quality feel to it.

App Availability

On WebOS, ... there are apps, but they do not compare to the amount of apps available for Android and Apple. If you choose to dual boot your Touchpad, you can access many of the Android apps (although YMMV, as some may not work well on the tablet).

Design

It has a very simple design to it. The power button and microphone jack is on the top, volume buttons are on the right side, and a central home button. The only gripe I have with it, is that there is a &quot;slot&quot; that&apos;s on the right side, that they should have put a SD card reader or something, but instead when depressed, just displays its model type and serial number. Seems like a waste of space to me.

Durability

It&apos;s a nice, heavy tablet. If taken care of properly, it will work fine. I have a screen protector on mine and it still looks like it had just came out of the box.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Godzilla</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Connection</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Decent Deal At The Time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For $219 this was a decent deal at the time. I can&apos;t complain about the performance, battery, or screen. It&apos;s a solid device. Downfalls are no SD slot and no GPS, other than that it does what I bought it for - surfing the web and games for the kids. Android ICS works pretty good on it except for the camera not working. Now that the price is coming down on other tablets with GPS and SD slots ($249), it may be a better value for you to spend your money there.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JVAN269</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pricing and Performance Best Tablet Ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast; Quiet; Powerful; Quality Display; Long Battery Life

Cons: It is not Feather Weight

The HP WebOS is amazing in that there is no learning curb. I thought that I would modify it but found no reason to. Everything comes naturally. For Pricing and Performance This is the Best Tablet Ever!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Angelteddy4t</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad Rocks!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Well since they decided it didn&apos;t make the hit that HP hoped for the price is awesome for the product. I am happy with the choice I made. Sorry that they didn&apos;t have the following that they needed to succeed. I had the Palm Pre Plus through AT&amp;T, so I knew the WebOS operating system. So I was excited that I could purchase this and sync them together. I can even accept and make calls through it if I choose. I would say buy it and for the price you can see for yourself that it is a great deal.

Battery Life

It has a great battery life. I haven&apos;t tested it thoroughly but I am pleased with what I have seen.

App Availability

Well if they could have continue on there would be a lot more apps for this product. I hope that the people who create apps will thin ... k of this product when they make them.

Design

great design
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>deepen03</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, easy to use, design

Cons: Lags at times, not enough apps, bad camera.

I can&apos;t really complain for being lucky enough to grab one of these for $99! It is a great product. Not as fast as Android and not as many apps, but it gets the job done and it&apos;s cool to have around the house..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>colakids</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value @ Great Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy of use, right size and great price

Cons: Design, weight and lack of apps

I got 32g one at $149, fortunately. I am not really sure if I want to buy this at $499 but still this is more than good quality. I bought it to my son who is attending Bronx Science high school. He loves it and said is very useful to study . He loves to carry this intead his laptop. I recomend HP tablet to my friends.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pinak1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product, works perfect, value for money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s sad that HP is discontinuing this tablet. This is a very good product, even though it is not that sleek or fancy like iPAD but it works great and best part is it supports Flash. I can watch Flash based internet movies which is a big Plus. It shows all my emails from different IDs in one place, updates my Chat messages and Face book updates. I have the Tunein Radio App and the touch pad works as a wonderful radio. The sound quality is good. It&apos;s bit heavy but good for a first generation. The screen is touch sensitive and clear. I have the plastic cover ON so I am not worried about finger prints on front and back, it&apos;s not a big problem as others have pointed out.

The only qualm I have is Google voice-video doesn&apos;t work in my touchpad... it will be awesome if someone makes an app ... for that :)

At $149 for 32GB it&apos;s a great bargain and value for money. WebOS is cool.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mignon17</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product!! I love my HP Touchpad!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price &amp; very easy to use!

Cons: Haven&apos;t found any negatives, yet.

I love everything about my HP Touchpad, but I also loved how quickly it arrived! What great customer service!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MIShopper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Heavy and short battery life</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easier to carry along than a netbook/laptop

Cons: Heavy, short battery life, small amount of apps

Pros:
1. Great user interface that shows off multiple running apps.
2. Low fire sale price.

Cons:
1. One of the heavier tablets around.
2. Short battery life.
3. Small amount of apps.
4. Power up takes just over a minute.
5. Web browser seems immature: it froze going to one web site; some links don&apos;t pop up with clicked on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JedEye123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Its better than I expected, well worth the money.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Easy to use, Fun, Nice screen, Fast, webOS, HP Customer support, Supports Adobe Flash

Cons: Small selection of apps, no main/rear camera, Sold out and impossible to find

I honestly expected it to be garbage for the amount of money I paid for it. When they dropped the price to 100$ I figured there was something fundamentally wrong with it for them to be basically giving them away. I am very happy to say that I was completely wrong about that.

It is a solid device, with a solid operating system. I am still planning to upgrade to Android when it become available, but to be honest webOS has won me over. I really do wish I could keep webOS, but the lack of applications in the market is frustrating to say the least. There are a lot of useful apps, but no where n ... ear the amount as Android. Other than that though, the OS in my opinion is pretty awesome.

It is extremely easy to use, and even someone who has zero experience using a computer (my grandparents) were able to pick it up and use it immediately. I just had to show them the home button, and how you can swipe between screens and they are pros at it now.

I think it is a great web surfing device for sitting at a couch or something, maybe sitting at a coffee shop and reading some news or something. It is also great as an ebook reader, or movie player. Even if you bought it just for ebooks, you would have paid less for it that you would a not as good standalone ebook reader. So it is definitely worth it. I love doing my reading on it. I have also gotten my grandparents one and taught them how to read the news on it as well, so they have canceled their newspaper subscription. That has saved us 200+$ a year, so it really has made us our money back.

I mentioned video playing earlier, and I want to emphasize how awesome it works for watching videos on the go. I often put my TV series on it, and will bust it out on a long trip to keep my occupied. The quality of the screen is awesome, so it plays videos perfectly.

As far as web browsing goes, it works pretty well. I could only find one browser which is the stock one, but it works pretty well. It has Adobe Flash installed, so all of your we ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>okstuv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad Craze Began and Ended</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Got it for fire sale price (minus $30 for a coupon). So I&apos;m pretty excited about the value this tablet offers. I&apos;ll be even more excited when I can dual boot it to Android.

CONS
WebOS needs lots of tweaks, using Preware, to turn off all sorts of cpu-wasting processes and logging.

Easily smudged, but who cares for just over a Benjamin?

PROS
Great battery life in standby - I get 4 days of light use.

Hardware seems like a solid platform for Android. Excited about this.

OVERALL
It&apos;s not as convenient as a computer for surfing. It&apos;s not as easy to carry around as a smartphone. But sometimes it fills that niche in between. It will probably find a home on the couch, or in the bathroom.

It&apos;s like a huge smartphone for dummies.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>leland</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Touchpad with webOS is nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Overall it&apos;s a nice table, which is made from quality hardware component. The display is nice. The performance is good enough for most of tasks. Definitely it worth more than $99. Actually a lot of people will consider buying it for $199. HP management made mistake on the firesale price. It lost more.

WebOS itself overall experience is excellent, especially its multi-windows/tasks management system(card based) is very easy to use. Yes, it&apos;s too late to the party to compete effectively with Android and iOS. However, it should not be difficult to leverage Android ecosystem if WebOS can run Android Apps. Many users would love this tablet and stay with WebOS.

The only issue is the localization. It can display Chinese in the browser, but all menus, labels of the OS and Apps can no ... t be changed to Chinese. I give 4 star rating because of this. Otherwise, I would rate it 5 stars.

HP probably made a strategy mistake. There is no way to sell it at $499, and $399.
It may be able to sell some for $299, definitely will sell a lot at $199. For $299 price probably it&apos;s close to its hardware cost. Since HP is too late to the market, it has to price aggressively in order to be in the game. Now HP quits the game with the firesale $99. Everyone loves it for $99 price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Saltek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>4 Stars but FIVE for 99 bucks!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, qualiaty and capabliities

Cons: Really, not much.

Let&apos;s put some of these 1 Star &quot;reviews&quot; to rest. If you don&apos;t have the time or patience to learn the device, or you&apos;re a iPad/Android &quot;snob,&quot; then save the bandwidth.
The HP TouchPad is a very capable device that does just about everything you NEED It to do. Once you set it up and UPDATE the OS, you&apos;ll find it to be a nice addition to your home. I have a first gen iPad which I love and a Nook Color hacked with Android CyanogenMod7 Gingerbread and it works quickly and flawlessly. BUT I&apos;m having lots of fun with the TP.
Great email, wonderful speakers/sound, excellent browsing WITH Flash support, MS Office compatible Quick Office HD, FIFTY Gigs of storage on Box.net exclusively for TP owners, Adobe reader, Ki ... ndle, and many others-the ones you will actually use. And, if you search carefully, you will find not thousands, but many apps that are refined and specifically for the TP.
The iPad is certainly the better device, but I would put this against most android tabs out there. At these prices, there isn&apos;t anything to think about. And once you get used to WebOs, you&apos;ll find it to be quite intuitive and easy to navigate. I also believe it will continue to be supported with updates to come.
It&apos;s thicker than the iPad, weighs more and the screen although excellent, is just a notch down from the Apple device. Jeeze, even if you put it on a stand, connect some powered speakers, and used it as your home entertainment system holding thousands of songs alone, it would be worth more than 99.00 with a touch interface this good.
I was lucky to get mine shipped from BBuy but am still on the original waiting list from HP. I will buy as many as they let me buy-Christmas is coming!
Don&apos;t let the nit-wits or snobs keep you from this excellent device. If you have a chance to get one, by all means GET IT!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TimTime</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best $99 I have ever spent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Needs more apps

Wasn&apos;t in the market for one but at this price it couldn&apos;t be beat. Quality construction, the speakers are the best I&apos;ve heard from any tablet, laptop computer period. At first webOS didn&apos;t impress me but after having it a week i am in love with it. Everything I want to do is there. Multitasking is great. Much better than Android. I&apos;m writing this while i chat with a friend. Easy The office apps have been updated so you can even edit your excel or word docs. Browser is great as well as the display. Flash works. The touch is very smart as to where you are tapping. I didn&apos;t think I would use a tablet that much but i gotta tell you, at home I am using it 90% of the time and my laptop 10%. Games are great too. Not as many apps as the others ... but i have 95% of the apps i need. Like i said, Best $99 i have ever spent. Bestbuy blew my order but luckily got it on a lightning sale on that other online giant that starts with an A.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love WebOS, need more Apps ASAP</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I really love the design and performance of the Touchpad and I think it is a great value compared to the other tablets on the market. That being said, I am underwhelmed by the apps that are currently available. How can there not be a Netflix app or a native Pandora app? ESPN? NFL? Come on HP! This is a great device - spend some money and political capital to build out the app market.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joel123456789</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Mobile OS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>WebOS is perfect for the tablet form factor. True effortless multitasking, great battery life, super fast, full flash support. You can&apos;t beat the price for such an awesome device either.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>John46229</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Somewhat useful, but don&apos;t give up your laptop.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Graphics, sound. Very easy to use.

Cons: Extremely limited in what you can do with it. Only two accessories and they are incredibly overpriced.

If you want a device to impress people with then this will not do it. Few if any apps are available. The Kindle app is only useful if you have never had an eBook and you want to start from scratch. If you already have eBooks you cannot use them. There are no applications that can be used effectively on a touchpad. All that are available are for phones and the screen image is limited to what you would see on a very small phone. I could have had a mini laptop for less than I spent for this and it would be useful and productive.

The accessories are limited. A simple one fold case that should cost about $10 is listed as $49.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bullonparade</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love it!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: fast, responsive, flash capable, excellent UI

Cons: not a lot of apps right now, there are new ones everyday though.

I&apos;ve had it for a month so far and its been great. I am a heavy web user and the TouchPad has been able to render 95% of the websites I visit. The flash player actually works well here. Beats audio is really nice, everything sounds crisp and clear especially when using headphones. All around it is the best non apple tablet on the market. With a couple more updates it will be on par with the iPad 2.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ROXXYREDD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast and easy to use.

Cons: Need more apps.

I really debated between the Touchpad and the iPad 2, but the web OS system just seems to be the wave of the future. My pad is fast, easy to use right out of the box and even has a &quot;Live Chat&quot; button in the Help section if you have questions. And now with the Kindle and HP movie apps.......it&apos;s AWESOME! Movie picture clarity is great and sound is good too, although I prefer to use earphones when watching a movie. The Touchstone for charging is a &quot;must have&quot; if you buy this tablet. The convenience of just dropping your tablet onto the &quot;stone&quot; even while in its case is a real plus, and it has adjustable height settings so you can use it as a viewing stand as well! The tablet cover (sold separately) is also adjustable for viewing ... . The only drawback I&apos;ve had is that I seem to lose my home Wi-Fi connection on a semi-regular basis and that&apos;s a new issue for me since using the Touchpad. It may be that I just need a new router and not be related to the pad&apos;s performance at all. I would be interested in feedback from others on this. All in all.........I am very pleased with my purchase and can&apos;t wait to see what HP comes up sith next. Next purchase? A wireless eprintef!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cmhouser</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice but lacking in a few key areas...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome OS, Great looks, Good web experience, Great Multitasking

Cons: Lack of support for networking, Little 3rd party apps, Lack of SD expansion, Too glossy

First off I spent a good month researching the various tablets out there for their strength and weaknesses. After my research and talking to a few people I thoght I&apos;d try the HP Touchpad. I knew I was taking a chance with the webOS but thought I&apos;d give it a try.

Main Purpose: Watch downloaded movies in bed, surf the web and play some games.

The good: The Touchpad&apos;s webOS is awesome! It looks good, it worls great and is super easy to use without being dumbed down. It feels like a good cross between an iPad and any other Android. Sleek look. The small amount of buttons that are actualy on this thing ar ... e well placed. It seemed very quick and responsive. Browser was fast and worked flash sites well. Display was amazing! At first I was very happy! This thing just screamed quality and design.

Now the bad: I&apos;ll start with the deal breaker for me. No support to wirelessly copy over files. I have a computer with almost 2 TB of movies on it. I can connect to it from any other machine even including my Android phone. I called HP just to see if I was missing something and was told I had to connect my Touchpad via USB to the computer to copy over any movie. No 3rd party app support. The HP has no other ports than a mini USb and thats very limited as well. The screen is almost too glossy. Actually the whole thing is. Lack of apps at the moment.

Synopsis: The HP could easily beat any tablet I&apos;ve tried but it&apos;s lack of transferring data over your network, lack of app, total lack of support along with its overly glossy screen sends me back to the drawing board. For an entry level user this is probably the best choice of any. But for more advanced users - I&apos;d save your money and wait for all tablets to grow a bit. Oh and one other thing... not that I have a problem with over sea&apos;s support but it is challenging to get a ot of hep very quickly on any software related problems with HP. Good Luck!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JAlfredBloomingtonIII</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hammer in search of a nail</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I had no prior experience with tablets such as the iPad but I waited specifically for the Touchpad to be released. I figure some healthy competition is always a good thing for the consumers and technology.
The Touchpad feels solidly built, has a very nice screen/image quality, and has pretty good pep. The speakers have very nice sound quality for music playback. WebOS has a nice user interface design, but right now I&apos;m still trying to figure out what the Touchpad is good for. I have a touchscreen Android smartphone that seems to have more handy apps than the Touchpad does at the moment. I also have an HP netbook with Windows XP that is infinitely easier to use for composing emails, not to mention access to the traditional computing experience and most Windows applications. I somewhat ch ... oke on the words, but so far the only thing the Touchpad does better than any of my other computer-like devices is pan and zoom on the satellite views in the Bing maps application. Being able to zoom webpages is also nice, but not every page behaves like you want it to--possibly not the Touchpad or WebOS&apos;s fault, but nevertheless an unfortunate drawback.
The email app that allows you to look at multiple accounts in a single view is a very nice idea, but it has a &quot;version 1.0&quot; feeling about it. I recognize the platform is very young so I&apos;m still hopeful for improvements over the next few months. Likewise the calendar needs some work; I have many Google calendars and the Touchpad calendar app seems to be able to display only a limited number of them, starting at the top of the alphabet.
I gave my review a &quot;not recommended&quot; marking, but that&apos;s not exactly accurate. I don&apos;t exactly regret making the purchase, but I do still wonder why I bought it. My best advice is &quot;try before you buy&quot;. Go somewhere and put your hands on it. Try typing an email that&apos;s longer than a sentence or two. Try typing while sitting down and holding the Touchpad in your lap, too. Make sure you know why you want it ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ebaggles</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, bad quality control</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing hardware, super fast operation

Cons: Horrible Quality Control

I stood for hours in best buy trying out all of the different products. Hands down, the TouchPad exceeded my expectations in numerous ways:

1.) Response time when touching the IPS glass

2.) Overall speed (jumping in and out of apps is blazing fast)

3.) Weight - All of the tablets impress me with their weight capacity vs. the overall utility. (I&apos;m not sure why people are complaining about the weight differences between this and the ipad. Here&apos;s some advice; if you can&apos;t carry 1lb comfortably, go to the gym. Seriously.)

4.) Performance - I ran up to 11 applications at once on the demo and playing two games ran unbelievably smooth.

5.) Browser - on most of the android t ... ablets, I was forced to browse on MOBILE browser sites. Not so on the Touchpad. Every website that I like worked 100% fine, and while the load times were slow, people nowadays have no patience. Waiting 5 seconds for a webpage to load is completely fine with me.

5.) Lack of SD card slot (why is this a benefit? Well, I found out that HP provides you with 50GB of free space, forever, on BOX.NET. WICKED!)

So, I ended up buying the 32GB touchpad.

I took it home ready to tear the box open and get started with my new tablet!

The tablet started up into a language setup. If you ever had a previous Palm phone with a palm account, as long as you have an internet connection, you can sync up your last save with your phone. How awesome!

After starting up the unit, I found that I could download programs lightning fast and they ran lightning fast. There were over 300+ applications ready to go.

Here&apos;s where it took a turn for the worst:

1.) I noticed the brightness was the lowest of all the tablets (but then again, this is my fault for not noticing this ahead of time). It&apos;s not bad, but it&apos;s very low.

2.) The battery charger provided wouldn&apos;t charge my tablet. I got a message (which I will attach as a photo) saying &quot;voltage or current is too low to charge the device.

I tried using multiple plugs, even drivi ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JayhawkToo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet experience on the market!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Outstanding OS, Very intuitive, Most Powerful, High Quality, Thin and light like a tablet should be, 32GB is perfect

Cons: Lacks a rear camera (I&apos;ll stick to my phone anyway, holding a tablet up for a picture looks silly).

WebOS is, hands down, the best operating system one could find on a tablet!

Its even better on this powerful device! It really is super speedy.

True multi-tasking is incredible! Why hasn&apos;t Android or Apple implimented this yet????

Synergy is an awesome feature, all my messages appear in one easy to use app, even Facebook and Skype! Email works the same way!

With &quot;Just Type,&quot; I can, well, just type and selcect from my favorite search engines, wikipedia, maps, twitter, and others!
Say I&apos;m watching a movie, I wake up the de ... vice, type in the movie title, tap IMDB, and boom, I know who that actress is now.

Soon every HP computer and printer will have WebOS (in addition to Windows), creating a huge ecosystem that I am proud to be an early adopter of with this TouchPad!

The hardware itself is first class. With a real computer producer like HP finally putting their might behind a tablet that&apos;s to be expected!

The price is right on par with the iPad 2, and yet side to side, its easy to see the power the TouchPad has over that device!

Screen clarity and sharpness is the same or maybe even better than the iPad 2. And I can finally get access to the full web with flash, unlike any Apple device.

Even though this device just came out there are already plenty of awesome apps to choose from in the app catalog! Since they use Citrix at my place of work, I can not only play, but get actual work done on my TouchPad!

I recommend anyone in the market for a tablet check this awesome device out!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>the1truereblangel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Poorly designed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Unreliable to say the least. Many times, the product won&apos;t even turn on. Not good for internet surfing. 

Battery Life

Battery life is 2 hours maximum. Many times, even after charging, the tablet will not even power up. 

Processing Speed

How slow can a tablet be? This one has got to be the slowest. 

Weight

VERY HEAVY. Not for use for extended periods of time without something to place the tablet on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dublish</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very very nice sply for the price.

Cons: spearers. no way I could find to connect to the tv.

First, let me say that I bought this at a discount paired with a laptop and was purchased primarily for my young daughter to play with. Turned out to be a great tablet and I use it a lot myself. The touchscreen is perfect, no complaints there, camera works just fine, sound is ok. Built in GPS is neat too, and at 32GB ... no complaints.
The finish is very very nice, I like the rounded edge styling, easy to hold and feels sturdy.
There are surprisingly large number off apps for WebOS - including angry birds :-) nothing like iOS or android - but Ive so far found everything I needed, including mail, facebook, news and weather, camera ... and a nice collection of games for my d ... aughter.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gaboxl42</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product, the worst customer service I know</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: General specs and low price

Cons: It´s discontinued, so it carries with a lot of exchange problems

I bought this online bundled with an HP laptop. I started using it for school and I thought the battery life was very limited. Tried to change it at my local store (as returning specs say in the document of the shipment that came with the product) and they did, but they replaced it with a physically damaged product (bad assembly and a noticeable scratch next to the camera, even when it was closed and sealed). Trying to re-exchange was a real pain, always blaming the store support and the online support, always blaming each other and sometimes telling me it was applicable to change and some others that it wasn´t, never giving me a solid resolution. After 2 weeks with more t ... han 12 calls, an open case that it just cancelled without a reason, i just dropped the nightmare situation and had to keep the HP Touchpad in not-as-new condition.

I WILL NEVER BUY A DISCONTINUED PRODUCT FROM BESTBUY AGAIN, AND I SUGGEST YOU THE SAME.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mnclint</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding workflow with full web</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: simple and powerful

Cons: no rear facing camera

Simply put, this product would have jumped ahead of other tablets if HP knew how to market. At their original price point, I too would not have taken the gamble.
The Touchpad is effortless and a true PC in your hands. Ipads are truly toys that need many apps to be useful, luckily developers are making the apps to slowly allow real work to be done on them..flash access please.....
If the next gen TP would shed thickness/and a little weight...wo-w, but that is not a reality. If you are fortunate to pick up a TP, go for it. Their firesale pricing is unbelievable for the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NAsir</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful; Long Battery Life; Quality Display; Nice like Laptop

Cons: Less Apps; Heavy

Very Nice Tablet got in the Best Price. Quick shipping from Brandsmart..Thanks</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bigjank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just as good as iPad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use.

Cons: not enough apps

Love it! Especially love that I got it for $149.00 with a purchase of a laptop for my college age daughter.

It does everything that an iPad does that I have found. Coworkers that have an iPad say that the apps/icons and tablet itself function and look just like the iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>popmusikdaddy1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price,features,surf the web,email,etc.

Cons: some the apps are mobile mode

I love my HP Touchpad. Easy to use,set up fast. This tablet is the best IPad alternative on the market. Now with the update, you Skype or with any smartphone to make phone calls with Bluetooth access,chat,transfer your music and videos,surf the web,email you name it!! Great camera and features check it out!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wayne922</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding tablet, WebOS works great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome price, outstanding performance &amp; apps!

Cons: Need to add an antiglare screen protector

I&apos;ve had this tablet for about a month now, and have downloaded many apps from the ver 1000 selections in the HP Apps store - many were free. Great apps, and responsiveness is now super fast from a recent WebOS update. The browser rocks, as well the Office App that handles files like Excel and Word. There is even a Kindle App for Amazon eBooks. Music sounds great, too! I&apos;m thrilled.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>irishmoma73</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price was FANTASTIC! Super easy to use!

Cons: Lags slightly.

I love my HP Touchpad! We have an iPad and iPad 2 in our house and I like the Touchpad much better. It could be an amazing product if HP didn&apos;t give up on it so quickly, shame shame.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>allday</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Find it. Buy it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you can still find this anywhere you need to buy it. It is downright the best value for it&apos;s cost.

Battery Life

I can use it for 7 hours straight.

Processing Speed

Definitely not as good as an iPad but very close.

App Availability

This is the only downside.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ARSENIO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>TOUCHPAD</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>EXCELLENT PRODUCT. Sorry to see it go. Hope HP re-considers and can see the benefits of continuing to support and manufacture this product. Price the Touchpad about $200 for the 16GB and $250 for the 32GB for the holidays and they will fly off the shelf. More apps would help too. Would love to see netflix design an app for the touchpad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NotStupid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overpriced</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use

Cons: Slow

Great if you like paying too much. HP had (and may have them again) for the price of [$], plus free shipping. They&apos;re a bargain at the HP price, but not for what they&apos;re selling them for here.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mobilelawyer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pleased so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed

Cons: A little heavy

I will admit, I got this at the firesale price. But had it not been available at that price, I would not be the owner of a tablet at all, and I am happy to have the opportunity to finally get to use one.

I will take it with me to meetings where a laptop is overkill. I am having to get used to the email program, but it has a short learning curve and the web os is a fast, responsive operatiing system.

I omtimized the Touchpad by tweaking it as suggested in some of the forums, and I find performance to be improved. I bought the HP cover and the HP bluetooth keyboard. The keyboard is fine, but, in restropect, I am not sure I will be taking it along. Carrying an extra peripheral sort of defeats the convenience of the tablet.

I ... have bought perhaps 10 or 15 apps, and have everything I need. Just got Splashtop, and can stream media from any of my computers over Wi-Fi. Tried it out on a Netflx movie, and it looked just fine.

No complaints whatsover.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rswain64</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen quality and sound

Cons: No sd card or hdmi out

Was a little leary of getting a WebOS tablet since I was use to Android. This tablet is amazing for the price if you can find one. Screen quality is amazing and ease of WebOS is great. After performing the necessary patches and overclocking this tablet flies. Wish HP was not abandoning this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>FLtechgirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fun on the go!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Soooo much easier to carry than my laptop!

Cons: Sound quality.

Great little device! Easy to use. Would like a few more utility apps for web-os, but otherwise a lot of fun. Can play games, surf the web, email, etc. Great for beginners too. Sound quality could be better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ranajit</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice tablet@$99</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: display, sound, price

Cons: webos

got the tablet when hp slashed price. I never thought I will be using it like any other leading tablet in the market. It is easy to use. Awesome display. Magnificent sound. If you compare the price you will not get a digital photo album like this. I gave 4 star as it has some some glitch in webos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>indianozi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid built product let down by lack of apps !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, easy to use

Cons: Lack of apps, definitely needs a case

Yes, i bought a HP touchpad during the $98 firesale !
And i have no regrets yet in getting it (for $98). It is certainly worth the money but probably nothing more.
Very solid built product. Good overall size makes it portable enough. The screen is very good quality and sensitivity is good. The speakers sound good, but not loud. Headphones on the device sound decent.
The WebOS is functional yet a bit laggy compared to Android Honeycomb (ive got another tablet running Android Honeycomb 3.2).
The other let down of the product is probably lack of apps, which hopefully will pick up due to the size of the user base now.
It certainly is a good entry point into the tablet world or for kids when u ... dont want to get them a really expensive tablet knowing they might smash it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mrasgar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good UI</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The user interface, the low prices currently

Cons: Long boot time

Takes a long time to boot initially, but it seems worth the wait. The OS is nice and easy, the display on this device looks great. Pretty good iPad alternative, especially when you get it for less than half of the iPad price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EthanHawke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beautiful tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, awesome multitasking

Cons: Sluggish at times

The Touchpad is a great tablet with an awesome OS. There are limited applications available and that is where the limitations reside. The Skype video calling is buggy, no sound, video works fine. It comes with built-in skype/gtalk integration for voice/video/text chatting.
Is it better than an iPad? Yes if you like multitasking and the OS itself is much superior than the iPad. What it lacks is applications which then translates to usability. Maybe HP fixes that. For the price though, hard to beat.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>At $99 Dollars A Steal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality build, performance, overall value

Cons: Lack of applications

Very happy with my HP Touchpad, WebOS works very well, too bad it is now an orphan. Downside to the TouchPad is obviously the lack of applications that are available now, or in the future.

Surfing the Internet, Flash video, YouTube, Email, and Facebook all work flawlessly, intuitiveness, and processing speed are very good, this is an excellent product. HP maybe pulled the plug too soon, but gaining momentum on iPad would be an uphill battle.. TouchStone charger is an excellent accessory.

I would buy this product again tomorrow, an excellent value!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MsToad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>JUST AS EXPECTED</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, size is just right and can do almost everything on it.

Cons: Nothing

I will say at first when the package arrived and saw that I didn&apos;t get the HP TOUCHPAD 32G that was ordered and paid for, I wasn&apos;t happy but when we contacted Best Buy, they did apologize for not shipping the correct order and that they would make sure I was sent a refund. This was ok with me since as of now you still can&apos;t find any HP Touchpads to purchase, so I got one and it is just as expected, use it everyday and am thankful that I actually got one.

Very Satisfied BEST BUY CUSTOMER</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>viskon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good device,great for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use,unbelievable value at $99

Cons: lack of apps,lack of customization

I got this from BB during the firesale. Ordered it on a Sunday morning. I got it by Tuesday afternoon. Great service from BB.

Now on to the device itself.

Pros
Feels solid and well built. WebOS is a nice OS, visually very nice. The tab is fast enough for me at stock, so I haven&apos;t had the need to overclock. The apps that are designed for the Tp are a visual feast. Beats Audio is fantastic.Beyond Synth and the USA Today apps come to mind as outstanding apps for the TP. Skype video calls works very well. Best of all is the $99 price tag :-)

Cons
WebOS is a nice OS. But for me coming from Android, I find the inability to set Widgets on my homescreen annoying.I frequentl ... y wish this could be as customizable as Android. It sometimes feels that WebOS is a poor cousin of iOS. The camera is average at best. The stock browser is a joke. The onscreen keyboard is very inconvenient to use- I am used to the excellent Thumb Keyboard on my Android Gtab. The biggest gripe is the lack of good apps and they seem overpriced for what they do.

Summary - A wonderful device which needs to mature a lot more. For the price, a great deal.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mrbarter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great tablet, great price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price,speed,size

Cons: nothing

I am so glad I got lucky enough to get this at such a discounted price [$100]. Will never lug my computer again. Everything I need in this little tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RunRat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value for a tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great price, easy to use

Cons: fewer apps

For the $150 price, definitely worth the purchase. May not have as many apps as the iPad, but for email, surfing and facebook, it does the job.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LeMoi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buggy yet fast</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I bought the Touchpad with the clear idea on my mind to use it as a backup tablet to the iPad i own and as a testing platform for things that will surely come to market.
I would have never buy it with the original price tag above $500, but for 140, yes.
It will be a great video player for my kids, a game platform (if any interesting games shows up), and in the mean time, a communications tablet for me on the Road.
The hardware i think it is good, after patching and configuring the machine runs fast and great (overclocking, disabling logs, decreasing brightness, eliminating tap ripple!). Charging without cables, with the cradle, is great!
As for the software . . . there the starts start falling from the sky (aka, bad performance). The apps are very simple and have very few funct ... ions and configuration options. For example, I cannot print to network printers, i cannot delete the deleted mail from the deleted bin all at once, the software doesn&apos;t respond immediately to my tap on the screen, sometimes is a delayed response, others the screen reacts to my tapping, but nothing happens, the software doesn&apos;t do what it is supposed to, follow a link, click an option. I don&apos;t know if the OS is lost within it&apos;s labyrinth or that i has problems dealing with the internet. I use the facebook app. for tablet, and it has very interesting functions and display options, but it is a horrible user experience, 1 out of 3 taps actually do something. and if i&apos;m writing something, an accidental tap anywhere on the screen can make you lose all the writing. I&apos;m afraid to use the tablet for real work, as i might suddenly lose important things because nobody in the developing company took the time to fail proof this things.
As for tablet improvement system set up by HP, if i want to look for apps, i have to go to at least TWO places (HP catalog and PreWare Catalog, there might be more) creating a mess of a search. The PreWare site and organization is efficient, open and reliable as a source of ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NanaPlay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You will love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So easy to use. Throw something off the screen to delete it or close it. Beautiful screen, does&apos;nt smudge either. Battery life is great compared to my Nookcolor. You must get the eprinter, I did &amp; everything syncs ,uploads to my touchpad!!!Easy. I want one for each of my grandsons, just can&apos;t get them yet. Would love to get them each the compatible cell phone as well. Buy it you will love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Price Ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I am sure no any product can beat the price HP TouchPad Wi-Fi offered. I got one but I was surprised to see the amazing things it can do. Multitasking, well that was the greatest features of all. Screen Resolution also looks good. Now I carry it all the time wherever I go. There are already plenty of apps to start with.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RSJH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Hands down there is no better tablet for the price. This tablet clearly is as good as the iPad. Web OS is easy to use and understand. Only hope Web OS is kept up to
date.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bonbon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>TouchPad Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I received the Touchpad way after the scheduled delivery date. Upon open up the package, the Touchpad was beyond my imagination. It is good design, fits firmly in my hand and very slick. The downside of this is there are not many apps in the HP store for the Touchpad that I can find useful and the users manual is nowhere to be found. The operating system is easy to use, initial setup is no problem, I had it up and running within 10 minutes. The Touchpad hang on me one time because I did not update the OS to the latest version. I was scared thinking that I bought a junk Touchpad but after searching the internet I knew how to forced reboot it and update to the latest OS version. Since then it runs like a horse, plays video and music as I wanted, and performs all functions as advertised by HP ... . The sound is unbelievable, awesome if I plug my headphone on. I would buy it again to my family members if I have a chance. Keep up the good work HP.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr12Fingers</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I can&apos;t believe this came out only 2 months ago.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>The only reason this tablet got 3-stars was because it was $140. If I paid full price for this, I&apos;d return it in an instant. Not only is there a lack of apps, but the UI isn&apos;t the greatest either. It can be a little confusing at times.

Perhaps the single most disappointing aspect about this device is the lack of a camera. This is the middle of 2011 people. Any tablet device without a camera is going be sub par.

All in all, I&apos;m keeping it because my wife can play flash games. I&apos;ll never use it. Not over my iPad 1 or my Galaxy Tablet, and especially not over my iPad 2.
If its the only thing you can afford, great. Otherwise it&apos;s pretty weak.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Schooby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love the feel of WebOS and the graphics on the games. I do hope they continue to make apps that will be compatible with this system because I think it outranks all others. I am very happy with my HP touchpad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Octoberlee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>So glad I was able to get this tablet at a great price so I could try it out and enjoy the conveniences of tablet life! I find it is quickly becoming my go to hardware in my house versus sitting at my desk at my desktop or lugging my laptop around. I love to shop using this tablet as I browse the web and play games while watching tv some nights. Very handy, lightweight, fast and has a long battery life!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BernardG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the Money I paid for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Worth the Money I paid for....

Very affordable, fast, and easy to use. Perfect gift for my Mom. Nice compared to cost of IPAD.

I WISH I COULD GET 3 MORE FOR MY SIBLINGS.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>willverduzco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A fantastic bargain. Best tablet deal.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>This is an attractive and feature-packed tablet thanks to the incredibly discounted prices. However, also owning a XOOM, a Galaxy Tab 10.1, and an iPad; the lag and UI inconsistencies in webOS are quite apparent. However, the Android port to the TouchPad is gathering steam, and we may see Honeycomb or Ice Cream Sandwich (Android 3.x and 4.x) hitting the TouchPad before the end of the year.

As for hardware, the TouchPad isn&apos;t too bad. While it is thicker and heavier than any other major tablet, the contoured design helps minimize the unwieldy feel.The glossy and easy-to-scratch plastic finish, however, is a tad disappointing. The dual-core Snapdragon is speedy enough at 1.2 GHz, and most TouchPads are able to handle 1.7 and even 1.9 GHz. However, even at nearly 2 GHz, the OS itself j ... ust seems slower than Honeycomb and iOS. Apple&apos;s iOS isn&apos;t a fair comparison since it can&apos;t do true multitasking other than through a few select services. However, since Honeycomb can truly multitask and is much more responsive, there is no reason for webOS to be so laggy.

Additionally, there seems to be something funky going on with the touch sensor, as I get loads of missed or mis-registered touch events. They&apos;re frustrating because I&apos;m not sure if the device has crashed. For the techies out there, a 1.2 GHz Scorpion (CPU segment of the Snapdragon, based off of ARM&apos;s Cortex A8 reference design with a few tweaks such as elements of dynamic execution) is roughly as fast as a 1.0 GHz ARM Cortex A9 (the CPU core in the Apple A5, nVIDIA Tegra 2, Samsung Exynos, etc.)

Luckily some patches from PreWare can help fix the lag problem--namely removing the tap-ripple effect. Even still, the software keyboard is almost unusable even with the overclocking and PreWare patches. The auto-correct also leaves A LOT to be desired. I had to disable it in order to have any kind of a decent experience.

Issues aside, for fire sale, there is no better tablet bargain. People bought the Nook Color in droves a ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wanda78</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>$99...this tablet was a steal! I use it for email, web, twitter, facebook and skype. Awesome! App store is developing, so far I have lots of useful apps. Don&apos;t need apps for everything since most of it works online thru the web browser.

Love the fact that it is easy to customize using preware. It&apos;s really fast and smooth.

Wish it had: Video out to TV; apps for audible/netflix; arrow keys on the keyboard;

I&apos;m really glad I got in on this deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>comego</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product if you know how to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Most attractive part is the price. The IPS screen, 4:3 screen ratio, build quality are definitely highlights of the product. The battery is fine but not good as IPAD2. No SD slot is somewhat concerned.

The major weakness is in the software. I in fact love the webOS at the first place because I was a palm fan before. I am very happy that flash can be opened by the browser and you do not have to install individual apps for different website as IOS. But that is it. Out of box the system is sluggish and you have to do some research to turn off the logging; the update was very difficult to complete without problems; the language support is poor. More important is that there are not many apps available comparing to either IOS or Android. Many people like to have option to read books, but ... HP is weak on this. Maybe because apple and amazon are both selling books but HP does not have a partner.

The bottom line is that after tuning, it is good enough for simple web surfing, video streaming, emails, and limited gaming. It could be better if HP had been more dedicated on the webOS development.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>UriBraun</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I wish they had patience</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This product suffers from four shortfalls.
1. No patience by management
2. Young app community -- not enough apps yet
3. No GPS
4. No camera app

That said, most companies would be jealous to be in this position. The lack of GPS is the only thing that would require a new device. The lack of a camera app should be an easy fix. Apps were being developed, especially considering HP&apos;s strategy on the software front.

Now for the strengths:
1. Battery life
2. Slick look
3. Can access it as a network mounted drive
4. Hackable
5. Color ereader
6. Mostly intuitive UI
7. Touch keyboard with numbers
8. Phone shows ALL contacts (Skype, phone etc.)
9. Can tether to phone for calls

Note: it take a minute or so to get used to closing apps by slidi ... ng them off the top.

Suggestions:
1. Keep making them
2. Add GPS
3. Provide a camera app
4. Allow categorization of apps -- three panels is weak give me folders, labels or something
5. Allow contact filter to select users that are online
6. Add close app to the menu
7. Provide a pdf app that allows annotating the document
8. Do something with the desktop -- let me customize it somehow. It&apos;s empty and waiting for innovation.

Overall, I&apos;m impressed with how fast this has achieved so much. A bit of a patience might get this product somewhere.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Mixed Bag</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Comparing the Touchpad to any other tablet on the market is completely unfair considering the vast divide in development for the operating systems. Simply put, WebOS does not have the market that either the iPad or even the Android tablets do, and this limitation in app selection severely hinders the utility of the product. That said, this product still has a mixed bag of positives and negatives and I would recommend it with a caveat.
On a positive note, WebOS has potential to be a very intuitive and useful tablet operating system. The syncing across separate systems for email and messaging are fantastic and are extremely impressive. The tablet is also well put together; although plastic and a finger print magnet, I feel it holds its own against earlier generation tablets and the screen ... has fantastic viewing angles.
However, considering the competition, the performance on this tablet is seriously lacking. General application usage is slower than what might be expected, and the browser falls well behind the standards available on other competing operating systems. My other smart devices that are much less impressive on a spec sheet will handily outperform this tablet for the majority of what I desire to do (web browser, email, messaging).
All said, I don&apos;t regret the purchase and would recommend the product at the sale price I received. However, in competing terms, this tablet does not fare well against the iPad or Android in a number of aspects. Although WebOS does have many strong points and the tablet feels solid, it simply isn&apos;t worth investing in a lagging ecosystem and sluggish performance.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Meggg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>camera is broken</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I bought two touchpads for me and my husband at a super deal price. But sadly, the camera in one touchpad was broken after I installed camera API. I heard several cases that the camera had same issues as mine. Why HP don&apos;t test them before they get out of the gate? Apparently, HP customer service has nothing to do with the problem, because they sold out everything. Be aware, you have risk to buy a camera disabled tpad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zhipeng</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The first time to buy a pad. It&apos;s a great product for its performance! Unbeatable for its price. Also a wonderful OS. The only thing need to improve so far is its web browser.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>aj262</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unbeatable Touchpad@$150</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got my HP Touchpad during the fire sale and really like it so far. It was slow out of the box, but the performance is much better after I changed the logging threshold to error only. I may try over clocking later but for now the performance is acceptable for my sparing use.

The best thing I like about HP Touchpad is support for Adobe Flash and the full browsing experience.

I&apos;m giving excellent rating for the price. Glad to have such a beautiful WebOS device for that price. I wish I could have a Pre 3 as well to go with this tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HusbandWifeNbaby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>it&apos;s ok</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i bought 32g touchpad. looks nice, better than ipad. one thing that suz is that there isnt enough apps. i&apos;m not huge on apps but really the apps are so limited on it. kinda slow at times. volume is ok not to loud but its not quiet. i think it might even be better than my hp laptop sound. its good for brouseing and looking at websites. ok facebook app. sometimes there isnt a back button avalible on some pages so if your looking at a pic or something you have to start all over, dont know if that makes any sence. i&apos;m just use to all the options a computer has like the mouse and right click button delete button and so forth. it&apos;s not a computer i&apos;ll tell you that. overall its great to use especialy for kids and games for them as well as learning stuff or just watching cartoons. my 10 month old ... loves the piano app. it&apos;s a great product for 150.00 bucks. wouldn&apos;t pay more for anykind of touchpad. hp has always been good to me. have their laptop and desk top 2. bought 3 of the pads one for me, wife and kid. like i said it was a good deal
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sfaerb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet at the right price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price, mutitasking, flash, notifications, synergy, touch to share

Cons: limited apps

It&apos;s unfortunate that WebOS is only appreciated after death. I am currently an iPad 2 user (and have been with iOS since first gen iPhone/iPad) but I am really impressed with the Touchpad WebOS. I purchased two Touchpads after the &quot;fire sale,&quot; one for my mother&apos;s birthday, one for my fiance&apos;s birthday; as they are perfect for first time tablet users and the price can&apos;t be beat. (I am looking forward to purchasing more from the last batch from HP as Christmas gifts) After helping them set up, I am very impressed with WebOS. Notifications are great and unobtrusive and true multitasking is a plus. They are perfect for web browsing and email. The apps are limited but now that there are 500K ... + instant new users over the last week I am sure developers will be motivated to optimize their popular apps for WebOS. In the tech world the lifespan of product innovation is a year at best so for the price it can&apos;t be beat even if it is discontinued and WebOS doesn&apos;t evolve further; in a year most people will trade up anyway regardless of device. (I sell and upgrade my Apple products every release) I am disappointed that the HP Pre 3 won&apos;t be sold in the US but I am trying to get one from the UK (or perhaps an AT&amp;T HP Veer) so I can test out the synergy and touch to share features which are also a big plus to WebOS. If HP could figure out a way to make a great tablet like the Touchpad at the $300 price point I believe WebOS would dominate that market. It&apos;s just too difficult to compete at the $500 price point with Apple.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ChapstickMedley</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great happy ending...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: EASY TO USE, AWESOME PRICE, LOVE IT LIKE I LOVE MY IPAD

Cons: ITS PERFECT.

I bought this HP Touchpad after it being discounted greatly. I can not be any happier with it. As much as I love my IPAD, the HP Touchpad really outdid itself. It is a great product, and even BETTER for the price. This Touchpad is worth sooooo much more than what it was sold for, I love it. Its simple to use, good quality and I like the touch screen better than the ipads :-X</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>marypari</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have an HP smartphone, HP laptop, HP printer and now the TouchPad. One of the main things I really like about this product is the interoperability potential to synch MS Outlook contacts and calendar with the TouchPad using Chapura Pocket Mirror in the near future. I use this syncing software for my HP phone and it works great. The TouchPad is a great product, easy to use, great screen clarity and lots of apps. I&apos;m just about to order the Touchstone Charging Dock. I have the charging stone for my phone and the convenience is wonderful. I liked the TouchPad so much, the next day I bought one for my sister who would be in the hospital for some time so that she could listen to talking books (Amazon Kindle Beta), use skype for calls, videos, Email, text, surf the internet and she only needed ... to take one small electronic accessory with her. It&apos;s GREAT!!!!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marcao</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Interface, Sound Quality

Cons: Battery Life

Wow. I was surprised to see how intuitive is the WebOS. I really like the fact that you can easily switch you tasks and discard them with just a flick. I really really like the fact that I can access flash-enabled websites. I could not with my Ipad. I like the App store, could have really like the Facebook app.
I am so happy with this tablet that I upgraded my phone to an HP Veer. I am a bit frustrated that I do not have the update from AT&amp;T that allow me to connect the Touchpad to the Veer by proximity. I m really liking this WebOS thing!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bestbuycustomer987654321</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Purchase!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Decent price, great sound and graphics, pretty fast.

Cons: Seems to lag a little on some applications, not all the applications fit to the whole screen.

I went into the Best Buy store undecided as to which tablet i was wanting to buy. After playing around with all of the tablets on display, I decided that the HP touchpad was the one for me. When i got it home, it&apos;s obvious that the tablet lags a little especially on applications such as facebook. The sound is very good, and the graphics are amazing. I was a little surprised and disappointed that the camera can only be used for video messaging; however, it works well. The internet looks and runs great. The HP app store isn&apos;t as good as either Android or the Apple stores, but i&apos;m sure it&apos;ll get there. Overall, for the pri ... ce and product, I am more than happy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>navinag</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product after the 3.02 update</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Love the device. Many issues fixed after 3.02 update. I also have a Asus transformer and at the end of the day, I gravitate towards the HP Touchpad.

I know the features of Android very well. I love the UI of the touchpad and its simplicity but yet so powerful. Sound quality is the best of any tablet i have used.

I gave this a 4 star there apps are quickly growing but not as many as android and i would have liked a device with a rear facing camera and an HDMI out. otherwise 5 stars</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tableteer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: cloud integration, flash support, great keyboard, fast, easy to use

Cons: nothing yet

I picked up the TouchPad the day it came out. After the initial initialization/syncing that keeps it busy in the first day or two (I do have several accounts including gmail, skype, yahoo, facebook, exchange, dropbox, etc...), it is amazing to see how well the TouchPad integrates all of the information from these cloud services into one concise and pleasant experience. You can&apos;t find this level of integration on any other tablet on the market today. I do have two iPads at home (original and iPad2) and I was getting tired of having to launch separate apps to access different information services.

The TouchPad is great for real productivity. I can launch multiple browser windows, ... access full sites with flash, use Google docs, read all my kindle books, read the news, read and reply to emails - everything just flows... it&apos;s just beautiful!!

I know there is a lot of &quot;emotional attachment&quot; to apple products but content restrictions, locked down functionality and premium prices apple charges for just about anything is just getting ridiculous.

After using the TouchPad for a month and can say with confidence there is nothing better on the market right now.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kpk54</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not such a BAD Tablet!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love it&apos;s OS system...

Cons: Could improve on application available...

Many people and reviewers have really knocked the H.P. I presently have 3 tables and out of the three I prefer the H.P. above the other two. It&apos;s OS system was very easy to operate. i can keep files better organized. It may not have all the &quot;BELLS AND WHISLES&quot; that a lot of the other tablets have. (Half of which I will really never use!) Battery life is good... And it fulfills all the basis needs I use it for...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Moris</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought at launch and so far has been great and its very easy to use, what i like the most:
- Battery lasts around 10 hours of use which is great.
- You can use it as an extension of your phone to continue calls via bluetooth or use skype.
- Flash support.
- Multitasking.
- Matches your contacts with your social networks so you can answer them by phone/sms/mail if they write you on facebook (works both ways).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pravesh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Touchpad rocks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been using the touchpad for over a month now and it rocks. Sound quality is amazing way better then any other tablet. After the web os 3.0.2 update the performance has improved a lot. It has been able to play all the flash videos till date. The facebook app is great and the exhibition mode is awesome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Frank3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Overall I really like the tablet. I like being able to quickly check e-mail and quickly look up information on the web. I have found very few websites the tablet can’t handle. I like being able to play games on the tablet, having a nice size screen and being lighter than my laptop.

A few things that need work
- The Getting Started document mentions the tablet should be fully charged before set up. An approximate time should be included.
- There should be an LED light that shows the tablet is charging, even when off.
- I had a problem turning on my tablet for the first time. I had to call customer support. All I had to do was hold the both buttons until the unit reset, this information should be in the Getting Started document.
- The Getting Started document mentions find ... ing information on logging into a network that doesn’t appear to read the User Guide. Could you have included a user guide? Can’t read it on my tablet since I can’t connect.
- There is a pop out door/button of some sort on the lower right side. What is it? Does this mean later tablets will have SD card readers?
- No Barnes and Noble ebook reader.
- The tablet does a good job with web pages, but there is no way to lock the screen so you can manipulate the window within. For example if you are using google maps you have to use the navigation buttons instead of dragging like you would with a mouse.
- Not sure if this is a plus or minus. The tablet automatically synced with my phone contacts. I would have liked to been asked if I wanted my phone synced.

What I like
- So far I have downloaded a bunch of free apps, yeah angry birds. There are a bunch apps for sale that look helpful.
- I like that Skype is built in.
- Web browsing is simple and quick.
- All my mail accounts were set up easily. I like the ease with which I can read e-mails.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rush</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a very techy person and love to have the latest technologies. But honestly I had no need for a tablet, so, I never even considered one. Now my non-techy wife, who harasses me every time I look at a new device, saw an HP commercial about the new TouchPad. I was ready to flip the channel. Much to my surprise, almost jaw-dropping, she perks up and says that she wants one. Puzzled, I started drilling her why. She has a Palm Pre with Sprint and loves the interface. She was impressed enough with WebOS that she wanted a larger device to do more of what she likes; photos, videos, web-browsing. So, I promptly got her one.

The free next business-day shipping was fantastic. She had her hands on this one the next day. The setup was extremely simple. If you already have a WebOS phone like s ... he has, you just simply log onto your WebOS account and all your personal settings transfer making the TouchPad personalized similar to her phone. I was actually shocked how simple it was. My wife was like, “so aren’t all devices this easy. “ NOT!!!!

I purchased the touchstone charger and case. They are a huge plus. The case makes it a breeze to handle with the non-slip material. The charger is like no other. Just place the device in the stand; no cords or connections necessary.

For the tech stuff, I found it to be sleek, reasonably sized and excellent fit and finish. The OS is responsive and plenty of apps for her needs. For a non-techy person, she was satisfied.

A couple things that I figured out to improve her experience were connecting her WebOS phone directly to the TouchPad and internet connectivity when mobile. The cell service connection from the phone to the TouchPad was a breeze. You simply pair the Palm Pre to the device. I also set up the phone features to work with her Skype account as well. Now for the mobile internet issue, I was a little concerned since the device didn’t have data services through a cellular provider. But, I quickly realized that my phone with sprint h ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bullet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Connection</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Has potential</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>This is my first tablet. I thought that in this day and age the &quot;trial by error&quot; method of acquiring knowledge had improved? NOT Only because I am a stubborn Irishman do I still have this. The good points are beginning to reveal themselves - I just wish the learning curve wasn&apos;t as steep. Because the price was $200 it has been worth it.
I hope that there is a brighter future for the software!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mharvin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I like my HP TouchPad Tablet especially I bought it as around $150 for 32GB. It&apos;s heavy to hold for a long time but the screen is nice. I&apos;ve already installed android so now my TouchPad has two OS in it. 

Weight

heavy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>deafraptor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Connection</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Glad I bought one.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The HP Touchpad came very highly recommended by a friend who is quite knowledgeable with electronics. After seeing some of the things he did with his, I thought it very necessary to get one of my own to see if I could do the same thing at my house. The Touchpad is very user-friendly and I have had a lot of fun customizing it and only minor issues with it so far. The battery life is amazing; Wifi and movies are obvious battery-killers. The portability factor is definitely a Plus. I just wish I would have caught it during the firesale.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jhopjsh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the money !!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This tablet have everything I hoped for and more..Fast and easy to use. Didn&apos;t want to spend the $ on an Ipad so I bought this on sale at Staples. I AM SO HAPPY WITH MY PURCHASE. No regrets it&apos;s not an Ipad

Battery Life

The battery life is AMAZING !!

Processing Speed

FAST, FAST, FAST

Weight

Not an issue

App Availability

Seemed to have everything I&apos;ve looked for

Durability

Haven&apos;t had any issues</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>vato</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Connection</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product with a small issue</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>The HP tablet meets all of my requirements and was a great value. The only negative was the non-functioning USB power cable. Fortunately I had a spare cable to troubleshoot with.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rikanaka</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent, quick, responsive</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent, quick, responsive, good battery life, hackable (Android)

Cons: Limited apps for WebOS, better for Android but not all work

Good purchase, definitely worth the bundle with HP computer deep discount but I wouldn&apos;t pay more the two hundred for it alone. Other Android tabs are dropping in price and may present better alternatives, as might the older gen iPads now that gen3 is out.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>trottytrue</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>this tablet is so much more than expexted.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use. touch screen excellent. great app. highly recommended.

Cons: no cons.

I love it. Highly recommend. Very easy to use. Like brand new condition.
touch screen is amazing. Think worlds ahead of ipad. This item does not get enough recognition. A plus in my opinion.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tabletman1105</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet for the Money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size

Cons: I have found nothing yet

I will have to say this is a good buy. I have used it everyday and love it. This is a great buy. I have no complaints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daven</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This touchpad is nothing less than great! It is great for everyday use and especially good for showing off to your friends... Also if you like to write docs on the go it also help. the physique of this tablet is amazing and is a steal for its price. LOVE IT!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hak8or</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Once you get android on it, for $150 it is the best out there.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>When you take into consideration how HP sold them for $100 and $150, that android has been ported to it, and that WEBOS will be opensourced soon, this is arguably the best tablet for $150 or $100 out there. The screen resolution is adequate, and while the screen may not output as much light as the top tablets out there, it is more than sufficient for use during a sunny day.

Speed wise, this tablet has a dual core snapdragon with a full Gig of ram, so it is very fast. Benchmarks show that this tablet is actually faster than the Ipad 2, which is fast enough for the average user, and even fast enough for the more demanding users out there.

WEBOS by itself is very empty of apps, but it certainly is not horrible. The good thing about this tablet is that you can put android on it, ... with all the apps and games that come with it. The process is very easy if you follow directions online.

The Cons about this tablet is that it is rather heavy, there are not much awesome cases out there for it, battery life is only a day of heavy use with screen set to lowest, and the display does not throw out much light compared to the top dogs. Also, when transferring to the touchpad via USB, it is VERY slow, only 1 MB/s. I have no idea why it is so slow, but something to keep in mind.

Battery Life

About a day of heavy use with screen brightness set to minimum.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>With the current price, it is a steal~</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For those who expected the same functionality of IPAD on this toy, you aren t getting it. Though it does not have the same function as an IPAD, it is still pretty useful for those who are looking for a cheap and affordable table. You can pretty much do anything from browsing the web, to reading an ebook on this tablet. I have been using this tablet for months to read my journal articles and ebooks and such. It is really convenient to use and the price is definitely affordable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>midtownshopper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Discontinued, but good.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: &quot;Special&quot; price was great!

Cons: Not being made/supported any longer.

Bought this as a gift for someone who wanted to try a tablet to see if they liked it. Since it&apos;s discontinued the price was good and would make a great &quot;try-out.&quot; They love it, so it&apos;s a shame it&apos;s no longer being made!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Niecetoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hard to beat for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price vs. functionality for a kid

Cons: outdated before I even purchased it

This was for a 4 year old and the price was the deciding factor since a 4 year old is bound to break it. It is a &apos;tester&apos; as when she starts school, there will probably be at least 10 new I pads by then. When that time comes, I&apos;ll get her an I pad since it will probably be the standard for schools and will most likely replace most if not all books by that time. With the purchase of the correct laptop, the price went from 600 to 150 dollars. With what I paid for the laptop, the whole price was still less than the pad alone or an I pad 2. It is also very functional and will teach her the basics of using a pad type computer which like I already said, will probably become the standard for students. ... Nice deal, Best Buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CB1102</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP TABLET</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very Portable

Cons: Hard to find covers

I bought this in a package with a laptop! My husband got the tablet and I the laptop buT of course we all use both. The HP Tablet is easy to use and has been used by everyone in the house. My 6 year old even has an easy time to use and mauver the tablet. Programs and apps are easily downloaded.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>biguser</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great starter tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up, easy to use, really fast processing

Cons: fact that HP will not be developing these further, lack of apps

We lucked out on this product when I was looking for a computer for my husband on bestbuy.com. There was a blurb about getting the Touchpad for $149.99 if bought with a computer. After checking the Touchpad out online, we went to the store and picked one up along with an HP laptop. The Touchpad was so easy to use--set-up was beyond simple and I was up and running in no time. We&apos;ve had this now for about 3 months and I&apos;m discovering things about it every day--like there is a Kindle app and I can download free books from my local library, and it can hook up wirelessly with our HP printer. We keep it on our coffee table and we&apos;re able to check our email ... accounts, Facebook, and look up various items lickity-split! I told my husband that he would love it once he tried it and I was right LOL! Now I almost have to fight him for it! I had been checking out various tablets since they came on the scene, but the prices were so scary and I really couldn&apos;t justify the prices in my mind since we already had 2 laptops and a PC--BUT, the $150 price tag was just right and although HP has decided not to continue with this line of products, it has given us a great idea of what tablets are capable of doing and I will be looking for an Android based tablet in the near future.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ImranChicago</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Touchpad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: For its price, its must buy

Cons: Cannot add sd card to add more memory, no camera on back

Its not bad at all for the price. I recommend you buy a case for it as soon as you get the touch-pad. I have webos and android installed so i love switching back and forth and trying different applications.

Cons: its hardware because you cant connect to external drive or add sd card to add more memory. Also, there is no back camera, just the front has camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rd11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality construction,

I wanted a tablet to check email and do quick searches , The HP touchpad more than meets my requirements, without settling for a cheaper quality model that cost more. Purchased through the buy one laptop get one for $149 deal fit the bill quite well as we were going to get a laptop for our high school graduating daughter anyway. And as for aps there are hundreds of them that I will never use anyway.As of 1,14,12 HP is still updating the operating system and more people are working on aps since the operating system has been released as open source. Perhaps company&apos;s should take notice that when a quality product is sold at a reasonable price , they sell like hotcakes!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gator03</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for my needs.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Set up was very user friendly and easy to understand.

Cons: nothing

I love the tablet and it allows me to do everything I need out of the computer. The nice surprise was to be able to purchase it as a bundle packet when I bought another holiday gift.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrsGeek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The price and quality

Cons: No further development

A great tablet. I had the Pre phone so i was used to th os. Unfortunate that it will not be developed further.... Creating tabs on the browser would have been great. Could use more apps. I love the way the photo gallery integrates from different locations such as facebook.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pawemwdad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>bah humbug</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size 32Gigs

Cons: limited apps

got this for the wife for Christmas ended up giving it to my daughter. Operates on the old Palm Pilot operating system. Limited apps for the device. Ok for a kids use around the house or a fancy E-reader.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>FDRy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Cons: close out item

Close out item, great price. Hard to update latest abode flash drive. Make sure you&apos;re in a good hotspot for streaming music and video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bww227</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price and easy set up, plus fast &amp; nicely portable.

Cons: The fact that it was discontinued.

Although I understand that this product has been discontinued, I certainly enjoyed having it with me away from home. I did have to return it after only two months of owning it because the power connection inside the Tablet was too loose to power it up. HP handled my request with amazing service and ability to quickly return the item for repair.I sure hope it lasts me a long time when I get it back!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nettdynamics</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product excellent sound &amp; visuals</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use and High quality craftmanship and sound

Cons: a little thicker than some of the competition

At first glance the HP touch pad looks not that much different than other main stream tablets. The web OS is supper easy to use and I am findin it very easy to do what I need to do with this product. Such as.

Flash enabled Browser-
Remote access to my windows desktop and windows servers-
10gb of free online storage from box.com (making my 32gb Touchpad a 42gb beast.-
Easy printing in my house to my network printers.
Beats Audio that gives the full rich sound a high grade set of speakers.-
Wi-Fi that works from 4 houses away-
Overall I am please at everything about this tablet. It is a little heavy compared to the samsung and Ipad2 but we are t ... alking ounces which does not overcome the initial fell of quality when you use this product. HP Please dont abandon these release more!!!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SFGwd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice size, Lots of memory.

Cons: Web OS. Hard to find apps.

I liked this tablet, but not enough to keep it. I had rather have a laptop or my iPhone.The primary reason I got the HP tablet was because it was a good price at $149, and I primarily look at my email and Facebook. Since I could rarely get my email to come up, it was a waste of $149.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tati</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredibly Fast!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quiet; Comfortable Keyboard; Quality Display; Lightweight; Fast; Long Battery Life

The price was so unexpensive that I never expected this touchpad to be so great. It is super fast and easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Savvy Shopper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful; Quiet; Long Battery Life; Lightweight; Quality Display; Fast

I was looking for the perfect tablet for my daughters that rival the Ipad without the Ipad price. I lucked up on these touchpads and purchased two. I&apos;ve used them briefly myself and am pleasantly impressed. They connect easily to our home network and are very quick when browsing. I&apos;ve found myself reaching for the touchpad instead of the bulky laptop several times. The girls play youtube videos and play angry birds and the quality is as good as my iphone and much bigger. The only downfall is a somewhat limited app market.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gertrude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This product is great! While I have no exposure to the iPad (which most people seem to prefer due to the large number of apps writen for it), the TouchPad more than meets my needs.

webOS is fast and user friendly. And, it&apos;s really cool that when the TouchPad is placed on the TouchStone to charge, it will slide-show through any pics you have on the device. If you have no pics loaded, it displays a clock. So it can really become part of your decor while it&apos;s charging!

Really wish HP hadn&apos;t discontinued the webOS hardware. I think with time, and more developers creating apps for it, this tablet really could have commanded the price at which it was originally priced. It was a bit premature to go head to head with Apple right out of the gate. But, as HP has probably seen, there is ... demand. Bite the bullet up front and take your loses...then as more users buy in, more developers create apps...then up the price.

Regardless, if you have an opportunity to purchase one, go for it! Totally cool...and I&apos;m now addicted to Angry Birds :-o
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jess3311</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Touchpad was very quick and easy to set up. Very easy for a first time touchpad user to navigate and learn. Really like not having to download or purchase a lot of &quot;apps&quot; to make it do what I want to do. Purchased it for my daughter, very seriously thinking about keeping it for myself and purchasing another one for her!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ManuelM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My new TouchPad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I am enjoying this new tablet which compliments the Apple tablet we own. The feel is good and the experience is great. This product has so much potential that WebOS should be maintained for developers to continue to write new apps.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VZSteeler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A huge deception but not by the product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight with good screen resolution

Cons: Very slow starting, and being upheld by HP

Three days after buying it, HP decided to go out of business. What a learning lesson !!!
The product is OK but it lacks software. webOS development is a joke, with just a couple dozen really useful applications (in my opinion)
It looks like a decent piece of hardware left in the middle of nowhere.
It became a luxury 150$ toy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WestCoastNative</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fun tablet at an insane price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: webOS looks great

Cons: A little heavy &amp; bulky for a tablet.

The HP TouchPad shows the potential of webOS. Sorry that the TouchPad itself is now dead, because the way it runs webOS, it looks and feels gorgeous, and is really well set up for the cloud.

The hardware itself was a little heavy, but speakers sound good and the display is crisp. The device really lets the software shine: webOS on a big screen looks great.

Web browsing on the device works great, too; speedy and it renders all the web sites I go to, no problem. Plus the support for Flash is there, a nice bonus.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AckRt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not an IPAD killer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Lack of apps limit this product&apos;s capabilities. Camera works well, printing is simple. USB connection makes file transfers easy. Great product for the sale price,I would not pay the original introductory price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrBilll</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Design... Needs APPS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Quality

Cons: Lack of APPS

I spent 3 days finding the right store and over 2 hours in line. Worth the effort. Lots of cases available on ebay.

It&apos;s great for pictures, viewing office docs, web browsing, Kindle reading... and of course Angry Birds. When I place in the charging dock, it becomes a Slide-Show screen saver.

I tried to read non-Amazon books. I had to use the P-reader. The experience could be better.

For $150, it&apos;s the best deal in the market, but without more apps it will probably become a picture frame.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TheBoogieman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the Closeout price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Closeout Price

Cons: WebOS

This is very nice tablet for the closeout price. Screen not quite as good as my I***d but look at the $99 price. I got this to install Android so I&apos;m waiting for the programmers to finish their port.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chung</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>webOS is good for multitasking</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price!

Cons: need tweaks to work well

At the firesale price, the TP is a no-brainer purchase. It does everything I need a tablet to do for me. i would say that if the price was $249/299, I would still recommend it.

Need to apply the various tweaks to make this tablet responsive, but they were easy tweaks. BTW, this has the best speakers for any tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MannyinOrlando</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sent back twice for repairs</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great for web surfing and email is ok

Cons: hardware is bad, camera is cheap when it works and gets laggy quick.

Buggy as hell OS. not sure if the hardware is faulty or the software is at fault. But until Android is released on this, i keep sending it back for all the intermittent issues. Even without the non functioning hardware, its still a great value for a $99 device.. But at it&apos;s original price it would be a 2 star item.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>YungLos</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: webOS!

Cons: No big company apps but Splashtop makes up for it!

Great OS, if a little sluggish. WIth the new Splashtop Remote Desktop App, it has become a complete system! Fun to use and great community to make the tablet better. AND you cannot beat the price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MusicMama2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent for what I need, just hard to find</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set up, apps are still available, can Skype with a decent picture

Cons: Not available any more

Purchased this as a gift for my pastry-chef niece who wants to put all her recipes on it and give up her bulky notebooks. Stood in line on an early morning and snagged the last ticket for a 32GB unit.

She put preware on it, updated to the last drivers, and has been thrilled with the functionality. She&apos;s in the process of transferring her recipe files and it&apos;s much more portable than what she was using previously. Her boss would love one but there aren&apos;t any more available (at the same price).

She does web surf and play a few games, and we can even Skype! Gotta say, this little unit does a lot!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rlc9cheeks</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought the 32gb hp tablet, absolutely love it!!! very responsive, great apps, love the touch screen. graphics are really good, speakers are great. I have only come across 2 downsides to this tablet, and I consider them negligible-There is no sd card slot, although there is obviously a spot where they could have put one and the hp app store is poorly organized, meaning when you search for an app, it is not always listed under the appropriate heading. However, they have over 2000 apps to choose from at this time which is plenty for my needs.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>larrysyr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet at an incredible price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It works great, with a full web browser that plays flash

Cons: discontinued, may be the last webOS device I can own

I got in on the HP touchpad fire sale and got this tablet for 149 dollars. Having a Verizon pre plus for the last year has made me familiar with the operating system, so taking to the Touchpad was like a duck takes to water. No major complaints at this price point. System update from HP fixed most of the bugs apparent in the just shipped state. I wish HP had waited before pushing this out the door and into the hands of iPad using tech reviewers who don&apos;t get the utility of a true multitasking tablet. Having owned several versions of ipod touch and iPhones, I have no illusions that any tablet will be the final word and last forever, so I&apos;m not worried about ... getting something that has been discontinued by HP.
.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>techlover2011</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: can&apos;t beat the price

Cons: lack of apps currently

Did not disappoint and great value for the fire sale price. Now, once Android is available and more apps are for the taking it should be a steal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kengee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HP Touchpad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Amazing Service!! Quick order and lightning fast Free next day delivery. Great deal and a solid product!!! Definitely look forward to doing business with Office Depot!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RAFF17</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet with lots of Potential!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price,OS....

Cons: Application&amp;Hardware

Purchased this during the HP firesale, I cant complain no more for that price. touchpad with few tweaks will give you a very nice and fast tablet. apps is limited but its okay. full web browser is really nice, with flash too! limited accessories but with original hp accessories will cover all you need. I hope HP keeps supporting this tablet for few more years!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gero</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Full Flash, Browsing, email

Cons: Beats audio speakers are non-existent, Tweaking required to make it smoother, faster

I bought this during the firesale having never used an WebOS tablet or phone before and i am glad i bought it. It&apos;s definitely worth the price......but it&apos;s can&apos;t be compared to an Android tablet (Asus transformer or Galaxy tab etc) or the IPad.

Very good for browsing the internet, youtube, checking mail, watching movies, has Full Flash :) which is an awesome feature.

Beat&apos;s audio is a joke, internal speakers suck.

Some tweaking in required to make it faster and smoother but overall it&apos;s one of the best buys of the yr. for me from Best Buy.

Samsung, Asus and Toshiba should learn something from HP and lower their prices ... a bit to better compete with the IPad.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Aftika</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I received my HP Touchpad during the $99 frenzy. I could not be happier with it.
The pros: Quick response to touch (I have an Archos 101 which is very particular as to how you touch it which is very annoying); screen is clear and vibrant; easy to dismiss the keyboard (another issue with the Archos); shuts off quickly; quick processor; multitasking is the best I have seen in any tablet.

The cons: Slow start up; a little heavy (much heavier than the Archos); no built in stand (which the Archos has); weak word processor is really just a note writer; no access to 3G; the USB port is only for connecting the Touchpad to a PC so the memory is not expandable; few apps but there seem to be more apps available weekly.

It does everything you want from a tablet when connected through ... WiFi. At the fire sale price there is nothing out there to beat it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pedro1850</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding tablet...one heckuva deal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lot&apos;s of power and capacity for the price!

Cons: Needs more app support to max out it&apos;s potential!

Purchased it during the fire sale for $99, this tablet rocks! I have not put it down. Loaded my music, movies, photos and games without any problems. Love the USB hook up and file transfer, for the non-techie like me this product is truly &apos;user&apos; friendly. Loaded the camera app and it rocks...loaded Skype am now ready for some &apos;face time&apos; phone calling!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RRARick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A must have</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, Multitasking tablet

Cons: Can&apos;t buy more.

The touchpad is everything you would want in a tablet. Able to access all flash websites. Very fast. The best email of any tablet. I like having all of my contacts in one place. It pulls in all contacts from Facebook and LinkedIn. Plays movies, music pictures. Pulls all of your pictures from facebook. Did I say fast. I don’t understand reviews that say the touchpad is slow. I have not found this to be true. I have 4 and they all work as you would expect. I have not found the need for more apps. The battery life is very good. I can use it all day on wifi and still have battery life left.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kyeongshik</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for awesome price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great browser, easy to use, like the cards for apps

Cons: Its a dying OS and doesn&apos;t have a lot of apps

I like this tablet a lot. For what I use it for (browsing the web, listening to music through Pandora, and light email) it works great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ew92</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Really nice keyboard and email app..and it has Flash!!

Cons: Some 3rd party apps are sluggish

Love this tablet...and the reduced price is unbeatable. Best Buy is incredible for honoring the firesale price! Best email client i have ever used other than on a PC. The sliding panes are great in apps. Love being able to keep apps running and switch between them quickly...multitasking is unmatched and so is Synergy technology. Has most apps that i would want. With the 50GB of free lifetime online storage i have 82GB total. More than enough storage. Too bad HP discontinued it though. Really enjoy this tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>abcdreviewer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hardware great, apps limited</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Browser and speed

Cons: limited apps

okay so I was one of the dudes who stood in line to get this for the reduced price. I wanted another &quot;fruit related&quot; tablet bud didn&apos;t want to shell out the $$$. I have been ridiculously impressed with this tablet. The browser is excellent and flash enabled so I can stream videos and movies from sites like Megavideo and others, which you cant do on other tablets. It has many apps that I find useful, like Skype, pandora, angry birds and email, but does not have the selection from the other platforms. Many say that it will be ported over to android instead of web OS but I am not counting on it anytime soon. I would say that for the price I paid it is so worth it even just for the internet browser.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EvlJP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for media consumption</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>At the clearance price of $150 I thought I would like to try WebOS and a tablet in general. I have found the tablet format to be limiting. WebOS has some nice features, but I have found the browser does not render every page accurately. One big disappointment is that it will not connect to an ad hoc wifi network, so I cannot tether to by android phone.

Overall, it is nice to consume media, but that is all I will use it for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>YARDBIRD6</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: PRICE, PRICE, PRICE

Cons: Limited apps

Was able to get this as a gift for my wife at the closeout $99 price...... thank you Best Buy. For the price it is fabulous, at the original price not so much. Limited apps, occasional internet hiccups. Does have a nice display and pretty cool functionality. Hopefully more apps will be developed, if not, still a cool toy for the price; considering my sons TI scientific calculator cost as much as this.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JFBowler09</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: webOS, skype

Cons: speed, no camera in front

I love this tablet! I actually like webOS better than iOS just because of the &quot;card&quot; feature, its very convenient. I also really like the way Skype works on the tablet, very easy to use, even for my mother who before didn&apos;t even know what Skype was.

Maybe the only things that may turn people off is the lack of a camera in the front and the fact that sometimes it is a bit slow. (can be tweaked however to make it go faster)

Overall, it is a great product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>aoewill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>performed as expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Got @ fire sale and got what I expected. It is occasionally quirky, but issues (so far) have all been resolved with a little patience and without calling 4 tech support.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Meedum</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Decent product for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been enjoying my Touchpad but the quality of the case leaves much to be desired. It is almost impossible to keep the screen clear of fingerprints and smudges. A few times i have noticed that the screen becomes unresponsive although i don&apos;t believe this is caused by the dirty screen. All in all, i am very happy with my purchase and would possibly buy another Touchpad if they were to go on sale again.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>HP TouchPad 16 GB - HP gloss black</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/14578044357694116485/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CPYBEPQCMAY4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>orod25</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Multitasking! True multitasking that it.

Cons: Attention to detail

Lets get this straight, this is a tablet that I most likely would not have purchased if not during the &quot;fire sale&quot;. Don&apos;t get me wrong its a good tablet but not what it could have been. Webos is great, along with the tablet itself, but after playing with it as one would do you start to find the missed &quot;attention to detail&quot; that other tablets and their os have. But for the price, its the best out there. The actual web browser is the best on any tablet and it would have been interesting to what this badboy could have if not ditched. It could have really given others a run for their money! Root it and overclock it and you have a pretty darn fast tablet at the tips of your hand. Apps are limited but it does ... exactly the same as others.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

