<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ibCotts</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet - for what it was intended to do</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, clarity, speed

Cons: Battery life, not the best Screen resolution out there

I have the new iPad which I use for everything and absolutely love. I read a lot of ebooks and wanted something smaller that I could carry with me and that I could hold with one hand while reading. I wasn&apos;t looking for an iPad replacement; rather, I wanted an ereader. I debated the nook tablet and kindle fire and actually went to best buy to buy the fire, when I saw the galaxy tab 2 I decided for an extra $50 I could have a real android tablet instead of the hacked interface of the fire. It was a no brainer - a full fledged tablet that had ICS and met my requirement of functioning as an ereader with the kindle and nook apps. I sideload many of my ebooks and it is easy to sideload into eith ... er app (kindle for mobi and nook for epubs).

The web browsing is sufficient, although I find the small keyboard to be a challenge with the size of my fingers. My only criticism is the battery life. One evening spent reading and doing some web browsing and the tablet needs to be recharged.

All in all a good value for the money. This is NOT an iPad replacement. It was intended as a BUDGET tablet to compete with the Nook Tablet and Kindle Fire. If you want an iPad save your money and buy an iPad...if you want something to supplement an iPad or something that will let you run apps from Google Play, surf the web and read books then this is a great buy.

Would I recommend it - without a doubt. I would suggest though that you first define what it is that you want to do with your tablet before deciding if this will meet your needs. In my case it absolutely meets them but I had a specific reason for wanting a 7 inch tablet. I realize that having both this and a new iPad might be out of many peoples&apos; budgets but if you are able to swing it between the two you will have the best of all possible worlds when it comes to tablet computing.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>9 out of 12 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tekio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Went from an iPad to this, and.................</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything but the battery.

Cons: The battery. :(

I like it compared to the other tables I&apos;ve used. I decided to go Android vs. iOS on a tablet. I use it for everything, especially reading and taking notes of studies. The size is just perfect to have large clear text, while being able to type, holding it normally, with two hands. That&apos;s one reason I strayed from the 10.1&quot; tablet form-factor.

The size and weight of this tablet hit a home-run, IMO.

The one thing I was sketchy about before ordering the 7&quot; tab was its screen resolution. I like crisp, and smooth looking screens on my tech devices. I was actually pleasantly surprised with the screen. The resolution is just perfect for a 7&quot; device.

there were some very minot annoyances:
1) button to tur ... n the display off is directly by the volume button. Sometimes when I put it on the charger, it will let out a very loud audio alert because I accidentally turn the volume up when trying to turn off the display.

2) the bottom menu strays away from Android, and was redone by Samsung. It features a back button, a home button, and screen capture button on the touch screen Sometimes while typing, I&apos;ll accidently hit the home button when going for the space bar on the keypad. This is getting less of a problem, as I get more accustomed to the layout.

My biggest complaint is the battery. Not too bad, but another hour of battery life would be ideal.

All-in-all, I&apos;m sold on this. I really, really think it&apos;s one of the best tablets on the market.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>samsungerforever</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet Ever - Smasung II 7&quot; Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, battery Life, SD Card Slot

Cons: Limited Accessories as compared to Apple

This thing is great. Because of it&apos;s size I take it everywhere. Isn&apos;t that what they are for? The large iPad and other 10&quot; Tablets are bulky and you end up not taking it with you. This size is perfect. Easy to carry, easy to see, and easy to use. The HD quality screen is perfect! It is fast with boo coos of apps. This tablet goes everywhere with me, I can take notes, take pictures, take movies, skype, and just about anything you can think of. Perfect Samsung - glad somebody got it right and at a very good price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tabman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>First the good: I use this tablet for games, email, web browsing, reading books, photo viewing, watching videos, listening to music and running various apps. I&apos;ve had it for just over 2 weeks and so far it has done everything I asked it to do. It has reliably run all my games and apps, haven&apos;t had any lockups or crashes yet. The tablet screen is large enough to comfortably watch videos, play games, read a book, or browse the web, and is small enough to fit in a large pocket. The 7 Tab 2 is much more portable than my 10 Acer tablet. Has decent sounding speakers. Works with 64GB micro sd card! (Has to be formatted to FAT32 file system, I used a free program called EaseUS Partition Master to format it). This was a huge plus for me as I like to have all my files right there with me, ... rather than having to download them from some cloud whenever I want to use them. The battery life is good, I can use this for 4 - 6 hours a day and still have 40 - 60% power remaining. I keep the power saving feature on most of the time. Charge time is reasonably quick, I&apos;d guess around 4 - 5 hours to get a full charge. It has a neat feature called Wifi direct which lets you connect directly to other tablets with that feature. Not too many devices have this feature yet so it&apos;s uses are limited but I thought it was neat. I was able to connect to another Galaxy tab 2 and was able to transfer a few files without much hassle. The screen brightness is good for the most part, it doesn&apos;t do well in bright sunlight though. Almost forgot to mention the screenshot button. I figured this would be useless but it&apos;s actually come in handy a few times. If I need to record a serial number or information from an app or website I can just take a screenshot and save it instead of trying to copy and past the info or type it into a document on the tablet. The button can also be disabled or set to open the camera app, load the search app, or open the application menu. And now for not so good: The cameras aren&apos;t great, similar to most tablets, but are adequate for occasional snapshots. It has an Infrared blaster for use as a remote for tv&apos;s and various electronic equipment, I used it briefly but the included tv remote control app is not great (Peel Smart Remote). Maybe I&apos;ll use it in the future. The Samsung app store seems very small compared to Googles&apos; Play store. Typing on the Tablet is ok, not as nice as typing on my 10 tablet but not a hassle either. The biggest downside to this tablet for me is it only has 8GB of internal memory. Of which only a little over 4GB is available when you get it out of box. The rest is taken up by the Android operating system and various preinstalled apps. (The ability to use 64GB micro SD cards makes it fairly easy to overlook this negative). An additional downside is that the preinstalled apps can only be disabled not uninstalled. I don&apos;t know why the Android tablets are all set up like this it is very annoying and a waste of space. It also has a mini app bar on the bottom of the screen. This can be brought up at any time to launch a few apps. A calculator, calendar, music player, and a few others. I find this to be rather annoying, I&apos;ve hit the button to bring up the mini app bar quite a few times and then have to close it too continue my game, video or whatever. I haven&apos;t found a way to disable this thing yet or customize it by adding my own apps to it. You are limited to the 6 or so apps it comes with which seems rather pointless to me. It also seems a little sluggish, I can just jump to the home screen and have access to all my favorite apps in the amount of time it takes the little app bar to slide up from the bottom of the screen. Despite it&apos;s problems I&apos;m quite happy with the Galaxy Tab 2, none of the downsides have been a major issue for me.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>7 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kelli9001</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Camera

Cons: nothing yet

I went looking for a good priced tablet that I could use for business and home. I had looked at the Ipad, Kindle and several other tablets. My criteria was plenty of storage, good camera, games, reading app. Pretty general, however all of these combined were hard to find until now. The camera was my hold up as I wasn&apos;t able to find anything in my proce with a camera. The price on the Samsung was great, slightly more than I had planned to spend but well worth it. This is the first one I found with a good camera. It&apos;s lightweight and easy to handle/carry. I purchased a screen protector and a carrying case with a flip stand to view movies. There&apos;s loads of storage for pics and files and I use Dropbox to transfer files and pictures to upload for bus ... iness. Battery life is adequate, not excellent but several hours worth. Would recommend this tablet to anyone in my price range,
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bornfree</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Much more than I expected!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Quality Construction; Efficient; Easy to Use

To Have the world information at your finger tips a [$] is astounding. The many applications that you can get free or low cost can help you or entertain you are amazing. I wanted it to help with a new sport (geocaching) to enjoy with my grandchildren, and when I started to use it is when I discovered just how amazing it is. Just the right size too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mommabear2011</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great gift!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great price, easy set up, easy to use

Cons: trying to find a cover that i want..

My husband just gave me this for my birthday on the 24th. I love it! Havent been able to take my hands off of it. It comes with alot of apps that i wanted already on it. Its very easy to use and because of the size I think its perfect for women to hold. The image is great. Sound is great. Takes pictures and videos wonderfully.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tambar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>&quot;Everything I expected and more&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Quality Construction; Reliable; Easy to Use; Efficient

I love the size of this tablet. It fits perfectly in my purse, to use when I&apos;m out and about. I find myself using it more often than my laptop, even when I&apos;m at home. It is just so convenient and love the long battery life.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>thecollector1992</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An Excellent and Affordable Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, screen size, battery life, Android 4.0, simple to use

Cons: Minor bugs (but rare), camera isn&apos;t the best (but not really important to me)

Before I purchased the Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 7.0, I owned a Blackberry PlayBook. While it was reliable and easy to use, the app selection was sparse. So I sold my PlayBook and picked up the Tab 2 7.0. I was immediately impressed. The construction of the Tab 2 7.0 felt strong and firm and didn&apos;t feel cheap, even though the body is made of plastic, and thankfully Samsung didn&apos;t make a plastic display instead of glass, looking at the price tag. The Tab 2 7.0 felt speedy and smooth when navigating the home screen and app menu. There was little lag. The Tab 2 7.0 comes with Android 4.0.3, aka Ice Cream Sandwich, which looks visually ... similar to 3.0 Honeycomb, but it has Samsung&apos;s TouchWiz interface, which luckily is a lot more improved than earlier versions but it may be an issue if you want the closest thing to stock Android. So far I haven&apos;t had any software issues, except for a rare case when the widgets got visually glitched with stretched text and images, but this has only happened once. It has a dual-core 1GHz processor, a bit behind for today&apos;s standards, but it was still good enough to get the job done quickly. 1024x600 is the screen resolution, typical for a 7in tablet, but it looked clearer and more vibrant than other 7in tablets. Videos looked good and audio was surprisingly good as well. The rear camera took decent photos for being only 3MP, but I never intended to use the tablet for taking pictures anyways. Battery life is very good as well. I got 10 hours of life before recharging, with WiFi on and screen brightness set to automatic. The Tab 2 7.0 only has 8GB of memory, with about 4.6GB usable, but it has a microSD slot so it was no big deal, just put videos and music on the microSD card and use the internal memory for apps. I also am using it as an e-reader to replace my Nook Color and text looks sharp and clear, even at small text sizes (using Nook app). The app selection is decent, and the screen is small enough that even phone-based apps look decent, but ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MelissaBK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love love this tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture Quality is great, Perfect size and Price

Cons: Nothing

I love this tablet. I really like the fact that it comes with a sandisk slot. So it&apos;s really nice to know that I can expand the memory. Apps are easy to download and download pretty fast. I&apos;ve watched movies on here and I was first concenrn that the tablet would be too small to watch movies compared to the 10.1 inch tablet but that was not the case. The movie was clear and big enough. I prefer this tablet over the 10.1 or the Ipad mainly due to size. I just don&apos;t want to carry something so big. This is perfect. I can read my kindle books, play games while on the train, and watch movies. So far so good. Personally I like the andriod operating system. I have an iphone and my husband have the samsung galaxy nex ... us phone and I love the way his phone operates so that was another reason why I chose to go with the samsung galaxy tablet over the Ipad. When I&apos;m due for a new phone, I&apos;m probably definitely going to go with andrioid. Also, price was a big factor too. You really can&apos;t beat $250 compared to$500-$700 for an ipad or other tablets.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DivineShadow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great general use tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, battery life, picture quality, value for its price

Cons: Camera

I bought this as a gift for my wife. It works great for applications like Netflix, Skype, facebook, and general web browsing. My wife also uses it for audio books and eBooks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ajbr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product for First Timers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It is a great tablet. Run smoothly nearly all the apps. The only problem is a bug with Netflix, it crash when I try to change of season. This happens with all the series. The sound could be louder since the speakers are on one side of the tablet. For on the bed browsing or watch Netflix (not series) is excellent. Is not the top performer for magazine or book reading. Apps support from Google play is mediocre as for all tablets. Battery life is average Screen resolution is average, colors a good. I believe that the size is perfect. Weight is good</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LipsmackinBackpacker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My new hiking buddy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Features, Battery Life, Performance

Cons: Not waterproof.

I needed a tablet to take along on trekking journeys. This to hold all field guides, maps (topo and street), books and various entertainment files. I bought the Nook Tablet first and it was great but it couldn&apos;t do topo&apos;s, No app compatibility. Didn&apos;t really care about no GPS, just wanted maps. Returned the Nook Tablet and bought this Tab 2 7.0.

This tablet is perfect for my needs. Longer battery life than the NT or Fire, has the hardware cams, GPS, is lighter and the sound is twice as loud. Loading topo apps is a breeze. No messy rooting (even when rooted the Nook Tab wouldn&apos;t do topo apps (the Fire can#). I just have to settle for a less than optimal reader now #the Nook Tab is far and above the Ta ... b 2 7.0 in this role).

Bought it today, loaded a Topo GPS app, and was hiking with it within an hour. Yep, just what I needed. Get a Pelican 1055 for weatherproof and submersible protection.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kls1955</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet at a Great Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Andriod 4.0 OS

Cons: Battery life could be better

I was all set to purchase a Nook Tablet. However after doing some more
research on tablets. I discovered the Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 7.0.
Being familiar with Samsung, have both a TV and Blue-ray player.
I went to the store to check it out. I was not disappointed. The Galaxy tab
was easy to use, had a great screen, it felt good in my hands, and it had
a price tag in my budget. The real selling point was it had a full Andriod
4.0 OS. Which the Nook did not. The Galaxy tab is a great product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LucasB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A lot of tablet for a low price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, good price

Cons: WiFi reception, availability of tablet apps

I love this tablet. It&apos;s great for streaming video and surfing the internet. It&apos;s compact, yet has a large enough screen to clearly see video, pages, and documents. $250 is a great price for such a powerful tablet. My only two gripes are that the WiFi reception is horrible. My iPhone gets much better reception than this tablet. Plus, the availability of apps from the Google Play store isn&apos;t as plentiful since many of the apps I like to use aren&apos;t compatible with a tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>superbear</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good enough for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price, expandable memory, built quality and sound quality

Cons: dual core processor, lags and watching videos

this is my first tablet! I have an iphone so i chose this tablet to start learning or getting used to android. i was satisfied with this product! it&apos;s affordable and you can do a lot of stuff in it but compared to newer tablets out there this is pretty outdated! it lags every now and then, only has dual core processor and i&apos;m not that impressed with the video quality when watching videos so i returned it and upgraded it with asus transformer pad infinity! if you&apos;re in a tight budget this is good enough.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MusicMan89</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Low Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is Cheap

Cons: Low Quality Low Resolution Screen, Sluggish Performance

Recently I bought this tablet for my fiance, I have always been a big fan of Samsung products, I have a Galaxy S III, had a Nexus S and have series 6 and 7 televisions as well as several of their blue-ray players as they have always been high quality. I was really disappointed with this tablet.

I already own a Transformer Tablet (TF101), which compared to this tablet is rather outdated so I expected a little bump in performance or at least comparable performance.

First off I would expect something from Samsung to at least have a high quality display. Not only is this tablet low resolution, it also does not have a great quality display in general. The color is washed out and not very ... crisp at all.

As for performance new out of the box this tablet was not the smooth experience I am used to with Android tablets. There was a noticeable lag when doing simple things like changing pages of the home screen.

To top everything off, the construction of the tablet is made of a very cheap feeling plastic. This one is definitely a let down from Samsung. I still will buy their other products, but this has deterred me from buying another one of their tablets. This one has been returned.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MargieK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product but an owner&apos;s manual is needed.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable, Sensitive touch pad ,Size, Google Play Store, Long battery life, Made by Samsung,

Cons: Does not include an owner&apos;s manual (frustrating for this newbie), Can&apos;t do a lot without wi-fi connection

First of all, this device does NOT come with an owner&apos;s manual which makes it really difficult for us newbies and is why I only gave it four stars as opposed to five. Fortunately I found what looks to be an owner&apos;s manual on Samsung&apos;s website so I&apos;m hoping it will be useful.

There isn&apos;t a lot to do on it without wi-fi connection unless you&apos;ve downloaded some apps and movies. Again, hopefully the owner&apos;s manual will explain if it can do more than that.

I really like the size and the fact that it has Google Play Store accessibility.

It&apos;s light-weight ... and easy to hold, for grown-up size hands at least.

This device has a very long battery life which is great!! My son watchedt a movie and about half of another movie on a single charge and we still had battery life left in it.

Can upgrade to 32GB of memory. This was a deciding factor in purchasing this product.

I&apos;ve looked at a lot of different tablets and was seriously thinking about getting the Google Nexus 7 but ultimately decided on this one instead and I&apos;m glad I did.. Overall, I would recommend this product to my friends, but I would also recommend downloading the owner&apos;s manual from Samsung.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bitsbytes68</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not being a fan of tablets, I was surprised</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, battery life

All in all very much worth the price. I&apos;m still not convinced that they are the &quot;pc&quot; of the future but they can be somewhat useful. More of a toy than a tool but performs as advertised.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Filichino</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great For New Tablet Buyers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery / Android Store / Processor

Cons: Hard to find Accessories

I am a college student,

This was my first tablet.

It was a great find and buy. Tablet worked great! The new android &quot;Ice Cream Sandwich&quot; Processor did its work and kept up with running applications. The programs on this tablet was easy to access and ran smoothly.

The only problem with the tablet was the accessories where only limited due to the new galaxy tab for the 10&quot; size. Some of the programs would crash but it wasn&apos;t the Tablet&apos;s fault.

Other than that great wifi range! and Perfect for your reading, checking email, bank accounts, facebook, and all your social needs. (Note: wifi is always required to check)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tigerphan2007</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Everything I wanted it to be.....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Beautiful Screen, very long battery life, nice software features

Cons: No native USB support

I bought this a few days ago. I have been wearing it out, and so have my kids. Beautiful screen, best I have seen especially in bright sunlight. Extremely good battery life, I&apos;m getting more than 10 hours of use on a charge. Decent speakers, sound good for the size. Very responsive, no software issues. The apps that I use work great on it and it comes with some neat software built-in. Fast 3.0 Bluetooth and 802.11N wireless networking. Has a great utility for sharing/saving/retrieving files from external network devices. Highly recommend!! For the money, I don&apos;t know how to beat it. May need to get a separate case and I got the Zagg invisibleSHIELD and the 16GB microSD card. Awe ... some purchase!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>StrawberryPeach</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Tablet for my needs</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use, Great size, Great Price

Cons: Loses WIFI signal, Pictures are just OK

I traded my Kindle for this tablet thinking that I could use it to read and check my email when I travel. Let&apos;s just say that I have not read a book since I purchased it and I have only been using my laptop to pay bills. I love this tablet. I can surf the web, play games, watch movies, use facebook, and I have downloaded all kinds of apps. This is a great machine for the price. The screen is very clear and the color is vivid. The speakers are awesome. I am not thrilled with the pictures that I have taken with it. It also can lose WIFI connection easily. This happens randomly and may happen quite frequently for a couple of days and then not again for a week. I know it is not my internet se ... rvice because other WIFI devices in my home are working. The only thing that makes me feel better about this is that my Aunt said her Apple IPAD also randomly drops the WIFI connection. It is however, very easy to reset.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>James the Jammer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>phenominal device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Functions Smoothly; Easy to Use; Easy To Set Up; Fun to use; Good sizefit; Reliable; Nice sound; Efficient; Quality Construction

Right out of the box the samsung galaxy tablet is an awesome device. I use it on a daily basis. what I like the most about it is the size. it more compreable the the other tablet that i own because it is easy to travel with and use on the road. Dont get me wrong I still love my 10.1 galaxy tablet, but it harder for me to use when im out on the road, unlike the the galaxy 2, which ccan easily slide right into my pocket. My one and only complaint about the Galaxy 2 tablet is that I cant update to andriod 4.1 (JellyBean) yet. For the price of this tablet, you cant beat it. One of the best tablets out there when it comes to 7.1&apos;s</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Happy Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exactly what I wanted!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Quality Construction; Efficient

Got this for daughter for her birthday. She was over the top happy and I loved the price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Granny into the 21st century</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fabulous!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Easy To Set Up; Efficient; Quality Construction; Reliable

I love this tablet! It&apos;s got everything I wanted in one device--email, ereader, two-way camera, video calling, music, television, movies and wonderful uses that I didn&apos;t know existed (like turning my handwriting into type inside an email)--and is wireless, which lets me go online at home and in most other places. The Galaxy 2 is perfectly sized at 7 inches, which fits right into my small purse. It&apos;s lightweight, which matters because I travel a lot. And the price was extremely reasonable. I couldn&apos;t be more satisfied. I bought a $20 leather case from [@]that has a strap and two stand-up positions, so I&apos;m carrying my tablet everywhere I go and consequently am more productive, which leaves me more time to rel ... ax and play. Honestly, I know this is effusive, but I am jazzed about it. I studied the options for about a year, and this is the only one that fit all of my needs and pocketbook. I never had time to watch YouTube features before; now I can do that while I cook dinner. Very, very cool device.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fredac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Plug and play simplicity with great battery life.

Plug and play simplicity with great battery life. Comfortable size and has intuitive navagation. Only problem is not being able to download iTunes. I still give it a 5.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rich</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well built product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality Construction; Easy to Use; Efficient; Easy To Set Up; Friendly navigation; Reliable

Very happy with this item. Good on battery usage and easy to view screen. Menu screens are friendly and unit is easy to set up. I use this daily for news, appointments, contacts and have everything in one place. Unit syncs well with other internet accounts.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Time Bandit</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Happy with Purchase</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up; Reliable; Efficient; Quality Construction; Easy to Use

Purchased this tablet to take documents on the go and for the screen size. Its a perfect size to see documents, but not so large where you carry it like a briefcase. Slides in my back pocket nicely! Always around wifi so very handy to use with email and apps for work. Perect for pdfs on the go.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mact28</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT PURCHASE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Graphics, Easy to use

Cons: Battery Life a little short

I love this tablet!!! I bought it for my boyfriend as a graduation gift and we both use it for games, netflix, and the internet. Watching netflix on it is like watching it on a HD tv in my opinion. I do use it a lot and have to charge it a least half way through the day. A lot of down time at work and school that I use this to pass the time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daringo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good but with some flaws</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Form Factor, Android Market, Price

Cons: Samsung Software, Glitchy Android 4.0 software, Quality

Ok people, I really wanted to like this device. After trying the Blackberry Playbook (which at $199 is still a great device if you can live with Blackberry&apos;s app selection) I had to give this a try because it was running Android 4.0 (ICS) and seemed to have more features (GPS, Apps, Infrared, not Blackberry).

And at first it was fun. Immediately after entering your gmail account your previously purchased apps download. Nice. Then they start to update... and Google Play has some type of glitch that loops the update screen and you pretty much have to task kill Google Play to get it to stop. Ok, annoying but I found a work around.

Wait, SimCity won&apos;t play on this? ... What Hulu Plus doesn&apos;t support this device? I&apos;m stuck with Netflix as a built in app? I&apos;m stuck with your TouchWiz interface and un-removeable software like that bottom tray of not-so-handy apps. Like the Email Pop-up that has never worked and gives me a &quot;Service has stopped responding&quot; error? EVERYTIME. Like your Movie Maker software that crashes when rendering a video and forgets to add the transition affects - EVERYTIME.

And this just happened way to often to ignore... yes it will require a double or triple tap every now and again to get things to respond. What version of Android is this? 4.0 and you guys still have problems with Capacitive touch? My Droid Razr performs FAR better than this.

And speaking of performance... Marginal and best. Grand Theft Auto III - Good luck. Try walking into an ally full of thugs and you can count the Frame Rate.

Finally, there&apos;s build quality. My unit seems to have &quot;loosened up&quot; over the last 3 weeks and now I hear/feel plastic creaking noise when I grab the tab at various spots around the edge. Like the plastic back has separated from the unit although there are no visible signs of this). Very concerning. And when you consider the unit heats up quite a bit while charging and watching a movie - my confidence that this product will last is very small. And could you put ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jelliottf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not bad if you want 7 inches</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good features and image for a small tablet

Cons: There are better options, but it&apos;s personal

I wanted a tablet and thought that a small 7&quot; one would have the benefit of portability (it could actually fit in my jacket pocket) to extend its usefulness. If you&apos;re after portability and want good screen image, features (Ice Cream Sandwich operating system), and speed, this will fit the bill. I determined that I needed more.

I need a larger screen (10&quot;) and some other nice things that my next unit had to offer. It was orders of magnitude beyond the &quot;not so bad&quot; Galaxy Tab 2 7&quot;. It was an Asus TF 300, the latest model, and while it is more expensive, it has the virtue of an optional attached keyboard/docking station that adds amazing things. The physical keyboard is gre ... at in itself, and it&apos;s a good one for its size. In addition, it has its own battery that will extend the total battery life to about twice what it would be with just the tablet. Plus, it has another SD card expansion slot up to 32 GB, which would be on top of the one in the tablet itself for up to 32GB. But the incredible thing is the full size USB port, where you can attach things such as an external hard drive for virtually unlimited storage of music, photos, and video. So with all this, I viewed the ASUS TF 300 as ideal, with one exception.

The one exception has to do with screen resolution. The iPad has been increasing screen resolution to the point where Android tablets need to play catch-up. That&apos;s where the ASUS TF 700 comes in. To be released in the June/July timeframe, it is supposed to be the 300 on screen steroids, with a full hi-definition resolution. It&apos;s hard to justify keeping the 300 with an already fine resolution, similar to the resolution of the 7&quot; tablet that is the subject of this review, when I&apos;m only within a month or two of having it all.

So, to summarize, if you want a smaller, 7&quot; tablet, the Galaxy Tab 2 is a fine selection, but your needs would be completely different from my needs for the ASUS 10&quot;. If portability is at the top of your list, then seriously consider the ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BCBman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, good battery for a tablet

Cons: slow speed

I got this tablet two days ago for my 13th birthday ,and so far i love it. It&apos;s good for gaming and videos. You can also control your television with smart peel. This device can download tv shows and stream them any where (even with out wifi, 3g or 4g service). Also it can do much more than the IPAD. The 2 thing that bother me the most are the speed and controls. This device also has good sound quality.

THIS TABLET IS A GOOD TABLET FOR TEENS, KIDS OR EVEN ADULTS!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hrdwr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great if you don&apos;t have a smart phone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, clarity, price

Cons: To delicate, wi-fi is weak

I just bought this Tablet last week. I got all caught up in the hype and figured I have to have one. It does live up to what they say. Nice picture and the 7&quot; size is just right. I wish the case was a little heavier. Here is the deal though. I thought that I would find myself doing more on it that I already wasn&apos;t doing. I found myself doing exactly the same things I can do on my smart phone, DROID X. Basically this is just an oversized smart phone, minus the phone. I really think that is the case with any of these tablets, including an IPAD. Sure youi can watch movies, but thats not free and who does that when you have a 40&quot; LED at home. The Tab 2 can be used as a remote for your TV, but I already have a remote. It ... can take pictures, but really, who is going to take a tablet on vacation to take pictures. My phone has a better camera. So ask your self, &quot;What will a tablet do that I can&apos;t already do?&quot;
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DifficultToPickName</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good hardware. Average software.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Hardware, build quality, size.

Cons: Software.

Samsung has made quality hardware for $250. The product has solid build quality, and has really good specs for its price. Battery life, RAM, CPU, and screen are the best for the price point.

The software sucks though. Android is not designed to optimally utilize the hardware. No matter how much RAM, CPU power you put to run it, the animations are always jerky, which spoils the experience of using the tablet. 1GB RAM and 1GHz dual core processor is pretty good in terms of the power, but Android cannot use it optimally. iPad uses almost the same specs, and runs smoothly.

The product will do what it is supposed to do, without any wow factor.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>moew</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung nailed the form factor!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light, portable, and responsive

Cons: Not much at all!

Wow, Samsung nailed this design. I heard about it online, more of a surprise. Went to a few stores and even BB was sold out so fast!

This is a smaller tablet that you can really take with you and it does everything android ICS 4.0 does. I&apos;ve got a bunch of other tablets, and have even owned cheap ones and even ipads. I&apos;ve stuck with my transformer because it gave the best experience out of everything.

This is a smaller tablet that has a lot of horsepower! Portable, great battery life, great screen!

The PEEL app for changing tv channels or your cable box, just amazing! This is where I wanted cell phones to go with IR control, but nobody did that without add-ons or additional software purchasing. ... Manu&apos;s should take note of the IR control!

Cons are probably the proprietary connector and 2.0 Amp charging plug, but nothing you can&apos;t work around for this amazing device! For the price point, it&apos;s just amazing. And the Wolfram or whatever chip is inside that audiophiles love to e-debate about, too! Sound is great on this device!

I got one at lunch, showed it to a few friends, one of them ran out after work and got one that same day. He was showing everyone around the office his the next day :)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>eric209</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A big win for samsung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Build quality, price, specs, software,

Cons: Camera

Build: It&apos;s all plastic and the screen is not Gorilla Glass. The screen is is bright and colorful but not nearly up to the standards of Samsungs cell phone screens. This is understandable as it would add $100+ to the price of the device. Good viewing angles and resolution, better than most at this pricepoint. High quality plastics and a tightly fit body components make it feel sturdy like a premium device (even tho this is technically a budget tablet).

Performance: Screen is reasonably bright with great visibility except outdoor on a bright sunny days. Wifi speeds are excellent as is GPS reception. Renders pages fast and does a PDF textbooks well for a smaller device even if it takes a second to render a page wh ... en browsing thru pages (out of the half dozen apps I&apos;ve used for pdfs, Adobe Reader feels the snappiest, surprisingly). I was just a little worried about the performance of the 1GHz 2x TI OMAP but the device is very responsive. Quadrant scores have been averaging about 2620.

Software: Feels responsive and uses the screen even better than Honeycomb. This is my first ICS device and it feels familiar yet slightly more polished. One HUGE gripe is how, after all this time, there&apos;s no easy/intuitive way to add folder/file shortcuts or files to the home screen. I&apos;ve solved the problem with a 3rd party launcher and file manager but this should have been implemented years ago.

Cameras: Cameras are decent at best. But with an 8MP camera on my cell phone I never really thought I&apos;d be taking pics with my tablet anyway. YMMV.

PS: Fits into the pockets of a man&apos;s jeans pocket pretty well unless you&apos;re wearing skinny/girl jeans.

PPS: No LED flash on the cameras but that&apos;s okay (see above).

PPPS: Although they are a little close together, dual speakers are pretty good.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Oiprac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Little Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light, responsive, great price for what it does and what its meant for.

Cons: Battery life, lack of day one accessories, lack of Android Tablet apps

I think people are getting the wrong idea of what this tablet is meant for. Multiple sites have done the work and have given an overview of what Samsung is going for; a simple, introductory tablet with stock ICS to compete with competitors&apos; eReaders. No, this isn&apos;t the iPad killer, nor is it Samsung&apos;s latest and greatest. It&apos;s a midrange tablet for eReader users who want a little more functionality and freedom from their device at a very, very reasonable price.

Now to the actual review...
I just purchased this tablet today and after a full charge out of the box (roughly 1-2 hour wait) it was ready to go. Initial s ... etup was simple step by step, linking the tablet to my Google account to take advantage of the app device to device transfer; so all my apps that I previously downloaded on my android phone I can now use on the Galaxy Tab. My phone is currently running the Sense UI with Android 2.3.4 so my first impressions of ICS and TouchWiz was a bit of a difficult one to adjust to: back button is in a different location, notification bar is on the bottom of the screen rather than the top, and many other adjustments.

It feels great after a couple hours of use. The dual core 1Ghz cpu feels much more responsive than my phone&apos;s single core 1Ghz, but only slightly, but I figured that because ICS may be more cpu demanding. Widgets are still here and are one of the main reasons why I stick with the Android os.

The entire unit is very light and easy to carry around (one reason why you shouldnt compare this to the more powerful iPad). The cameras are below average; VGA front, 3mp rear, but again, thats just to add to functionality over say the Kindle Fire which has no camera at all. Play apps are there: market, music, and books. GPS is there so using maps is possible without a wi-fi connection.

The screen is good. Using this as a reader produces ample quality to read for a couple hours. How this compares to other eReaders is that you can download books from the Play store, a ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tinman64</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good value ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, speed, capability, price

Cons: 8GB, Headphone jack.

Just bought it yesterday, after returning my Ipad2. It was easy to set up and configure. Screen is clear and touchscreen works well. Lots of apps. Had no problem w/ Skype, Gtalk, etc. and the camera&apos;s are clear. Can&apos;t wait to keep exploring. I&apos;d like for more apps to be configured to the 7&quot; screen than there are but the hardware is fantastic. Also, add another 12&quot; to the power cord so it can easily reach from the floor to a desktop. When connecting to a PC the PC sees it as a camera not an sdCard. Do get the USB attachment, it&apos;s well worth it. Overall quite satisfied ... hated the proprietary nature of Apple. Yet to use the Remote functions ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dougf4</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Close but no cigar...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, ICS

Cons: Very slow scroll response

Overall too slow for my likes. Compared to my rooted Nook Tablet this thing crawls through screen scrolling. Netflix is pretty much useless. You can scroll (more like agonizingly creep) about one video choice at a time, whereas you should be able to drag at least 5-6 choices left to right at a time. Up and down scrolling is almost invisible in Netflix.

Other Apps such as Taptu News also are very jerky when scrolling. Tried to upgrade the Flash Player but apparently already have the latest installed. I am not running, GPS, Bluetooth, maps, navigation, etc, so that is not slowing it down.

Video playback (Netflix, YouTube, A&amp;E) is pretty nice, very crisp and detailed. I did note some slight pixelating in videos w ... here the Nook Tablet remains very crisp. The speakers are phenomenal for a small tablet, very loud and clear. (yes, tinny, but you can at least use them)

Being used to GoLauncher on Android 2.3 on the Nook Tablet, I find myself frustrated trying to navigate around in this menu system. I have to find a blank screen and hold and press, then select, &quot;Applications and Widgets&quot; in order to display the pre-installed apps - very weird.

I&apos;ll take it back and let a Geek see if there is some sort of screen response setting or such that is out of sorts. If there is no solution, I&apos;ll be returning it and wait on another manufacturer to release a 250-300 dollar tablet. I gave up on the whole Asus Memo build, but now am seeing that there may still be something too it. Another option might be to spring for a Tab 7 Plus as they seem to be much more powerful.

If my Tab2 performance is typical, I&apos;d expect these things to be flying back onto the shelves and into the re-furb market in droves and probably sell for under $200.00.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TotalHouseInspection</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, good price,

Cons: Nothing yet

Just got this tablet today for my kids to use it. I am very happy with overall performance. Very responsive to touch, screen display is great, easy to set up. For the money is a great product so far. I wish that Samsung will still have an 8.9 display tablet, and more options as far as storage (16,32,64GB)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Tablet at its price range</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features this tablet offers are good valve compare to other tablets on the market

Cons: Loses a Great score for me b/c front facing camera doesnt do HD shots.

I really enjoy this tablet, ive had a few other tablets before i.e. 1st Generation Galaxy Tab, Nook Color and Nook Tablet 16GB. Really nice display, love the feel of the device in my hands and it&apos;s light in weight. I definitely would recommend this over a Nexus 7 , Kindle Fire HD &amp; Nook Tablet HD. If you looking something like an IPad this isn&apos;t it, but its completely different OS on the devices so i feel it isn&apos;t fair to compare them. If your an android user you will definitely enjoy this tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>horselover3411</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect 7 inch tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This tablet is fast enough for.web surfing, can handle.the latest version of flash, and is a great.ereader. It has more flexibility than a kindle or nook bc you have access to the full market. The screen is vividly bright to watch movies and speakers are loud enough to hear without headphones. Battery life is pretty good. Overall a nice 7 inch tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HypnoV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality, Color, Size, Speed

Cons: Camera

I love my tablet, but I have the student version, which came with the keyboard. It&apos;s fast, and the sound quality was impressive. I love the fact that I can use a keyboard and have the touch screen. Overall I love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dino1a</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works really well.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Android OS is great and offers alot of apps from various vendors. Great feature that allow you to turn on tv,sync roku a

Cons: Battery

Had a problem with camera freezing and it stopped after firmware update. Other wise a excellent Tablet for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple to use - bang for buck, great size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, portable, reader, computer, does almost everything

Cons: traditional word processing, I need to figure out HOW it needs to be done on this media

i have an iPhone, and iPad, I needed a reader and didn&apos;t JUST want a reader. This was the compromise. I&apos;m thrilled with everything it does. Full web access. Document and email access. Truly a light weight alternative to a laptop that fits in my purse, and glove compartment that I don&apos;t mind carrying. The iPad was still to big and expensive to truly be portable. Slightly more piece of mind worrying about leaving behind a $250 piece of electronics than $650. performance, screen quality, operations, stability... all great</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Phetzer1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kies file transfer software issue</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price

Cons: Kies Software for connecting to a PC

The tablet is great but does have the following issue that I can&apos;t seem to fix. The Kies software does not work well with the USB connection. If you get it to connect by updating the drivers it will seemingly remove them once you disconnect the cable. If you want to verify what I&apos;m saying Google &quot;Kies USB Connection&quot;. You will see that some people have a solution but I have not been able to get any of them to work permanently. Like I said once I remove the cable it fails when reconnected. Kies is used to copy files from your PC to the tablets internal memory or SD card if you have one installed. You can do this though a wireless connection but it should work with both. If you call tech support they are of little or no hel ... p in resolving this issue. Also the camera is of low quality. When I turn on the video camera the picture is very grainy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AndrewP001</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product, very happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Features, weight

Cons: SD slot

This is my first tablet and I&apos;m very happy. The price point allowed me to not get overly excited if it wasn&apos;t a good product. It has exceeded my expectations.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Yasue</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Content liberation and a great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portability, ease of use, multi-function, solid build, strong wifi connection, freedom to buy media from anywhere

Cons: camera button too close to other buttons: takes unintended screen shots occasionally

I was on the fence about buying a tablet because I wasn&apos;t sure how much I would use it, so I took my time choosing and did a ton of research. Now that I have it, I don&apos;t know how I got along without it! (More on that at the end)

While smartphones offer a lot of the same apps, the screen size leaves a lot to be desired. The 10&quot; tablet offerings were not within my desired range for portability. The 7&quot; is a perfect compromise: ideal for reading and for curling up to watch a movie in bed. The ability to add an SD card for more storage is a big win. The Google Nexus ... 7 is worth looking at too if you want to save even more money. We have that as well and it&apos;s great, but it won&apos;t suit everyone&apos;s data storage needs. Since I don&apos;t generally need the full computing power of a laptop and I like to free my phone up for doing crazy things--like talking on it--this has been an excellent investment. The built-in wifi will also save your precious phone data usage.

E-readers tempted me for years, but I don&apos;t like to be told where I should buy my books. I hate iTunes and only used it once when I realized it more or less trapped me in the Apple &quot;content ecosystem&quot;. The same goes for any type of media and I&apos;m glad to see a tablet at reasonable price that handles everything I want to do without dictating how I should do it. The good news about books is that you can still get a Kindle app, a Barnes and Noble app, in addition to several other e-reader apps. More choice is always good, especially when it comes to apps in my experience. Also, because this an Android based device, you can choose to buy (or if you&apos;re bold) download apps from anywhere you please.

How I use this:
-Reading e-books
-Reading news (love the News360 app!)
-Reading favorite blogs/online magazines offline (Google Currents app)
-Streaming Netflix and Amazon Prime (must use a browser to stream Amazon) and several *free* sources for movies and shows
-Streaming music, talk radio, podcasts (Spotifiy and TuneIn apps to na ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Philip</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Slick as tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>With Samsung you know what to expect, so no surprises here. The screen is perfectly acceptable and has good viewing angles. Scrolling through a web page may not be as smooth as say the Google Nexus, but we&apos;re spliting hairs here I think. I like the ability to add a cheap MicroSD Card easily, Android 4.04 is well integrated and Wi-Fi is fast. Battery life for my kind of usage is a couple of days, so ticks the box also. All up a wise choice for those who just want a reliable and well made compact tablet without the weight of an ipad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ed88ed88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice starter tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to use..The screen is beautiful...

Cons: I can&apos;t think of anything...at the moment...

Very nice tablet for the novice....or for the advanced user...the screen is very clear and vivid....very portable...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ilovetechtoys</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This tablet is compact and light</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The battery life is super long.

Cons: The case I bought for it at Best Buy. It&apos;s the only one they had.

I own 3 tablets this is by far the best for my money. I take it around with almost all the time. Screen is great clarity. The speakers are the best out of all the tablets I&apos;ve tried.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Llarsen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Get rid of the Camera for work projects</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Being able to write on screen capture for inspections

Cons: Wish the battery was a little better.

I enjoy using the camera and flash while doing inspections, it lets me screen capture and write notes on picture. So far this has been a great small devise for small work spaces and dark places. Most of the apps that are preloaded...for me...are just not useful. Wish they would offer you a choice in app packages or reduce the price and just let you pick the apps you want.
All in all I like the speed, and have not had any issues yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gadget fan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect tablet to take anywhere</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design; Durable; Portable; Easy to Use

This is my second Android tablet. It feels as solid as my Galaxy phone as I holding it in my hands. When compared with a 10&quot; model, the 7&quot; form factor is much lighter and easier to carry around from room to room, or along for the daily commute. The screen is adequate, but not spectacular. Amazon books look pleasing to the eyes. The dual-core processor is well matched with the 1GB of internal RAM so that streaming apps like HBO GO or Comcast Player produce very smooth video playback. Games are also very responsive, although that is not the primary reason I made this purchase. I also recommend Samsung&apos;s optional USB and SD connection kit, which allows the tablet to be connected to peripherals or another SD card.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jay109</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: lightweight and easy to use

Cons: Nothing yet

I had checked out the Kindle Fire and other similar tablets but Best Buy employees recommended the Samsung and that was an easy sell since I have Samsung smartphones. I have been extremely happy with the performance and graphics.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JARDONN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile, User friendly and affordable

I love the Samsung which I got for my mother. She finds it quite handy, easy to use and versatile as a remote control, alarm, web surfer etc. great value for its cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TerryLindaB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great display, great battery life

Recommended by Best Buy associate... very good choice over the Kindle Fire, newer OS, apps, etc for only a little more $$. Convenient size, bright clear display.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Charmed179</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Packs a big punch for being so small.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight, cameras, speed

Cons: Have not found anything yet

I gave up my ipad3 for one of these, The ipad was just too heavy for the amount of use it was getting. This Tab is smaller but still very easy to use , I love the size a lot better and I can still see things on the screen. Does not seem slow at all and that is a plus because coming from the ipad I did not want to lose the speed I was getting while using apps. Have not had it long so time will tell how it goes, but for not very happy with the 2 we picked up.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great value priced Android Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light weight, convenient size, running OS

Cons: Nothing so far...

Great entry level media tablet. Use it to net stream media, music, reading ebooks, internet browsing, and playing games. Extremely happy with my purchase. Best featrues for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paulafromri</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Absolutely LOVE It!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Efficient; Reliable; Easy To Set Up; Easy to Use; Quality Construction

I am totally addicted to my tablet. Love to create my own designs. The HD pictures look great. It was an impulse buy. One I am not regretting. Thanks. Samsung and thanks to Staples for all your help.. Paula</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bigfuzzy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I really like this tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: One touch access to all my most used apps

Cons: Battery life could be longer.

My first tablet. Good price. I like it. I can use it as an e-reader, check emails, facebook and do lots of things online without having to drag a laptop around with me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LizzyTee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great all around tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, decent battery life, lightweight and portable, great screen and os

Cons: default keyboard not as responsive or intitive as I&apos;d like; limites accessory options; does not seamlessly sinc with pc

I&apos;ve had few issues with this tablet. Battery life has been fine for my functions (email, web browsing, app usage, using as a reader). I haven&apos;t watched full length videos on it yet, so I can&apos;t judge on that, but overall it&apos;s a decent little machine. Standard keyboard is awful for touch response and intuitiveness which really is essential on a touch screen no matter how good a typist you are. And I would appreciate better pc to tablet sincing particularly with ebooks and their apps. Samsung&apos;s kies does not currently support ebooks transfers, and it leaves me with a ra ... ther convoluted way of moving the files over. Would like more accessory options, but overall for price and function it&apos;s great.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PowderyTrain</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Expandable storage, ICS

Cons: Not too much

I have turned my tablet into a sort of mega ipod touch with the use of a 32GB micro sd and doubletwist air sync (usb sync does not work with ICS) right to my sd. Ice cream sandwich is great, processing power is sufficient, and so is battery life. All in all for $250 I don&apos;t think you will find more value in a tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MV92691</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great form factor for learning Android 4.0</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, expandable memory storage and portability

Cons: Battery life shorter than expected but not a deal breaker

I purchased the Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 for three reasons: 1) I wanted to learn the new Ice Cream Sandwich (ICS) OS (Android 4.0) as I was bored with the IPad OS and may switch to an Android phone next year (the IPhone screen is too small for me now and not a great experience any longer); 2) I wanted a smaller form factor than 10.1 inches for portability and less strain on my wrists (the IPad mini is still a rumor afterall); and 3) I wanted another tablet device as my daughter requisitioned by IPad. All three reasons were easily met by this product. ICS is fun to use and is very good once you learn it. The lighter tablet does not hurt my wrists after long perio ... ds of use, and I can carry it everywhere in my back or front pocket. My daughter (3 years old) does not even bother to touch the Galaxy Tab 7.0 as she is happy with the IPad. The lack of a home button prevents her from turning on the Galaxy Tab and playing with it, which is great and the result I was looking for. The battery life is shorter than the IPad, but since it meets my needs, it is not a big problem for me. I added movies and music to the SD memory card and now this is my &quot;go to&quot; device for entertainment and other content consumption, especially RSS news feeds. The sound is average, but I use headphones most of the time or pair it with a bluetooth speaker. It will definitely go with me when traveling this summer, and I will use it more for notes and .pdf and other document viewing during business meetings. I duplicated most of the IPad apps I use except for certain TV show streaming apps, but I do not miss them as I thought I would. I suggest getting a screen protector as the glass screen attracts fingerprints. Also, I added a carbon fiber textured skin to help with gripping the device. I have a case from Poetic for the tablet, but use it only when out of the house as I prefer to use the device without a case to satisfy reason #2 above. Hope this review helps you.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrGood2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best of the 7&quot; tablets on the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed, memory, dual cameras

Samsung has blown away the competition with this little tablet. Being the fastest 7&quot; tablet on the market and sporting the newest version of the Android Operating System &quot;IceCreamSandwich&quot;. With a dual-core, 1Ghz processor and 1Gb of onboard storage this little tablet performs extremely well. The memory can be expanded by adding a 32GB MicroSD card for movies, music, photos or whatever else you want to store.

This tablet is a great alternative to the Nook or Kindle Fire in that it has the ability to add apps for compatibility with both of their storage systems so you don&apos;t have to choose one or the other. It also has tablet features that neither of them have. The dual facing cameras are great for those who may want to Skype with family member ... s, or take pictures/video. The high definition display is beautiful with a great response from the touch screen. Battery life is also good even with the wi-fi left on.

Built in software and remote transmitter permit control of multiple devices in your home theater or living room. Simply select the devices, then go to the TV listings and select what you want to watch. The software controls turning on each device and putting it in the right mode/channel to watch your show. Better than the Logitech Harmony remotes could ever perform.

For the price and features, this is not only the best value, but the best quality product on the market in 7&quot; #or now in 10&quot;# tablets.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Dont want to be tethered? This is your 7&quot; tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, access to all android apps and content providers

Cons: Returned 1st unit when a row of the backlights failed

I bought this tablet for myself. I wanted something inexpensive, in the 7&quot; form factor, and not tethered to Amazon or Barnes &amp; Noble, this fits the bill perfectly. For computer novices, this is not as simple to use as an ipad and the apps are definitely much more limited than for Apple. On the other hand, you can comfortably hold this tablet in one hand, the battery life is great, it plays flash videos, and it can access just about any content available on the internet (except Apple, of course).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>APIT80</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Performance

Great tablet, ICS runs flawless and all the apps run great. Easy to put movies or music on, expansion slot for micro sd card is great. All around tremendous tablet for any use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lynn0704</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Decent price, great size (fits in my purse)

I love my Galaxy Tab 2. The 7&quot; size is perfect and I can put it right in my purse. This is my first tablet and I&apos;m still figuring out how the mobile apps work. Any problems I&apos;ve encountered thus far are probably caused more by user error than anything else :-)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sooo Easy to Use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use; Efficient; Reliable; Easy To Set Up

I didn&apos;t think I&apos;d use a tablet or a book reader device...however, this goes everywhere with me. It was so easy to set up and learn how to use...Great value and simplicity even for the skeptical user.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DonkeyChewingAWaffle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for family</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to setup. Easy to use. Good price point.

Cons: n/a

Quick and easy to setup.

Purchased primarily for a 4 year old. The kid loves it.

The adults enjoy it just as much.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>urfavoritebuyer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product, Great Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Ease of Use, Travel Friendly

Cons: No Camera Flash

Great price for a tablet. This my first one I have ever bought. Keep in mind that this will not compared to the 10&quot; models but for the size of this tablet, it&apos;s a competitor. Loved it so much bought a second one for the wife! Also, tablets are not cameras so not having a flash isn&apos;t a big concern for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bobby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this primarily for business as an internet marketer. I have used it for about 2 weeks now and cannot find anything to complain about. The size is perfect, lightweight, easy to use, and full of features. I had a Xoom last year and hated it cause it was so large and heavy. I had been looking for something to replace it that was less than $ with bluetooth and wifi, well here it is!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>scottx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great 7&quot; tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery life, speed, size, weight

Cons: Not a 10 inch?

I&apos;ve owned 4 other seven inch tablet&apos;s before this one and this is by far the best. I run custom roms on everything I own. This has a great developer community behind it already and it&apos;s still new. Buy this tablet, you won&apos;t regret it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cjpcrew</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great tablet. I have tried alot of tablets and love the 7 inch size. I bought the 10.1 but was not happy with it. This is fast, great apps and ICS is easy to use. I also have the 7.0 plus tablet and wouldnot trade foran ipad. Ifyou are an android lover like me you should try these tablets.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kidzone</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for young teen.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to figure out with little to no experience.

Cons: Nothing

Bought this product for my daughter&apos;s 13th birthday and she loves it. All she really wanted was a cell phone and we got this instead and she absolutely loves it. She doesn&apos;t even want a cell phone now. She can text through our WiFi easily without cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TomTheBomb024</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 - Excellent Budget Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Low Price, Size, Weight, Portability, WiFi, eBooks, Play Store, Google Music, Gaming, Speaker, Android 4.0, Performance

Cons: Performance, Screen, Battery Life

Debuting at ~250$ plus tax, this is tablet is steal at launch.
Best tablet I have ever owned. The combination of small form factor and light weight make it possible to stuff into your pocket and a pleasure to hold with one or both hands, even for longer periods of time. A perfect attention waster for long waiting rooms visits, or a lazy day of fun.
The WiFi is noticeably stronger than on other similar devices I&apos;ve frequently used, Galaxy Tab 10.1, iPhone 4, and a few others.
This tablet has reintroduced me to reading, both books and comics. Though I am an IT person, I had avoided the eBook format, always ... in favor of traditional, paper books. No more! Several simple and easy to use eBook apps let you quickly purchase and read official content without confusion. I personally use only the Amazon Kindle reader app that I believe is pre-installed. It has smooth page transitions, excellent text legibility and a built in dictionary for painlessly taming &quot;Game of Thrones&quot; and other titles with large vocabularies.
For “unofficial” eBook and comic downloads, you can find many apps in the Play Store. I personally use “ComicRack” mostly for reading the various comics I have downloaded on my PC. To transfer the files to my PC I use “WiFi File Explorer”, another Play Store app. Once the comic files are on the PC, the ComicRack app locates them automatically and populates your library. An amazing experience and a tremendous value, I read every issue of &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; for the price of the app. Certainly cannot do this on the iPad without tremendously greater effort as iOS does not allow direct access to the internal storage of the device without the use of iTunes. Building on those points, Google Music is just great. Upload any MP3 you’ve ever downloaded on your PC and you can stream to any Android device you own, also for free.
Gaming is surprisingly good, very little slowdown on most games. I haven’t played many actual Android games, but I have emulators for the SNES, Genesis ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rara954</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ok for non power Users</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and Cost

Cons: Slow response

The device is ok for the money and comes with a good set of tools that can be used for basic task. The size is perfect to carry around work or for personal use. However, if you are somebody that is a power user and expects the device to respond to your every need in a split second, stay away from it. You will need a tablet with a better processor and a lot more power for that. That is exactly what I did kept my big tablet for power jobs and use this one for quick and simple task.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gipsymagpie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great device but watch the screen</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The device is great. Good price point and good set of features . Works well with a Galaxy So acting as a hotspots. Integrates brilliantly with wifi network structure accessing the network hard drives for movies. The home screen is slightly annoying in that it doesn&apos;t fill the whole screen. The display is bright and vibrant but a little reflective . The BIG thing is that it scratches easily. Not like the S2! The size is perfect for holding to read books or PDF.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Casper82</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not Quite There Yet!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Display, Price, Easy to Set Up, ICS Operating Sytem

Cons: Sd Card does not work, Slow download speed

Beautiful Display and an excelllent price. My main complaint is that that you can not save to the sd card by default. Went into the browser settings and set it to save downloads to sd card and it did not work. So I had to manually copy to the sd card everytime I downloaded something. Which is a big headache,since out of the box you actually only have 4gb on the device, which is very little available space.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BearCAE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the size and speed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery life, expandable, and speed

Cons: Nothing

Froze when not wifi connected and tried to open internet, but reset it connected it and have had no problems since then. Takes a while to learn controls, but caught on after the first day. Fast, expandable. Camera image isn&apos;t great, but I did not buy it to be a camera. Also the perfect size and price for a tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SuperCesar73</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sweet for my first tablet.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The price, and easy to use

Cons: Not sure yet?

This is my first tablet and it is great so far. At first I wasn&apos;t sure if I wanted this one because there are so many of there so I took a chance and bought it. But first I took back the Samsung MP3 Player to get it cause I had 30 days to exchange it and so far I&apos;m not disappointed. I liked it so much that I wanted to get one for my wife too. Netflex works great I put on I heart radio and its cool. Go out and buy one..The sound is AWESOME!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>shopper66</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great buy for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sleek, fast, ice cream sandwich

Cons: nothing so far

I have been waiting for a little powerhouse to come along at the right price. This was the perfect opportunity. Ice cream sandwich is so fast and it has nice little add ons included such as Polaris Office &amp; Smart Remote. You can even choose between a few fonts for the system. The camera is clear and fast, and the ability to add storage via microSD is another bonus.
Only had it for a short while, will try to update with additional information as I use it more.
*Wish Bestbuy had more options for accessories for this particular item, but that is not the fault of the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gmarrese91</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Little Device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, Responsive, Great Display, Portability, Micro SD Slot

Cons: Lack of accessories as of release date

Wow, where to begin. Such an amazing tablet, for an even more incredible price. No-holds-barred Android 4.0 OS, With Google Play Store and Android Appstore. Streaming video is extremely clear, UI is intuitive, and it fits in the breastpocket of a suit. Slightly laggy at times, and some apps crash on occasion, but not enough to even be frustrating. If you have been waiting for the next tablet with ICS and a low price tag, don&apos;t hesitate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>freak4f1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: For the most part everything.

Cons: It isn&apos;t a iPad. Otherwise, great tablet!

I thought for the first time I would buy a tablet just to see if I could use one. Now that I have, I will be returning mine and getting an iPad. Don&apos;t get me wrong, it is a wonderful device! I had not one problem with it. It worked perfectly and flawlessly for me. I am just to spoiled with Apple products. If you don&apos;t like Apple products or just don&apos;t want to spend that much, this is the device to get then! If the iPad did not exist, this is the tablet I would have then! I think anyone that would pick this product would be purchasing a wonderful device for a very reasonable price! You won&apos;t be disappointed!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OnceUGoBluUNeverGoBack</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Returned it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Expandable Memory, loud speaker

Cons: Resolution, Speed, Interface

I bought this item to do a side by side comparison with the Nexus 7. It failed. Other than the expandable memory, &amp; the loud speaker, there wasn&apos;t much i liked about it. You can see the jagged pixels around the icons and small fonts. It would lag playing games as simple as Robot Unicorn Attack. I found apps that would let me customize the Nexus 7 to mimic what i did like about the Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 (stupid name by the way). This includes a volume booster app i bought with the $25 credit i got for purchasing the Nexus 7.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zenuza</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My mobile PC.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact, Expandable Memory, Battery Life, and Convenience.

Cons: google+

Great item! I brought the Samsung tablet just to store and review notes for schooling. But, eventually found myself doing everything else on it as well. The battery life is excellent, i sometimes use it 3-4 hours a day 5 days a week with Skype, music, and IMing without charging. The great thing if your a student is the option to load up files from a flash drive with the USB adapter. There are also headphones out there that are great for android devices. The one i brought had a controller on the mic that lets you switch through songs, pause, and answer VOIP calls - convenience.

Can&apos;t Forget the memory card slot, 32GB Class 10 Micro SD was a major selling point for me. It holds EVERYTHING&gt;</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nursey63</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Definately suits the use and much less expensive</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, affordabiltiy

Cons: Don&apos;t have a negatives so far!

Worth the money. Easily set up and usable. Much more sensible than an iPad 2 that was so expensive and no much better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>IdiotForBuying</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product considering no instructions.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price

Cons: Virtually no instructions.

I can&apos;t believe anyone will actually read this and care. But, here goes. Bought the Samsung Tablet 2, 7.0, one day before leaving on a five week trip. Salesperson was somewhat helpful, but there were NO WRITTEN INSTRUCTIONS OR GUIDE with the item. Called back to the store later that evening, and the phone rang for at least 15 minutes without anyone answering. Could not figure out how to download anything except an item I paid for at Amazon. Free books from my library just sat there out in space. Took me 3 weeks to get Google to &quot;allow&quot; me to open an account, and that didn&apos;t help either. Item rarely worked with the Sprint 3G/4G Overdrive Pro I also purchased and paid mightily for. Usually only able to go online when in a Wi-Fi ... area. After about 3 weeks, the Sprint 3G/4G OverdriveProB80 does not work at all. It requests a password, which I was never given.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hueroloco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small Tablet Packs a Punch!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Has all the features of the big tablets in a smaller package.

Cons: 8GB model only really has 4GB due to OS.

I bought this for my wife, who is not very tech savy. This means I get to play with it a lot to get it to do what she wants. The interface is simple, even to her, she figured it out in less than an hour, downloading apps is a breeze, we were able to install an app called &quot;Line 2&quot; and now the tablet is a phone as long as there is wifi. The size of this tablet is perfect, you can watch movies and play games just like on the 10 inch tablets, the display quality is excellent. BTW, I am in no way putting my wife down, but for her to like something like this says a lot!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TheFreezy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable, battery life, available applications

Cons: none

This tablet has been great so far. I purchased one of these to replace my iPad 1st Gen which was getting some age to it. I was in the market for something that was more portable, but could still handle a lot of the tasks that I use tablets for. I&apos;ve had the Tab for a little over the month and use it daily.

I&apos;m an Network Administrator and use this tablet for managing some of my networks and accessing information in the cloud. There are plenty of applications out there to help you get work done. This device is fantastic for taking notes.

You can add a bluetooth keyboard too if you&apos;re planning on doing a lot of typing on this device.

This device is for you if you&apos;re on the go a lot and need to ... take notes, or send emails while on the go.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kyyote</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>New tecnology/old school</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small, portable, easy to handle

Cons: Hard to get apps to work.

My only complaint is the Skype app. Even after downloading itunes, Skype wouldn&apos;t download. I have accts at both sites and still nothing. I&apos;m not tech savey so take it w/what it is. Love the ebook feature so I can read books etc. no matter where I am. Still learning how to use this. Worries me about Samsung being sued and Apple winning their case.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>neilt631</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the ease and look, but...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Clarity

Cons: Storage

I bought this tab because I&apos;m a big fan of the Galaxy format and comfortable with it since my last 2 phones have been Galaxys. However, after I opened my new toy and went through the TRUE specs, I realized that its not 8gb at all. Normally something that says 8 you can expect to be a 6 or thereabouts. But this tab is actually only 4.69gb. And after all the factory preloaded stuff, it&apos;s down to 4.24gb.
Again, the tab is beautiful! Works well and all. But if you need more than 4gb worth of data on it at any given time, look elsewhere. The 8gb in the product name is misleading.... some would say false advertisement.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lil Mama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Mulit-Use Gadget!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Value; Kindle Ap; Nook Ap; Can Use As Reading Device

We love our tablet! The whole family can&apos;t wait till it&apos;s &quot;my turn!&quot; Wonderful little gadget. The kids like the aps. Mom likes the reading! Dad likes [@] and internet capabilities!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OhLordHelpMeChoose</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wifi issues</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size for the money

Cons: Wifi antenna isn&apos;t good

I purchased this the first day it was out. and returned it because the wifi antenna wouldn&apos;t link to my home network while in my back yard. The Acer A100 did. I also have trouble keeping my mobile Samsung Droid Charge hooked to my home wifi network while at home.
So if you purchase this product, please test out the wifi capabilities before your 30days is up for returns.
I won&apos;t be purchasing any Samsung Galaxy products until they use
a better wifi antenna.
If anyone finds a fix for my problem please let me know with a reply to this post.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>spectre71</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: speed

Cons: :)

Great size, super fast... Android 4.0 is so smooth
This is the perfect tablet is you want to save a little money and still be able to have a great tablet experience.
The TV remote feature is kinda cool and the app to look up shows that works with it is a nice add on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marke Wrapper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Valuation (Slim, Handy and affordable)</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was greatly impressed with this tablet - budget wise. May first consideration was my budget and I saved around one hundred fifty dollars. What makes this unit awesome is its handy and slik design and not to mention its phone capability. The screen is just right for me with pretty impressive images. Since this operates with an Android OS platform, I have ease in configuration and with greater flexibility. Over-all, this tablet is cool.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>photpbug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet at great price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use with good speed and a quality screen.

Cons: Nothing so far.

I read our local news paper Tech. writer Robert Evatts review of this new Samsung Galaxy Tab2 7&quot; Android tablet, and went to my local Best Buy to check it out. I already own a Kindal Fire and Apple iPad2 but never had tried an Android device. I had found both Amazans Kindal Fire and Apple iPad2 to be somewhat heavy handed in just what they allow one to use on their devices. After doing a little limited playing with the Tab2 not much one can do if you can&apos;t get a internet connection and this device Best Buy would not connect to their WiFi. so being a rewards customer and get a good buy and return policy, I just bought it and took it home to give it a go. It was very easy to connect to my WiFi router ... and after reading the very small and limited Samsung Tab2 manual I just started trying things. after getting Google Chrome for the internet looking I download the Fire Fox mobile device as I use Fire Fox to connect to my Yahoo e-mail account. Yahoo took a lot of my time getting it to except my password, but after many try&apos;s and using Google Chrome to log in I again tried Fire Fox and did get Fire Fox to work with Yahoo. I don&apos;t blame this on Samsungs Tab2. anyway I don&apos;t wish to bore everyone with more details I will say the processor seems fast getting around the Net. is quick and simple. Screen is IMHO very good. I did buy a sandick 16gb Micro memory chip on sale at best Buy for $20 to get more space on the device as it only comes wit 8gb and about 4gb is taken by the operating system. Best Buy does not carry any other tethering cords of chargers for the Samsong T2 but a I finding them online is easy. If you are wanting a really easy to use quality small tablet the Samsong Galaxy Tab2 will your needs. and if not happy within 14 days just return it to Best Buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>onthedot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Apps crash constantly</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size is great. Nice screen

Cons: Samsung won&apos;t acknowledge keyboard crash problem.

I love the tablet, but the longer I keep using it, the more apps keep crashing. It has the newest version of ICS Android, and everything I bring up a text box that uses the keyboard, the app crashes.

Do a search on the web, and you will see it is not only common, but Samsung won&apos;t acknowledge the issue. The only solution is a factory reset, and completely wiping the device clean. Unacceptable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>appsung</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect tablet for it&apos;s size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, quality, simple OS, speed,

Cons: Screen quality

I originally had the 10.1 version of this tablet, but i felt it was too big to carry around and use comfortably. This tablet&apos;s size is excellent. The fact that i can use it in landscape mode and not have to super stretch my thumbs to get the those keys in the center of the screen makes it much more usable and comfortable. The dual-core 1ghz processor is pretty snappy. Despite a little lag here and there, it still was quick and responsive with moderate use. The front and back cameras are decent, but nothing special. Front camera is average quality from a cellphone, and the back camera is about the same as the front (but higher res.) I had originally planned on getting the Nexus 7 tablet, but worries of getting a lemon ... and it being impossible to find anywhere; i ended up just going with Samsung. One thing that i didn&apos;t like about this tablet compared to others including the 10.1 version is the screen quality. The colors are a little dull and washed out, Most likely because of the slightly lower resolution. Overall, this tablet is an excelent choice for those looking for a small easy-to-use tablet that give all the features of a full size tablet, but in a more comfortable size.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>livalidle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet, No problems</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Price, Easy to operate, Great battery life, nice features

Cons: Needs more accessories

This tablet works just as good as my wife&apos;s Ipad. I didn&apos;t want a 10&quot; screen or a $400 price tag. Also really easy to set up.
Only complaint is that there is no good case for it. The Ipad has a really cool case/cover but Samsung don&apos;t offer anything for these.
It may be a little slow once in a while but not bad at all. Seems to be well built. It has a very clear screen with sharp colors.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Printer76376</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice little tablet for play that beats the iPad!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 7&quot;, wifi, web browsing, games, Google Play app store

Cons: Nothing that I can think of!

I like this little tablet because it is MUCH better than the iPad! The reason it&apos;s better is because of the size...7&quot; is MUCH nicer than 10&quot;. I bought this because I kept going into Best Buy Mobile all the time just to play with it because I was waiting to see if the price would go down to $199.99 or something. I use this with my Mifi from Virgin Mobile USA so it&apos;s with me just about everywhere I go (especially work). If you want a tablet that&apos;ll beat the iPad (my opinion), this is the one for you - perfect touch keyboard, size and features it has!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>maggie1952</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very easy to use and navigate through

Cons: haven&apos;t found anything yet

I have really enjoyed my new Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 -- I have downloaded some apps (I had never done that before, but it was easy.) I have been using the &quot;dropbox&quot; since that was already set up on my computer. I&apos;m having fun with it and would recommend this to others.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LGbill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cool device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: A little hard to grasp

About what I expected. Great for couch surfing. Peel remote function was great, until it failed to work after two weeks. &quot;They are working on it&quot;.
Battery life good. Some web sites do not render well, but a great product overall.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>itsbebe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Husband&apos;s first pad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size

Cons: hard to keep smudge free

Bought this for my husband, who knows nothing about computers, but wants to play on them. This has been a great alternative...he doesn&apos;t take direction well, but has figured it out on his own. He loves it, and keeps up with it. The guys at his work also love playing with it, so I would say it&apos;s a hit. The size is just right, he has big fingers, and uses a stylus, but this size is great!
Fingerprints on the face are terrible!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MMJohnson</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic tablet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, connectivity, features, gps, apps

Cons: best buy sales staff REALLY wanted me to buy an iPad

I bought this tablet at my local Best Buy, about a week ago, as a gift for my wife. I researched all the tablets, and read every comment I could find, good and bad. My priorities: small, reasonable price, expandable memory, front/rear cameras. fortunately, my wife loves it and is delighted with the features that she is still discovering. Her priorities: Skype, book consumption, light internet searching, games. We are both fantastically pleased with this tablet!

The glass is pretty &quot;draggy&quot;, compared to Apple product, but I added a screen protective film, and it is now appropriately slick.

It is not as intuitive as iPad, so be prepared for that. You do have t ... o explore the menus and applications for a while before some features can be located. Some of our difficulty could be from general ignorance of Android devices prior to this one.

My only other issue isn&apos;t with the product itself, but with the Best Buy sales staff. I made up my mind what I wanted before I went to the store. All I needed to do was to confirm my decision by touching the actual item. When I arrived at the store, I went directly to the display. A staffer was standing next to it and asked if he could help. I told him that I was interested in the Galaxy 2 7.0, and wanted to know what he thought was fantastic about it. He replied, and I quote here, &quot;not much&quot;. After a short conversation it became clear to me that his purpose in life was to sell iPads, and I wasn&apos;t there to buy one. I told him I was buying the Galaxy 2 7.0 anyway, and then I had to ask where I would get one for purchase. He pointed to the shelf below the display. I grabbed the boxed product, and he then took it from me so that he could ring it up. On the way to the register, I asked about covers, while I was glancing at the dozens of choices on a nearby rack. He said &quot;those are for iPad&quot;, and then pointed to the lone $40 cover available in-store for the Galaxy. I said, &quot;I&apos;ll look on online&quot;, made my purchase, and got out of there. Afte ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>geek96234789</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>very nice tablet, but i cant print to my printer..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: small, powerfull, light, expandable memory

Cons: samsung only printers, wireless internet range, 3mp camera

Operating system - Androids new OS is nice, but samsung only alows their printers to be used on this tablet :-( .... HUGE setback. Lucky for me there&apos;s an app for that! Other than that the OS is amazing, its easy to use since i have an android phone i knew where most icons were and how to change settings and appears to run faster loading apps!

power - i love that this tablet is light AND powerful. I can watch movies, surf the net and much more without lag(so far#. Used it at work all day long and still had 20% left for solitar after work! I can finally read a but without turning the page every five words#cell phone# or taking breaks because my wrist gets ti ... red of hold the tablet up #ipad3#. If you took out the printer restrictions and added a 8mp rear camera i would consider it being a good replacement for my ipad3 for work.#i need to take HD pictures#

screen - screen size is perfect for what i need, bigger than a cell phone yet smaller than an ipad. Makes it easy to read a book or watch a movie without straining your wrists. Also, the screen seems to be very durable, i have had it for weeks now and there are no scratches on the screen.#yet#

camera- The camers is something that i could stand to see upgraded as it&apos;s only 3mp. Dont get me wrong, it takes good pictures but u can tell they are not very HD.

Micro SD card reader- I have not yet needed to upgrade the memory of this tablet yet. I have al ot of pictures and applications stored on this device so far and still have 2gb left free.

This tablet comes with an app called smart remote, this app is awesome! I programm\ed in my TV without telling the wife and had a little fun with it. Changing channels, raising and lowering the volume, awe it was a lot of fun#for me). Drove her nuts, in short it worked great and its a nice feture if you have a lot of remotes you can never find.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bsam358</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best value 7&quot; Tablet out there.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Almost everything.

Cons: Only a 3 MP front camera.

I have been waiting for a 7&quot; Tablet, with the features that I wanted and so far this is it. I own an iPad and an Asus Transformer. I love the Transformer, but needed something in the 7&quot; size with the features that I wanted. One of the features that I had to have was a Micro SD card. The only reason I gave it 4 Stars, was the low 3 MP camera. Other then that....I love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gant</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Android Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The device was shipped and recvd it the next day. Setup was easy and I gave it to my wife. She took to it quickly and hasn t put it down. It s not mounting the micro SD card so I still have to figure that out. Overall I d recommend the purchase. I m an iPad user so I ve seen both systems. This is a cost effective alternative to an iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tech4Pro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t waste your time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything but the speed.

Cons: The speed of this device is terrible.

The appeareance of this product with the combination of android is the best. The only problem with this device is the lack of processing and memory power. Android is overall better than apple due to the freedom of access. The only completeoption right now at the stores is the ipad 2 and 3, even when you have a monopolized and extremly restricted operating system, it is complete, smooth and the fastest responsiveness compared to any Android Tablet. If you are buying today I&apos;ll recomend iPad, but today Android Manufacturers (Samsung specially - the closest competitor) have a lot to equip with better hardware (Quad core over 1.5GHz CPUs, 2GB RAM, Full HD displays), to be able to perform above iPads.
I ... &apos;m going back to Apple because because it is better than Android, but because the lack of competion (Responsiveness, Quality, Performance).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dimmer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gift for wife</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: surf the web,watch movies,play games,listen to music

Cons: battery life

The Galaxy Tab 2 is a nice tablet. I added a 16 GB micro sd card with music,pictures, and movies on it. This unit didn&apos;t skip a beat and played all the media . It is very responsive to the touch and has plenty of processing power for everything my wife does. My grandson and her take turns playing songs they like and it is cute to watch them. The only drawback is the battery life is only about 5 hours with wifi on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DeeCee123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, great price, everybody wants one!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, lightweight, great for on the go.

I just can&apos;t seem to put it down! My sister makes fun of me because she says it looks like a really big cellphone but then brags about how shes going to get one herself! Everyone that has seen it tells me they want one because it&apos;s just really worth the money and all around everything you need in a tablet! It&apos;s really lightweight so it goes with me everywhere, I don&apos;t have to carry my laptop around for school anymore (unless I have papers to type up, which on the tab might be a tad difficult to do), I just take this with me and with the use of some pretty handy apps, I can save my docs online and send them to the printer at work or school wirelessly. If you are trying to decide on a tablet I would definitely recommend the Galaxy T ... ab 2 7.0, well worth your money!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJI1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, functionality

Cons: nothing so far

Bought this for my mother to replace her unused laptop. It does what it is supposed to do. Great combination of features and price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brick01</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for quick read.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice size to hold in one hand

Cons: Ability to access internet.

Has too many default internet settings which are hard to navigate around but once you finally get the url you want it works okay.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ktrose</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it. It is so functional.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The camera actually is pretty good. love the panaramic function. Connectivity is fast. Battery life is decent.

I absolutely am in love with this tablet. It has full gps capability. GREAT fast and accurate accelarameter. Auto brightness....high resolution. Gradients are not a problem for this tablet. Panaramic pictures. TV remote thru infra red port. Well worth the money. I highly recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>305Diva</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for teens!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Just the right size; Portable; Engaging; Easy to Use; Fun; Durable; Attractive Design

Cons: Can&apos;t think of any yet

I bought this for my 14 year old for his birthday. It&apos;s just the right size for him and he can use it for reading, gaming, photos and music - just to mention a few.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Twyste</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for a beginner like me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: quick, does exactly what I bought it for

Cons: does not like my secure home network

This was my first tablet. To be honest, I was looking for something that would let me stay in touch while I do some travelling (twitter, im, email), and some casual gaming. Didn&apos;t think I&apos;d need a lot of memory, since this isn&apos;t my main computer, and I was right.
I&apos;ve been very happy so far. It was easy to set up, find my apps of choice, and get going. The only problem I&apos;ve had is getting it to connect to my secured network at home. If the network is open - no problems connecting.
Definitely get the screen protector. Learned that fast enough. Should have got it at the same time, but didn&apos;t think how necessary it would be.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>proma</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love this tablet over my iPad. Good size to carry and better compatibility first of all. It can read most types of video and music fines. With additional 32GB microSD card this perfectly serves my needs. I gave my iPad to my kids.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tojodunk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: small, portable, easy to use

Cons: accessories expensive

I really like this and take it everywhere with me. Very user friendly. I keep a calendar on it, use it for photos all the time, access the net, let my kids play games on it, read books - very inexpensive comparitively and really useful!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>89mustangowner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really good tablet for the price....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: dual web cams, dual processors, ice cream sandwich

Cons: cant transfer apps to sd card...

Really good tablet for the price.... I wish samsung would update the firmware so that you can move apps to the sd card. It only has 8 gb of internal memory, which about half of that is used for the operating system.... so really you only have a little over 4 gb available. You can put data on the sd card which helps some. Data being...... music, book, and videos..... I still would recommend this tablet....... I tried the bigger sizes at the store, but felt like they were awkard to hold. The 7 inch fits the hands better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OldPerson1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just Right</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small and easy to carry around - replaces books, newspaper &amp; PC

Cons: Nothing so far - would have been nice to include cell connection.

Bought this tablet when it came out because I felt it was the right size, not an Apple, had the new Android Ice Cream Sandwich operating system, could expand memory to 32 GB with micro SD card and was priced at only $250. I now have downloaded books from Amazon, barrowed ebooks from library, copied a DVD to the SD card, used it for emails &amp; text messages, surf the net, listen to my music and cancelled the newspaper since it was no longer needed. It is a little small but that is the trade off to being able to take it everywhere</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>f4ichick02</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I guess you get what you pay for....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The newest Android OS

Cons: Everything else

This is the most bulkiest of bloatware tablets I have ever seen. It was bought for use with scanning barcodes (QR) and it does NOT auto focus, which meant that it could not detect 99% of barcodes. The new OS was the best thing I could find about this cheap tablet. Spend an extra $100 bucks and get a real tablet that can actually do something....</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TiminLA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Too small, speed is OK

I really was not that impressed with this device. The speed was OK but the 7&quot; screen is just too small for my liking. I return the unit.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ElectronicBuyer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice instrument, well worth it!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Transportability, works for what I need it for

Cons: Don&apos;t have any cons at this point.

I wanted something that was easy to use and transport. I found my netbook to be cumbersome even at it&apos;s small size and even though the netbook is more powerful I find the Tab is handling everything I ask from it so far. I was looking at the kindle fire as well and found for my needs the Tab was the better choice and Android has a kindle app which works fine. The kindle was far heavier and slower to process information compared to the Tab. The Tab also has a micro-SD slot which the kindle doesn&apos;t have. Good unit and I was not disappointed buying the TAB!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>arfish</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Galaxy Tab 2 7.0 Problems</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Great Pad in looks and feel, however, very weak wi-Fi reception to the end that sometimes there is no connection. Not so good since this is a wi-fi only tablet.Just doesn&apos;t work a lot of the time. Maybe the one I got is defective, but I do not know how to deal with that situation.Should have more than 8 GB memory as well (16GB would have been the right way to go)..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ko-Ko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>&quot;Exciting, Excellent, Educating&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Set Up

My son is 11 years old and I wanted to get him something special for his birthday. He is always using our device at home. This was one of the best items I&apos;ve ever purchased in a long time. He is not just playing games but he is reading books and researching information for his Science Project. Bravo Samsung!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AngelRising</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Poor Tablet for Video Consumption</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very nice speakers

Cons: Incompatible with Several Popular Video Formats

I am guessing you are not thinking about buying this 7&quot; tablet to surf the internet or to read email, you can do that on your smart phone already. So the only thing left is to play games and watch movies. You can play games just fine on this tiny tablet but you will NOT be able to watch every video format. This tablet refuses to play Quicktime movies from the Internet. It seems to block them. Cannot play Hulu and there is no HBO app for Android, so forget about watching TV episodes online in most websites.
It does not play videos from DSLR cameras shot in 720p or 1080p. Basically it only plays extremely low resolution videos like a smart phone.
So the only use of this tablet is for playing An ... droid games nothing else.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jagman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This Tablet is a Mini Laptop!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This Tablet comes with me everywhere! It&apos;s 7 size is just right. I&apos;ve added a Bluetooth keyboard for Email, but otherwise it&apos;s on-screen keyboard works fine. There are lots of useful Apps from Samsung and the Android Market to add to those included with the Galaxy Tab 2. The screen is bright enough for me, and I am still arranging Widgets and Apps to my liking.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 2 (7.0) WiFi 8 GB - Titanium silver</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/10749738519022648190/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CIQCEPQCMAc4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zarko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best value for money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good combination for regular use, all the things one needs in nice package and right size. I am not a gamer so don&apos;t cite me for gaming experiences but as trip companion, e-reader, GPS and internet communication just perfect.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

