<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Vivid display, very good performance, odd size feels good in hands, attractive design and hardware

Cons: iPad has better app selection, priced similarly to 10-inch tablets, virtual keyboard sometimes feels small

The Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 tablet packs all the power of the full-sized Samsung Galaxy Tab 10.1 into a smaller, easier to transport form. Although the 8.9-inch form factor isn&apos;t common, reviewers report that the slate feels comfortable and natural in their hands. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tigereg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Alternative to Ipad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size, good battery, easy and fun to use.

Cons: Placement of buttons, headphone jack, speakers. (Not a deal breaker)

The Samsung Galaxy tab is a great alternative to the Ipad. My wife has an Ipad but I enjoying using my galazy tab. I love sense UI and widgets which allows me to read and check my email without having to go into an app.

The 8.9 is a perfect size as its not to small like a smart phone and not to big like Ipad. To me its the perfect size for a tablet for everyday use.

Only gripe is placement of the buttons, head phone jack, speakers and charging station. I wouldn&apos;t say this is a deal breaker but sometimes while using it I forget about the placement and turn it off or wires can get tangles since the placement is all over the place.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dia1411</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Godd tablet for budget-minded</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great screen resolution, lightweight, long battery life

Cons: Find that the volume does not go as loud as I need

My first tablet. Did not want to spend more than $375-$400, so I looked at this, the Sony, and Kindle FIre. Still learning how it works, but am very pleased with screen color/sharpness, battery life, it looks like it can do a lot. Like the smaller size, too.

Hooking up to computer could be a little easier, and the transfer software (Samsung Kies) is slow &amp; cumbersome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RichardMR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung Galaxy 8.9 Tablet rocks....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Perfect 8.9 size, great price deal

Cons: Short battery life.

I love my tablet. Awesome performance. Can do anything my pc can do. Always connected to social networks. Great stereo sound. Very satisfied customer. Perfect size, light-weight, durable, and fun to operate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RetroDigger</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful unit for travel access of information</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This Galaxy Tab 8.9 has proven to be a great tool while traveling to access email, internet and volumens of helpful information. The apps were great for getting hotel fees, gas prices, store locations and general directions. The entertainment value of the Tab is extensive with access to movies, games and communication.
I have never owned or used a Smart Phone but found this pretty easy to learn and use effectively. The screen size is a benefit to me vs. a small phone screen (age makes reading harder). The wifi connections were easy and quick. Glad I didn&apos;t get a 3G version as wifi is so common at hotels, restaurants and homes that the only times I needed constant access were while driving. With a 3G unit from Sprint (or Verizon or others) that is possible.
Glad I bought this and real ... ly like it. Battery life is terrific. Only drawback are screen smudges and can&apos;t keep opwer cord attached when portfolio case is closed.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>r1y1a1n</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>for me, perfect in all ways</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>First off, mine came with gingerbread3.2 not 3.1 like the internet said. This tablet is the perfect size. That was one of the main reasons I bought it. It is super thin and light. It doesn&apos;t have an SD card slot, however, you can use a micro flash drive (or any flash drive) with the usb adapter. This will also allow you to use a usb mouse. The sound quality and volume is awesome for such a slim tablet. The Android operating system so far has been flawless. I love 3.2, its laid out very well. Bluetooth and gps are great features not all tablets have. The rear camera takes very clear pictures with a very bright flash. I haven&apos;t found any zoom function yet but an aftermarket camera app might work. The screen is crisp and bright. It even comes with great sounding ear bud headphones. Battery li ... fe is awesome. On my first charge I have used it about 6 hours so far playing games and browsing the internet and still have 47% battery left. So far I have been 100% happy with my purchase.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Susan1952</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Perfect Size Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, ease of use

Cons: Price, virtual keyboard

My husband has an IPad, but I found it just too big and heavy for frequent use. My phone is a Galaxy, and after playing with the IPad, I found that I much prefer Android over Apple. This was a logical extension to my phone and the perfect size and weight for me. Although it doesn&apos;t have 3G, I use it mostly where there is WiFi available, so that hasn&apos;t been an issue. Plus I could activate the mobile hotspot on my phone if I needed it and therefore have WiFi all the time.

There are lots of customizable features, it was very easy to get it up and running out of the box. Battery life is not great, but I do use live wallpaper and other battery draining apps, so some of that is just what I have to expect.

There are ... not as many apps as there are for the IPad or even for my phone. Many of the Android apps aren&apos;t designed for tablets, so they work better on the phone. Hopefully this will improve with time.

Because of the size and newness of the 8.9 tablet, there are very few accessories available, such as cases and screen protectors. Again, hopefully this will improve if this tablet sells well.

Unlike the Galaxy phone, there are not a lot of useless apps pre-loaded that can&apos;t be removed. Thank you Samsung for that!

It&apos;s easy to switch between apps, there are 5 different home pages to customize, the camera and speakers are very good. It&apos;s a snap to add, relocate, and remove things on the home pages.

My complaints are the location of the charger port - it&apos;s on the bottom, which is awkward when the tablet is in the case. Wish it were on top or on the side. The keyboard is a nightmare. I am a woman and have small fingers, but am constantly getting something other than what I typed. Part of that is Swype, which IMO is handy but needs a LOT of work. I have the same problem when touching links on a webpage - getting the link above or below where I am aiming. And I think the price is outrageous.

Overall, I&apos;m very happy with it and it was the right choice for me.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dakota1973</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good price, came with a free keyboard.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, very portable. Battery lasts a long time on a full charge.

Cons: No usb slot, no hdmi.

We bought the 8.9&quot; tab because it was $50 cheaper then a 10.1 and the size is not much different. It also came with a free keyboard dock which comes in very handy($79) value. It does take a while to fully charge but we can use it all day on one charge. It should come with a usb port although you can purchase the adapter seperatly. The charging slot would be better on the top or side rather then the bottom. Was going to upgrade my phone to the Samsung note 5.3&quot; screen but choose to get a bigger tablet instead, dose the samething, just can&apos;t make calls on it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jacksuhn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great screen, not as awesome processor</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen

Cons: Processor

I&apos;ve had the Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 for about two months now, so I feel I&apos;ve done my due putting it through the paces. I should also mention that I don&apos;t have experience with any other tablets for comparison.
What stands out the most on the device is the screen. Great resolution, very sharp image and good playback. The dual speakers aren&apos;t bad at all, although I generally use headphones anyway. The responsiveness of the touch screen is very good. But being an EVO 4G phone user, I am used to a much more sensitive screen.
The camera is just okay, as with any mobile device. Good in well lit situations, terrible in low light.
The battery life is very good. Out of the box it would last 5-6 days with heavy video and internet use. I could drag i ... t down to single-digit percentage and still have it finish the day. Now it goes about 2-3 days on heavy use. If I leave in the morning and it&apos;s on 30% battery, when I get home, it will be dead. It&apos;s very disappointing to have it drain while not being used, but since I&apos;m gone, I just have to plug it in. It does make me wonder how the battery will hold up in another 6-12 months.
I was expecting a lot more from the dual processor. Don&apos;t get me wrong, it&apos;s a pretty fast device and very slick over all. But all too often when exiting an application it will take a few seconds to have the home screen be fully functional, loading all the widgets and app shortcuts. This surprised me. Likewise, I have had a handful of different apps crash or freeze on me. But it resets itself pretty quickly.
Overall this is a pretty sweet tablet and I am enjoying it thoroughly. It&apos;s not perfect, but what is.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rhynole</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Near Perfection</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size

Cons: Lack or connectivity(no usb, no memory card, no hdmi)

wanted a tablet that was bigger than the 7&quot; mini&apos;s but smaller than the 10 inchers. The 8.9 incher felt perfect in my hand. Screen is crytal clear. Speakers sound great. Camera takes much better pictures than my phone. Approaching the clarity of my regular camera. Front facing camera great for skype. Love the Samsung touchwiz interface. Just got one for my mom too.

The only thing preventing me from giving it a 5 star rating is the absence of usb port, memory card slot, and hdmi connectivity without buying an adapter.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CalaLilly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great First Tablet!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size. Vivid images. Battery life good.

Cons: Nothing right now.

I really like it. I use it primarily for web surfing and uploading sermons. We looked at several tablets - money not being an issue - and decided on this one because of its size, support of Adobe flash, and available connection kit. The tablet fits easily inside my zip-up portfolio, even in the tablet&apos;s case. The colors are bright and vivid. I am able to upload documents to it from a flash drive and view pictures on an SD card via the connection kit. Sound is great. Battery life has been good.

I did have one issue with accessing information on a website. I wasn&apos;t able to make a select from a drop-down menu. The system seemed to redirect me somewhere esle. Not sure if this is related to the tabl ... et or not, but is was frustrating.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MC17</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Can&apos;t think of a thing....

I&apos;ve had this for a couple of weeks now &amp; absolutely love this tablet. I&apos;m new to the android market but found it very easy to adapt to. It&apos;s flash compatible, which was important to me. Perfect size. Not too small or too big. It has a beautiful display. Great battery life. Very responsive. I couldn&apos;t be happier.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lytewate</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awesome tablet; easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, ease of use

Cons: no usb port or sd card slot

This is my first tablet. I chose this tablet because of the screen size and its android operating system. I dont own any apple products and im already familiar with android market. Battery life is awesome, easy to download apps from android market. Front and back camera is nice, video too. Easy to buy ebooks and magazines. If you&apos;re thinking of purchasing this, dont hesitate, you wont be disappointed. I would suggest getting a case (m-edge for 50 bucks is well worth it). The only negative thing is it doesnt have a usb port or sd card slot BUT there is an adapter available for it. I plan on getting one but havent had the need to at this point!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lemondrop1974</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I decided to get this tablet instead of the nook tablet, thanks to my husband suggesting I go all out and get a &quot;real tablet&quot;. And I sure am glad I listened to him for once! I had a nook color and utimately started using it mainly for apps and the web. There is no comparison between this tablet and an e-reader. This thing rocks! It&apos;s lightning fast &amp; smooth, easy to use and set up, and just plain fun to play with. My whole family uses it, even my 6 month old baby #lots of cool baby apps#. I also got the M-Edge Incline Jacket for Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9, and it is perfect for protecting, and propping up; and the Rocketfish stylus #it&apos;s great too#, keeps the screen clean from fingerprints. This tablet is the perfect size, not too big, not too small. Very portable. Speakers put out alot of ... sound, pretty loud, good sound quality. I would definitely recommend this tablet! I love it!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chipzzang</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fast and portable with excellent hardware</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything else include price and performance

Cons: Accessories and tablet apps compared to ipad 2.

Right size and weight for me to play around my office, classroom and home. It is fast and has a crystal clear display screen. I am really enjoying it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>br0wnhon3y</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, Screen size is great, Graphics are great also.

Cons: Nothing so far!

This is a great tablet. I can watch tons of movies on it (which I do almost constantly), I can read books on it and play games. I also update my calendar and email functions. I have had this for a month now and I love it. So far I haven&apos;t had any problems with it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pbfactor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>perfect size and light weight</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Perfect size tablet. The 10.1&apos;s seem awkward and the 7&apos;s to small. Very bright screen. I&apos;ve had a xoom and a galaxy tab 7.0. Samsung uses alot of plastic. Maybe it saves weight (this thing is much lighter than an ipad 2). My galaxy 7.0 and galaxy s phone both had plastic backs. It flexes and makes noise on the 8.9, unexcuseable for the price. I expect that from archos not samsung! It should be aluminium. The ui is typical great samsung. The wifi speed is a little slow. My htc sensation is much faster on the home network and so was the xoom. Great little, light tablet. Some things for samsung to iron out, but very usable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Screen Size. Volume

Cons: No micro SD expansion

I Love my Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9. It’s the perfect size not too big and not too small. I bought it at best buy and since the most important thing about the device for me is playing movies. I turned you tube on all the devices they had on display and determined that the Samsung had the best quality audio. All the movies I have on there are ones downloaded from the internet and they all look great. No problems with the video.
The only one problem I did encounter was that once it froze up on me. I started to panicked and was getting ready to return it when I read online that you need to hold down the power button and the volume down button at the same time. It worked.
My wife bought an I Pad and then returned it after a ... couple of weeks. The Galaxy tab is more customizable.
The only thing I would change is adding a micro SD slot for adding more storage. But I can deal with 16 gigs. I just need to delete the movies after I watch them. I definitely wasn’t going to pay more money for the 32 gig Tab.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CRD1219</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, picture

Cons: Battery seems to go fast.

I have an ipad 2, but wanted to get a Tablet to see the difference,also my 5 yr daughter seems to want my ipad as soon as I go to use it. The ipad has much better apps, even for the ones that are made for both, their better on the ipad. The tablet supports flash player with is a bonus. The samsung is a nice size, as thin as ipad and very good picture.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cje138</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Perfect size and weight, real operating system in Android, fast performance

Cons: Quirky app open/close sometimes, can&apos;t change the apps in the task bar.

This thing is great. It&apos;s my second android tablet and is far better for day to day use than my Asus. It&apos;s mostly about the size and weight, it is small and light enough to hold with one hand, but I don&apos;t feel like I&apos;m using a smaller screen than the old 10.1&quot;. I love it and it&apos;s speed. Very much looking forward to how this thing will shine with the ice cream sandwich update!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SGBE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Almost perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent size/form factor

Cons: Plastic bezel near the docking jack could be better (less flex)

Other than the display bezel showing a little too much flex where it meets the docking port jack, this 8.9” Galaxy tab (7310) is almost perfect. The speed, IPS display, and overall nice quality in a super thin form factor make the 8.9&quot; Galaxy tab a solid choice for any Android user. Once Samsung releases the ICS 4.0 firmware update, the experience will be even better. No, this unit doesn’t offer onboard HDMI, USB, or a media card reader, but that is the tradeoff that I accept for a tablet this thin. Additionally, the docking port does support all these features via a very small and low cost adapter pigtail or media dock (yes, the 10.1” media dock and accessories work with th ... e 8.9”) so it’s all good. I have both the iPad 3rd Gen and this unit next to me daily and find myself using the Samsung more. It is lighter, feels better typing on, and supports all the web content the iPad does not. I do love the iPad’s new FHD+ retina display, but the Samsung’s IPS display is still among the best I have experienced in this size class. Great job Samsung!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>perrysvillebill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good overall, lacking some features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, weight, android, its not i-anything

Cons: lacks SD card slot, HDMI slot, USB slot

Generally this a good choice for me. Size is just right. Seven inch models are a bit too small, and the form factor of the 10 inch models is like carrying around a textbook. Samsung needs to include the above mentioned slots to make this a really great tablet. Android need native printing, Samsung&apos;s included print app is a poor substitute as it only works with Samsung printers (and I didn&apos; know they made printers until I got my Galaxy). Pages load fast, videos are without hesitation. I even teathered it to my smartphone via bluetooth. Good alternative to apple, good choice if you want an in-between size. Because of the size, I found choice and availability of accessories (cases/cover ... s) to be lacking. Speakers need relocated from the bottom.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Timegg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome device!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery life, size, quality, speed

Cons: Nothing

This is my first tablet, and I absolutely love it. The 8.9&quot; size is perfect. I looked at the 7 plus, which seemed too small, and the 10.1 which seemed too big to be very mobile, but settled on the 8.9. I use it a lot for on-the-fly grading in my high school classes, and it works great. I would definitely recommend it to others.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>20724</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing tablet from Samsung!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight, display, battery life, decent speakers

Cons: Honeycomb OS

Perfect size, in my opinion, it&apos;s light, thin, and easy to hold even with one hand for reading, web browsing, etc.
The display/screen is amazing, great color, very sharp, not quite as nice as some of Samsung&apos;s Super AMOLED displays, but it&apos;s not as expensive as those either...Samsung really has the best display tech out there.
I&apos;m not a big fan of the Honeycomb operating system, (sometimes get force closes, crashes, etc) BUT, Android 4.0 (Ice Cream Sandwich) is on the way for this tablet, which should improve it in many ways over Honeycomb.

Sound is decent, with 2 speakers on the bottom of the tablet, not on the sides like the Galaxy Tab 10.1.

Battery life is very good, not quite ... an iPad, but not too far behind,I am getting very respectable battery life.

I&apos;ve owned iPad and iPad2, and I like this tablet a lot..I have to say that this ranks right up there with them in many respects and exceeds thm in some ways. The Android market for tablets is still relatively weak in selection of tablet specific apps, however.

Overall, I love this tablelet, and would recommend it highly!

Another great product from Samsung, I&apos;m really impressed with some of their products lately!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LynnG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet for new users</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, speed, weight, screen sharpness

Cons: short cord and extra large plug

What,s not to love? I,m new to tablets and originally purchased a Toshiba Thrive. After a it quit charging, returned it to Best Buy ( whose customer service is awsome by the way ) &amp; received a brand new replacement. Less then two weeks later, it quit charging &amp; turned that in for my Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9&quot;. No problems at all so far. Had it for 5 weeks now. Goes everywhere with me. So much more convenient then my previous netbook. Would not go back! Thought I would be purchasing the keyboard as an extra but find the on board keyboard is just fine. So much more responsive and faster then the netbook ever was. Couldn,t decide between the 10&quot;, 8.9&quot;, or 7&quot;, not ever having one before, so I w ... ent middle of the road with the 8.9. The screen is super sharp and the color is beautiful! Very quick responce time whether I,am playing a game or on the internet. I find there is tons of free apps available for downloading from the market place. Loving it! The only draw back so far is the very short and inconvenient charging cable that comes with it, and the extremely large power plug that takes up 2 outlets. Would ( and have ) recommend this to everyone.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>stevonovitch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet out there</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size

Cons: nothing

iPad watch out. Samsung has delivered a lot of innovative products in the Android line and this one stands out because of its size. The full-size tablets (iPad, Xoom, even the full-size Samsung) are too big and the smaller (blackberry playbook, etc.) are too small. The Samsung 8.0 is just perfect. The battery life is also nothing to shake a stick at and the WiFi connectability is second to none.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Digger58</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great in beween size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: East use right out of the box

Cons: Battery life could be better, minor issue

Bought it for its 8.9 screen size. 10&quot; too big, 7&quot; too small. Had it completely set-up within a few minutes out of the box. Fantastic
HD screen, Colors just pop out! Would Recomend it to you.
Can&apos;t go wrong.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KenDotCom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and battery life.

Cons: Can&apos;t think of anything!

Excellent product. Exceeded my expectations in every way.
Lightweight, compact size, long battery life, excellent screen quality and more apps available than I could every use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect fit!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size. Great Price. Tons of apps to increase usability.

Cons: Not many cases to choose from.

The size of the 8.9 is perfect! Not too small that it feels like I&apos;m holding a giant phone, not too big that it becomes cumbersome. I can easily hold this with one hand while using the other to navigate without having in actually grip the screen. Extremely responsive due to it&apos;s quick processor. I can stream all my movies from my network drive right to the tab. Gorilla Glass keeps the screen from being scratched. Perfect!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RobertWS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung knows how to &quot;get it done&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Image quality, construction, useful

Cons: NA

This is a wonderful product by a company that understands how to make the product fun and useful. Highly recommended!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sjoerd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfectly sized, beautiful, lightweight tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, weight, battery life

This tablet delivers everything it promised. The main reason for me to wait for this specific tablet was the weight and size. All the ~10&quot; tablets are too big for me and the smaller ones are, well, too small. I don&apos;t need 3G &apos;cause I use my phone for that (Nexus One). I did decide to buy the 32 MB version since the memory card slot was removed between the prototype and the final product. I haven&apos;t seen vanilla honeycomb, but the few touchwiz additions are pretty good. The Samsung Hubs (social, media) aren&apos;t very useful. I&apos;ve watched plenty movies on the tab and it&apos;s pure bliss. Other than that I use it daily for e-mail, news, websurfing, facebook, games, music. I use it a couple of hours each day and charge it every third or fourth day when the batte ... ry&apos;s running low. I watched movies on a flight for 8 hours straight. The tab itself is eyecandy too. Can&apos;t do without anymore. It was definitely worth the wait.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Android Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The new Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 is a huge improvement over the Galaxy Tab 7. The larger 8.9 display is a great improvement over the 7 which makes this tablet a serious contender to the iPad. The price is very competitive and available in 16 and 32GB formats. The Samsung has a great battery and is full of features and utilities that makes this a better business tool.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Good Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size, light

Cons: Touchwiz

In my opinion the biggest thing with a tablet is whether you can comfortably use while only holding it with one hand. This tablet doesn&apos;t sacrifice on hardware and maintains a great screen size while keeping its weight down and being very easy to hold. It has a tad bit of lag but that will disappear once Android 4 gets ported to it. Tablets like the 10+ inchers just aren&apos;t very portable. The seven inchers are easily too small. I could go for a tablet without the Samsung touchwiz skin but I can make it work. I have owned pretty much every tablet there is and this is my favorite easily with the ipad 2 after that.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent tablet for pilot flying an airplane</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: works perfectly and can be customized to heart&apos;s content.

Cons: no 3g

I use the 8.9 inch tablet when I fly airplanes. Perfect size for displaying instrument approach charts. Navigating between charts is easy. Can customize how you use it very easily. Two must have apps are Astro file manager and ezPdfReader. ezPdfReader can view charts in night mode - white text on black background. I flew a night sortie of 1.6 hours and the tablet had 82% battery life remaining. This is an excellent tablet in daytime conditions as well. Can see charts in sunlight no problem. Tablet is great for all the other uses it features as well. It is wifi only so you need to preload everything in advance. The 7 inch tablet makes a great 3g companion for checking weather and filing flight plans, e ... tc, etc.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>basiltbs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great consumption device</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great battery life. Given my heaving reading and email use - I prefer the smaller size. Typing is easier and can hold device for long periods of time. I did not care for the keyboard and bought one from the market. Use the device primarily for reading - RSS feeds, emails, kindle, netflix and tracking hours for contract work. Still waiting for market update for music. Overall - great device, great experience.

Selection of accessories is very limited for now.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sithc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size &amp; Weight

Cons: Price

This is my first tablet so not sure I have much to compare to. Love the 8.9&quot; size because it seems 10&quot; is tad too big and 7&quot; a tad too small. So far its working fine. Was pretty intuitive to set up. Screen is vibrant and I have it set to about only 1/3 of the way. Mainly use it for games, quick browsing and Facebook. So far no major issues.

There is some lag when opening certain items, but hoping Ice Cream Sandwich will fix that. Power button is a little too close to volume buttons like another reviewer commented.

It&apos;s a little spendy, especially paying an extra $100 for the 32GB version. But the quality/size makes up for it. Overall I&apos;m pleased with it and a believer of you get what you pay for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RedBaronRay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>USB 2.0 PORT!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great size for handling, especially good for reading

Cons: No ports. Current high price.

Despite what the specs state, this excellent tab does NOT have a High Speed USB 2.0 PORT! A dongle or USB Adapter must be purchased, and used, with its not too convenient installation. It also adds a bit to the overall cost of this already high priced tab. In addition, dual core processors and even Android 3.2 will shortly be left behind with the explosion of technology.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Qosmokid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best size for a tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and battery life

Cons: Nothing I can think of

I&apos;ve had my Galaxy Tab 8.9 since the day it came out and I just love it. After handling 10 inch tablets I must say this is by far the best size for a tablet. It feels much lighter and is a pleasure to read on for extended periods. Battery life is also great. I can easily go over two days before needing to recharge with normal usage. I am recomending this very high quality product to anyone who asks for my opinion.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kenny2840</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>before purchase, make sure you know bestbuy policy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>15 day exchange only policy, We purchase this one only a month than the battery is dead, we go to best buy ask for exchange thay do not accept. I can&apos;t belive about $500 dollars only has one month fun. Bad product and bad sevice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>StartMeUp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It Can&apos;t Be That Difficult. Can It?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The physical package is great.

Cons: Downloading movies is a challenge. Web browsing is slow.

My needs are pretty basic. I travel weekly for business and really just want an entertainment center for movies, music, ebooks, games and web browsing. I don&apos;t need my office apps on a tablet, I have my laptop for that. For me the iPad and 10.1 inch tablets are just too big and the 7 inch tablets are too small for movies. I watched the market for a while and was really excited about the 8.9 GT. Just the right size and under $500. It is well laid out and very light. The screen is nice and bright and the battery life is good too.

But it has been a big disappointment in terms of consistency. Specifically Samsung&apos;s Media Hub application, the Android Movies Market, the Video ... Player and Web Browsing.

Connecting to the Media Hub is spotty. Sometimes it does and sometimes it doesn&apos;t. And when it has, I have been unable to make purchases because it will not accept my MC number. I haven&apos;t had problems with this card using any other applications, including the Android Marketplace.

Speaking of which, the Android Marketplace has a very limited selection of movies and at least 50% of the time the downloads don&apos;t work for one reason or another. Too many different error messages to go into here. Very inconsistent. I don&apos;t have the time to be troubleshooting this stuff all day long just to watch a movie.

Browsing the internet with this device is very frustrating. The browser takes a very long time to connect and display pages. Sometimes they don&apos;t display at all and time out. Not good.

Games download and work well. The Kindle app is great. And moving my music over from my home PC was a breeze. I expected that downloading and watching movies would be just as easy. But it is a nightmare. So back to the store it goes.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>6gadget9</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Technology</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I am an ipad owner and decided that I would try a smaller form factor device. When I first purchased it I thought it would be too small and remind me of my Evo phone that I hated so much. I was truly surprised that this device is really impressive. The first time using it I immediately noticed the weight difference between the ipad first generation and my new tab.

The long and short of it is the device is great and if you have to choose between ipad and tab choose the tab.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DeadlyParrot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>8.9&quot; form factor is excellent; needs Honeycomb 3.2</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Very good machine--8.9&quot; form factor is excellent--easier to handle than the usual 10.1 but more versatile than the 7&quot;. It does, however, need a 3.2 Honeycomb update to better utilize phone apps. Speaking of apps, what&apos;s the deal developers -- there are so few good Android tablet apps...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shazboticon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Subpar video player</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight and screen

Cons: Poort H.264 support

For the most part I really liked this tablet. It&apos;s a great size, very light weight, reasonably fast and the screen is bright and sharp. Unfortunately H.264 video playback is crippled by the Tegra 2 processor and any videos encoded with B-frames, regardless of resolution or bitrate, playback choppy and are pretty much unwatchable. Effectively this means ONLY H.264 videos encoded using baseline profile will play properly. I did dozens of tests with Handbrake to confirm this and @SamsungSupport also confirmed that Tegra 2 cannot handle B-frames. I was able to encode with CABAC with no problems, even at 1080p, but no B-frames. And that&apos;s a deal breaker for me because all of my videos are encoded with either main or high prof ... ile. As a result I returned it and now I&apos;m crossing my fingers that the Galaxy Tab 7.7 will be released in the U.S. which will use Exynos and should solve this limitation and be better than the Galaxy Tab 8.9 and 10.1 in almost every way (Exynos, Super AMOLED Plus screen, MicroSD slot, IR blaster, thinner, lighter, etc.).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>allaboutprocessor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Size, Weight and OS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, battery life, and processor speed

Cons: lack of accessories

Let me say that my key criteria for a tablet relate to using it first as a reader, second as web browser, and thirdly for everything else (games, social networking, etc.) For that purpose, I have used my wife&apos;s IPAD, but found it to be bulky and uncomfortable to hold for any extended period of time. I researched the Galaxy tab 10.1, and in general I liked the honeycomb system with the TouchWiz overlay, but again, it was too bulkey and awkward. I likewise looked at the 7 inch tablets, but found the screen size too limited to do much more than read. But let me say that I believe Samsung has hit a homerun with this tablet. It&apos;s screen size is perfect as a reader, and in my opinion, just as good as an IPAD fo ... r web activity and other purposes. The screen, as you may have read, is outstanding. It has the same number of pixels as the 10.1, but in a 8.9 frame. The device weighs less than a pound, so you can hold it for a long time with no discomfort. My wife is already jealous of the apps I have available through the Market that are not available through Apple. I carry this thing everywhere. It is almost exactly the size of a book or a standard Day Timer. I take notes all the time (with handwriting recognition software free from the Android Market). I have reading material available at all times. The browser is very zippy. The battery is amazing. It lasts longer than my wife&apos;s IPAD battery. I can&apos;t say enough good things about this device. The only draw back at this point is that there are still very few accessories available in the USA (September 2011), but with the success of this device in Europe, they have an excellent selection of accessories at Amazon UK (check out the website). I assume those things will be hitting our shores soon enough.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJ1Blue</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Giving Apple a Run for the Prize</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Customization

Cons: Prices of mostly all tablets in general

If you do not want an Apple iPad, this is the one to get. I love the screen from both sizing and viewing standpoints. It has mostly everything you will need so I am very excited to be able to use for both home and work applications.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Saigonese</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Not too small nor too big

Cons: a little bit hard to hold it while laying down

Great deal, my mom loves it and now she is owned it. I have to buy another one</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NCPhilliesPhan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really like this tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reasonably priced Android tablet

Cons: No SD card slot

I really like this tablet. The screen is great with nice, sharp colors - great for apps like Google Currents and Marvel comics. Videos seem to play well too. Not sure how I missed this when researching, but no SD card slot. Overall, a very good tablet, picked it up on sale at Best Buy for $350 - good value compared to iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tonitouch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>i love my products</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i really appreciate how these electronics are very easy to work with.. :-) also i am very happy my two daughters age 12yrs. And 4yrs. Also play with it very easily... Very useful for alot of school essentials...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mjd1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE this Tablet!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: You name it... everything!

Cons: I wish the speakers were on top, instead of the bottom. But not a really big issue.

This tablet is awesome. It does everything. I thought my smartphone was cool, but this Galaxy tablet blows it away. The screen size, sharp resolution, the speed, the wi-fi, the storage capacity and just everything else about it is incredible. It has become a part of me. Everywhere I go, in the house or away, I just have to be sure I have it with me. I must say.... my laptop isn&apos;t in use much anymore!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kenogypsy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for non Movie Lovers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast little internet browser

Cons: Usless for movies

This is a great little unit for internet browsing. Small and does most everything you need to do. Not upgradable. The charging unit and accessory output is definatly in the wrong place. If you use the extension hub to watch a movie, it is stupid to have it on the bottom, can&apos;t rest the unit on your lap or table, poor design. Movies can&apos;t rotate. It will play an avi movie if pluged in but not while streaming. Samsung should fix this asap. If you want just an internet tablet, there are more useful and cheaper ones available.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RRWIRSI</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great product when you understand how to use it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: screen size, weight, apps,

Cons: no ability to download directly to computer. No paper manual

I bought the Tab for my wife. Fortunately, our son-in-law showed us how to get started and use the product. It is very different than using our desk top and lap top computers. There is no manual included with the Tab product. The manual is obtained on-line but this information was not stated with the Tab product. Would have given a 5 star except for no direct ability to download information directly to our computers and no paper manual with the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>texancowboy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>perfect size.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: portability and size

Cons: um... nothing

i purchased this as a chirstmas present for my self 8-). i like it for the reason that it is portable and the screen size is perfect to browse online, watch movies, videos and check social sites on the web. i didnt need it but just wanted to get one since it look nice and i received a gift card in return for the purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best Android tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is the best Android tablet that I&apos;ve used so far. Very light and portable. Very fluid and fast. I&apos;ve used the Kindle Fire and other tablets. This one is the perfect size. It does have some limitations with Vimeo and Hulu. A few things could be improved, but a huge step forward.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jpfsc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>the goldilocks of the tablets, just the right size but with the same resolution as the 10.1 screens.
not too keen on samsung&apos;s added software but it stays out of the way mostly.
For a media consumption device, the lack of msd slot would be problematic though not an issue for me.
I had a xoom before this and tbh xoom ran a touch faster on transitions and the wifi connection had more &apos;authority&apos; at boot up. samsung screen is significantly &apos;better&apos; though.
With the weight and handling improvements over both apple and android offerings, this is just right.
power cable is too short for charging while using.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>stonecgi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Android Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: lightweight and crisp diplay.

Perfect size and very quick.
I had a motorolla xoom (10.1&quot;) and found it was too heavy for reading my kindle books in bed. I downsized to this 8.9 inch galaxy tab and it is perfect. PLENTY big )screen size) and much lighter.It does everything I want it to do and I dont get tired holding it.
Display is crisp and responsive and browsing the web is quick.

This is a GREAT tablet for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GabeGadgets</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good But Not Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Thin &amp; Light

Cons: TouchWiz, Seems Laggy at Times, Uninstallable Apps, Price

It&apos;s thin &amp; light, no doubt about it. However, it isn&apos;t small enough to tell a huge difference between it &amp; any other 10in tablet.

The TouchWiz interface blows. I prefer a stock Honeycomb experience like what you get from the Xoom. I don&apos;t know if it&apos;s the TouchWiz interface slowing things down, but the tablet doesn&apos;t seem as snappy as it should.

It&apos;s full of uninstallable bloatware from Samsung. The only one I was able to uninstall (without rooting) is the Samsung screensaver.

It&apos;s not a bad tablet, but I&apos;m returning it and waiting for the 7&quot; Thrive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BikeNerd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything.

Cons: Nothing, yet.

I have been wanting a tablet for a while now. I just started working, so I was able to purchase this.
I grabbed this because it was on clearance and because I am firmly anti-Apple. I have not used this for it&apos;s true potential yet, but for traveling it is a lot easier than dragging my laptop around and trying to use it mid trip. So far I have no complaints, other than my greasy fingerprints being all over it. And I need to get it on my home network, so I can listen to music files without loading them up on an sd card or transferring them. Need to also figure out which video formats will play on here.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CMHAR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Tablet, Good Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, not very pricey, good transition from pc to tab

Cons: Nothing major

It&apos;s hard for me to get used to a tablet because it&apos;s more like having a smartphone than a laptop and I still expect it to do laptop things. But that would be any tablet I&apos;m sure. This is an easy to use Android-based tab at a good price if you aren&apos;t ready to commit to the expensive iPad. Apps are easy to download and majority are free! Hooking up to the internet is a breeze. As with any tablet, pushing the correct tiny button with big human fingers can be frustrating, but I think using a stylus would help that. It boots up and shuts down quickly, and is lightweight. Another cool feature is you sync it with a Samsung tv to watch things off your tab on the big screen. I wish it had a USB or ... memory card slot, but you can get a USB connector at a small extra cost. I also think the rotation of the screen could be a little quicker (orienting from horizontal to vertical, etc). Otherwise, a neat little tablet.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>seaver78</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exactly what I was looking for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: screen looks great, battery life

Cons: transition between menus sometimes a little sluggish

I wanted something with a bigger screen than a Fire or Nook, but something more portable and hold-able than an iPad for reading. This size is perfect for me. Streaming internet video and apps play flawlessly. Battery life is great (3-4 days between charges with fairly regular use). Camera is not outstanding but is acceptable</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Tablet works as advertised. Arived before expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: ??

I use this tablet for work primarily and also to read my school texts since I am always taking something new. I have an app- Quick Office HD that I use in meeting to keep up with all of the items I am responsible for. I just send to one of my e-mail accounts and open back up in my office PC and make any necessary changes on the bigger screen. Only drawback is I never forget anything now, but I always have an answer now when asked. I also purchased the Bluetooth keybd case from Samsung and it is really awesome - just like carrying my laptop to a meeting in a smaller form.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>r0xx0rz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Web access on the go, ebook reader etc...

Cons: Size and availability of covers.

I really wanted to get an ebook reader. Then I thought, why not combine devices and use for email as well as surfing.
The Galaxy 8.9 is great as an eReader. I have an extensive library and I was easily able to move it to the Galaxy and read almost all formats (good-bye .lit...).
The browser is great and I have it set up so I can hear tones when I get email - a different sound for each address, so I know when it is business or fun.
The only problem I have is the size. I was using an iPod Touch which has a really small screen. I originally wanted to buy the 7&quot; Galaxy, since I thought 10.1&quot; would be too large, but when I saw this one at the store, I thought it would be perfect. Not to ... o large, not too small. And the resolution looked great. I was wrong. It is a little too large for my purposes. I should have gotten the 7&quot;, but now that I have this, I will never adjust to a smaller screen.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RightWingMan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Size and Great Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, performance, quality

Cons: Lacks microSD slot for storage expansion

Really Nice device. I bought it for my wife to read books etc.
This is a really great size at 8.9&quot;. it is bif enough to read, but she can still fit it in her purse. My dad just went to by one for my mom, but was told this is a discontinued item.. Sounds like we this size may not be available anymore. Hope thats wrong as i was looking to by another for work.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GuiM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tab!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size

Cons: Accessories

I took almost a month to decide about a tab. I was not intend to spent a lot of money on an iPad and in the same time I would like a small one. I was looking for the Iconia A100 and the Samsung 7&quot;, but then I found this Galaxy that has a very good relation between size and price! It is not so big as the 10&quot;, so I bring it easily on my bag and it is not so small as the 7&quot;, which I would need to zoom websites everytime. One bad thing I see is that, since it is not a standard size, it is a bit difficult to find accessories to it, like a case. Also, the bluetooth headset I have do not work properly with Skype, for example. From a search on the net, I saw that it seems it requires a special headset.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Matthew1977</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet, just as good as an iPad.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Beautiful screen, great response time, more free apps than itunes market.

Cons: Some of the android apps were design for phones. Battery is a bit weaker than the iPad.

This tablet really open me to a new mobile computing market. The screen is beautiful, the operating system works well. The respose time is just as fast as an iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dbeaumont</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 with 16GB - Metallic Grey</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size.portable,speed, not to mention its a Samsung product

Cons: Nothing bad to say

I love my new Samsung tablet. Its portable so I take it everywhere. I have the ability to take pictures and videos. I can even connect to my wireless network to upload pictures or music. Functions as an e-reader and I have linked to my local library and downloaded a few books. I have the 16 gig and it serves me well. One caution, one of the main reasons I purchased was so that I could watch Hulu movies (Not Hulu Plus) however, the movies are not supported on the table platform. I can watch these movies on my laptop with no problem. There are some app and browser call Dolphin that will allow you to watch the videos, but the viewing is somewhat choppy. All in all I have a great little table ... t and I am sure an update will come out soon that will allow me to watch. I may even upgrade to Hulu Plus which I am told I would be able to view the movies on the tablet. Also, be sure to purchase a pouch and a rubberized backing as the tab does feel a little slick to hold in your hand.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Youngblood8503</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Overall</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very solid Android platform

Cons: Swype keyboard glitches at times

Love it. Works just like I would expect, except the Swype keyboard :/ cuts the last few letters off of many words...not really sure why</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dabbler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I say &quot;Honey, I love your tablet.&quot; most every day</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great sound, good price, look great

Cons: proprietary connector for everything

I chose a tablet with a high priority on sound quality so that my wife can use it like a transistor radio. And we have not been disappointed. Unfortunately, I like this tablet so much that maybe I should get another one for my wife too!! :-)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>FATboySLIM9481</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No More Heavy Laptop</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Nothing so far, if it is bad at something it&apos;s something I don&apos;t use and don&apos;t notice.

Bought for my wife. She graduated from college and didn&apos;t really need Office programs, but still wanted to surf the web, pay bills, take on vacation, etc. Picked the Samsung Galaxy because it supports Flash so the Internet isn&apos;t broken like my mothers iPad. Very user friendly...hesitant on Android OS, but very satisfied. Colors are vibrant. Nice to watch movies on. My wife is small, so the 10.1 was a bit overwhelming, but handles the 8.9 very well. Not really any cons to complain about. Got the Zagg screen protector and it doesn&apos;t leave nearly as many fingerprints as it does without. Speakers aren&apos;t awesome, but it&apos;s a tablet and better than my iPod speakers. If I wan ... ted great speakers I would watch something on my home entertainment system.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>estebang2010</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great tablet , exceeds expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Best android tablet out in the market, had the bb playbook but returned it to get this one for the lack of apps that blackberry world offers, works great with my samsung led tv 7000 series in which I can controll and share stuff directly from my tablet, I am really enjoying this tablet and would recommend to anyone who is searching for a tablet .college student</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daniam724</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Apples &amp; Androids</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I ended up buying my tablet at Best Buy also due to the lower pricing. They have the 16GB model on sale for $350. I have owned mine for 3 weeks now and can&apos;t find anything to complain about. I&apos;ve had a few programs crash here and there but it has nothing to do with the hardware. I can&apos;t wait for the ICS update coming this spring. I have owned 3 different iPhones starting with the 3G and now have the 4S (work phone). I went to compare all of the models at the store. I just couldn&apos;t get myself to buy an iPad. They seemed like a blown up version my my dang phone minus the phone capability. I went with the Samsung Tab 8.9 because it was the perfect size. If you buy this thing make sure to download a split keyboard. It&apos;s perfect for this tablet! You can hold this baby in one hand and not get ti ... red of holding it after 15min. Also the flexibility of Android is awesome! Yes, it takes a little time to set it up the way you want it, but it&apos;s totally worth it in the end.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gman43</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this tablet just over a month ago and so far I really love it. The only sad part of the story is that now my laptop --a Macbook Air--is very bored and lonely sitting unused in the corner of my room. It is hard to find a reason to use it now, as I do all my daily stuff when I get home from work with the Galaxy Tab 8.9. I have a desktop for the heavy-duty stuff.

I did a lot of research before buying this product and it lived up to my expectations; I am also excitingly awaiting the Android 4.0 update that is hopefully coming in March, which should make the product even better.

As soon as I got the GT 8.9 I installed ADW EX Launcher and applied the Ice Cream Sandwich theme, so I don&apos;t have much experience with the standard home screens. I can definitely recommend ADW EX ... Launcher if you are interested in a different home screen experience. You can download it in the android market. I also recommend the SwiftKey Keyboard over the stock ones--their text prediction is great.

A few other apps that I have really brought more functionality to the tablet are Adobe Photoshop Touch and Adobe Collage. They allow me to be creative on the go (my time on the subway just flies), and are just really cool to play around with. I make all kinds of photo collages and mood boards and share them with friends.

Anyway, I really like the tab and can recommend it for those looking for a nice lightweight tablet. It&apos;s been tons of fun and makes computing around the house really fun and comfortable.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>yodasoda</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>this the tish</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: so many apps and so many of them free.

Cons: it&apos;s not so great as the 1080p full HD tablet I&apos;m gonna get from samsung once more unless its for carrying then there no

This tablet is awesome! I can work on my laptop remoteley from anywhere at blazing speeds and I still have a mouse and a keyboard :D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leather</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound is great

Cons: Picture and video is not good at all

Does not play nor have App for Hulu or Hulu+, Does not play CW nor have an App for CW. Will play Amazon prime .... somewhat, it will play the standard videos and the picture is not very good, if you try HD video, just forget it, as it studders it way through the show and blacks out every 30 seconds. I even took to Best Buy thinking something was wrong with mine, and they said no, that is they way it is suppose to work, not happy at all and I can not even sell it on Ebay in good conscience knowing that this is just a glorified Ereader. It says it plays Flash yet the pictures are so bad you can not make out what anything is.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gadgetman1972</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this for my complete computer eliterate 78 yr old mother. She gets confused when it comes to dialing on a cell phone. I have a Motorola xoom, and from the simplicity of how the software runs I nw I had to get her one and get her caught up to the information/social age, AND she LOVESIt!!!!!! She knows how to read,send and forward emails, she knows how to open the you version bible and work the bible plans, she knows how to open and play memory games. It is a awesome companion. If you ae a senior and technology freaks you out get one of these. Android operating system allows you to customize your home screens and have email gadgets on the home page giving you complete ease of access. You will enjoy your new campanion, lessons learning, note tacking, movie vatching fun pad!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ladyhawke49</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best pad on the market- WIFI!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love this pad, have wanted one since iPad came out but did not want to pay the high monthly charge. Love the WiFi option as I do not need to have a service contract to use this wonderful and convenient tool. I can do almost anything with this tool and it is so much better than lugging the laptop. Samsung&apos;s display is 10x better than any on the market and I have downloaded 55 free apps that I use frequently- Thanks for offering this item- the size fits into most of my handbags- perfect for on the go! best purchase all year!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kazy27</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>fast, quick to learn on, small enough to carry</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: right size and fast

Cons: need more of a handbook to figure all out

I like it its fast, unlike my home computer. It is easily carried from place to place. It has plenty of free apps to experiment with. Good view on the screen. You definately need a screen saver or you&apos;ll constantly be wiping it off. worth the price and more. but cheaper and smaller than an IPAD.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SDEvans80</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good, could be better</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, speed, android os, it isn&apos;t made by apple

Cons: No sd slot, camera could be better,

This is my first tablet, I have had several smart phones over the years, including Blackberry, Iphone, and Many andoid phones, I have used Android since it was released on T Mobile G1. That being said I was excited about purchasing a Android Tablet. I bought the tab 8.9 and the Kindle Fire for my wife. I enjoy using this tablet very much, it is fast, snappy and the screen is amazing, Samsung really hit the mark on all of these things. My only real complaint is the lack of micro sd card support. If this thing has a card slot it would be the total package. As for the Fire, It doesn&apos;t have camera, not that big of a deal for a lot of people, and it doesn&apos;t have Google Marketplace, only ... amazon app store, which is great just not up to par with google market. Overall this would be a 5 star review if it has the card slot. Comparing it to Ipad is easy, Ipad has more apps, but this one has a lot, and the fact that you can use all different file types and not have to deal with itunes makes it better than the Ipad. If you want to spend less and still have a totally awesome little tablet, get the Fire, it is well worth the pricetag.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Keoki</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Typical Samsung Mediocrity</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, display, speed

Cons: Completeness of systems

My wife and I have now had 4 Samsung phones &amp; tablets and I have to say the same thing about all of them. They never finish the guts of their products. Sure, the screen is awesome, it is fast, thin, &amp; light. But so much time is wasted on the tablet&apos;s inability to handle web pages screen placement, a system that freezes up often, and what seems to me to be the inability really run apps well, including many of the pre-loaded apps from Samsung, which are always freezing up.

If you are just using this for the web, consider something cheaper. The Kindle Fire&apos;s web app is much more refined than this tablet. If you need more app power, consider a different tablet all together. I am no fan of the iPads but they c ... an&apos;t be any worse than this thing.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AIRMAN23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WAIT FOR THE IPAD 3</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice looking screen

Cons: everything else

I picked up this tablet early in December when it was on sale for $399. I waited all year to buy a tablet because I didn&apos;t want to buy a gen 1 gadget and all the usual bugs and glitches so I waited for the Gen 2 versions to come out as I thought that by then, at least some of the bugs of the Gen 1 tablet would have been ironed out. I was exited about getting into an android tablet as I have never been a fan of the Apple Ipad but after dealing with this Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 and it&apos;s buggy and glitchy android 3.1 OS I can&apos;t wait to put this thing up for sale on ebay and use whatever I can get for it to buy a Apple Ipad 3. here are some of the problems that I have encountered so far with this tablet.

1. The Best Buy app ba ... rcode scanner that I&apos;ve tried to use in the local Best Buy store to check some reviews of the merchandise does&apos;nt work, I can&apos;t get the the scanner to successfully scan one item, also a few other bar code scanner apps don&apos;t seem to work either. I&apos;ve checked to camera setting and everything seems to be ok there however I noticed that when trying to use the best buy barcode scanner the camera seems to be trying to focus going in and out but cannot successfully scan a barcode.

2. When I try to download an app from android market, the download freezes and says &quot;Waiting to install&quot; and just stays there. and the only way I can complete the download is to disable the wi-fi connection and then reenable it

3. At various times when connected to my Samsung SCH-LC11 Verizon mobile Wi-Fi LTE hotspot the connection just freezes and again I have to disable and then reenable the Wi-Fi to get the connection going again. None of this happens with my Apple Ipod Touch 4th Gen

4. I&apos;ve had some apps crash on me. One of them just won&apos;t work at all.

When I use my Apple Ipod Touch 4 gen using IOS 5.01 to scan barcodes or anything else I have no problems using the Ipod touch 4 Gen . It works all the time and I&apos;ve never had any problem with crashing apps or hanging downl ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TKDbilly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>2 Weeks New</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve only had the Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 with 32gb for 2 weeks so still accessing the longer term impressions. First impressions are as follows:
PRO:
- ergonomics: thin, light yet still large enough for video, email, gaming; this is a beautiful thing; better than 10.1 sized devices
- I think I like honeycomb but anxiously awaiting ver. 3.2
- still responsive after loading an additional 13 games, tools, utilities including Netflix, destroy gunner and bar code scanner; nothing major

CON:
- off button too close to volume control on top left
- speakers on bottom edge so you either cover them up if resting on that edge or if you turn it over, you potentially turn off the device or change volume
- proprietary charge plug that requires bulky USB adaptor

Quick as ... sessment more to come.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gmoshe27</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet, perfect carrying size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: super light compared to other tablets

Cons: I do have gripes, but they are small compared to how much I like the tablet

I bought this tablet the day it came out. I was going back and forth between and iPad 2 and the Galaxy Tab 8.9. I have an Android phone so the obvious sharing of apps from the marketplace was a big draw for me. I had access to a first gen iPad for work in my last job and I liked it, but in the end I knew it would be a split experience (especially for google apps).

I&apos;ll get to the chase. What I knew and still feel, the iPad is the premier tablet for premium content. Netflix was only available on the iPad and select Android phones, but not tablets (when I bought it). It&apos;s available now and works very well! I have a Wired Magazine subscription and ... free access to the extras on the iPad app...if I had an iPad. I also read the Economist which has an iPod/iPad/Android app, but that app isn&apos;t available yet for Android tablets. It seems like the big publishers have Android in their sights, but not immediately. There are also a lot of great apps available for the iPad that are starting to make their way over to the Android tablet platform (Honeycomb).

Since I purchased the tablet in early October, I noticed a number of new apps showing up in the marketplace that really make the device shine. A few of my favorites so far are: Swype Keyboard, Pulse, News 360, Netflix, Ted Air, Comixology, Words With Friends, Clouds &amp; Sheep (for the munchkin), Skype (for video chat!), Gmail, the stock Browser, all the Amazon apps (kindle, mp3, store, etc...) and Verizon&apos;s Fios Remote.

Verizon and Amazon both have a very good Android roadmap, but something that still irks me is that Amazon&apos;s app store doesn&apos;t work well in Honeycomb. It has trouble registering selections after scrolling through the available apps. The fios app had a similar issue which was fixed with an update.

As for the device. It has a great screen, a really nice footprint and like all Samsung devices, is remarkably light and thin. When it shows its &quot;A&quot; game, it&apos;s really fast. Although live wallpapers and background process ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SAL001</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and weight - given that it&apos;s the same spec as 10.1&quot;

Cons: Price - however, don&apos;t have to carry Amazon + B&amp;N readers

Since last year, I&apos;ve been stuck between the iPad, which is too big and heavy, and 7 inch devices (Android 2.2, usually), which are too small. The Samsung 10.1 almost had me at hello, but it too was just a tad heavy and large for one-handed reading. While the Asus Eee Transformer seemed like a compromise (the keyboard-dock bears the weight), I realized it would be too much to carry, so I&apos;d be better off carrying a cheaper netbook.

Samsung has hit a home-run with the 8.9&quot;. My primary needs are to be able to read books (Technical PDFs from Cisco and Juniper; Amazon Kindle App; B&amp;N Nook App), browse the web, update appointments and tasks, ... read news and follow up on email. Watching videos is not of concern to me. The best part of this form-factor is that my thumbs can meet in the middle of the keyboard while in landscape, making typing a breeze. It has several additional keyboards built-in, such as Samsung&apos;s and Swype, and Swype allows you to shrink it to one side such that you can hold the tablet in one hand while Swyping with the other across a smaller area.

After charging it for the first time, I toyed with it continuously for about 9 hours, tweaking, setting up my apps and accounts, browsing, opening PDF&apos;s, playing cloud-music, watching YouTube videos and movie-trailers, etc. Then I woke up and played with it for another 2.5 hours before it shut down on me (I purposely ignored all warnings to see how long it would last).

I know that many people are concerned about the lack of a SD-card and USB port, but that depends on what you&apos;re going to do with it. If you intend to use SD to transfer files (where the SD card is temporary), either use DropBox wirelessly over-the-air, or get the SD adapter for $30 (or get the USB adapter for $20 and use your own media-reader). I happen to use DropBox for transferring files and I uploaded my entire MP3 collection to Google&apos;s servers so I can use Google&apos;s Music app to listen in the cloud without using any space on the unit.

If yo ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lafina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love my tablet, I dont even use my phone anymore. This is a great tablet to have. I love it so much &amp; videos, pictures &amp; apps are also great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Casey4132</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung Galaxy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This tablet is excellent and very easy to use. Great speed and many free applications. Would recommend this tablet to everyone!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nestyco</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good offer.

I bought it as a gift to my boyfriend and he is very happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ghas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>it is better than my laptop camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very easy to set up

Cons: need to recharge the battery every time I use it

overall it is good product but the accessories not available as should be</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MB6271</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice size and nice features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Exactly what I was looking for. Not too big and not too small. Not many other tablet options in this size. The price was nice, too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joyax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Question</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Can anyone tell me if this model has HDMI slot? Thanks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mzkoko11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great apps,easy to download</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy setup...fun apps

Samsung tablet is great!!!! I love it! Helps to reduce my stress and just fun to use when I have some down time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jneg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Galaxy tab 8.9</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Better then expected. Does everything it should. I like it better then my wifes ipad2</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Yuriys45</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality

Cons: Adapter

Good. Only one problem: need special Samsung adapter.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Reallyrotten</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love product, buy from Amazon!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It fits in my purse!

Love my Galaxy Tab, wish I would have waited 3 weeks for the price drop at Best Buy!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tabletperson</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Got this a few weeks ago and absolutely love it! I went in for an Ipad but decided on this and have no regrets at all! Going to get another one for my son!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>swmn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderfully Gift</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this as a gift and it was very well received.
Has been enjoyed since.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doron</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I like this product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Excellent technology, greate apps &amp; web browsing</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spenny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Tab.... But!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>The Samsung software that runs with Android makes the OS seem very Laggy. Also the lack of expandable memory makes this Tab less appealing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pizzle22</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Everything I was looking for in a tablet. Size is perfect, not too small not too big.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Tab 8.9 WiFi 16 GB - Metallic gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/17865318765265902238/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved0CMEBEPQCMAI4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The apps are great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The galaxy tab is great for school.It also great for music.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

