<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer></Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy></ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Quizo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, responsive screen with and without S-Pen, great features, great Samsung integration, awesome battery life

Cons: lack of accessories, price, dedicated charging port

I bought this tablet the day it came out. I had been considering the Galaxy Tab 2 for a while but went for the Note because I liked the S-Pen features.
The price was a bit high, I spent $100 more than I would have on the Tab, but I definitely think it&apos;s worth it for the S-Pen, as well as the faster processor.

PROs:

I love that this tablet has a micro SD slot. Too often with tablets do you see no expandable memory.
The screen is beautiful, it&apos;s not as high res as the new iPad, but I honestly don&apos;t think you can tell. The screen is too small for that to matter.
The S-Pen inte ... gration is amazing. I can write and it translates my handwriting into text. It also does algorithms, and it&apos;s easy to incorporate images into your work. S Note is a great app, I use it all the time at work to jot down notes.
I use the Galaxy S3 as my cell phone and the integration with my tablet is prime. Using my Samsung and Google accounts, I am able to transfer almost anything effortlessly. With the purchase of this tablet, you are also able to get 50GB of DropBox storage for free.
The battery life on this tablet is much better than any tablet I&apos;ve seen. It lasts me a full day with heavy use, I&apos;ve never had it drop below 50% battery before plugging it in at night.

CONs:

The charging port is not the universal micro USB, I would much rather a universal charging port than the dedicated design for this tablet. I have to but an extra charger if I want to plug it in at work. This is where the extra battery life comes in handy.
The casing is made of plastic. I don&apos;t mind it much because it makes for a lighter tablet and it has a better design than other tablets, but I can definitely see how that could make some people cringe. It has a cheap feel to it.
It is very difficult to find accessories for this tablet, the fact that it is a few millimeters bigger than the Tab and the S-Pen slot is right on the corner make using Tab accessories impossible. I ended up going with a universal case just for trav ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>silvermemeber</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice try</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: like the IR blaster, SD slot and great battery

Cons: screen quality and price

At the $500 price level there are many tablets out there. I chose the note because I love the IR blaster and the peel software (although why can&apos;t you figure out how to include the ability to record from dish I still don&apos;t know) which is such a nice feature, and because I have 6 other samsung devices. However I have had issues getting the Kies software to work correctly. This tablet falls short though. This is really about a $350 tablet. the screen at 1280 x 800 is much lower res than the ipad and asus infinity at 1980 x 1280, but it is bright. The S-pen is a nice feature but the software execution is awful so it really doesn&apos;t live up to the hype and very few programs take advantage of it whi ... ch needs to be programed in for each one. Only a single app uses the palm ignore option but they don&apos;t tell you that before you buy. Thing is fast and benchmarks well and does demanding applications without a jitter but the touchwiz overlay makes everything feel slow and mushy. The battery goes on for hours which is good because the only cord they give you is only 3 feet long. For this price they could have given you a 6 footer. And like the tabs they use a proprietary connector instead of the common USB mini every has laying around. The speakers are loud and pointed right at you. This has an SD card slot which I can&apos;t imagine living without, and some great tablets lack. This still hasn&apos;t been upgraded to Jelly Bean yet and I think that is a huge mistake for samsung. The case feels and looks cheap. One thing I can&apos;t understand is this doesn&apos;t support NFC? This was huge with Samsung this summer and now the flagship tablet doesn&apos;t support it? I was hoping to beam things from my other 5 galaxy phones, but not with the note. Wait for the price to come down on this or get one of the better tablets at $500.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SinCityLV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for student or family</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: S Pen, screen quality, fast,micro sd card, good battery life,front facing speakers

Cons: no hdmi output

I am very impressed with this tablet. I bought this tablet to replace my laptop that died. I wanted portability but also more bang for my buck. I also thought Apple&apos;s ipad was far better than any Android tablet out there. I have to be honest, I love this tablet way more than the ipad. Now for me, thats a huge statement.

When i bought this tablet, i honestly thought i was going to return it because i wanted more bang for my buck in a laptop. Before i even opened it i told my wife i was most likely going to return it. I quickly changed my attitude after just a few minutes of using it. What a great product!

I didnt think i would like this tablet so much. It ... is perfect for me. I take it to work and do a lot of excel and word documents. I also receive a lot of documents that i have to sign and send back. The apps that work with the S pen are awesome. I use my tablet for everything work related. I love being able to sign documents and send them back. Great business and student tablet.

Screen quality is great. I watch a lot of youtube and movies. The quality is great!. People complain about the screen resolution not being high as the ipad. I enjoy the movies better on the tablet than on the ipad. My friends (ipad owners) also have to agree.

The S pen works out great for my young kids. They love to draw and use the coloring books.

There are so many features i love with this tablet that just makes it hard to live without. I would definately recommend this to even Apple fans.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rolmix</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>OK tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Was at Bestbuy store recently and tried both Galaxy Note 10.1
and ASUS Transformer Infinity. Of course, purchased ASUS right away. Quality, appearance and performance is way better than Samsung!
For the same price 499$ u get 32 GB, 1.6 Hz processor and 1GB Nvidia Tegra 3 Video, gorilla display, up to 9 hours battery and much more! Even better than iPad3!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nakk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Arguably the best tablet available today.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ipad smoothness without the Ipad&apos;s limitations. Fast. Great Speakers. Battery life.

Cons: SD card slot is a little too recessed.

I bought the Note 10.1 16GB, and I would return it in a heartbeat if it wasn&apos;t well worth the asking price. The thing is, it is. Even without the pen, it&apos;s hands down the best Android tablet out today. The screen isn&apos;t as high a resolution as some, that is true. However, the vast majority of people will never notice that; all they will notice is the beautiful, crisp and clear screen. If you have great eyes, are under 40, and like holding the tablet right up to your face to see the difference, sure you will see the smallest fonts are slightly pixelated. Other than that, this tablet just plain works. Simple, but true. Everything just plain works ... . No force closes, no hang ups, no problems with video or PDF rendering. Everything is quick and smooth. Just like an Ipad, without an Ipad&apos;s limitations. Performance wise, it&apos;s the fastest tablet available today, yes benchmarks and real world performance beats all comers, including the new Ipad.

It is true that many reviews are negative, not from real world users though. Trot on over to XDA-Developers and read user reviews. You know, the site where they REALLY know mobile devices. The acknowledged experts in the field. Everyone LOVES this device. Absolutely rave reviews from real world users. Why the E-zines don&apos;t like this device I don&apos;t know. Perhaps Samsung is not spending enough marketing dollars? If you understand the industry, you&apos;ll understand that if you don&apos;t pay enough in advertising, you don&apos;t get good reviews.

After a few days of owning the note, the things I really like about it are:
The touch screen. Very accurate and responsive input. It just plain works.

The screen. It&apos;s crisp, bright, clear and color accurate.

The speakers. Wow. Best speakers of any tablet or laptop I&apos;ve ever had. Easily usable and pleasurable for watching movies and listening to music in hotel rooms. (I travel a lot.) Given a choice between watching a movie on my wife&apos;s Ipad3 or my Note, the Note 10.1 wins hand down due to the superior sp ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SleepIT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet...errrr...Note!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Blazing fast, super smooth, accurate stylus

Cons: Shiny back cover

I&apos;ve had mine for a week now and love it. Browsing the web is super-fast, just like using a PC. The stylus adds a TON of value...I can now effectively manage servers using Remote Desktop (I use the Ericom Access-to-go app). On other tablets this was very frustrating because the Windows user interface was not built for touch use. With the Note&apos;s accuracy this is no longer a problem. The included Photoshop Touch app is very powerful and is great for retouching photos. I&apos;ve also noticed a marked improvement playing the Draw Something game...the lines are drawn exactly where I want them versus the &quot;finger method&quot; where it&apos;s hit-and-miss. Did I mention how fast this tablet is? It has the same Cortex A9 proces ... sor as the new iPad...only with DOUBLE the processing cores. This thing waits for nothing! The sound is very impressive...it has great volume and depth. I&apos;m very happy that FINALLY a decent tablet has FRONT FACING speakers (hello, my ears are in front of the tablet when I&apos;m using it, not behind it!). The cameras work great...I&apos;m especially happy with the front-facing camera...it has great quality and sends a great picture when Skyping. I&apos;m not a fan of the shiny plastic used for the back...the tablet looks very professional and well-built from the front, then you turn it over and it&apos;s an acre of shiny plastic. I can&apos;t wait to get a case for it to cover it up. Yesterday my girlfriend commented that she is wanting one of these to replace her iPad2 after seeing me use it this past week. I can&apos;t speak to it better than that!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SS7878</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Tramples the Ipad ( I own both)</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fluid OS, Floating Apps (web and video), Great Sound, Web Video, Stable OS

Cons: 7 to 8 Hour Battery Life

I’m a fan of apple, and a fan of android. What I didn&apos;t like about previous android tablets (and I’ve had a few) is that they were slow, unstable, choppy, web video was horrible. This tablet however is spectacular. Fluid in everything that you do (browsing, web video). My favorite apps (that apple doesn&apos;t offer) are floating apps. I can play a youtube or any other type of video and have float around the screen while I surf the web or check e-mail. Imagine an “Always on top” function….with both a video player and/or a browser…..spectacular. Battery life is about 7 hours…maybe a little more.
The resolution of the screen is great. Not as good as the Ipad 3, but grea ... t. I would say comparable with the Ipad 2. Typing is easier on the ipad because of the size, but the keyboard on this tablet is re sizable in 3 different way…makes it very functional. As far as apps and comparing the functionality of this to an Ipad…this tablet blows the ipad out of the water. Can’t say enough about it.

To be honest, I don’t use the S Pen features….really bought this to be more for e-mail / entertainment / web browsing…if the S Pen is your thing, then this is your tablet.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Analyst003</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet for note taking</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful Android, lets you hand-write notes and open up apps side by side.

Cons: Price

I was looking for a tablet that I could use mainly for taking notes. I&apos;ve owned this tablet now for about a month and it has as exceeded my expectations. I can rest my hand on the screen while taking notes without a problem. It&apos;s powerful and fast (have not noticed any lag in performance). It is expensive for a tablet, but if you are looking for a tablet that lets you take notes and open up two applications side by side, there is no better product out there -- this is the tablet for you.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KebbBH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet Ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Super Fast, Works like a Champ!

Cons: nothing So far

I have had this tablet for awhile now, pretty much since its release and I have loved every minute I have been able to spend with it. Do not believe the horrible reviews that have been filtering around the web. I read some reviews, watched some videos and I was not going to bother messing with this tablet.

Then I saw some benchmarks for it and my friend ended up getting one to try out. We messed with his for a couple days and everything we threw at it, the Samsung Galaxy note10.1 cruised through it and was ready for more. HD videos, HD games, Netflix, cruising the web, etc. The look and feel of it is smooth and sleek and it is very sturdy. So I do not know what the critics are crying about. I am guessing since ... it does not have a big apple on it, they are just going to hate it.

Truthfully, Samsung outdid themselves. The android sytem on this tablet works amazing and is pretty much flawless. Jelly Bean is also coming very soon and that is another big plus. The front mounted speakers are loud and sound fantastic. The screen is not HD, but Samsung did something because everything is crisp and all the colors just pop out at you. I am very, very impressed with the Samsung Galaxy note 10.1. If you are looking for a tablet that will make all your friends and family jealous (especially the ipad fanboys) purchase this tablet, you will not regret it.

P.S- I WROTE this entire review on the tablet...did not type, WROTE...
with the cool pin that comes with the tablet, pretty awesome!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dtabor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very user specific tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Front facing speakers, Home entertainment system integration, very responsive stylus

Cons: Screen quality, feels cheap

I own an Ipad 2 and a new Ipad aka Ipad 3. These tablets are great but as an artist i wanted a better stylus/tablet experience. When i heard Wacom supplied the stylus technology to the Note 10.1 i was excited. I did not have a problem with response time when switching between stylus and finger like some people had. The stylus using the app Sketchpad was a great experience. I had to end up returning it and getting an ipad because of lack of screen clarity. It always looked blurry to me, i guess i was spoiled for the Ipad retina display. The feel of the Note 10.1 is very cheap. It flexes and somewhat bends when you are holding it. I also find the internet ... speed is not as fast as my S3 or my Ipads. Since Best Buy has a 30 day return policy, feel free to give it a try. I still recommend the Ipad over all.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Refreshmentsdirect</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice and smooth</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Samsung Android ICS/Stylus

Cons: Fit and finish plastic feels flimsy

Was in the market for a new Tablet, my ipad 1 still works flawlessly but i wanted to try a droid tablet. Got it was pleasantly surprised with the Samsung android integration. I recently moved from a iphone 4s to a HTC x 1 (only for 2 days hated the feeling) It seems Samsung does a better job of using Ice cream sandwich.
Its pretty fast with most applications surfing the net is a breeze all the bells and whistles work as advertised. Have not had any apps crash yet, battery life is exceptional. Front facing speakers are Great!!!
unfortunately the plastic feels a bit flimsy and it flexes when you hold it a little bit, I&apos;m not certain this will last 3 years (like my ipad 1) but I could not bring my s ... elf to buy another ipad ....
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>vocalscpunk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for students</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use, setup, and navigating

Cons: Small stylus

I love this tablet, after getting an Ipad as a gift I tried to use it in class for a few weeks to takes notes on (ppt, pdf, etc.) but the &apos;stylus&apos; for the ipad just wasn&apos;t cutting it - my notes took over the document. I researched high and low and finally settled on the Note. The Note&apos;s stylus makes taking notes simple and easy, the features are awesome and since I have an android phone and google account(s) everything syncs back and forth so if I forget my phone my calendar still reminds me or if I forget to bring my tablet to class I still have access to the document (free online cloud space). All in all I would definitely recommend this to any student who is looking to take notes. There are plenty of apps on googl ... e play and amazon to rival any apple app you think you can&apos;t live without. Also plus the speakers are on the FRONT of the tablet (don&apos;t know why some companies put them on the back) and the sound is legit. Battery life thus far has been anywhere from 3 to 5 days depending on use.

The only issues I have stumbled across as of yet are lack of places to buy accessories/cases (slowly coming out - amazon is starting to host third party companies&apos; products) and the small size of the stylus. For people with large/clumbsy fingers the pen will feel ALMOST too light and too small to use, almost but its not like trying to write with a toothpick. Fortunately they do sell a larger pen (think &apos;pharmaceutical company&apos; oversized with a decent grip) that I plan on getting as soon as I can.

I hope this helps and I would definitely (and have definitely) recommended this tablet to anyone on the fence about what to get for a tablet (this still won&apos;t replace a laptop in my opinion but it is very close to making me &apos;forget&apos; my laptop at home some days).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mustanggtguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>one of the best android tablets on the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: fast,sd card slot, front facing stereo speakers, s-pen, light, thin.

Cons: could use a better screen resolution, but still looks great.

I really enjoy using this tablet very much, i have had an ipad, and motorola xoom. The front facing speakers are so nice since u don&apos;t have to blast it to hear movies, videos or music. The overall look of the tablet i find is very light, clean, and easy to hold. The s-pen is very cool, i can jot down notes very fast. This tablet runs very smooth, fast with ICS, i cant wait for jelly bean, this should run nice with the upgrade as it really made a difference on my xoom.. overall i do not regret in anyway purchasing this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OlegVorkunov</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>S-Note is not up to speed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light, Battery

Cons: S-Note application slow

This tablet is very good for regular tablet functionality, but s-pen addition suppose to make it very attractive. I hoped for S-note application shape recognition to be very useful in drawing diagrams, but it is not. After 3-4 squares, s-note freezing and not drawing anymore. If shape is not recognized, for example, connection arrow between shapes, is not drawn at all. S-Note is good just for plain handwriting, but not recognition. I am still going to keep it and not return for now, because at least I have a digitized pen with very good palm rejection to make notes. I hope, that Samsung is going to fix it. Also S-Note does not have landscape mode, and when tablet is rotated in landscape, &quot;drawing&quot; page rotates back to portrai ... t. Hope Samsung will add more templates to S-Note with bigger page size, not only A4, but up to A1. If you are not looking for s-pen, or it is not your primary function for the tablet, go with another brand, which has much better resolution. Screen resolution is very poor while reading web sites with small font. You would be able to see pixels, and it is going to be hard to read.

This is a second day, I am using this tablet, and battery at 60%. Very good.

Response is not what I would hoped for. Sometimes I have to hit back soft button several times, before it responses, and of course I am back several times I clicked. I do not think this is a Samsung fault. This is Google Android fault, because button is processed in a single thread, instead of separate thread to make screen react much quicker. And if there is a lot of code running during back button press, device will respond poorly.

Printing is hardwired only to Samsung printers. Hello??? There is a cloud printing from Google. At least try to incorporate it.

S-Pen location is wrong. If you dock this tablet, s-pen is not accessible. Should&apos;ve been on the top or bottom right side and not on the button of the tablet.

Computer USB will not be able to charge it. Only wall adapter capable to ch ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mouyo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very responsive, easy to navigate, good battery life, S-Pen is nice for drawing and handwriting.

Cons: need to side load adobe flash and a little pricy comparing to other tablets

Comes with a good set of productivity software too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lorrain</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far I am Loving it :)</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: S Pen, 2GB Ram, Expandable Memory

Cons: Screen Resolution

So far I have had my Note for 4 days. And so far so good. I love the S Pen, note taking and multitaking capabilities. The sreen size is great. I also love that the speakers are facing you and not at the back. I also have an iPad but it is not capable of taking my note as the Note does, I primarily use my Note for taking notes, reading my emails, sketching etc. My number one thing is I love that I can customize (Android) my tablet with out having to Root it like you would need to with an apple product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tsnajera</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Android Tablet yet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quad core Processor, 2 GB RAM, Front facing speakers, S pen, S pen applications and more!

Cons: Resolution, two tone color look

As the title states, I believe that this is the best Android tablet yet and here is why:

It&apos;s Quad-core Exynos processor flies past the competition. Also with 2 GBs of RAM, you can run multiple applications lag free. The front facing speakers are a genius idea that should become the new norm amongst tablets and phones. As a computer engineering student, I take a lot of notes for my different classes. But that means having to carry around various notebooks and textbooks to each class. With this tablet I can store my books via Kno (which this is the first android tablet to have it) and I can take notes with my S pen. I know that you can st ... ore books on other tablets without Kno, but I like the interface a lot better. I also know that you can take notes on other tablets through applications found on the play store, but this tablet is specifically optimized to work with the S Pen. Writing on this tablet is almost as accurate as writing on a piece of paper. It also has a formula matcher that looks up the solution to whatever math equation you right. There are many other applications like PS touch, which is a photo shop application that allows you to edit pictures.

cons:

Like most people complain about, the resolution is very low compared to what ASUS, ACER and APPLE have brought to the table. But to me all of what I just mentioned totally overcomes screen resolution. HD movies still look beautiful on this screen and it is still very responsive when writing or web surfing. I also don&apos;t like the two toned color look. How the deep gray has a silver border. But I presume they did that because APPLE would probably cry about it.

bottom line:

If you are looking for a tablet that you can seamlessly write on, then this is for you. It does a better job than both the IPAD and any other android tablet. The S Pen is a genius idea and I hope to see more innovation in that direction.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RKWerchan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I wish I knew more about Android!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Smooth operation, fast, very good picture despite lower resolution, upgradable with microSD, great sound

Cons: Android OS not as user friendly as iPad, lack of accessories (no cases at Best Buy, yet!)

I must admit, I&apos;m an Apple guy. I bought the 10.1 to see what all the Android hype was about. Still not sure if I&apos;m going to keep it or not. What I will say, though, is that I&apos;m extremely surprised at how well this tablet runs. Everything is very smooth, and all programs open up very quickly. It feels much lighter than my iPad, but I don&apos;t really get the &quot;cheap&quot; feeling others have spoken of. The picture really surprised me, as I was expecting much less due to the resolution. The speakers are great, too! Better than the iPad. I&apos;m sure they&apos;ll put the better screen on the n ... ext model, but then I&apos;m also sure that would drive the price up. All in all, I&apos;m very pleased and think I picked the right product to learn Android with. I recommend that you should atleast give it a try!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>G60coupe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great features, great quality, class of its own</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: s pen!!!

Cons: casing a bit cheap

simply wonderful unit! great quality, and unique!
The battery life could be better but still nothing to complain about!
The S pen use &amp; user feed back set this tablet in a class of its own!
The only two issue I have is the casing feels a bit flimsy, front side is great but the back side has a bit of flex to it and the coatings used the casing really makes every finger print show.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Le1901</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great tablet, look nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice with front stereo speakers. Except the display, everything inside is the best at this time.

Cons: $500 tablet with a cheap display (not the size). Many less expensive have better screen than this &quot;Samsung&quot;

First, I want you to know that I have the top model iPad 3 (The new iPad) 64Gb with Att LTE. Many time I was trying to return this tablet to Best Buy, because I have no used to it, BUT I DID NOT. This is a beautiful baby with quad core processors, and quad graphic, S-pen, latest Android, fast, 2 front speakers, attachable pen etc.... Every time, when I am trying to put it back to the box for returnig, holding the tablet on hand make me change my mind. I am keeping it.
Great built in white, front camera, rear camera with flash, Auto focus, and this tablet could ... even replace your home theater remote with built in IR. I don&apos;t want to say anymore about its feature because I think you already know. The most important and the key is this &quot;Samsung galaxy note 10.1&quot; could play ADOBE FLASH PLAYER VIDEOs.
If you want an Android tablet. You can not go wrong with this one.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Raul Tellez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excelente tableta</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Indeed there is a significant difference with the other tablet on the market. This has great connectivity thanks to its expansion possibilities via sd memory card or usb. The primary camera flash is excellent and the sharpness of the photos too, not to mention the videos. An important thing is the polaris oficce that comes preloaded and allows you to create and edit Word, Excel and Power Point. The retractable pen is a great tool and I am using it in MBA classes so do not hesitate to buy it, you will not regret</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jimbo2236</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awful</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast

Cons: Everything

Got it withouth reading the reviews and returned it after 5 days. My wife was watching Netflix on the first ipad and and I was watching it on the note 10.1 and the difference was night and day, the quality of the video on the iPad 1 was far far better. It is quick but feels cheap, the s pen feels and looks like it came with a happy meal. I really wanted the note 10.1 and was excited about getting it as I have the note phone and love it but the note10.1 is the perfect example of a great idea gone wrong. I would recomend you give it a proper try out if your thinking of buying it because the s pen will suit some people and I do like the look of it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kellyehk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very Fast, Clean Graphics, Flash Player works

Also have Galaxy Tab 10.1. This 3rd gen Tab is amazing.
Blazingly fast, nie graphics, Flash player installs and works and Pen works great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>analog2pixels</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Under Rated - Fantastic</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wacom Pen, Remote for TV and DirectV

Cons: Cant find anything not so great

Once again, Samsung for me personally, has done a great job with this Tablet. I originally had a ASUS Transformer with Keyboard. And although I really liked the tablet, it really doesnt have that certain appeal for me.
I really wanted a tablet that was as good as the ASUS, but with a Wacom Pen. And I have had a Galaxy S2, I currently have a Galaxy NEXUS, and the Galaxy S. And just bought two samsung UltraBooks. Im basically helping Samsung pay off the lawsuit with the patent trolls at APPLE. And before you say that thing you were thinking, I own three IMACS, MacPRO and I use to own an IPHONE 3GS. All apple products are in my opinion, over rated and over touted.
Now, this Tablet, compared to ... my previous ASUS tablet simply is everything is better. Im in Visual Effects, and I wanted and waited for a tablet with a Wacom Pen, so I could use it for notes and or communication from onset or notes to remote artist. With PS and other pen software, this tablet fills the gap that I have been looking for.
The additional software that Samsung has created, such as the Remote Control/TV Guide, is awesome. Basically, you set it up for your TV&apos;s all through the house, and your cable box, I have Directv, and within seconds, I was browsing what was on TV on my tablet, choose the show you want to watch, and then say watch, and your tv turns to that channel. You can even set to record.

Everything you need in a tablet. Is there. The tablet is built very well. Im not sure what the hell other reviewers on the web and here, are reviewing or even had this in there hands, but the build and quality is very well done. Top Quality.

I love that the speakers are in the front. Thats a good design feature.
The Pen, how does it work. Flawless. I have used Wacoms since they were introduced. And this is without a doubt a really nice feel and touch and pressure sensitivity.

I really bought this from Best Buy in Huntington WV. With the plan to return it, because I had heard some so so reviews. Im not r ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mj23chifan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Even better than expected...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been waiting for this device since its &quot;teased&quot; debut back in February &apos;12. Six months later, I finally have my hands on one (literally, as I type this) and I&apos;m not disappointed in any way. It&apos;s fast, smooth, the pen is amazingly accurate for note taking and drawing, and despite its &quot;lower resolution&quot; compared to some new tablets, the screen is amazing. I&apos;d rather have the dual-core processor crunching my input, than being eaten up just to make the screen resolution &quot;better&quot;. Unless you hold it an inch from your face (and why would you do that?!), it looks amazing. The ONLY thing I wish was better is the hand-writing-to-text feature... it&apos;s not 100% accurate, at least not with MY hand-writing. Overall, Apple fanboys can keep their iPads... I&apos;m MORE than happy with my Note 10.1. Way ... to go, Samsung... and THANK YOU for making me one very happy customer!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechnoINFLUENCE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW Talk About Innovations!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing ability to Multi-tasking vice Versa iPAD

Cons: Nothing that i can think of?

Seriously, ive read all these reviews on this new tablet and it sounds like the reviewers have some past issues. I don&apos;t mean the users who use the Table later on but... OK! BacK to the review: i am a current Samsung note owner and i love the device when i first used it. -Simplicity combined with functionality- the features of this device think, from my opinion, exceed the apple&apos;s ipad ! Features like: Multiscreen, stylus, built-in Remote, Simple organization system compares or apple&apos;s, exclusive gadgets, Photoshop software, etc really out done itself and its competitors. Besides from affordability, its funtions is also business and educationally inpired.

Last of all: this is the ... : &quot;BANG for your Buck&quot; if you ask me :]
Updated with the latest and greatest software and gears,
i think it earns its renouncement of technologically innovation status.
[ for its price price].

I can go on and on about its spec. but its up to you to decide rather its good enough for your usage or not.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nurseturnedstudent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not For Me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Thin, light, easy to use

Cons: Cannot perform the most basic function...no Adobe flash drive

I owned one of these for about 6 hours. Easy set up. Already own a Samsung Smart TV...so I was excited. Watched the tutorials. Beautiful...until I tried to get on a website for a school assignment. Needed an Adobe download....because of the problem between Apple and Samsung...not able to download after August 15th. I am not a techie, and this was the primary reason for purchase. Returned it immediately. To Best Buy&apos;s credit, they refunded the entire amount, even for the screensaver and installation. Tried my son&apos;s IPad with the same result. After I read reviews on other tablets, I will return to purchase at Best Buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GT500guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent tablet! impressive!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything so far! very fast and stylus is excellent for artsy people like myself!

Cons: That they don&apos;t have alot of accessories out for it yet lol!

This is my first tablet, I was very skeptical about purchasing it and well.. laying down $500 plus tax. You do get a 30 day money back &quot;no questions asked&quot; if you don&apos;t like it so you have nothing to lose when in the market for a new tablet. I&apos;d also like to throw in that I hate when they have employees working that know absolutely nothing about their products! Anyways, the tablet is very nice, got the white one and after a few days of use I love it. The battery life is very good and the tablet is very fast, for example the internet is faster on the tablet than my laptop or my desktop that have wired connections! The stylu ... s pen is my favorite thing about this tablet, if you are an artsy individual and love to draw..you&apos;ll love this thing and did i mention the photoshop already built in! SWEET! As far as I can see I&apos;ll be keeping this thing and very happy about my purchase. Now they just need to hurry the heck up and release some accessories for this thing. Hope this review helps!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bjdog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great tablet for anyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: beatifull screen, very fast touch &amp; pen very good

Cons: nothing everything great

Love this tablet. Very fast and responsive touch. Pen is excellant. Speakers sound great, being in front of tablet you can tell their stereo. Movies and music sound great. Would hightly recommend to anyone wanting a tablet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bakka</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung&apos;s new premier poorly built low res tab</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: CPU is super fast, plenty of memory

Cons: Flagship product with a low res screen and flaky case

I can forgive the not so sturdy build if the screen wasn&apos;t so underwhelming. The good news is this is one of the very few Android tabs that really does work almost as well as an iPad.
At the same price as an Acer a700 with half the memory and much lower resolution, this just can&apos;t be an option. At 349 sure, but not 500.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>princessgravez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Advanced tablet, easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: So many features to explore

Cons: Available protective cases

I origionally had an ipad but became disappointed with the functionality. While returning it, I came across the Note. I was immediately impressed with the features and functionality. I absolutly love the Android based program and setup. You will not be disappointed with your purchase...I still own and use an iphone but the Galaxy Note is the way to go for a tablet! I&apos;ll admit that there are many aspects to the Note that I have yet to learn...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kcml1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sammy tablet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Trying to get my wireless printer to print from the tablet.

So far so good. Learning all the functions and capabilities takes time.
These tablets are way to expensive for what they do.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wally2424</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the screen and picture quality is excellent

Cons: the ps touch tutorial is hard to understand and not very clear....and hard to operate

I have a ipad and i never use it, i always go to my galaxy note, the picture and video quality is excellent, the only downfall is the tutorial on the ps touch is hard to follow. But i would recommend this product. Enjoy it everyday</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>yomomma2501</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The S pen rocks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is great for taking notes

Cons: Needs an option for turning off the notification bar while using S note.

This tablet blows my Motorola Xoom out of the water, Ice cream sandwich runs better on the Galaxy note than the Xoom. I have to say my favorite thing about the note is the S pen. this thing is great for taking lecture notes. The handwriting recognitiion works perfect, this thing will even make my chicken scratch look good. The other thing I like is the app Kies Air, you can use this with a mac or pc to transfer music and other files wirelessly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>livingincr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stylus is what this tablet is all about</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Can take hand written notes, pressure sensitivity for drawing

Cons: Best buy needs different options for cases &amp; screen protectors

Love this tablet, the apps are getting better and better for journals, and drawing. Many of the android apps are adding in the s pen support which helps a lot. If you get one of these I highly recommend getting a case and anti-glare screen protector. The case for obvious reasons, the anti glare protector because I personally hate the mirror effect and it gives writing a more natural feeling. Get sketchbook pro for drawing, best one I&apos;ve found, so far. S Note is still one of the better apps for notes/journals, but try some of the popular ones, S Note just takes a little time to figure out, once you get it, it&apos;s great.

Negatives, wi ... ll only print with a Samsung Printer unless you use different services like google cloud print. The s pen is not always perfect, there&apos;s a very small contact point that takes a little time to get perfected.

Long story short, I have not been happier with a tablet. I have owned the Motorola Xoom, HTC Flyer, Nook, Fire, this is by far my favorite. Its a journal, unlimited canvas, ereader, complete entertainment system all in your hand.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>simplymarv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really diggin` my note tab10.1</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great features, good set up, great feel 2 it

Cons: pen features, price, nfc functionality

I have the original galaxy note so, It was only right 2 get BIG brother. My expectation of this version of the note series was very high. Glad to say that most of it was met. Some great features I feel make it quite the tablet especially, since its the only 1 on the market that really uses the stylus(S pen). Quad core processor is a work of art, multiscreen function is a great feature to use, it takes no time at all to setup, love the screen display, &amp; The IR sensor is a great touch. Now, the faults. I still gave a good rating Though. A bit pricey to not have a 4g LTE set up installed in it. Probably should have been $50-$75 less. I also don&apos;t like the fact that their&apos;s no writ ... ing pad 4 the S pen when writing emails, im&apos;s, texts, etc. What happen to the NFC capability? I thought i would be able to send info from my phone to the tab by just bumping them together. I hope when a new update comes Out this issue is fixed amongst others. Their are other pros and cons 2 it but specifically i focused on these cause their what matter 2 me. I still say its a great tab compared 2 others on the market. I believe it has the ability to be the best with the right updates and next gen modifications.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nicktechnomasta</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>amazing device for anyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i bought this for classes since im a college student and it has been nothing but amazing. it comes with every office program needed which save around 100 dollars in app downloads and it also makes working on the go a breeze. ipad cant touch this tab at all!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>uma</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>the best gadget i used</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use my samsung galaxy note in the university classes to teach students. It lets me to save a lot of paper i used before. It is very good that gadget has office and book readers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nervad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Tab with great hardware and features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Of course the S-Pen, plus amazing battery life

Cons: For me nothing

I must say I love this thing, the S-pen is flawless, the battery life is amazing, quad core performance and the features this tablet comes with is nothing short of great. The adobe photo touch is a great feature on this, if there was anything to complain about, it would be that it did not come with android latest software jellybean but I hear it will be getting an update soon :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VonSazi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet by far with the most features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features and flexibility

I&apos;ve used other Android tablets, the Kindle Fire, and IPads. This tablet works great, and has the best features for creating content. This tablet also has much more flexibility/customization options than the KF or IPad. It does take a little longer to learn how to use, but that is mostly due to the fact that there is more to it than these other devices--really that only means a little extra time here and there over the first couple of weeks of usage. After that you know where things are and how they work, and again, there&apos;s more that you can do than with other devices. The stylus works great for taking notes (much better than a finger), and the split screen function has definitely come in handy. I mostly use this for business purposes, but did test the ... drawing capabilities, and you can do some really cool detail work that would be impossible on other tablets. There are great built-in apps, and I haven&apos;t come across any app type that I wanted that can&apos;t be obtained.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best niche, great overall</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pen, power, battery, internet speed

Cons: Screen

While i admit the screen could be better, it is low res becuase of the Wacom support built in. the screen remains a low res because Wacom equipment cannot handle higher resolutions at that size. However, in everything else this one shines. give it a try, it is amazing. pen has no lag whatsoever.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RNR1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>potential ipad killer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have never seen any tablet match upto the Ipad, and I bought this device only after I received an assurance from 3 different people at bestbuy that i had 30 days to return it- no questions asked.

The screen resolution does not match up to the Ipad (but this is really not noticeable at this screen size- for serious movie buffs, wanting HD clarity you need to buy a 1080p 65+inch screen TV); I can only say that so far it has outperformed the Ipad in every other way possible.

Out of box setup and connectivity- no problems at all- like with all devices you need to create new accounts with samsung, and dropbox and many other things (new user IDS and passwords to remember), but once this is done, I dont think it asks you to sign into anything again and again (like the apple app st ... ore issue)

The Internet connection and page loading speed is almost as good as my Sony Vaio VPCSC1AFM (which In my comparison, while running Norton in the background, is faster than a macbook without antivirus program).

The Polaris office software is good, but again I doubt if anyone buys a tablet to do serious work on office productivity software. I hope Microsoft will bring out compatible software- there is a huge market out there to be captured.

The adobe reader platform on this is not great, but if you open PDFs using Kindle free software, it is great.

The Adobe PS is Outstanding- i think this software must be expensive- it is versatile for photo editing- I thought the tattoo option was really cool, but there doesnt seem to be a way to insert your own text in tattoo font.

I have had no printing issues- I use the iprint software with Brother 7860DW- ABSOLUTELY no problems- I do both wireless printing and WIRELESS SCANNING- very cool.

The TV remote option is fantastic- i can review all the programs on TWC and choose what I want to see from the device- it integrates seamlessly with my panasonic TV, panasonic Home theater and cable set top box.

The GPS option is very good- I tried it wh ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BradIT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have the iPad2 and am happy with the product but it felt that it was lacking in the processing power and multi-function capabilities.
I bought the Note 10.1 on the 10th and am very happy so far.
The multi-screen is helpful with taking notes and sending emails while surfing the web (planning a wedding). I was nervous when I read it had a stylus but now am floored of how easy and helpful it is with its functions. I have been in IT for over 6 years now and loving the functions I can do off-site with this device.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SLMARK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Its ok not all that</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: its a nice tablet

Cons: freehand writing is slow you have to wait like 4 seconds or more to see what you wrote

got because of the salesman hype. it was ok at first then tried the freehand and its slow as heck.... it freezes up and opening pages also slow sometimes..

not that good nor worth the 499.00 wait till it drops 100.00 bucks</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mbucks911</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>the fastest and most feature packed tab to date</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, fast, and lots of great features added over stock android

Cons: screen is just ok but better than expected, not many accessories YET

ive had the transformer prime and the transformer infinity and this tablet is much better than both, except for the infinity&apos;s screen. this tablet is very reliable and fast, and the features that samsung added are very useful, they are definitely not just gimmicks, and i love the stereo front facing speakers, so much better than the ipad&apos;s and the transformers, and i use the s-pen way more than i thought i would. all of these features make this a much more powerful and productive tablet than the iPad, while still being just as smooth thanks to its awesome gpu and samsungs famous exynos. the one shortcoming ive found is its acc ... essories, or lack of them. there are some good cases available, but not nearly as many choices as the ipad but thats to be expected with an android tab. i really wish there was some kind of keyboard/case for this tablet like there are so many for the ipad, but there are none, so i had to settle with carrying around the android logitech separate bluetooth keyboard, which is a small annoyance. since this is an international product and samsungs flagship tab for now there are sure to be more accessories in the near future
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MLCPA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Must have a Samsung printer to print!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: nice display

Cons: tough to get it to link to your networked devices

Was more then pleased with set up, processor speed, display was great. Also like the S pen even though the experts didn&apos;t&apos;. I Will be returning it!!! To print you must have a Samsung printer!! Who ever heard of that? Also linking to your other network devices is very tough to say the least.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>crazybuckeye5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Tablet!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This has been a great purchase so far. I actually use it for work purposes so i use the pen every day. So far i can&apos;t see any way how the ipad is better than this device.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>islandart</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Samsung created a winner!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: nothing

Samsung Galaxy note, Puts Apple I pad to shame! I am a business professional and a artist!! I have been dreaming about a pad like this! The apps are wonderful!! the split screen is great for those multitasks I love everything about it ,so much to explore. I purchased the 1st day it was available at best buy I cant put it down! Way to go Samsung!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ProfessorTech</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Tablet Yet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: S-Pen For Sure

Cons: Resolution

I have had this tablet for 2 days, but I have been an iPad user since its first version. I have tried every stylus that exists for the iPad to take notes and use for instruction in classes. None of them are great at all although they come close. I even tried the Lenovo tablet with the n-trig pen. None come close to this tablet. This tablet with the integrated pen meets the needs. I am able to take notes, edit documents, etc. as if I was using paper. I compared the resolution to the iPad 3 and couldn&apos;t see much difference even though technically they are different. The speed is great also and while it is plastic, it works even if not as high quality built as iPad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>steathware</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>amazing virtual notebook</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a big fan of taking notes on tablets, this tab errr! notepad well both, helps me keep all my notes from school in one place instead of having a whole load of books with me, coming from an iPad which was a hazzle to take notes with, to a tablet made just for that, I can even rest my palm on the screen ! I know people complain about not being retina display, this tablet still 720p tho, good enough but the best part is the pen .... I really feels like I have a paper and pencil with me, now when my classmates need to copy my notes I don&apos;t have to lend them my book I can just email them my notes straight from here nice tablet and amazing paper pencil feeling I can&apos;t believe it</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>skdev</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good tablet for use in business</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the pen/stylus, cpu speed, sd card slot

Cons: proprietary connector, lack of apps that take advantage of the pen

After using a crayon like stylus to write on an iPad, the stylus on this device was a welcome change. I can now write on this device as I would on a legal pad with a ball point pen. Being able to do this gets a solid thumbs up from me and was the key feature that made me decide to switch away from the iPad.

On the downside, the amount of software available to take advantage of the pen is a bit limited right now, but I beleive developers will bring out new stuff pretty quickly to take advantage of the pen.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Briwil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Digitizer!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Stylus/Digitizer! Light, thin.

Cons: Camera sucks, android-based, feels a little cheap

I&apos;m a life-long apple lover, going back to the orig Mac, and I can&apos;t believe I actually have an android tablet sitting here next to my ipad3... But as a designer, having a tablet with a real digitizer and stylus has been a long time coming. I still prefer the iPad for most things, but for creative application, the stylus is awesome. I was worried about reviews claiming the Note was sluggish, but I haven&apos;t seen anything to back that up. It does feel a little cheaper than the ipad physical, mostly because its entirely made of plastic vs the ipad which has aluminum and plastic. But on the flip side, it&apos;s thinner and lighter than the iPad. The camera kind of sucks, but I doubt I will use ... it much.
If you want a tablet for casual use, go with the iPad. If you are a designer or illustrator, consider this.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Arteesimo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good, but pen requires too much pressure</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, mobile, pressure sensitive

Cons: pen doesn&apos;t respond to light strokes very well

This is a great device. I love to draw on the go, so the pressure sensitive s pen is great for that. I just wish that I could draw lighter strokes, but the pen doesn&apos;t seem to pick up anything at the lightest touches. Definitely not a Cintiq, but it&apos;ll do for quick sketches.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cu2sr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not a good long-term investment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Still waiting on my update

I&apos;m writing this review because I have another Samsung tablet and I&apos;m still waiting for an update to the android OS. They&apos;ve never updated the firmware or OS since I bought it. That was TWO releases ago. Don&apos;t fall in the same trap. The device will be wonderful for awhile but unless you want to shell out another $500 for the latest, much improved OS a year from now, go with another vendor.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NYKenny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pen

Cons: Still need to improve Pen&apos;s response time

I&apos;m not using my old fashinoned notes and pen anymore...

I use this for meeting note / Remote in to my work computer / Emails / Books / Movies / other funs...

Pen is really awesome. It took me some time to get used to it, but works great!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Metskin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT TABLET</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price easy to use

Cons: nothing

Kicks ipads butt, why would anybody want an ipad over the Samsung Note</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Nothing

Love the Samsung 10.1 Tablet. The whole family is enjoying using it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Essy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I recommended this tablet 100%</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-unstarred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive Design; Durable

I use this tablet for my personal use. Everything is great about this tablet. I would recommened it 100%</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Isa303</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best tablet and I have gone through 4</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast, easy

I have gone through LG slate, Samsung 10.1 Tmobile, Samsung 2 10.1 and finally the Galaxy Note has made my life easier.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 WiFi 16 GB - Deep gray</Item>
     <URL>https://www.google.com/shopping/product/18037922351374011575/reviews?q=tablet&amp;hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf.&amp;fp=866a6645ee4f4ad7&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=582&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=qXuRUImMEsy_2QWDqoHICA.1351711657672.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=KoGRUPK1HYTXqgH6loBg&amp;ved=0CKICEPQCMAk4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>divide</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best 10 inch tablet with pen</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>
&lt;DIV class=rsw-stars-small title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;
&lt;DIV class=rsw-starred&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The tablet is fast with the 1.4GH CPU and 2GB RAM. I have been using it for a mounts and it never lacks it is just amazing mostly the vibrating mode.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

