<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>olcorral</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quality headphones regardless of price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality build. Great sound and inline control moudule. 5 star.

Cons: No negatives at all.

After two months of shopping, I chose the Image One headphones.
Simply put, they sound great, comfortable and attractive looking. Out of the box I was impressed with the case they come with for travel, the cord is strong and the build is quality. The inline control module for my iPad 2 works perfectly and easy to use with the large buttons. Volume, track and microphone all contained in a light weight easy to find module. Definite must for those who travel or don&apos;t want to want to pull out your music player to access.
The sound is superior. Crisp highs and solid low end and not sacrificing the mids at all. While they do not have the ear pounding bass, they do succeed with perf ... ect balance. Comfort is important and these are very much so. Lightweight, they can be worn for hours of movies or music.
You can spend untold amount of money for headphones for audiophile bank breaking sound. You won&apos;t need to for the Image One.
I found accessing the iPad equalizer made a huge difference with sound. One last thing: you don&apos;t have to crank them up to have the great sound quality that other sets I have owned needed. Great for all music types and movies.
Spend some time and listen to the really great sound and all your old playlists to rediscover your music once again. Also, give them some time to burn in. It does make a difference over time.
Wow, love these headphones.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MusicIsMySanctuary</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wish I Could Keep Them</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound/Clarity/Price/Power

Cons: Fit/Pain

I&apos;m an avid music lover. Living in city apartments/condos now, you have to have headphones (I do anyway or would probably be promptly evicted within a month#.
I can no longer wear those earbuds. Even the smallest fitting won&apos;t stay in my ears. I need those plug-in type earbuds or the bass and full effect of vs. those type that just kind of &quot;sit&quot; in your ear. Maybe it&apos;s because I use them so much #for years# but my left ear started swelling and hurting - like there&apos;s a callous in there or something.. Months later, same in the right. I see more and more people ditching those in Chicago and using these smaller type &quot;real&quot; headphones.

While out of town, I noticed the headphone display at Best Buy. Checked these out and KNEW ... I had to have them. I know the Klipsch name.

I&apos;ve had these for about a week and I&apos;ll tell you.....after about 1/2 hour they HURT! They&apos;re pressing your outer ear into your head. I&apos;ve even tried a &quot;looser&quot; type of adjustment. No luck. I guess the true over-the-ear headphone is better for me. I just liked the size/portability of these, and of course the sound.

On a positive note, they sound superior to the high-end, true over-the-ear style Sony headphones I have that are about 20 years old #on an ipod anyway#.

Going to give it a few more days, but, unfortunately I will probably have to return these.

P.S. I have no idea why this page keeps changing some of my parentheses to # signs, I tried editing 5 times.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>OZSAINTLOUIS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HAS ATAILORED SOUND</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice case,good simple design,folding flat into case,can get loud, microphone on cord works great with skype on iphone4.

Cons: Drivers are pre tailored.. Mids are cut bass is boosted.Turn off any eq and you&apos;re set. NOT good as a studio monitor

PUTS OUT EXCELLENT VOLUME BUT EXPECT BOOSTED 250HZ frequencies.. AND CUT 400HZ AND/OR ~750HZ. STILL SOUNDS GREAT. BOOSTED BASS GETS SO LOUD THAT THEY START VIBRATING ON YOUR HEAD. (a good thing) Better than not being able to push them enough.
I use it with my iphone 4 mostly and when travelling especially in a noisy environment the ability to get loud pays off big time.
Isolation ..above average I&apos;d say.
Does not have noise reduction, you don&apos;t want that anyway IMO</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Billyb111</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound for price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: designed like bose, price and quality. manufacturer 2 year warranty

Cons: on ear is not as comfortable as over the ear.

These headphones are well worth the price. I had originally purchased the Bose QC 15 and did not find them to be worth the price when it came to the sound quality. Thanks to Best Buy&apos;s return policy, I was able to exchange them for these. Although they do not cancel noise anywhere close to the Bose, the overall sound is superior in my opinion. I do have to say that I am partial to bass, so this was definitely one of the reasons why I really like these headphones. I also like the fact that they fold similiar to the Bose and the case is sleek and does not take up much room. I considered the Beats by Dre, but found them bulky and did not hit the mids and ... highs as well as these do. I do not think that you will disappointed with these as long as you are a casual music listener looking for a good headphone at a decent price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW, best headphones below $500!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great hard case for travel, great value

Unbelievable sound! I&apos;m not a big Klipsch fan for their tower speakers and home theater systems. But these headphones DESTROY the Bose and Beats by Mr. Dre (He&apos;s not REALLY a DR.)!! Had the Bose AE2&apos;s for about 2 hours, they kept cutting in and out and sounded overall very muted compared to a full range sound experience. These have tremendous clarity and I swear the have deeper bass than any car I&apos;ve ever put a system into! I have a complete Martin Logan sound system with a $1,500 subwoofer, and these headphones sound just like my best 2 channel setup! They feel much more solid in terms of build than the other top rated headphones (I&apos;ve bought and tried them all) and the in-line microphone has come in very handy! I designed HT systems fo ... r Magnolia for 5 years, and I would definitely say that I&apos;m an audiophile. So my discerning ear will notice the slightest nuances in music reproduction and the ability of the speaker to handle the power. These headphones do so with flying colors and with a very impressive soundstage.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t Waste Your Money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: OK sound quality, if in a quiet location.
Average comfort.

Cons: **WAY** overpriced: These are no better than an average pair of $40 headphones. Definitely not what I would expect from Klipsch. They feel cheap and sound no better than a pair of $40 headphones.

The claim of &quot;noise isolation&quot; is bogus. These headphones do nothing over and above any other headphones for taming noise. If you plan to use these on a train, in a car, or in an airplane, get a pair of active noise cancelling headphones.

Poor build quality: Overall construction is cheap plastic. Be careful with the ear pads. One of them came off during my first listening session and was very difficult to get back on.

Don&apos;t waste your money on the Klipsch Image One.

Would be 4 stars i ... f the price were $40 or $50.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GiLLLL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent sound/quality! doesn&apos;t completely cover</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, style, quality, price!

Cons: MIGHT have slight ear discomfort, but it might just be me. =]

Ok just want to say that I love these headphones, style is clean and high quality. Sound is superb, nice bass and crisp highs. The iPod controls are very easy to use.
The only thing that (to ME) would be perfect is: if the cup was a little bigger so it would actually cover my ears. I don&apos;t have &apos;big&apos; ears, but compared to the Bose over-the-ear headphones, these are a little smaller. I mean they do cover my ear so you can&apos;t see it but some of it is still on my ear. So far after using it for a couple of hours the upper part of my ears started to hurt, probably because the cup is resting on my ear and not around. Maybe I gotta get used to it?
BUT i still like these and p ... lan on keeping for a long time, but as well, if it keeps giving me discomfort then i&apos;ll trade for something else.
OVERALL, these are very well made and for the price its unbeatable. My next set of in-ear headphones will be the Klipsch Image S4.
Def try these out! =]
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Counttess</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easily The Best Quality for the Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality, Looks, Comfort, Size

Cons: I&apos;ll let you know!

I work at customer service at a Best Buy, and I consistently have Beats returned due to an earbud going out, etc... and even our display pair are broken. We recently got a new stock of headphones in, and I was planning on buying the new Phillips pair (at $79.99). However, these were sitting right next to it, and I&apos;ve always held Klipsch in high regard so I had to try them out.

Immediately I noticed the sound quality was dramatically different, and these are so incredibly light and the ear padding feels fantastic which is great for me. I&apos;m usually looking for great sound quality for my Xbox, and after finally buying a pair of Trittons, I wanted a great pair of headphones for my computer and MP3 player. These e ... xceeded all of my expectations.

It has really great noise cancellation. When my boyfriend says something to me with them on, I simply hear some mumbling and with the TV on right now, I merely hear some background rumbling. What I do love is that when I put them on, no one around me can here a thing. I can&apos;t even hear anything if I press down them down right next to my ears on my head.

These would be a great gift for someone that annoys you with loud headphone noise!

The music has amazing clarity. I had already sworn off on my laptop speakers, but these make me ashamed of them. The bass, as many have said, is the perfect balance. It is definitely there but not overpowering whatsoever.

I highly recommend these... much over the Beats. Also, just personal preference I suppose, but I love the way these look much better. Smaller size, basic black... (I find the Beats look silly though).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jkfaul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones in this price category!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Quality, Comfort

Cons: No Color Options

Tried out about 7 pairs of headphones before I found these. They sound as good as the VModa Crossfadess and fit way better. Also liked these a lot more than the SOL Republic Tracks and some of the Skullcandy headphones I&apos;ve had.

I listen to primarily EDM and these headphones deliver - great bass and lower tones in Breakbeat as well as clear highs in Vocal Trance.

Check these on the Dash Berlin 4AM mix of AVB &apos;Not Giving Up On Love&apos; for vocals and &apos;Flashing Lights&apos; by Chase and Status for some bass.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JeremyGFL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome sound and comfort.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Volume level, bass, comfort

Cons: price

I don&apos;t fully understand why products like head phones are more than $50. That being said these are the best I have heard. I mow the lawn with them over my ears and music on level 8-9 out of ten. I can hear the music and I am not going deaf from overly loud music. I had a pair of noise canceling headphones that featured a battery for extra amliphication but these Klipsch don&apos;t need it. They are loud, full of bass, and very comfortable. So far they seem durable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Purawwave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfort, sound

Not the cheapest headphones in the world, but not the most expensive, either. For the price, these are very good value. The sound is clear, volume is great, and bass is strong - you can feel the vibration with the volume up. Very very comfortable, too, compared to others, such as Skull Candies. I particularly liked that they were not overly large ear cups, too, but the perfect size to block out a lot of sounds.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wolf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Klipsch YES, don&apos;t bother w/ the rest.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: nothing

First, yhis is the 3rd pair of phones I have tried recently looking for a sound that would try to equal quality external speakers. the other 2 were
1. dre BEATS HD. $200.00 loud heavy bass which muttles horribly the mids &amp; highs regardless of EQ settings. The ipod controls are poorly designed w/ no definiton to feel so don&apos;t try operating them in the dark or w/out looking.
2. AKG k172HD $220.00 . Didn&apos;t take 10 seconds to realize that I had used $20.00 phones that sounded much better, maybe I got a bad pair enough said.
Finally, upon my 3rd visit to best buy I picked the Klipsch ONE phones $150.00 and took them out of the box in the store to try them. Immediately I could hear the definition in the music. The head room is incredible, ... the bass is responsive &amp; perfectly balanced, the subtle nuances in the music are well defined &amp; the vocals are crisp.
They are very comfortable, to the degree that I forget they are on my head (right now) &amp; well raised control buttons for effortless use. Thanks Klipsch, my search is finally over.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wesley</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Klipsch Image ONE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The best sound I&apos;ve heard out of a pair of on ear headphones.
Perfect balance of highs mids and lows, nothing seems drowned out by one aspect or another. Great isolation for non-noise cancelling headphones. Virtually NO sound leakage at high volumes.

Cons: Become slightly uncomfortable after extended wear. (Around 2 hours)

The case it comes with is amazingly well put together and the accessories included (Two jack adapters) are of the highest quality. The three button control/mic works great with my iPhone 4 as well.

Don&apos;t pass up a chance to own these headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MyCoig</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great over-the-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Impressive sound, deep bass, fold flat design, integrated iPhone mic and buttons, design

I&apos;ve always been a strict in-ear headphone user. I recently purchased the Bose IE2 in-ear headphones, which sound great, but weren&apos;t cutting it on flights. I looked at over-the-ear headphones, but was turned off by the high price tag and/or style. I saw the great reviews on BestBuy.com and thought I&apos;d take a chance. So far I&apos;m very impressed. I&apos;ll be taking them on a flight next week, and I don&apos;t think I&apos;ll be disappointed.

They sound better than any in-ear headphones I&apos;ve owned. I&apos;ve used them around the house and have used the iPhone buttons and mic for a couple conference calls and it worked flawlessly.

I listen to all types of music including hard rock and hip hop and the ... se headphones deliver deep bass that doesn&apos;t drown out vocals. For the price I&apos;m very happy.

I specifically bought these for travel and flights, and I like the fact that these headphones fold flat, unlike others in the same category.

If I had to find a complaint, I&apos;ve noticed that after extended use, my ears do get hot. This is probably common with over-the-ear headphones. I&apos;ll be on a 10 hour flight in a couple weeks, and I think I&apos;ll have to give my ears some air every hour or so.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>zeddemore</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones You Can Buy for $149. Period!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: well rounded, clarity to bass ratio, mic &amp; remote, 2yr warranty

Cons: maybe not as stylish as other brands

It really comes down to a simple choice. Either you buy headphones to look cool because they&apos;re stylish OR you buy headphones because you want the best possible sound quality for your music. If the latter is more important to you, then by all means, BUY THESE HEADPHONES! Seriously people, they are half the price of the Dre Beats and almost twice as good, and here&apos;s why: the Dre Beats sacrifice ALOT of clarity and texture for bass. Bass is not the most important feature in audio quality, just one component, so why spend a fortune on headphones that will: 1. break down in about 1-6 months and 2. will not giveyou a true, well rounded quality of sound for your musi ... c. The Klipsch ONE have the bass of the Beats, but the clarity of the Bose. There is NO sacrifice of clarity for bass. Great for listening to all types of music, from classical to hip hop, unlike the Beats which are only decent for hip hop. If you don&apos;t believe me, do yourself a favor and try them out for yourself at any Best Buy store. Most stores have them both on display right next to each other. Also,I would encourage anyone who&apos;s looking for a good pair of headphones to stop being lazy and do a little homework before spending your whole paycheck on a pair just to &quot;look cool&quot;. Snce when was it ever cool to do the exact same thing as everyone else. Much cooler to do something different and have everyone else follow after you.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wcvet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Return BEATS now for KLIPSCH One!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality and price

Cons: Nothing

These CANS are the truth!! I returned the BEATS in ear earphones and the SOLO HD headphones and decided to give these a try. I am one happy customer!! BEATS look good but I was looking for quality sound. I was surprised to hear nice soothing bass and crisp clarity!! By far the best headphones I&apos;ve owned. Have the clarity of BOSE and the bass of premium studio headsets. GET THEM NOW, you will not be disappointed!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>instinct29</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Klipsch will always be number one in my book</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfort, sound quality, in line IPod/IPhones controls, great build

Cons: Not as stylish as the Dre Beats,but built a lot better

First off, let me explain how I choose headphones. Everyone has the best set of monitors ever made - the human ear. However, because we&apos;re all made different, different people hear different sounds differently. On this note, I listen to a variety of music and my ears have been blasted to the point of near bleeding, but these headphones blew my mind. I listen for detail, depth, and how close to a flat response they represent. You&apos;ll see reviews on here where people say you need the &quot;perfect EQ&quot; for your IPod to get the most out of your headphones. The answer is NO music should have to be EQ&apos;d to sound good. You want a flat response so it sounds ... like the studio master did. Over a cross section of 20 songs ranging from country to rock to rap to classical, these headphones produced the most true to life sound out of a group of 4 (BOSE, Phillips, Dre Beats, and Klipsch).

Second, compression quality equates to sound quality. A 128kb/s MP3 will NOT sound as good as a 320kb/s MP3 and MP3 will never sound as good as Apple Lossless/FLAC/WAV. My collection for my IPod is in 320kb/s with a few 256kb/s and 192kb/s MP3&apos;s mixed in. They all sound amazing, but the bass is tighter and cleaner with the higher bit rates.If you&apos;re dumping 150+ on headphones, then you&apos;re going to want quality MP3s otherwise you might find yourself underwhelmed.

Comfort is tops on these cans. The headphones make a nice seal that is tight but not uncomfortable. Noise isolation cuts out about 85% of background noise at reasonable levels. I can have my volume at 50% and just barely catch a conversation happening next to me. Also, leakage is pretty much non-existent at normal listening levels. You won&apos;t be disturbed and you won&apos;t be disturbing anyone else.

The in line volume and track search control is both handy and simple to use. Someone needs to talk to you? Just hit a button and it pauses your IPod. Hit it again when done and continue where you left off. It&apos;s also at a good place on the wire so it won ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Van4MSU</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great clarity with no distortion at high volume</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price and clarity with no distortion

Cons: Cord could be a couple of feet longer

This product exceeded my expectations. The sound quality was great. The headphones were actually clearer than some higher priced models</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tyler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Value; Good Bass; Lightweight; Great Sound

Wonderful headphones. Was always attracted to the Beats headphones because I was impressed with what I heard in the demos. After trying out the Klipsch ImageOne headphones, I&apos;d take them over Beats any day. Sound quality, especially with bass, is comparable if not better than Beats. Factoring in the price difference, it&apos;s a &quot;no-brainer&quot; on which to buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent audio, to new to rate durability</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound

Cons: size of over ear, fit in case

Not too satisfied with the fit of the protective case, and the over the ear pieces are a little small.
Sound is excellent, making up for the small minor technical misses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>randyvee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the gym.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound of the bass.

Cons: The price

I am a penney pincher to the third degree. The day I walked in Best Buy and seen the display for the head sets, may have changed my penney pinching days. At one of the displays I was able to connect my iphone to the head set. If I didnt get to do that I may have not bought them. It was the best sound and comfortable.
Went to the gym and belive it or not my work out went by fast as a matter of fact I stayed 30 min longer and didnt even realize it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SleeperGT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than Beats By Dre, Half the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: High Quality Sound

Cons: Nothing

I bought these last year and love em. I was considering the 300$ Beats by Dre, then i found these and checked reviews on both. Plain and simple at half the price of beats pro and NO batteries needed these are top dog. These have better sound quality than beats at high sound levels. Nothing but high quality from Klipsch...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>magkdrmr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Soynd</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Value; Great Sound; Good Value; Comfortable; Good Bass

Got as christmas gift. Kept them on for over 16 hours the first day and my ears were not sore afterwards like with most headphones. Sound quality was excellent.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>StarrLove</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lives up to the Klipsch name!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound quality, comfortable, stylish, durable, and comes with a hard travel case!

Cons: The proprietary to Apple 3-button remote

My boyfriend has a full set of Klipsch speakers for his computer that I find amazing, so when I saw these on display at Best Buy, I had to try them. Fell in love right there in the store! Unfortunately, I was not the first one to discover this as they were sold out, so I ordered them online, and was very pleased when I was updated on their every move via email until they arrived at my front door. The memory foam is very comfortable, though they do take some getting used to as they are shaped to fit your ears as they are: tilted. The sound quality is just as amazing as I thought it would be, and I do not see myself breaking these very ea ... sily. My only complaint is the 3-button remote only being designed to work with Apple products, as I try to avoid such things. A small sacrifice for amazing headphones!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>meo123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sound and Comfort is great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking at many different headphones for my young son and did not want to go the Monster route and spend money just for style. I wanted something that also sounded great. I looked at the Skullcandy brand but didn&apos;t want to deal with batteries to get that extra base that my son wanted. Then I can across this one at Best Buy and they sounded great. After some reviews On-Line and more listening to them, I decided to buy them when Best Buy had them on-sale and my son loves them. They also came with a nice case.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TSS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not too bad...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality and comfort

Cons: No real complaints

I just returned my Bose QC-15&apos;s because after 3 weeks, the power was cutting-out... How odd! I even emailed Bose, with no response. I own many Bose products and have been happy- until now. This has seriously brought doubt to my confidence in their products. (and customer service#. As an option, I decided to try these Klipsch Image One headphones, and am quite surprised at how well they sound #also helps that they were on sale the first week after Thanksgiving for $30 off!!! ) :0)
The sound reproduction is nice, and the bass is full, and rich; but not overpowering like the &quot;Dr. Dre&apos;s&quot;.
Only issue: Had to tighten the screw on the LH earcup where it rotates on the headphone frame (it was a little loose, therefore- st ... arted rotating past the inside &quot;stops&quot;). Easy/simple fix though. Good phones!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mattxmj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Audio Headphones for LESS MONEY---GO FIGURE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Superior Sound

Cons: Nothing

Lesson for the day:
THE MOST EXPENSIVE OR MOST ATTRACTIVE HEADPHONES DON&apos;T EQUATE TO THE BEST AUDIO EXPERIENCE.

After having compared the Klipsch, Bose, and Beats headphones extensively, there is no question that the Klipsch headphones are the best BY FAR. The most important thing to look for in headphones is how accurately the headphones communicate the source material to your ears.

The Beats headphones deliver far too much artificial bass, which actually reduces the sound quality of vocals and most instruments other than drums. You want your equalizer to perform this function; NOT YOUR HEADPHONES. While bass is certainly an important aspect of music, ideally one wants a balance of all the elements. On a side note, the plas ... tic headband on the Beats headphones, like most plastic, will stress and weaken over time---no matter how big or small your head is. With this in mind, it is no doubt the reason why these break so often, and, for the price, there is simply no excuse as to why this should ever happen. These headphones are the Chrysler 300M of headphones: they look like a Rolls Royce, but they are far different &quot;under the hood.&quot; If you want a pair of headphones that just &quot;look good,&quot; then these are for you.

The Bose headphones, by contrast, with their noise cancellation feature cut off critical elements of the music experience as a result of this process. As a result, the music on the Bose headphones lack the depth in both vocals and bass. If you plan on working near heavy machinery and flying on airplanes, then these are the headphones for you. These headphones are meant more so to tune things out rather than tune you into the music.

The Klipsch headphones provide the balance and, yes, CLARITY that you want , delivering the crisp vocals and perfect bass that elevates the entire music experience. In addition, the form fitting ear foam readily cancels out outside noises while not compromising the quality of the audio in the process. Like their ear buds, Klipsch ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Corsair1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product, Superlative Service</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Balanced Sound

Cons: N/A

I did alot of homework durring the past months deciding on a great set of cans OR a great set of Buds and I found that as good as some of the best buds are, like the Bowers &amp; Wilkins C5, or Monster Turbines, they just cannot compare to a great set of OE headphones. So many these days are over balanced on the bass side, These were a perfect balance of bass, midrange and trebles! It came down to these or the B&amp;W P5&apos;s and at half the price, these were a steal. As good as this product is, it can&apos;t compare to the service I received and PROFESSIONAL assistance that I rec&apos;d at the Irvine store on Lake Forest, CA. They understand SERVICE and I will continue to buy as much of my electronics there. And I tell all of my friends to go there as well! ... ! Thanks lads and laddies for being so good!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AMAZING</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I have been wanting klipsch to make over ear headphones for a long time now, due to how much I love their speakers. When I found these, I immediately had to buy them. I love them. They are the best headphones I have ever used, even compared to my sennheiser HD 280&apos;s. The bass response is excellent, and the clarity is perfect, as long as you have a good source. I use these paired with my HTC Evo, and even though the volume buttons don&apos;t work, it still recognizes the microphone, and the center button to pause/play music.

Cons: Hurts my ears sometimes if I wear for long periods, but they are usually very comfortable. The cord seems like it could be ripped from the headset kinda easily.

The carrying case that they come in is very nice too. great for stuffing into your backp ... ack or taking with you where ever you go.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex_SF</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome travel headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Honestly I cannot say anything bad about these headphones. They are very stylish and a light design without compromising build quality. The leather cups with on-ear design are comfortable to wear for hours at a time while I am at my desk in the office. They block out just enough external noise so I can concentrate in a cubed space. The bass response is superb without overpowering and when music calls for subtle sub frequencies these headphones shine. After breaking them in for two weeks the sound quality seemed to get better. I also love the controls for volume, pause, skip, etc. on the cable. I plug into my iPod Touch and don&apos;t need to access my iPod when someone walks up I just hit the pause button. You can also use the built-in mic to talk on an iPhone/Android phone and it works great o ... n my HTC Evo.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sammy1399</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great noise reduction</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I wasn&apos;t expecting the high quality sound. I was pleasantly surprised with the &quot;no battery&quot; noise canceling design and how well it worked. I will be buying another pair for my wife.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Seg8</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for all ages! Better than the Beats!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound Quality, Good Price

Cons: Nothing

These headphones are absolutely wonderful!!! I originally purchased Beats by Dre Solo HD and was not satisfied. Beats had the &quot;look&quot; i wanted but they were really uncomfortable and i heard they break easily. I bought these Klipsch headphones and i LOVE THEM. They have just as good bass as the beats and the sound is crisp. And compared to out headphones i give Klipsch a 5 for comfort (although i have not worn them too much yet)! If you are unsure about buying them just GO TRY THEM OUT! I got lucky and got these on sale which is such a steal. Also if you buy from Best Buy I suggest you get the insurance. I normally don&apos;t but for $20 for 2 YEARS, i had to get it AND the insurance covers anything. you could step on them or spill ... drinks on them and best buy will get you a new pair!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dmnlink</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exellent Headphones.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, Bass, Quality

Cons: Ears can hurt after a while.

After buying and returning the klipsch s4, sennheiser hd 428 and testing the Skullcandy Aviator in store. I ended up with this bad boys. I would just recommend anyone to go to their local store and try them as well as the aviators which i think sound overall a little bit better but you sacrafice the awesome base these have. Also the build quality of the aviators does not compare with the Klipsch one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CBreezy231</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones. Period.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Treble, Bass, Quality, Value

Cons: Look is just &apos;ok,&apos; Discomfort Over Long Periods of Time

Let me start this by saying that I am an employee in the MP3 department and got to kill a lot of time after hours sampling our display headphones.

Between the Skullcandy RocNation Aviators, Solos, and these Klipsch headphones, there are only marginal differences. But, I ended up going with the Klipsch...and, boy, and I happy that I did.

The Dre&apos;s give you the best aesthetics and descent bass. But, I think you&apos;re more or less paying for the look and name--but, some people swear by their Dr. Dres (and I guess it depends on the type of music as well).

For my ears, the RocNations offer a good amount of treble but lacked the amount of bass I was looking for. Comfor ... t was probably best with these (I don&apos;t like the way Beats sit on my ears)...but that wasn&apos;t my primary concern.

Then there are the Klipsch One headphones. The ugly duckling, if you will. If you want something that packs a punch in a compact design without paying upwards of 300 dollars, these are your guys. In a side by side comparison using &quot;Revofev&quot; by KiD CuDi, I found that the bass &quot;hit&quot; hardest with these. But, the overall sound quality was exceptional as well.

If I have one complaint with these, it would have to be that my ears get a little sore when I have them on for a few hours (let&apos;s face it: some week nights offer nothing better than an opportunity to sit back and indulge in some tunes)...but I figured that would happen since I have big ears and these are on-ear headphones.

Overall, though, these are the headphones I recommend to all of my customers in this price range...and I love mine as much as a dude can love an inanimate object.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gumpo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I LIKE BACON!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent sound quality, duh! These sound comparable to models with twice the MSRP from B&amp;W. Construction is wonderful, lots of very soft leather and some textured plastic that bends where it needs to without feeling cheap at all. The ear covers are about the most comfortable I have ever worn, normally on-ear headphones end up getting uncomfortable fast, but its not really a problem with these.

Did I mention they sound great? Response across the board is great, plenty of thump without overpowering the highs or mids, regardless of type of music your listening to.

Comes in a hard travel case with several adapters, a nice touch.

Cons: Volume +/-/Mute buttons on the cord don&apos;t work on most devices, usually only on apple devices. (My Motorola Android phone likes t ... o redial the last number on any press.)

These are probably the best headphones out there for the money right now. They blow the pants off of everything else I&apos;ve heard that wasn&apos;t considerably more expensive. (Beats, Bose, Skullcandy, etc. don&apos;t even come close.)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jo??o Vitor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality and affordable price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these phones with my iPod, iPad (those earbuds aren&apos;t that good...) and plugged in a guitar amplifier in order to study silently. They have great sound and are very comfortable, for a price well under the more famed competitors. Thanks BH personnel for pointing it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good sounding and comfortable headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sounds better than the best beats or bose.

Cons: Nothing so far

If you thought about getting headphones, get these .I have had these head phones for about two months and I have dropped them a couple of times and no damage that I can see has happened. Great sound and very comfortable. If you want headphones that have bass, mid, and hi, these are the exact headphones for you. Beats Bose and Beats Audio by far. Truly amazing headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TotallyUniqueName</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>nice!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: they fit well and sound great

Cons: nothing thus far

I initially purchased some $50 Sony headphones. Less than 1 month later, I took them back and got these. Very happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Solhays85</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound is amazing!

Cons: Wasn&apos;t free??

I believe anyone that is buying most of the Beats head phones should have saved their money and bought these head phones. This company knows audio like the back of their hands. They have been around for a long time know and have always made amazing products. Beats sound great, has great product backing with TV spots, their speakers are being put in a lot of new laptops now, but I tell you this will 100% honesty, Klipsch &quot;beats&quot; them hands down. For a buck 50, you aren&apos;t going to get a better set of head phone, the price of these is half what most pay for lessor brands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SkisInTheTrees</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Your gonna love &apos;em</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Just good all-around headphones...no joke can&apos;t beat &apos;em for the $

I have a home system with all klipsch speakers and these headphones are on par with their home equipment. Planes ,trains, and automomobiles - these headphones are great. As far as fit problems go... Take a sec and put them on so they&apos;re comfy...don&apos;t just set them on you&apos;re ears. A good fit takes a little &quot;caressing&quot;. Lost a leather foam ear surround at the bar when they were around my neck and klipsch had 2!!! New ones at my house in 36 hrs. Great sound and uncompromising customer sevice-you won&apos;t regret buying these headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rfozz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best sounding lightweight headphones on the market</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light, good price, carrying case, amazing sound, durable, good cord, iPod controls on cord.

Cons: Your ears get sore after wearing for 4+hours. They don&apos;t fold down ackward to carry around becaus of that.

I purchased these after owning two pairs of beats solos (one broke) and using my friends Bose for a week. They are way better sounding than either of those headphones the low end isn&apos;t overpowering like the beats and there&apos;s more lows to these than the Bose. And the mids and highs are amazing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>feverdog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not very comfortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nothing great. They are comparable to other headphones.

Cons: Fit and comfort.

Sound quality was good and they have a nice semi-hard case to protect them while traveling. I returned them because they hurt my ears if I wore them for any length of time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fishindave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good headset for average listening</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price when on sale

Cons: Bass gets fuzzy at times.

These headsets have an enhanced bass and some times on heavy bass it gets fuzzy. I use for my iPad and am very happy. Are these good for listing to your mega home stereo...no. Average listing they are very good. A great price on sale. Don&apos;t think I would pay full retail price. One other thing. These have ear cups that turn flat when not in use. Good idea, but whey you first put them on, the cups are not perfectly flat and can be uncomfortable for a time. They come with a great hard case, and adaptors for home stereo and airplanes.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>boola47</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent all around</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: works with all of my Apple products

Cons: none

I listen to music but also watch movies on my IPad2. I have been looking for several weeks now for the perfect headset and I think I have found it. The sound is great and is pretty good at shutting out outside noises. I have a hearing deficite but do not wear hearing aids (yet) so listening to dialog without outside noise is important to me. This product nails it. My husband has the $350 pair of Bose and they are definitely good but these are the perfect fit and meet my needs completely. I also travel and these will come in handy on those long flights.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hoagyman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sounding Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice sound, hard travel case and adapters

These headphones have a great all around sound. The price is higher than many others but worth the cost. I listend to many less price and higher. The Klipsch won me over at $99 on sale from $149. They were twice the amount I cared to spend. Great buy !!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>surnwayne</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound

I purchased all the so call, what&apos;s in headphones. Dr Dre, Soul, skull candy, Sony monitors, V-Moda, etc and found myself returning them. Sounds were good, extended use became uncomfortable. Then I tried the Klipsch One and wow, what was I thinking. Look no further. Comfort, great sounds, and durable. They are light weight and constructed very well. I let several of my friends listen to them, since they were much into the Dre&apos;s and they became upset that they spent much more, but didn&apos;t sound better than the Klipsch.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechPastor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound And Value In Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good quality and value.

Cons: Can become uncomfortable after a while.

Like many others, I tried several other brands of headphones. I listened to the Beats by Dr. Dre, and the Bose, both of which sounded really good; but I really loved the sound of these Klipsch Image Ones. There is a full, rich sound that enables you to hear all the music on the track. I recently used these on a long flight to China. They were effective in minimizing the noise on the plane, and they really enhanced my listening pleasure to the music and movies on my iPad, as well as the onboard entertainment system on the plane. As far as comfort, they Image Ones feel fine for a while, but after a couple hours I needed to take them off and rest the ears for a bit.
The headset comes with a nice carry ... ing case, 1/4 inch adapter, and an airplane adapter. Another plus is the inline mic and volume controls that work with Apples iOS products. I was able to use the headset to talk with my wife on Skype while in China.
All in all, a great sounding pair of headphones that also work as a Skype/iPhone headset. Well worth the money IMHO.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PlayerXXX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than Beats...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Kids wanted the Beats headphones for X-Mas. I knew that they were falling into the brand/name trap so I did some research and found these.

Let me tell you, everything about these are way better than the comparable beats (the $199 ones). They sound better and overall build quality is way better. Prob why it has a 2 yr std warranty vs just 1 with Beats.

Kids are Very happy with these. The bass response is great, which they love. Yeah it doesn&apos;t have the &quot;I&apos;m hip, check out my new Dre. Headphones&quot; factor, but you know what, who cares about that.

These are way better, and I got them on sale for $99, which was so great I bought a pair for myself!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great on ear headphones.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: wow these headphones sound great. I compared my klipsch with some beats at best buy and the beats were overpowered with bass. The klipsch on the other hand sounded more balanced I would say. I like the overall look and feel of the headphones. They feel like a soft matte finish to it. They are comfortable on my ears. I would recommend them.

Cons: The control buttons won&apos;t work on some devices. But who cares.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TooFreqTraveler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than ear buds for Sound Quality.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality

Cons: Comfort

I bought these headphones because I disliked the sound quality of ear buds. I even had expensive ear buds ($200.00+). The upside is better bass and a better frequency response. The downside is they get to be a bit uncomfortable after a few hours of wear. The main place I use these is on longer flights listening to music or watching movies. Again great sound but after and hour or two I need a break to let my ears &quot;breathe&quot;.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MVstar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing sound, great price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound, great price for the quality

Cons: A little uncomfortable if worn too long (&gt;2 hours)

OK, I admit the headphones I really wanted to buy to use for a trip to Europe were the Bose QC15. Yes they are rated as the best noise cancelling headphones on the market today and I believe that. But I couldn&apos;t get myself to fork out over $300 for some headphones. So I found these Klipsch Image Ones, read about it on cnet.com, and bestbuy, read all the reviews and decided, &quot;well if I really don&apos;t like them I&apos;ll just return them.&quot;
Post European trip and after using them for hours on the planes and now here in the office, these headphones past my test. The sound is awesome! Clean highs, low lows. Yes, they are not noise cancelling and yes they do tend to get a little u ... ncomfortable after wearing them for a couple of hours. Oh and also they can be used to talk through with an iPhone! Only thing is they can ONLY be used of an iPhone. But for about $129, they are well worth it compared to the $300+ I was going to be out of pocket for with the Bose.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DAG3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better value than beats</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality

Cons: Little uncomfortable after wearing them for a long period of time

I bought the beats solos for myself about 2 years ago and they finally snapped which i found out is common on the beats. Yeah a pair of $200 headphones snap but it&apos;s common. Recall it then!!! Anyways I was thinking of buying the solos again but my friend recommended these Klipsch saying that they&apos;re cheaper and sound the same. Bought them and indeed it sounds actually better. I did not think they would have the bass response that the solos had but they did and they were $70 cheaper. They also seem to be a little more durable &amp; materials used are better than the beats but I only had them for about a month now.They are a little less comfortable than the beats but overall I&apos;m very hap ... py with these headphones and would pick them again against the beat solos as far as the beats studios probably not.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound quality, poor comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound!

Cons: Really uncomfortable.

These headphones are some of the best quality in terms of the sound they produce: great punching/kicking bass; nothing is overwhelming; not muddy; can hear every aspect of music. But they lack in the comfort zone: after 30 minutes - 1 hour of listening, they have to be taken off because they are not comfortable. Most $150 headphones do not have this much of a comfort issue, although most also do not have this level of sound quality. I bought these because I thought the audio quality outweighed the discomfort level, but after wearing them for an hour, I could stand to have them on any longer. Also, they have a deep enough earcup to put your ear inside, but not a big enough circumerence to properly fit the whole ear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ben0318</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound, bad comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound

Cons: Fit, Comfort leave a lot to be desired.

I bought these instead of the Bose AE2, and shouldn&apos;t have. the iphone controls are handy, but the &apos;phones are so blasted uncomfortable that I can&apos;t wear them for more than 1/2 hour at a time. Taking them back and buying the Bose.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Scooter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent sound quality for the price. Very comfortable to wear and a nice, long cord.

Cons: None.

I&apos;ve owned for around a month or so at this point and wear them on the bus to and from work. Ear bud style &apos;phones won&apos;t stay in my ears very well and my bus route can be pretty loud so I really wanted something that would block everything else out but still be comfortable. These more than met my expectation.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>vikefan69</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The sound was very good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: They sounded very good

Cons: The rubber came off from the ear phone and I could&apos;nt put it back on. 3rd time using it.

The sound was very good. I thought they were nice until the rubber came off from the ear phone and I could not put it back on. I returned them for something better and cheaper.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Korey</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Buy...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these mainly for air travel but I will use them to listen to my laptop and iPod. The headphones are comfortable and attractive. There is a three button control built into the cord. As far as the sound, I can&apos;t quite say enough. The set has sparked a music renaissance where I am re-listening to all of my music. Every range of sound on these &apos;phones are clean and powerful. The only thing they lack are noise canceling. The set comes with a sturdy case and adapters for various audio devices.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>racz68</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Quality for the Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Apple product compatibility

Cons: Noise Cancellation

I purchased these while traveling because I was barely hearing movies on my iPad while on the plane with ear buds. I didnt want to spend a lot of money for the hi end Bose and was not interested in Beats. I reac some reviews, went to the store and tried these. I have taken them on the plane and use them on the subway as well. The sound is great and they are comfortable to wear. I love the fact that it works with my iPhone and iPad with the mic and easy volume controls. It comes in a nice little case with some attachments for other equipment. They are not bulky or heavy which is nice considering that I am carrying them in my briefcase everyday. Please know that these are not complete noise cancelling. They do bl ... ock out enough sound that I greatly enjoy watching movies, tv shows and listening to music on the plane and subways. I would recommend this product to someone who doesnt want to spend $200 or more just because its a musicians head phones.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dizneyfreek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE these!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Tune out the world

Cons: Can&apos;t wear them if I&apos;m wearing earrings

These are so cool. It&apos;s great to listen to my music and if a call comes in I can answer the call and then go back to my music. I also use these to match movies on my iPad. The sound is great. My husband has these too and he loves his. It was because of his recommendation that I bought mine.

HIGHLY recommended!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LunchboxG5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Uncomfortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality

Cons: Uncomfortable

These headphones sounded really good, but I couldn&apos;t keep them on my head long enough to enjoy them. I admit to having a large head, but it was actually the earcups that hurt the most. They are positioned to sit on the ear (instead of over or in), and after a half hour or so, the pressure got to be too much. I can&apos;t speak to durability since I only had them for two days, ultimately returning them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mks568</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sounds sooo much better than the Beats Audio junk.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sounding, incredibly comfortable.

These are by far the best sounding headphones you can get at Best Buy or anywhere at this price point. Sound much better than the Beats line of headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>whatiship</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>light weight, comfortable, great sound.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: klipsch makes great products no matter what.

using with ipod when i go running. really like how they stay put and sound, ear cushions are perfect, controls in wiring comes in handy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Eriptron</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hurts your ears too much to listen to the music</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Their Sound

Cons: How bloody uncomfortable they are.

These are, without a doubt, the most uncomfortable headphones that I have ever worn. They hurt my ears so bad that I can&apos;t enjoy their good sound quality and in 10 minutes I have to take them off. Really, REALLY!

While I am blown away by their sound but if they hurt your ears ya got nothing boys! Maybe they labeled mine for the left and right ear backwards as that is the only way that they are comfortable...Seriously!

The ear cups rotate (drivers forward) for storage but when rotated back to the so called listening position they do not even make it to the parallel position and ideally they should rotate past the parallel position so that they lay &quot;on&quot; the &quot;angle&quot; of your ear. They angle forward so the re ... ar of the ear cushion puts the most pressure on the rear of your ear...that&apos;s the part of your ear that sticks out the most. It&apos;s the other way round people at Klipsch. Did they never look at a human being&apos;s side of the head? It tapers towards the face. And guess what, the ear does even more so.

I have had Klipsch speakers for over 25 years...actually the same Forte&apos;s that whole time as Klipsch don&apos;t even make speakers that good anymore. Last year I added 5 Klipsch speakers to make an incredible 7.1 home theater sound system so I like Klipsch as I won&apos;t own any other speaker manufacturer thus my huge disappointment in what appears to be such a bad &quot;fundamental&quot; design mistake. I&apos;ll take them back and try a second pair and see if they are the same way. If they turn out to be the same way too then I&apos;ll hate Klipsch for making such a miserably uncomfortable wonderfully sounding headphone.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>martyrant</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>terrible</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Klipsch name, sounded fair on bass heavy rap/electronic/dub.

Cons: Audio quality is sub par for sure, I bought a $3500 set of klispch&apos;s about 5-6 years ago now and they are some of the best sounding speakers, on par with the system in my car (mb quartz before kenwood bought them), and I had a pair of the first klipsch image custom-1s which was pretty fantastic from an audio standpoint but build quality (though not the wire) could have improved. these were more expensive and felt cheaper. To be honest, you really can&apos;t listen to anything other than bass heavy music on this. Movies suck. Talk radio sucks. EQing does not help. I love Klipsch, but man do these suck especially at $150, if they were $15-25 I&apos;d say they might be worth it but you could still probably find better in th ... at range...recall to save your name Klipsch imo.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Erroroprtr101</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One of the best headphones out right now</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound, durability, comfort

Cons: look of headphones ha no complaints though

these headphones amazed me at how detail and bassy they are.. the bass is powerful but not overwhelming and does nut muffle the clarity out of the highs and mids everything sounds so clear and like i said before the bass is a clear good bass very precise. not surprising coming from klipsch.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Him3167</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These are built horribly</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound

Cons: They fell apart after first use

Sound was great actually very Impressed by clarity and range
However one of the earpieces fell apart after first use!!

The cushion fell off couldn&apos;t easily put it back on so I brought it back for refund and bought Dr Dre studio

For $149.00 these are junk!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kath</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>wonderful sound quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable; Great Sound; Lightweight; Good Bass; Liked the extra jacks

Cons: None for me

Liked the fact that the earphones fit nicely on me and I could have the sound up and no one could hear the music</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>psc69nyc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome headphones. Sound better than Bose.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound. Comfortable. Perfect for travel.

Cons: Nothing

Went to Best Buy to pick up a pair of headphones before leaving for a trip to Vegas. I planned on getting the Bose On Ear headphones. The Klipsch caught my eye. I liked they way they looked. Black with chrome trim. I tried them on and they were very comfortable and they sounded great. Better then the Bose and even the cheaper Beats. They were on sale as well so it was a no brainer. Wore them for most of the 5 hour flight coming and going and was very happy. They are not noise cancelling but they do block out alot of the backround noise on a plane. They fold easily into the carrying case which fit easily into my laptop bag. Klipsch makes great speakers...they also make great headphones!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fin Diesel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Decent Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For the price, I don&apos;t think you could ask for much more. I side-by-sided these headphones with lots of other headphones (including Bose) that were 100-150 dollars more. These headphones are among the best noise isolating headphones for under $. I would say you&apos;re not going to get much better unless you get active noise cancellation or spend 300+. A little small around the ears if you have large ears, but definitely comfortable for the average Joe. Would definitely recommend these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Taramina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best ones yet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound and very comfortable

Cons: little spendy but its worth it.

I have gone through more ear bud headphones, over the ear headphones than I care to admit. Almost ALL of them are either too large or uncomfortable or simply cheaply made and come apart.
These provide stunning sound and dont make me feel like my head is in a vice. They also do not feel like they are going to fall off. They are not advertised as noise reducing, but they fit well enough that they block out ambient chatter around me at work. The volume and mute are very easy to use without even looking down. I&apos;d give three thumbs up , but I only have two hands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MadMaxXx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than Beats</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Better than the rest for less

Im a fan of klipsch audio and have the earbuds as well, I think these over ears are better than the solo Beats and can compete with the studio Beats and Bose overears easily, for a much better price</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dan63</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound - not comfortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound

Cons: Comfort

The sound on these beat the Bose AE (Around Ear) headphones when I sampled both in the store, but wearing these at work when I&apos;m grinding away on the computer is a challenge as after not all that long they hurt my ears. I know they don&apos;t want to be too loose and fall off, but the ear cups are too small and the overall fit is too snug - and there is no way to adjust it - they press against my ears and make them sore.

One other minor knock - I knew these are advertised as portable phones, but the cord, which is 5 feet long, is too short to use at a desk if you move around much, and audio extension cords don&apos;t work with these since the plug has three contact points due to the inline control buttons. If you use them with your computer rather than ... your iPod, you won&apos;t be very mobile.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MSanders</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price

I&apos;ve only really got to use these on a flight from PA to TX, the sound quality was good and they were very comfortable. The noise isolation isn&apos;t as good as some of the more expensive headphones out there, but for the price, I can&apos;t really complain. Overall, a quality set of headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RickW204</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The SOUND is FANTASTIC!!!

I purchased these to use with an iPod. The sound is amazing! It&apos;s a little bass heavy, but iPods need a little bass boost anyway. I leave the sound EQ at flat and the sound is perfect! I can hear things I never heard with the earbuds that came with the iPod. They sound BETTER than headphones costing over three times as much especially those two major brands that start with &quot;B&quot;!

The fit is OK for me, they sit on my ear. The cushions are soft and comfy, but they can get a little uncomfortable after a while. A little adjusting can help.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrScrappyDoo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>On Ear?... Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I have a pair of AUVIO that are 1/2 the price and With the use of an adapter I hook up two cans/phones to my ipod Touch4 and then tried it with my home stereo receiver.I was able to listen useing one phone and then switch to the other without much noticeable differance.I then hooked up each headphone seperatly and wore a blind fold.I guessed the Image ONE two out of three times, my friend guessed it on the third try.I pluged these into the TV headphone jack just like my other H.Phones and they sounded terrible and didn&apos;t work well at all,I don&apos;t know why but it could be the 3button controll switch.I like these alot and would have kept them but the ear pads didn&apos;t rest on my ears very good,they actualy fit over my ears but uncomfortably.I purchased the AUVIO&apos;S for cheap,cheap because there ... discontinued and I can&apos;t recomend those so YES I would tell a friend about these,for sure.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sploofus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Bang for the Buck</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Superior frequency response with impressive noise suppression

Cons: A bit bulky.

I use my Bose QC3 phones for gaming and situations where I really want to hear the low, bass frequencies. These Klipsch phones rival the QC3 at half the price! The bass response is unbelievable, the high end comes thru much more crisply than the Bose products. Extremely durable and comfortable... If I&apos;m going to watch a live music concert I will wear my Klipsch phones over my Bose phones, the frequency response is excellent, and these phones somehow put you &quot;right there&quot;, unlike the Bose products. While I&apos;ll never give up my Bose headphones, I actually find these Klipsch phones to be superior, depending on the setting, and at half the price. Get them!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>elrokas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound but really uncomfortable after an hour</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound and build quality

Cons: pinch the ears they get sore

The sound is great the quality is good but if worn for more than an hour at a time they simply get uncomfortable. My outer ear was really sore so i had to returned them and instead got the AKG K-240 Studio Headphones simply much better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sokerito337</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality

Cons: Little uncomfortable when you use them for a log time

I was looking for good headphones. I was going to by the Beats by Dre, but they were too expensive for what they were plus they didnt sound that good. Then i checked Bose, they were good but I wasnt impressed. When I tried these I liked them very much. very fine sound and they are not so big. The only thing i noticed is that when I&apos;m listening music for more than 1 hour my ears start to hurt a little, but nothing that will stop listening excellent quality music. I really recommend this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Soundguy1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Almost everything possible!!

Cons: Not noise cancelling.

I&apos;m a world class musician that plays/ listens all genre of music. I cannot believe the fidelity of sound, quality and comfort you get for the price! It cant be beat. They sound superb w/ iPod&apos;s, MP3 players, all cell phones &amp; w/ Hi-End home receivers/amps. They distribute crystalline highs &amp; mids w/ wonderful rich bass. You will hear things in your favorite songs you&apos;ve never heard before. Important note: if you travel a lot on planes or noisy conditions these wont be for you. Go w/ active noise canceling headphones such as Bose for instance.
One listen to these &amp; you will believe. .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SpoonyGwald</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfort, sound quality, price

Cons: none

These headphones are awesome! I listen to different styles of music, and these headphones handle deep bass and also handles highs well as well!! If you are looking to buy Beats or Bose...DO NOT...get these! In my opinion these are probably the best headphones on the market right now!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>REEview</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Smashes the Dre Beats</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>First I tried the HD Solos and couldn&apos;t keep them on for more than a half hour because they were too tight. Then tried the Studios but didn&apos;t feel they were worth $300. Next I tried the Shure 440s and felt they were too bulky. Right when I was about to give up I tried these on in the store and was amazed at how good they sounded.

They have the sound equivalence of the solos without having to pin your ears back, the noise isolation of the Studios without having to use batteries and most importantly cost way less.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>chentecruz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: -Bass Sounds great
-3 Button Control works great with my 160gb Ipod Classic
-Fits perfectly around my ear
-After long periods of time with these on I don&apos;t feel any discomfort

Cons: -None for me

Got these on sale and I am happy I bought them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Willsta</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So-so</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price.. Sound

Cons: Comfort, fit

Great sounding headset... A little too much bass for me... Uncomfortable after an hour or two.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Disserning</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect gift for a musican</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile; Bargain; Comfortable; Easy Controls; Clarity; Clear Sound; Lightweight

excellent clarity and very comfortable</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Razzy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>worth every penny!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile; Durable; Clear Sound; Lightweight; Easy Controls

perfect size</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Seean</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awesome headphones!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones sound great! Much better than the beats. These sound similar to my desktop speakers, and has a very nice bass. Highly recommended!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pkitup</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good quality for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very good sound quality and comfortable.

Just as nice as my previous Beats with better durability.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>King Lawler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>hhgregg</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound quality and comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact; Comfortable; Great Sound

Whole family uses these headphones and the storage case is vey useful when traveling.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>blackice17</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>just as good as higher priced cans</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: they are comfy headphones

Ive Tried all headphones made
they are better than any of the others.
for the price.sony cant touch theses.
beats cant either.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Win3K</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality is good, look solid, good sound.

Cons: The 3-button remote stop working after 3 months with my iPhone4. Hated the cable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tredkid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Sound quality is very good and the noise canceling worked better than I thought it would. Headset feels light on the head.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Klipsch Image ONE - headset - Ear-cup, Binaural - Black, chrome</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/8142853961496396234/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.31&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=JqSRUPiBB8Kg2AWeg4GgDw&amp;ved=0CJMBEPQCMAE4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>junior909</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best headphones i&apos;ve ever owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

these headphones were the best ones i&apos;ve ever owned i was so supprised of how wonderful they were i would greatly recommend these to anyone</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

