<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>NHristofis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pair of headphones.....if the right price is found</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: amazing bass; good looking

I picked up a pair of the Beats Solo HD by Dr. Dre from Monsters website a few weeks ago and paid $60. For this price, these are absolutely worth the money, but for the $220 MSRP? Not even close, as there are much better options available in that price range.

The package overall is impressive as you get the headphones which fold nicely to fit into its carrying case which has the Beats by Dre logo on it. You also get a cleaning cloth and a detachable cable used to plug your headphones into your audio source. This cable is an attractive red, seems solid and also holds the control talk which is at a pretty good height when wearing them allowing for seamless transitions from conversations to listening to music.

Now to the most important par ... t, the sound quality. I bought these headphones to work out with and I usually listen to a lot of Hip-Hop so the bass reproduction was very pleasant to hear as it is crisp and pulsing which is great for cardio workouts. The mids are clear, but the highs seemed a little weak to me but I haven&apos;t layed around with them enough to full test them out.

Overall, this is a great pair of headphones for about $80 or less. Anything higher and you are better off elsewhere.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>ShaneOmac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bumpin Bass, Style, and Audio Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have to admit I was a bit skeptical purchasing these headphones as the previous generation Dr. Dre Beats solos got some poor reviews in terms of an overpowering bass and poor build quality. Considering this price point I assume a lot of consumers are looking for the same things I was in a pair of headphones: high fidelity sound, great build quality, and style. Upfront these new HD Solo headphones represent in all there categories. High Fidelity: I tested these headphones out in several genres since I listen to an eclectic mix. First thoughts was I found the sound a little too tight and not broad enough. There needs to be an initial burning in period to get the full sound quality, lets say 8 hours or so of heavy listening and these bad boys find their sweet spot. The first cd in the mix w ... as Kings of Leon Only by the Night I put on &apos;Sex on Fire.&apos; You get some nice high notes and kick drum beats in this song as well as some killer electric guitar. What impressed me was how sweet the vocals were in terms of clarity and vibrato while still letting the instrumentals shine through. I like my music loud and clear, and these delivered...the kick drum literally vibrates your head with every beat while keeping the mids and highs spot on! The next cd up was some Lil&apos; Wayne I Am Not A Human Being. I put on the first track &apos;Gonorrhea.&apos; Dang boys and girls this is where the Solo Beats HD shine, pow pow, like bass so far gone you wonder is there an earthquake in my head. Followed up by a great rendering of the electrical beats and smooth bellowing vocal licks and you know these headphones just busted out a five star review hands down. I wanted to slow this tempo down with some acoustical guitar from my man Ray LaMontagne. So I will round out this fidelity review with his live performance of &apos;Empty&apos; off his latest cd Gossip In The Grain. I figured if these headphones would fall short, no doubt it would be on a song like this. The breathy vocals and pedal steel guitar on this track gave the Solos HD some difficulty. I seriously doubt this would be noticeable to most listeners. I found the instrumentals to be a bit spacey on the low registers with the speakers focusing more shine on the highs. If I were to judge the solos entirely on this performance I would still give them 4 stars. I also watched an episode of &quot;Glee&quot;, yeah I said &quot;Glee&quot; Boss! It sounded excellent. Crisp dialogue and nice full body rendering of the song performances. Mercedes preformed a rendition of &apos;Rag Doll&apos; from Tina Turners old release and it sounded phenomenal. Overall I found the sound quality to be excellent and all encompassing across the numerous genres of music and vocals. The build quality and style of these headphones was equally impressive. I know there were some previous issues with the head band snapping in the Solos, but they seem to have fixed that with a metal band that is hidden below the padded head rest. The band seem to has a lot of give and flexibility while still feeling firm. I was most impressed with the tightly fitted hinges where the ear pieces fold out and the thick metal used to extend the ear cups. When extended the ear cups do not fold but firmly remain in their locked position. The padding around the ear is the softest synthetic vinyl I have ever felt and could pass for calf skin leather. The headphones feel soft and supple around the ear. On the head they feel firm, almost too firm at first but do loosen up like a good pair of shoes over time while stile keeping their rigidity . I think this is a true sign of build quality. After breaking them in they feel extremely comfortable on the ears and I have a fairly large head. The &apos;Control Talk&apos; cord is in one word, perfection! It is long but not too long, red in color and has a thick rubber skin. The 3.5mm L-shape adapter on the end is idea for plugging into a music player or laptop as it bends inward and safely stays out of the way. I cant count the number of headphones I have had that fray or break off because of jutting out and being pulled, bent, or rubbed to death. I like how...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>hello91x</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth atleast a Consideration...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Typically, the Monster brand has been infamously known for investing their money into advertising rather than releasing products that are on par with the price asked. However, there are redeeming qualities in the Monster Beats by Dr Dre Solo that makes it worth at least a consideration for a purchase. First of all, these headphones were designed for portable use, and the construction of the Beat solos solidify that statement with its foldable headphone ( albeit a big fragile at the hinges), solid isolation, comfort and replaceable 3.5mm cable (any will work) for public usage. In addition, I will admit that these headphones are indeed beautiful with its glossy finish (which is unfortunately detracted by cheap rubber pads). As for sound quality, do not hold high expectations with weak perfo ... rmance with one tone bass, weak mids and harsh highs. Overall, these aren&apos;t bad headphones, per se, but there are clearly much better alternatives for those seeking more audio fidelity. I strongly urge people to look at the Sennheiser HD25-1ii if given the option. Although not as good looking the Beats solo, they perform much better.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>5ZERO3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High hopes, severely disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Look, Bass, Size, No tangle cord

Cons: Sound quality/Clarity

I didn&apos;t hesitate to pick these up when I decided to dish out some cash on headphones. The look, size, and color of these were PERFECT. However, I was really disappointed with the sound quality. Rap sounded great on them, but rock and other types of music almost sounded unclear or muffled. I was really surprised about it so I compared them with my roommates studio beats as well as my regular iPhone headphones. To much disappointment and surprise the iPhone headphones held their ground against the Solo. Sure, the bass was nowhere near the solo, but the clarity of the vocals for all genres discluding rap was better. To little surprise, the studios GREATLY outperformed both. Since I already spent $180 I feel bett ... er about dishing out a little extra for the studios. If you like lots of genres and have a little extra dough on you then I reccomend spending a little extra for the studios.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>BillyD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Dr. Dre</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>High quality headphones. Good in normal bass, compares well with others in this range, for those use to heavy thumping bass look else where, and figure on spending more! This is an excellent set for normal uses. For this price range, I&apos;d rate them at the top in quality and performance. If u want heavy, gut rattling bass figure on spending quite a lot more for a high tech set of phones. For all other expectations, these phone shine.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>NTisdabomb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome product, GREAT price &amp; Super del</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Value; Lightweight; Good Bass; Stylish; Great Sound; Comfortable

Awesome Headphones. Great looking and lightweight. No problems. Mostly use them with my iPad for watching movies, listening to music &amp; Apps! Love them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>andrewneff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Absolutely amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: price

These headphones are the best out on the market, i cant see anyone who wouldn&apos;t buy them. i bought them for myself because i was sick of using the two doller ones that you can buy at walmart. the headphones are so comfy and have a great fit. its almost impossible to hear anything else but the music. the noice canceling in them are amazing. the bass and the treble do not over power each other, and the music is crystal clear. the only thing that im not to happy about is the price. but its not to bad because of the quality they are made and what so good of sound they produce. if you are looking to upgrade to a better set of headphones these are the ones. it sounds like you are in an audio room with the artist you are listening to. i do not know why y ... ou wouldnt buy them. i also snowboard and i take them snowboarding with me. they are tight and do not fall of. and you do not heart the wind when you are flying down the mountain. like is said i do not know why you wouldnt buy them, they are an amazing peice of technologiy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overpriced garbage.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: - Aesthetically, they look great - this is their main appeal
- Detachable cable that doesn&apos;t tangle
- Lightweight
- Portable
- Comfy

Cons: I won&apos;t go into the nitty gritty details of the sound and use all this complex terminology, but to put it in a nutshell: the sound is absolute garbage, and this is what ultimately matters with headphones. Most people buy these because they hear that the bass is what shines the most. Unfortunately, the bass is very distorted in many songs, drains out the rest of the sound, and everything else sounds atrocious for the price. To put it simply, the Beats use a type of bass where it tries to cover up what the rest of the headphones sound like - but as soon as you reduce the bass, you instantly notice the true quality of these headpho ... nes.

I was hoping that a lot of the sound quality would be improved from the regular Solo&apos;s, but this is simply not the case. Unacceptable for headphones at $200.

They also break easily, cheap plastic.

This is a perfect example of celebrity advertising at its finest. Honestly, these are just a fashion accessory - a very expensive one at it. They look cool to wear on your head or around your neck, but that&apos;s about it. The sound quality for this price just doesn&apos;t deliver at all. Unfortunately, the target audience for these headphones are the people upgrading from the stock headphones that come with an iPod or whatever, so most people don&apos;t know what expensive headphones should sound like, because the only thing they&apos;ve ever at this price are the Beats or Bose on display at a local store.

Do yourself a favor and go look into some other companies - Sennheiser, Audio-Technica, Koss, Denon, anything. Hell, even go check out Bose if you want (gonna warn you that these are still overpriced though). To put it in perspective, my $150 headphones sound way, way better than the $300 Beats Studios, let alone the Solo HD&apos;s at $200.

Buy anything other than Beats by Dr. Dre
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>PenguinPow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Monster Cable Dre Beats Solo are Exceptional</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good looking; amazing bass; quality; Amazing

Cons: overpriced; muddy bass

The Monster Cable Dr. Dre Beats Solo Black On-ear Headphones with Control Talk is a very decent pair of headphones. I have had my fair share of other headphones - Shure, Bose, Audio Technica, Sennheiser, Klipsch. These are by far the most stylish, comfortable, and easiest to wear in my opinion. The black, red, and white look is a very good match and the quality of the headphones is phenomenal. It is comfortable for long hour flights and for use in public. Also, the good thing about it is the ControlTalk, which acts as a microphone on your cellularphone for incoming or dialing calls. The quality is really good as well, a very clear, crisp sound that is comparable to Bose. Some minor problems with t ... hese headphones are that, as with all Monster Cable products it is way too overpriced. These headphones were very expensive, but the quality is amazing. Also, the bass can be a little overpowering at times, but it can be adjusted. Overall a good buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>CarterSS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice headphone, but too much money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good looking; amazing bass; quality

Cons: overpriced; muddy bass; Monster in general sucks

These headphones have received quite a bit of media attention lately. If you&apos;re a fan of Dre then you&apos;ve probably appreciated the commercials. There&apos;s even a Justin Bieber edition if you&apos;re into that.

And the amount of media attention it has received is really indicative of the type of product you are purchasing. Heavily attractive and stylized, but lacking a bit of substance. They headphones sound good, the fold up nicely and are really attractive. They high-gloss finish and red coloring gives in a fairly &quot;hip&quot; feel to something that can frequently feel a bit dorky looking.

Sound wise, the headphones produce a decent sound, but it&apos;s a bit bass heavy. The headphones ... seemed balanced toward hip-hop and heavy bass notes. This sounds fine when you listen to hip-hip but other styles of music come off as a bit unbalanced.

The headphones are also a bit fragile. Since they are hinged to fold up, they feel as if they could bend too far. Lastly, they are just overpriced, if you can get them for a cheaper price they are worth it. However, in general, Monster products are way overpriced for the quality.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>aphorism</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Decent sound, hip Dr. Dre Beatz headphones to own.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good looking; quality

Cons: overpriced; muddy bass

These are the talk of the town. Perhaps the most advertised headphones series, Dr. Dre has something going on for him, perhaps, especially since pairing up with Lady Gaga.

The first thing you&apos;ll notice about these, is that they hold up quite nicely and fit into the included carrying case. It&apos;s a handy inclusion, and especially useful if you plan on taking these on trips or general go abouts outside of the house. The design includes a volume rocker (with pause/start button) attached to the cord, and these are very aesthetically appealing headphones.

However, as for the sound it&apos;s not special. The bass is fairly weak and any audiophile would probably scoff at you for purchasing such &apos;phones. But for a first ... purchaser of over-ear headphones, Beats isn&apos;t such a bad choice.

Overall, if I had to choose again I probably would not pick Dr. Dre Beats. But, if you&apos;re just getting into the scene of over-ear headphones, you might want to check these out before dawdling in higher end (and way more expensive!) brands.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Garsk11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Some of the best headphones ever!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: amazing bass; good looking; quality

I&apos;ve had these headphones for about a month now and i love them SO much! I use them just about every day for recording music or just listening to it. These go along great with my Bose SoundDock Portable system. I listen to all kinds of music and these fit every style perfectly. I will probably buy some of these for my brother. He really needs some good headphones. Please buy these! They are outstanding!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>ohfckitzeric</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Emphasizes your sense to hear!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: amazing bass; good looking; best bang for buck; quality

Cons: overpriced

These over-the-ear headphones are absoutely AMAZING, they really do cancel out noise from outside to maximize noise inside, which we as music listeners is what we want! These are certainly fantastic, their sleek design makes them even look fashionable. Their non-tangable cord that connects the headphones to the jack is waterproof and CANNOT get tangled! They really are a huge bang for your buck, even though they are quite expensive, if you are a music listener, or just have a need to really listen to sounds, then this is the product for you. The ear covers are so delicate to the cartilage in your ear that it doesn&apos;t add any pressure at all avoiding the sharping pain of other over-the-ear headphones ... . Lastly, the &quot;phone&quot; part of these Beats are amazingly, the music is really emphasize, if you were to listen to an entire band, you could hear every single instrument being played--unlike other headphones or earbuds where you can BARELY hear the drums or guitar. These headphones will make you hear even the BASS player!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>justinbieberlovesme</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bass loving headphones!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: amazing bass; good looking

this is a great [pair of headphones if you are really into listening to music and wanting to get the best sound quality out of it. the beats by dre solo hd have the most amazing bass i have ever heard and you can really hear it thumping in your ear. the sound in vocals are also very clear but highs may be very muddy at times because of the overpowering bass. the looks of the headphones are really attractive but the price point is a little highbut at least your getting good quality sound looks and goood build quality. the control talk also works very well especially with apple products such as the iphone and ipod touch. it also works with other android phones and mostly all mp3&apos;s and cd players out there. the cable is very thick and durable and will n ... ot tangle or break easily. from these headphones, you can tell monster and dr dre teamed together can produce very nice quality sounding stuff for typical consumers.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>TeddyBear01</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overprice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Looks nice

Cons: sound

Looks nice but they are better sounding headphones out there with half the price.
Way overprice, probably due to the Monster cable name, which is another overprice name</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>chatterbox606</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>like an high-quality stereo on your eyes</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality

Cons: poor control talk technology

I preferred the beats solo over the studio for 2 reasons. 1. As neither a producer or a DJ I could not bring myself to pay $300 for headphones. 2. My ears are very sensitive to the noise canceling frequency in the beats studio headphones.

Nevertheless these headphones provide a great sound quality for their size. I am a choreographer and these headphones allow me to hear each and every part of the music and helps me stay consistent with what I hear at home and what I hear in the studio. I have not had any durability or structural problems with the headphones. But at $180 a pop I don&apos;t bang them around.

Good choice if you wanna get something from the beats family but don&apos;t wanna pay $300.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Quattro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Comet</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Sound Quality Around</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this item from the Bedford branch and unlike your competitors I was able to listen to the headphones with my own device before I paid.
I have upgraded to these from previously using Bose and the sound quality (especially the bass) is noticeably better.
I know they are expensive but they are well worth the extra money if you are looking at the premium end.

Although the headphones do feel and look flimsy they are pretty durable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>CurrentReview</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beats Solo - Breakthrough in Mobile Sound.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Are Beats pricey? - Absolutely. Are Beats worth the money? - Absolutely. The bass is amazing, until 2 day&apos;s ago, I didn&apos;t know my iPhone had a equalizer, I changed it to &quot;Bass Booster&quot;, and that made them sound even greater! I also enjoy the fact that they come with a ControlTalk button on your cord. The ControlTalk does everything for music. I would prefer getting the finished Beats (The shiny ones). I got the matte painted one&apos;s, and they are very hard to clean. Also, keep in mind that these are Just Beat Solo&apos;s, these provide more bass. The Beat Solo HD&apos;s provide more treble, this will notch the bass down a bit. I would highly recommend buying the Beat Solo&apos;s.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>oneals2focus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love em.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound and bass!

Cons: The price, possible lack of durability?

They sound good to me. I wish they were cheaper though. Works great with my iPhone 3G S. If you have a high power car stereo in your car and have the money you should pick these bad boys up.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>iStax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Bass Headphones Ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass, Portability, Design And Mic For Iphone

Cons: Nothing Everything Is Great

These are so comfortable I can wear for hours when on my laptop. The sound is amazing, with my phone maxed out in sound these don&apos;t distort at all. The bass from these are amazing. Majority of the music i listen to is Hip-Hop, R&amp;B, Lounge And Electronic, all sound awesome on the solos....These are definitely worth the money if your looking for some modern high end awesome bass heavy headphones....GET THE SOLO&apos;S YOU WONT BE DISAPPOINTED.....LOL :^D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>karmaic1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>SWEET Headphones!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Design, very comfortable, sounds is awesome!

Cons: A little pricey!

I was skeptical about buying these headphones for almost $200 bucks. I had previously bought the Lady Gaga ones and while the sound was excellent with those as well, they simply would not stay in my ears. So i returned those and another purchase i made and got the Solos. I am really pleased with the sound quality, but I wasn&apos;t surprised since I&apos;ve heard nothing but good things about Beats. I personally think these sound better than Bose. They are really comfortable and can be worn for hours with no discomfort. The price is a lil steep but i guess you pay more for quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>logman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>these are the bees knees</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 30, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: excellent sound, good quality bass, very fresh lookin

Cons: Nothing at all!!!!!!

These are the best headphones that i have ever had, and trust me i have had a lot of headphones, i liked these more than any bose headphones that i have ever had. Everything about these are amazing, the look, the quality, Everything!! i reccomend this to everyone who loves music. Buy them!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>natedude78</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Heaphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good looking; amazing bass; quality; best bang for buck; Amazing

I love my beats solo hds. They are so good. The quality is amazing and the bass is perfect. Eventhough they are expensive, they are one of the best investments i have ever made. They are flawless and dreamy. They are very comfortable and I can barely notice them while they are on. I am wearing them right now as I type. They are great to use while you are doing work or writing. I always wear them around the house and they are a great way to pass the time. I love to listen to them. They are also a great way to pump you up for a sporting event. Before a game, i always pop my headphones on and prepare myself for the event. People try to compare these to the studios. The studios are a waste of an extra 100 dollars. I ... personally think that the solos are better than the studios. The studios are a waste of money and the solos are a great investment. I love them so much and I hope you will to. You will hear things that you have never heard before.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>kwamebrown54</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beats by Dre</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice looks; Good sound; Convenient

Cons: Expensive

These are the most expensive headphones ever for what you get. I believe a lot has to do with the Monster cables since all of Monster&apos;s products are really overpriced. I only purchased these because they looked very nice when I saw them on display, also they were made by the one and only, Dr. Dre. I&apos;ve received a lot of compliments and have had people point at me because of these Beats. These headphones are also used by a lot of NBA basketball players as well as by many singers/ music artists. It is a bit pricey though. I&apos;m not going to lie, these headphones get you compliments and they provide awesome sound, I think they need to cut the price a little. I like the convenient button they provide so that you don&apos;t have to ... pause your music; when someone is talking to you, all you have to do is push the on the &quot;b&quot; on your left side of the headphones and it will stop the music allowing you to hear what the person is saying to you. The only bad thing about that is that you need to hold onto the button, otherwise the music will just resume. Overall, I plan on keeping my Beats, but just to let you all know, if you do plan on purchasing it, it will be pretty expensive.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shanee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best headphones i ever had</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound. Bass is crazy

Cons: I have nothing bad to say yet. But i hear these get dirty quick. Im hoping they dont.

Love these headphones. Only thing is I just hope they dont get dirty being that they are white. I bought the best buy warranty so im not worried about them cracking or breaking because ill just get them replaced every time. So far so good. No regrets. Love EM!!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>piratecalvin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Quality

Cons: Shows dirt, uncomfortable after a while

I had been looking for a pair of high quality headphones for a while since another pair i had broke. I had been through 3 different ones since I bought these and none even remotely compared to the quality of sound that these headphones have. The bass is a little higher than some other brands, but I find it to be just right. The only problem I have with them is that after a while(a couple hours) they start to get a little uncomfortable on the ear due to the pressure. Typical with any on ear headset, so only a minor deduction. Overall, my favorite headphones to date! Buy them!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>ilovelamp</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best christmas gift yet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>bought these for my daughter who mentioned she wanted a pair 6 months earlier. she loves them and wears them all the time. said sound quality is great and blocks outside noise (i sneak up on her unintentionally all the time now). i would buy another pair for myself if they weren&apos;t so dang expensive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>SuperSpideyDude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Umm.. Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Bass Is Through The Roof

Cons: They Broke On The 3rd Day!

Ok I got them on Friday May 14 at a best buy near my house! So in the car when my mom is driving home i try them on and the first song i hear is incredible!! like as a write this review im listening! the bass and audio quality is incredible!! so all my freinds were hating on me! but its ok i luv hater.. but anyways as i was saying! so on sunday may 16 i take it to 6 flags right! and one of my freinds that works there wanted to try them on! and im like no! but it was 2 late she grabbed it from me and then she like widened them up 2 put them on and then BOOM! they snap like at the side!! and im so mad cuz i just bought those! so im like u better buy some new ones! but anyways thanks god they returned them at be ... st buy cuz if not i wouldve had been mad and now thats y im writing this review for u peoples that want these beats solo that are mad good but they just break 2 fast i suggest u get the 2 year guarantee with them!! peace peopless! im out
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ryan2012</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Bass in Town!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing bass, loudness, and sound quality; cord rarely gets tangled; easy and compact storage

Cons: Snapped in half when taking off my neck...

Absolutely amazing bass and sound quality..feels great on your ears and when theyre around you neck they blast loud for everyone around you to hear and be jealous of! The only thing is, they snapped in half at the top when i was merely taking them off from around my neck..but thats not enough for me to not love them..absolutely the best $180 i have ever spent!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sizzo1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>read below. its helpful</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: style, comfort, duribility, protability

Cons: nothing

I just got these a month ago and i love music more than ever befor. the sound quality is amazing and duribility is good. all the reveiws that peope put tht there hinges r not even and tht they break easily. they probly treated them like cr&amp;p. i keep mine in the case wen im not using them and they have been fine. my cuz has the studios and they were good but i didnt like how big they were or tht they included batteries. he solos are also less expensive and they have a cool mat finish instead of glosy. as long as u take care of them good they will not break. definetly worth the money you pay</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dricent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Really great, but.....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound quality best ive ever heard

Cons: Durability

When I first got these I didnt know what to expect.... But thank god.... these were worth the money. The sound quality is the best i have ever heard. Although the bad thing is that only after like a month or 2 they broke. The headband at the top is made out of a material that is far to easy to break. ;_;</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>kareem5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beats by Dre!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything!

Cons: Have not had same experience as other ppl.

I was a bit skeptical in shelling out big bucks for these bad boys, however, i got a discount and decided I am not a producer so I might as well go with the Solos. Not only do they work with my storm2, but they go with me everywhere and I mean EVERYWHERE! They have a great sound and have revolutionized how I listen to music, I would never go back to any other brand.
Everyone complains about price, but the beats by dre are entering a different market, a high end headphones. Honestly, if you have the money, pick these up and I could see buying the warranty because you never ever know. I treat these headphones with great care, they are expensive, why wouldn&apos;t you be careful?</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chip1347</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREATEST HEADPHONES EVER!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 22, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound, style, and functionality.

Cons: The price, however WORTH EVERY PENNY

The greatest sounding headphones i have ever owned(and i have owned ALOT). A little snug but not too bad. They sound AMAZING and look better than any headphones i have ever owned. I will definitely be showing them off.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>TRUEST1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sounding headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass, Style, Comfort, iSonictalk cable

I originally purchased the Tour in-ear buds but exchanged them for these Solo on-ear headphones. I also picked up the Bose on-ear headphones which is the Solo&apos;s most direct competitor. First of all these headphones are highly recommended. They definitely emphasis the lows in the music so those looking for &quot;bass heavy&quot; sounds will love these headphones more so than the Bose. The issue I had with the Bose is that they made the bass in all the songs I tested sound the same. The bass was too &quot;punchy&quot; in my opinion and sounded the same no matter what genre of music I was listening to. The Solo&apos;s do a better job of reproducing natural bass. While both provide good sound, the Bose were a bit more clear than the solos. I would say that when using ... the Solos be sure to utilize the EQ on your device. For example, the Bose allows the vocals in the music to come through louder than the Solos. Using my iPhone 3GS I set the EQ to &quot;spoken word&quot; and the Solo&apos;s sounded just as clear in terms of vocals as the Bose. The Solo headphones also come with the iSonictalk cable which include volume controls, next track controls and also a mic. So when a call comes through you can continue what you&apos;re doing without having to take the headphones off you can just answer and talk away! I chose to keep the Monster Beats by Dr. Dre Solo over the Bose on-ear headphones because of two reasons: the bass was better and the iSonictalk cable is convenient.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>ricankevo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound very comfortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 30, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Style, Comfort, Sound quality

Cons: Price

Just got these headphones a little while ago and they&apos;re great so far. The only issue so far is that the control buttons on the headphones (volume up/down, answer/hangup calls) isn&apos;t supported on the iPhone 3G only the 3GS :-(</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>soundmaster09</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>cool headphone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 28, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the style

Cons: the price

cool headphone same as the black one but both headphone dont have AAA battery to put in the headphone. the headphones dont take any battery.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>stukovx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beats Solo are overpriced pieces of junk</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: muddy bass; overpriced; Monster in general sucks; Google

The only thing I had to hear about before knowing this product was garbage was &quot;Monster&quot;. This company is infamous for their shady business practices. Do a quick google search for &quot;monster blue jean cable&quot; and you will find lawsuit Monster tried to file against Blue Jean over a cable that looked too much like...a cable Monster claimed to have sold. Needless to say, that was dropped. Notice how in all the recent Dre Beats commercials that the Monster brand new is not mentioned. Monster was wise in not letting people associate their name with Dre Beats. The headphones are a fashion accessory, that&apos;s it. They are muddy, cheap, uncomfortable, headphones that distorts music so badly. These headphones claim to have major bass ... or &quot;beats&quot;, however, all I hear is the same sound signature I hear when car passes by me with a 10,000 watt sub thumping in their trunk. Just a loud annoying overpowering mess.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Monwar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Comet</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>beats..base..4 my iphone 4s</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It was a brilliant buy lov it to bits.. although i cud not manage to work th talk control.. Dont care love th beats &amp; bases just thrill with it, a different experiance but a little bit pricey yes its worth it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>softball28</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome On-The-Ear Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The crisp tones &amp; pumping bass! These are very nice

Cons: They are prone to break at the folding point. Make sure to close the extensions all the way prior to folding them.

Love these headphones! A great starter pair from the switch of an in-the-ear to the over or on the ear set.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>travanti1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best headphones i&apos;ve ever owned!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality

Cons: after awhile they can make your ears sore if u have a big head

these headphones r worth the money i spent on them, i don&apos;t know how they got them to sound so good without using some kind of battery to amplify the sound but they did &amp; they sound great! i see others talk about muddy sound, i think not, maybe the pair they got were faulty, but mine sound awesome!
nuff&apos; said!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>jcup</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>blue marks?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: bass

Cons: the blue marks

I opened mine up and had the same blue marks on the band as another reviewer on here. I&apos;m almost 100% sure that it comes from the the black case. I would leave them in there for a while and then there would start to be more little blue marks. Even a faint outline of the zipper teeth. I returned them and will be ordering the black ones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>une109</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Where are black spots come form?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great beat

Cons: The Painting work(?) is no good.

The cable is great. thick and strong, not tangly. Great sound, but the paining work on the outside of head frame is terrible. I bought white one , there are 5 small but noticable purple, green spray marks all over. And they are not coming off. mind that.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>HowardZ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>dont purchase them</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: they look cool and say Dr Dre

Cons: sound quality and grossly overpriced

I was so hoping these would be as amazing as they were built up to be. I was so disappointed. As an over the ear headphone I thought the base would be be amazing. The base was not powerful. The high frequencies were a little tinny. I wont trash these as I have the large Dre&apos;s and the ear buds and like them. Do not get these headphones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ricebowl92</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great but fragile</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound quality, comfortable

Cons: frame is fragile

Great sound quality but the frame broke easily. If you do purchase these be careful as to how you put them on, dont try to strech them around your head, mine snapped in half. Otherwise thet are amazing. I love them</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Oahu</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: portable

Perfect Xmas gift, so comfortable to wear, blocks out sounds while in an airplane. The music clarity is amazing, looking forward to purchasing Lady GaGa&apos;s headset!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>bernie619</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>muddy sound / cheap build</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: stylish, comfort, single cord, iphone 3gs integration

Cons: muddy sound, cheap quality, overpriced

these are a fashion accessory more than great headphones. i checked out the beats studio headphones and thought they sounded great, but not for 300.00. so i waited for the release of these solos at 180.00 -- i figured theyd have similar audio quality.

unboxing them, i noticed right away that the cushion that lines the upper headband didnt meet flush w/ the connecting piece (on both sides) and this would be problematic in the future (reading many reviews on the studios, these beats headphones tend to be built poorly) -- i unsnapped the cushion and noticed that there was just too much slack in the material.

i plugged them into my iphone 3gs and flipped thru my ... playlists. even though they arent noise canceling, the cups suction around your ears blocking most of the outside sounds. from rock to hiphop, the vocal tracks (hi end) just seemed muddy and nothing in the EQ could be done to brighten the quality. this is sort of a bummer because the beats studios werent like this at all.

at 200.00 including taxes, there are just much better alternatives; these are going back tomorrow...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>babygirl19803</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Viewpoints</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>headphones with audio cable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good looking; quality

Cons: overpriced

i think this product is an alright product. other ways i think its that its really i really think a product like this should really should be wireless that way if children get there hands on it they dont strangle them selves</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>kickercomp15</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great For Working out</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass

Cons: on ear not over ear

my girlfriend bought these for me today, great headphones i workout all the time and i used the apple headphones and they would always fall out...these dont slip off my head at all...kinda noise cancelation but not as serious as the studio&apos;s but i would really recommend these to anyone lookin for a good pair of headphones...great for rap...good for rock/metal</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>ShadowDC007</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not that great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: look great, cushin for ears

Cons: sound is not great for price the headphones that come with ipod are almost same quality

If you want the best sound quality you will have to buy the $300 pair otherwise dont buy these cause they are not worth it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shoxya</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simply BEST ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Beats!

Cons: Nothing! Every thing is great about these

Loved these headphone. Purchased them for 21st B-Day in November but have to return them cause needed the money around the holidays. I will def be buying a pair or these in the near future. Diddy beats down, Dre beats UP</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Flem54</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones i have ever had</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome Bass, Sweet compatibility, Works with iphone

Cons: The microphone only works with the IPhone 3GS

I would totally recommend this product to anyone!!!!!!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Elisa14</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy with service</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good listening device.

Cons: Can be uncomfortable to wear for prolonged periods

I am pleased with the service and headphones. I will shop again with Best Buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Xclusively1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 22, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfort, ease of use, sound quality, great price

Cons: Cable is a bit short...

Okay, I have had about 3 or 4 different skullcandy models, the Bose on the ear, in the ear, and over the ear models, the Beats Studio, and now these. The Studio model is by far the best I have used. That being said, in a close second would be these Solos. Great bass response, superior sound quality, and the design and attention to comfort is unmatched. I have never been able to wear a pair of headphones for three hours and not feel a puddle of sweat in my ear, or like they were about to fall off, yet, with these I can use them for hours on end with no problem. This is by far one of the best buys (no pun intended) I have made this year...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>JWL1123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones in history</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound quality is the best

Cons: It&apos;s to expensive but I like it

Get these earphones becacuaese there the best so go to besbuy and get them hurry up!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>bella187</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awsome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound is awsome and it worth the price.

There so cool and i love the bass and i use it on my iphone it sound so AWSOME!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bestmomever</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best mom ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Purchased for 13 year old christmas present as two other gifts fell through. He was thrilled beyond belief. Thanks</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>jakobi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GOOOOOD</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: gOOD SOUND AND SOO COMFERTABLE AND SOOO AWESIME

Cons: NOTHING

tHESE ARE AWESOME HEADPHONES AND I SUGGEST U BUY THEM</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Solo with ControlTalk Headphones - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/10614057002537931689/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1366&amp;bih=653&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.23&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=iKORUPTpE8Sf2QWrtICYBg&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE</URL>
     <Reviewer>rocklover429</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>it says online that they are over-ear but....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>it says online that they are over-ear but are actually on-ear</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

