<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dayandnightstudio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Be warned!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Style, sturdy build

Cons: Ridiculous price, terrible comfort, average sound quality, tricks people into thinking they&apos;re paying for the best.

First of let me say that I am a producer and a recording artist, as well as an audiophile. I&apos;m writing this hoping to help people make an informed decision when it comes to purchasing headphones.

Basically, only buy Beat&apos;s if all you care about is style. If sound quality is a concern, you can get far superior sound from countless other headphones

When I put these on, they felt heavy, pushing down on my neck. They were annoyingly shallow. That is to say, for an over-the-ear pair, you&apos;d expect (and want) your ear to fit comfortably within the cushions. Unfortunately, my ear was met by a foam padding that prevented it f ... rom going as far in as it would have liked. That being said, the cushions themselves were rather hard, and the &quot;leather&quot; felt fake and cheap. These are some of the least comfortable headphones I&apos;ve ever worn.

Sound quality: Well, I just spent 400 dollars on a pair of headphones, so they&apos;d better be amazing quality, right? Well, sadly no. If you&apos;re used to a pair o 15 dollar Sony&apos;s then yeah, these will sound better. And I think that&apos;s a key point. Beat&apos;s targets their products to inexperienced teens who don&apos;t have anything to base there opinion of quality off. Skullcandy? Forget about it. No comparison. While this is a clever marketing idea, I advise you to think carefully. Try other headphones. Borrow from a friend, listen for an hour or so. You will find that compared with any decent pair of cans, these really aren&apos;t anything special. The so called &quot;amazing bass&quot; is blurred and muddy. The highs are sharp and cold, the mid range is okay. While the bass is a strong point, the sound image as a whole is rather obnoxiously high sounding. It&apos;s as though someone turned up treble boost so that the mids were blurred, and then randomly added excessive bass. There&apos;s no balance at all, little clarity, and not a very good range.

Appearence- Hmm, these are pretty good looking aren&apos;t they? I can just imagine it. Being a teenager myself, I have been subject to the ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>7 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>As good as sound gets.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound. construction.

Cons: Price. Comfort.

Let me start out by saying that these headphones are definitely not for everybody. If the primary genre of music you listen to is rap or hip hop and you&apos;re looking to rattle your teeth with bass, move on. These headphones will not satisfy you. I&apos;d recommend the Beats Studios, Sony bass phones, or even the much cheaper &apos;bass boosted&apos; Skullcandy Skullcrushers for that. However, for every other type of music, it&apos;s almost impossible to surpass the sound you get from these. Unless you have experience with headphones costing much more, or a home theatre system consisting of multi-thousand dollar def tech speakers, you will be blown away. The clarity is unbelievable. The highs reached without being overly &apos;tinny&apos; are unlike any I&apos;ve h ... eard in other headphones. Subtle nuances in songs you didn&apos;t even know were present will be apparent to you with these....for as long as you can manage to keep them on your head. The most prominent drawback to the beats pros is the comfort, er, lack thereof. I personally can only stand to have these on my head for a couple hours at a time before the compression of my ears against my skull becomes overwhelming (even after being broken in!). Because of this, I save the beats for cranking up my favorite tunes and being consumed by the quality of the sound. I put these on when I want to get lost in my music. In other words, these have become special occasion headphones for me. For casual listening I&apos;d much rather just turn on the beatbox when at home, or pop in klipsche earbuds when on the move. As for the construction, I will mimic what almost every other review on this website has said. It&apos;s second to none. I feel as though I will have these headphones forever. They feel solid enough to survive years of abuse. Overall, if you can deal with the way the beats pros fit your head, and don&apos;t expect pounding lows, you will NOT be disappointed. They have the ability to turn your music into an impressive listening experience.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 4 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marky1Mark</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Da beats rock!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The crystal clarity high dynamic sound.

Cons: Just need to find your fit for the headset.

All I have to say is they really rock! They are the closest thing to what I had in my perfect jeep car stereo. Which was crystal clear highs and mids to very tight bass. I mean realistic bass not the extra extra make your cars go boom bass. I currently have $200 Bose headphones and these are definitely a dramatic difference on a iPad comparison. This made my ripped cd&apos;s from the 80&apos;s ect sound like today&apos;s digital standards. Now I remembered what they actually sounded like on my $2000 jeep custom sound system that had put together in 1993. To sum it up they are definitely worth the $399 prices tag!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 4 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>pblanton</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Monster Beats Studio are very very nice.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound. Great bass response. stylish

Cons: price

I love this headset. It has great bass response and great audio. Many people complain that although the bass is good, the mids and highs are muddy. I haven&apos;t experienced that issue with mine. If you do, maybe you should return them for a new pair.

I replaced a headset by Philips called the Stretch. Best Buy doesn&apos;t carry the exact model I had, but they do carry the Philips stretch headphones. The ones I had also have the inline iOS control and microphone so they work with an iPhone. They were very good and cost me about a third of what these Dr. Dre Beats did, but I still ike the beats better.

I also own the Beats on the ear Solo and I like them as well. I carry the solo in my laptop bag and leave the s ... tudios on my desk.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Glitz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good overall listening experience</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Clarity, Construction, Comfortable (after you find your fit)

Cons: Price is a little too high for what they are...

I have a feeling that you might be paying for that snazzy looking &quot;b&quot; on the side of the headphones in a lot of the 399.99 USD cost.

Where to start, I own some nice IEMs by Klipsch S4, X5 but had never stepped into the high end Over Ear or On Ear headphone category. This could be considered my first foray into the category, but I have auditioned other phones like the Beyerdynamic MT770, Audiotechnica ATH-M50, and the like. And to me the sound is close enough (if not better) on those that 400 USD seems a bit much. The build quality is amazing on these headphones, however, and I believe they might hold up under extensive use compared to other he ... adphones.

The sound is different, and at first I wasn&apos;t much for the way my music sounded. However after having listened for 20-ish hours I like it quite a lot. The music is right up front, and sounds quite decent. A tad bit bass heavy, but nothing like the Studios by Dre; in fact to compare the Pros to the Studios is completely impossible the Pros are miles ahead.

I would definitely listen to them first as they might have a little too much bass for some, especially if you are planning on listening to lighter music like acoustic, or classical (but I don&apos;t think you are the target audience of these headphones).

Just so you have reference I listen to rock, metal, alt-rock, dubstep, techno, house, drum&apos;n&apos;bass, hip-hop, and a few other similar genres. So my preferences are pretty biased towards a strong punchy bass, and the Beats by Dre Pros deliver on that without crowding out the other sounds!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>rocky531</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Top of the line headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great bass Durable

Cons: High price

These headphones are the best from Beats. They are way better than the studios. What happened was that my studios earcup broke (very cheaply put together) and I returned them and switched it for the Pro all within the thirty days I purchased the Studio. They don&apos;t need batteries and have stonger bass and are far more durable than the studios. For 109$ more you should get the Pro, don&apos;t go through the trouble of breaking them returning them and some time later repeat the process. They also don&apos;t leak as much as the studios do. I could be blasting my music at 65% and people wouldn&apos;t know what I&apos;m listening to. They give more powerful sound than the studios and better highs and lows. I admit the Studios are more flashy and have better so ... und isolation but i&apos;d rather go with these. These right away you can feel they are more sturdy and are heavier the studios are much lighter than this. Overall they are really expensive but is worth it and go with Pro instead of Studio. I recommend this to anyone who enjoys music with bass especially rap and electric funk sounds insane.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>strebor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent headphone for the serious listener</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: audio quality is superb

Cons: a bit pricey

The Beats Pro/Monster headphones are on the expensive side, but the great sound more than makes up the cost. They are very efficient and work well with Iphones, Ipads and various other audio devices. Every frequency in the music from deep bass to the highs is clear and pure. They are extremely well constructed and will take lots of rough use. The collaboration between dr. dre and Monster resulted in a great design and good quality headphone. They are the best I have heard yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJScubaD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superior Sound &amp; Isolation</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>As a DJ I will say the sound is great. It was a toss up between these and Pioneers HDJ-2000s i went with the pros. They are over priced but you get what you pay for. Highs are crisp and pierce at high volume, mids are tight, bass is superior. Isolation is awesome. They are a little tight to the head and feel like they are crushing if worn for extended periods. I like the flip up cups for beat matching. I wish they had swivel cups like pioneers HDJ 2000s. Ive been in the back of a car with subs with my pros on and never heard the car stereo. May get a pair of Beats MixR as an everyday pair of cans</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joel7</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quality Music</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality sounds..Bass, mids, highs

Cons: nothing

I use these for enjoying quality listening with my iTunes music library. I have 2 pairs of Bose headphones but they can&quot;t compare. I find these to be high quality and the weight does not bother me. I can wear them for hours at a time. Well worth the money..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BUYTHIS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Monster, Beats By Dr. Dre - Pro Edition</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality, durability, style

Cons: Portability, comfort

I am a very avid listener, I listen 3-8 hours everyday. I have owned 3 pair of Monster Beats, Solo, Studio, and now Pro.

I bought these headphone online because I had a gift card and no Best Buy in my area was in-stock. I ordered 2-day shipping, but Best Buy received the wrong address and I had to change this over the phone (great phone services). After changing the address, the shipping speed changed to 5-7 day shipping and this was permanent. After waiting 7 days to get to my shipping address (California to Arizona) and when I received them, they were in a bag not a box! Worried about them being broken I quickly opened them and thanks to Monsters quality packaging they were fine, but, the box was badly ... bruised and torn. I suggest waiting until a Best Buy in your area is in-stock and buy them online and request store pick-up.

Sound Quality:

The Beats Pro is by-far the best sounding headphones of the Beats&apos; series. They combine clear-punchy bass and defined mids - highs. I can hear an absolute difference between my Beats Studio headphones compared to the Pro edition. With the Studio headphones when no music is playing is the powered noise isolation, this adds an &quot;electrical type sound&quot; to your audio; in fact, this noise can be rather annoying.

Comfortability:

The first two to three days of owning the Beats Pro, the headphones stressed my ears and would have to readjust them every 20 minutes or so. Now after owning these headphones for 2 weeks, these headphones no longer bother me. Also, these headphones are the heaviest headphones that I&apos;ve ever owned, this takes some getting used to, if you&apos;re not a &apos;frequent headphone wearer.&apos;

Style:

The Monster Beats are famous for their step-up in style compared to headphones of the same price bracket. The Beats Pro headphones from looking at them, whether it be a picture or in store, Monster gave the Beats Pro a new look and feel to them. I appreciate Monster&apos;s ingenuity in style with the Pro headphones.

Durability:

Th ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jaybirdnyk11</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Audio Out There</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Bass, Clarity, Durable, No Batteries, Cord is long, Daisy Chain

Cons: Price

Great sound( The Best) and the comfort is extremely comfortable. I have had them on for multiple hours and feel no discomfort. Dont know why people are complaining about that..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>birdman51</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound, comfort and durabality.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Flexability, durability and phenomenal sound

Cons: The price for the average user.

Ok, first off, I&apos;m no DJ or any kind of professional music person. I&apos;m your average &quot;Joe&quot; who works hard and like to listen to music. I suffer from some hearing loss and can&apos;t have the stereo cranked up so load anymore, it annoys my wife and the dogs, who like to join in and bay to the music so, headphones are what I turn to.

These headphones were bought for me as a gift so I really appreciate the thought and bucks that went into them. I have many other headphones to compare these to and will say one thing, the sound output is WAY better than my others. The basses are deep and throbing, the highs are crystal clear with no distortion like some of my other headphones. I was listening ... the &quot;Holtz: The Planets&quot; which was performed by the Boston Symphony Orchestra. It was like sitting in the middle of the 6th row, in a concert hall, fantastic! Next I listened to some acoustic classical guitar, I could hear the artist&apos;s fingers slide over the strings and the pick of each string. Again, it was like being in a small cafe, a very intimate experience.

The durability of these headphones is really top notch. The head band is very strong and will not break, in fact the entire construction is so strong, it will stand up to way more abuse than any of my others ever will. The aluminum construction is very strong and yet still light enough so, they can be worn for hours on end.

Now my head is large, I wear a 7 1/2 size hat and I can wear these headphones for hours without getting tired. The noise canceling is very good. I can watch folks having a conversation right in front of me and I can&apos;t hear a word they are saying. Now this is very important because, when ever I fly, the dang engine and aircraft sounds drive me nuts but, with these guys on, nothing but pure music of my choosing. I love the detachable, locking cord and the fact that I can choose to attach it either the left or right headphone. The unused port then becomes a second output port for another device or headphones s ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Drags23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>If your gonna buy Beats You gotta go for the Pro&apos;s</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass, Sound Quality,

The Pro Beats are way better than the studio&apos;s i had. The price tag is a little extra but i think its well worth it. They are definetly more comfortable than the studios, becasue of the soft cushions that fit around your ears. They do not need batteries like the Studios and do a much better job of blocking exterior noises. They are heavier than the studios but thats becasue they are a lot stronger and durable. These are definetly the best pair of beats out their so far( hint the name Pro) i have the tour, gaga, solo, and studio beats which i use for different occassions but the Pro beats are by far the best ones, sound quality and durablity is amazing. I use them every single day while im at school doing homework, becasue they help me concentration and blc ... ok out all the distractions around me especially those loud annoying people.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rasj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Expected more noise reduction.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very Sleek &amp; Flexible/Provides Good Comfort.

Cons: The Noise reduction.

This provides good comfort. However; for the price it cost, I was expecting more noise reduction capability. The quality of the headphones are good but I was expecting more features than what was currently available.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>user1534</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>OVERALL AWESOME</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: quality, durability, looks

Cons: case provided

Everyone needs to quit complaining about these headphones. Obviously they are expensive and not for everyone. I bought these about a week ago and they&apos;re awesome. I don&apos;t know why everyone is saying they are so uncomfortable, they fit me really well and i haven&apos;t had any problems with comfort. They are bass heavy though but sound amazing. They are very durable and heavy duty however the case that comes with them is a soft case not a hard case but you can buy one for $20 online. The people in the store told me the 1/4 adapter didn&apos;t come off when it wasn&apos;t even on them when i opened them, DON&apos;T listen to the guys in store, they have no idea what they&apos;re talking about since they have someone come professionally install the dr ... e beats that way no one can steal them. I HIGHLY recommend these headphones.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>CoolDude123456</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Sound Quality, Will Blow Your Head Off</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Awesome, Great Build, Awesome Cable, Awesome Everything

Cons: Nothing

The Pro Beats By Dr. Dre are amazing. A Lot Of People Say They Are Heavy, But Truly Not At All!!! Bass Is Amazing, Mids And Highs Amazing. Swivel Ear Cups Are Great For Monitoring Outside Noises. Cable Is Amazing. Every Thing Is Truly Amazing. Ears To Get Pinched Put Move Your Ear Around To A Different Position And Good To Go. I Recommend These Over The Studios!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>munningsj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Music on a whole different level</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: quality of sound and performance

Cons: nothing

These headphones are unbelievable. i had the red studios and when i would listen to my music loud my girlfriend would yell at me that she could hear the music. i didnt pay 300 for headphones that would leak sound out of them. so i jump to these pro series and they are May be exspensive but are deffinetly worth it. If u can afford them u wont be dissapointed.The highs are crisp and the low end bass is stunning.they literally shake ur ears. i was nervous when i would collapse my studios in fear of breaking the plastic frame,with the pros they are well built and theres no need to fear of breaking. i link these headphones with my verizon htc rezound phone with built in Beats audio and the sound screams even louder</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>49erFaithful</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stop Whinning!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Almost everything

Cons: Expensive

I would not recommend buying these online without going in to your local best buy to test drive them and compare them to the others. That being said, I love these headphones in contrast to the others. The bass is great but needs to be toned down with a EQ. The Highs are crisp and the Mids come through clearly. People give these a bad rating because they expect to get $1500 studio quality for $400 price tag, period. They are built very well and feel very sturdy.

I listen to everything from Eminem to Disturbed to Alanis Morissette to Mary J. Blidge, so believe me when I say that these headphones sound great with any music. BUT... Remember to adjust the EQ for different styles. a Rap EQ won&apos;t sound good for a Rock song because usual ... ly the bass will drown the Mids of the guitars, etc.

The headphone are a bit heavy but, for $400 they better be! They are built like a tank! I usually take a break about 2 hours or so in for 10 minutes then right back at it.

The best thing to me is that these have to be cranked up really really loud to leak. Now if you had the Studios like I did this is a hugh improvement! The Beats Studios leak worse that cheap pampers. But the Pros conceal the music very well.

Overall I love these headphones, but like I said just go to best buy if you can and try them before you buy them. Or check out some videos on youtube that show you some of the qualities.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>bigtman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best headphones i&apos;ve ever used.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Best sound quality, extremely comfortable, very well made, one year warranty included, and the professional cord.

Cons: Little Pricey.. But totally worth every penny!

First off, i&apos;ve owned these headphones for about two weeks, and i couldn&apos;t be any happier. The sounds on these is AMAZING! The clarity and attention to detail is unmatched. It&apos;s pretty wild hearing background instruments, singing, and/or sounds that you&apos;ve never heard in songs you have listened too for ages. The bass on these are superb. With bass boost on my iPhone, these headphones really give a sub woofer experience. The next thing i am really impressed with is the craftsmanship. The headphones are made of a high grade aluminum, making them very sturdy, sleek, and not to heavy. The cushioning on the top ... band and the ear cups are really squishy and soft. Another big plus for me is the material doesn&apos;t make my ears sweat like previous cloth ear cushions i have used. Lastly. the cord for these headphones is unlike any other cord i have ever seen. It is really long, extremely durable, doesn&apos;t tangle, and the audio plugs are reinforced so you can pretty much forget about the inside wires becoming exposed. But what else can you expect from Monster Cable? In my opinion, if you are looking to step your musical experience, whether you are a DJ or an avid listener(like me) and have the money to spend, buy these headphones.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>NaomiR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Do not believe the hype</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I tried these out based on the hype, and the name. After all, the person who&apos;s name is on these is a world class producer who would be interested in quality sound.

To be succinct, these are not great headphones. They are muddy and indirect. Too heavy on bass, and very sloppy mids. Highs are sharp and tinny.

Essentially, these are 50.00 phones, with great packaging, sexier marketing, and a big name endorsement. I would guarantee that Dr. Dre does not use these headphones as his music listening phones. They are simply not good enough, and over time would ruin a persons ability to hear what is there.

If you are willing to spend 400 on these, then I would recommend saving an extra 100 and look at some of the better Sennheisers, or lower end Beyerdynamics.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ltgary</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These are great if you want deep extended bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality construction

Cons: Like all Monster products somewhat overpriced

These oftentimes get bad reviews from audiophiles. I dont think thats fair. They are great headphones if you want extended bass.
Very well made and they do reduce much of the outside noise you encounter. Are they perfectly balanced, no but neither are most other headphones. I have Senn 600 and 650&apos;s and Denon 7000 all of which are much higher rated but I enjoy the Beats just as much depending on my mood/music/location. They are easy to drive and both my Zunes and Ipods can easily drive them. While I admit they sound better with a external headphone amp one is not really needed. If your taste is towards heavy bass you will love these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SoCalJL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Cans, Steep Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Build Quality, Sound, Bass

Cons: Brand Name, Price

I don&apos;t like to equate myself as an audiophile, but I do critically listen to music both at home and outside of the home. Recently, I&apos;ve listened to a good handful of headphones, high priced and lower priced, and none of them allowed me to enjoy the music as I did with the Beats Pros.

I am not a big fan of name-brand labeling, nor do I necessarily care for endorsements from celebrities either. So Dr. Dre&apos;s name stamp on this product means little to me; moreover, I care less about the Monster name brand. What I do care about is the style overall and the build quality. Aside from having Dre&apos;s name I think these are some of the nicest looking headphones I&apos;ve seen. They feel nice as well, however having tried other h ... eadphones out -- Shure, Denon, Pioneer, Audio Technica, and Grado -- the Beats are the style most appealing to me. The metal gives these a sturdy feel, albeit heavier than most headphones, and don&apos;t feel flimsy or cheap to me.

As for the sound quality, these are fantastic. They are not the best sounding headphones I&apos;ve tested, but as I said in the beginning, they are the ones that allowed to enjoy the music the most. To a critically tuned ear, there are more detailed and airy headphones out there and there are headphones that have a bigger frequency range, but these sure impressed me still. Obviously, the reason to want these are for the bass reproduction. The midrange is not quite as pronouced as most others I tried, and the highs didn&apos;t quite sparkle as other headphones, but they also aren&apos;t as fatiguing to listen to as some other cans I tried. spatial sound stage is good, although it never appears to go beyond the headphones, like several of the other headphones I tried. But, as I said, these headphones allowed me to enjoy the music. I would give these a sound rating of 8.5/10, overall.

As a whole, these headphones produce a sound that is worthwhile for me to keep. The price point is very steep, but that&apos;s the price you have to pay for the name brand a ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>iHeartLadyGAGA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Straight out awful!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It&apos;s almost indestructable

Cons: Everything else about these headphones

These headphones aren&apos;t good for any genre including hip-hop and rap. The mids and trebble sound muddled. The bass sounds artificial and distorts the music when you crank the volume up. The sound feels like it&apos;s being shoved down your ears. These headphones aren&apos;t even close to what their value is worth. You can get a pair of Sennheiser HD 558 for less than half the price of the Beats Pro headphones that sound 100 times better. Even the Sony Extra Bass headphones sound better than the Beats Pro, and they cost less than a fourth of what the Beats Pro cost. The only real good thing about the Beats Pro is that they&apos;re built like a tank. They&apos;re almost indestructable.

Also, if you are looking for ... the best headphones in the world and don&apos;t care about a realistic price range for the average person, check these headphones out:

Audio-Technica ATH-L3000
Ultrasone Edition 7
Sony MDR-R10
STAX SR-007 Omega II
Sennheiser Orpheus HE 90

These headphones give a listening experience like no other and are the epitome of greatness. These headphones are what true professionals use.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BassNick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t Bother</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: nothing

Cons: everything

These headphones are awful, in fact all of them are. If you are going to spend this kind of money buy some headphones from Shure or Sennhieser. Honestly there is a fine line between PRO audio and HOME audio and these sit comfortably in the home audio department. If the price was less I would recommend them for someone who listens casually in their home, but you can get $10 Sony earbuds that sound better. The bass was too much, too muddy and gross and the highs were not crisp and clean. If I walked into a studio and they had these I would turn around and leave. They were, however, decently comfortable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mrhappyface</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Meant for studio and for stereo use, not mp3 use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality, durability, dj and studio features are perfect

Cons: not as high quality items included in package

Seriously people, if your thinking about buying these headphones you must buy them for studio and stereo use, i&apos;ll tell you why in a few seconds. I&apos;m just going to say that these headphones are just amazing with sound quality(if you use it with the right machines). The bass is very powerful, but is rich and defined without being overpowering to the other frequencies. Mid bass is great, not as good as the low bass, but better than the mids. The mids are a little lacking but your not going to notice because the bass and mid bass make up for it. The treble was just unbelievably clear and crisp without being sharp, which surprised me for bass intensive headphone ... s. The reason why you cant use these with a mp3 player is because the mp3 player can not put out enough power to actually power these headphones, and if you do use them with an mp3 player you&apos;ll find that they are as bad sounding as skullcandy&apos;s. These just take up to much power for the mp3 player to sustain for more than 10 minutes, the mp3 player will put out as much as it allows itself to but no more, which really cuts back on the quality of sound. THe comfort is ok, it doesn&apos;t hurt but it sits slightly on the ear making it kind of awkward when compared to the studios. Also they are very heavy, but if your a tolerant person then you should be fine. Although this is huge improvement durability wise when compared to the studios, these headphones are very thick and durable, also made out of aluminum so you could throw them around(but why would you with such high priced headphones). I am kind of disappointed with what comes in the package with these headphones, i mean the carrying case is just a little pouch, nothing compared to the studios hard shell case. Also there is only one cord, but it is replaceable like always so you can fix it if needed. These headphones have a swivel design which replaces the mute button, i see this being much more useful for studio producers and for Djs since they need to know what peo ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>NoSympathy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Went from a pair of Denon AHD-1001K to this, WOW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quility, durability.

Cons: nothing yet

So up until a few days ago I had a pair of Denon AHD-1001K, 150 dollar headphones from denon. I had always been impressed with how clean and accurate the bass was on them. The only thing I hated about the Denons was that I got fatigued from the highs after about 30-45 mins of music listening. Couple things i&apos;ve noticed from reading reviews on the Beats Pro headphones. People DO NOT understand what music is supposed to sound like. People seem to think the bass MUST rattle your house, and highs must burn your ears out. This is never the case. I would take a set of headphones that were not bass heavy, over a set that was, if the bass on the first set was cleaner than the second set. Now, the highs on these headphones are great, ... I have been using them today for near 4 hours straight with no ear fatigue. Also the bass has been great. I would also like to point out that I have maybe 10 hours listening into these headphones, and so they are not fully burned in yet(somewhere between 35-45 hours seems to be a normal on cans for burn in.)

I also am happy about the aluminum design. The denons were all plastic, and I actually broke one pair. Also the ear covers are very easy to take off and put on, a nice welcome over the denons where I had to spend time, tucking the liner around the plastic base. Also, something Bose does, that I LOVE, the only thing Bose does that I LOVE, is the cable disconnects at the headphones, so if you break the cable, you can replace it! Always hated that about the denons, and is the reason I had to replace them.

I had also had the beat studios and was very unimpressed. They don&apos;t have the same cleanliness of these headphones, probably because they use noise cancellation tech. You always get reduced sound quality with this. I also hated the fact that the studios sit on your ears and not over them. Something I grew very used to from the denons.

I would also like to point out, for the people I have seen complaining about no iphone cable, and no protec ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JBDesign</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better -- not perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality, durability, style, dual input/output ports

Cons: Price, comfort is somewhat lacking

The Beats Pros sound fantastic -- though perhaps a tad bit bass-heavy. They leak sound, though not nearly as much as the Studios or the Solos. Stay under 70% volume and you should be ok.

Lets also get this out of the way. Beats are overpriced. Everybody who works in audio will tell you this. In fact, you could probably get similar sound out of headphones in the $200-$250 range.

So why Beats?

Aesthetics and build quality. Beats Pro are the most aesthetically pleasing pair of headphones I&apos;ve seen in a long time. They aren&apos;t glossy like the Studios, so no worries when it comes to fingerprints. The Pros still come with a Monster fiber cleaning cloth, howev ... er. Also, the earpieces are washable (the Monster instruction manual says to only do this seldomly)

The Pros are also durable (for the most part) -- a first for the Beats series. Everything up until the Pros (the Studios, Solos, etc) have had so-so build quality. The complete metal body of the Beats Pros is a huge plus, though they are somewhat heavy. The headphones also come with a red Monster connection cord (thick, will never tangle) and a thin, soft-shell carrying case

Now, my head is fairly large (though not huge) and the Pros apply pressure that just surpasses the realm of comfort. If you plan on listening to your music for more than an hour or two at a time, you may need to take breaks in between, for your head&apos;s sake.

In the end, the Beats Pro headphones are... well, &apos;satisfying&apos;. The dual input-output ports are an extremely cool feature -- as is the swivel &apos;DJ&apos; design. Unfortunately, the $350-$450 price on the headset prevents me from giving these headsets a 5-star review. Again, you can find similar sound quality around the $250 range, just do not expect pleasing aesthetics or excellent build quality.

iPOD OWNERS, READ HERE: Unlike the Studio&apos;s, the Pros are not battery powered - which mean that they take power away from your iPod/MP3 player. While the Pros will work just fine with the iPod Touch and i ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Killzone3248</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sound quality at its finest</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality, construction, style, bass, comfort

Cons: Price, little heavy

These are deffinately the best pair of headphones I have ever purchased. I became a huge fan with the studio beats which I also loved. The problem I had with those were that I always felt like I was going to break them. The beats pro are durrable and rugged enough to withstand your everyday use. The sound is amazing especially with that hard hitting bass. I can wear these for extended periods of time without my head hurting or my ears feeling uncomfortable. They also have a great clean cut style that stands out to most other high end headphones. I do agree the price is a little steep, but if you&apos;re an avid listener or audiophile that is constantly listening to music, then these are for you. I hi ... ghly recommend these to anyone who wants to hear music the way it should be heard.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mus1cman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awsome beats for the casual listener</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: durable, dont need to be amp&apos;d, alot of bass, decent sound quality

Cons: eq&apos;d bass, price is a little high, strange exchangeable input/output ports

Let me start off by saying that the reason the sound quality is only a 3/5* is because these phones are eq&apos;d. The bass is jacked way up and mids and highs are a bit low. So if you are doing any music editing, these are not a good choice for you.

Now with that out of the way, there is a significant increase in quality over the beats: studio. Metal brushed parts add weight and make these cans feel very sturdy. The optional 1/4&quot; plug is also a plus. For all you rap/r&amp;b, techno, or dubstep listeners out there; these phones will hit you hard with the bass your probably looking for. Comfort wise, these are mediocre. The ... y have nice beg pads that just about go all the way around the ear, but there is a squeezing pressure that might agitate some like me with a bigger head.

I have tested these phones both amp&apos;d (Headroom Ultra Desktop) and un-amp&apos;d through a ipod or computer 3.5mm jack. Even with the ipod these guys still played very nicely. All in all, Monster Beats Pro by Dr Dre may not be the best choice for a individual looking for neutral headphones, but to the casual listener, they will supply a bass rich environment to please the ears.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sbryant2000</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome sounds, durable construction.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Rugged and heavy duty.

Cons: Wears a bit too hard on the ears.

Excellent sound, great responses, durable construction.
The headphones do fit a little too snug for me, and I imagine they will become uncomfortable to wear for long periods (planes, trains, other travel).
I will update this review after my overseas trip in May 2012 to give a real-world travel review of these headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cristos</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome headphones!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound

Cons: heavy

The sound on the pro are great, make sure its to an audio system or comp. On the iPod it sounds decent, doesn&apos;t give the true sound on them. I used to have a mp3 i could adjust the eq on them so it had more bass. If your buying for an iPod it won&apos;t be the best, I would go with skull candy&apos;s or something cheap. Great highs and even better lows, if u want it for bass!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sparetime</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass

Cons: After a couple hours my ears start to get sore....take 5 to grab a coffee and I&apos;m good as new for a couple more hours.

Excellent bass....Good mids....Great highs.
Excellent build quality.
A little pricey.....but well worth it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dave12dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Please educate yourself on audio first</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: style and strong bass (albeit overly strong)

Cons: build quality, requires battery, mid-range and high-range, overly colored sound

I write this review to forewarn you about Beats By Dre, by Monster, as a brand and headphone line. While they are nice sounding headphones, compared to other headphones in the same price range made by truly reputable long running headphone makers, these fall short sound quality-wise. (AKG, Grado, Sennheisers that cost more than $200, Audio-Technica, Sony Studio Pros)

On a scale of 1-10 these would rate about a 6.5 or 7. Most people are used to your run-of-the-mill department store headphones (skullcandy, sony, white apple earbuds, etc) and compared to those, these sound worlds better, however if you compared these to truly good headph ... ones then you&apos;d hear what you&apos;re missing. These have a good bass response but are lacking elsewhere.

These are just highly marketed to a specific segment of the population to fool you into thinking you&apos;re getting the best money can buy. Don&apos;t believe the hype. Read a reputable headphone/audio forum, such as head-fi or audioholics, and you&apos;ll see the overwhelming negative opinions by people who both, KNOW audio and don&apos;t fall for the marketing and peer blitz.

If bass and style is all you care about, and over spending for headphones is your thing, then go ahead and get them. If you want the best sound for the price and don&apos;t care about style and image then you can get comparably sounding headphones for less, probably half as much. This is a good article that&apos;ll explain it more: http://2011/07/headphone-popularity.html
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MattTheFatCat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pair of headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For what you pay, great experience. They take a while to stretch out into the fit of your head but after that they fit just fine. They sound amazing, crisp sound, great bass. If your a true lover of music and you have the money, then I totally recommend these. Ps. They smell great:D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ween</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Sound, High Price, Very Pleased.....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound Is Amazing, Durability, Style

Cons: Price

I am pleasantly surprised with this product.
I drove up to Best Buy with all intentions in buying the Beats by Dre Studios, until I heard that the Warranty does not cover physical breakage. After reading all of the reviews on the studios I knew not to get the them due to weak plastic design. So I purchased the Pros.
The Pros are VERY sturdy compared to the studios..
Even though the pros cost about $100 more they are worth it to me for peace of mind..
And get the Warranty, If you are going to spend 300 to 400 dollars on some headphones spend the extra couple of bucks for some coverage.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kevhortz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: daisy chain, durability

Cons: uncomforatble, sound is mediocre for the price

These headphones are outrageously expensive and not worth the price.

The only positives I have found are two fold:

1. Ability to daisy chain them with other headphones
2. Extremely durable

Other than that, the sound quality is comparable to that of a Sennheiser or Shure at half the price. They are the most uncomfortable headphones I have ever owned. They don&apos;t swivel or fit the ear well. The cans kinda go over the ear but kinda go on them. They are extremely heavy and can hurt the neck after awhile. I also have a small head but they are way too tight with too much pressure.

I have since returned them for the $320, noise-canceling version, and have no regrets!
&lt; ... br&gt;What a gimmick these are!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>brooks1460</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>previously owned the studios, will never go back</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound and build quality

Cons: nothing so far....

let me start by stating the obvious, i previously owned the studios so i can&apos;t obviously rate these lower than what I earlier thought was perfect.

i think the main points i can hit on that previous reviews may have said or not said is that the pros are more balanced and smooth. if you are more worried about bass heavy music, the pros may or may not be for you. the studios are amplified, therefore they give tremendous bass output. they are for those of you out there that love hip hop/techno. the pros, though, are much more well rounded. they still deliver the deepness of the studios, but, happily, more subtle. the entire sound spectrum of the pros is just plain more balanced than the studios. you miss out on nothing ... , the sound quality is still the best but with no &quot;fuzz&quot; sound from the studios and much better clarity.

also, it must be noted that the durability of the pros is by far, by FAR, better. i had the studios, and those broke after about a year. for those that don&apos;t know, they are made of PLASTIC. YES - PLASTIC. the pros are made of aluminum. they shouldn&apos;t break for years to come. definitely happy with this addition to the line of product slection.

if you listen to some of everything, these pro headphones are for you. if you just want some great headphones for mainly rap, go ahead and get the studios.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>LT22</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome headphones, but comfort may be an issue...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality

Cons: Comfort

Absolutely love these headphones. Got them as a Christmas gift and I haven&apos;t been disappointed since. The bass on these are just amazing. And these headphones don&apos;t discriminate to the genre of music you&apos;re listening to. You can listen to something bass intensive like rap or rock, and then switch to something like classical or jazz and not see any drop in performance of sound.

However, I can&apos;t seem to keep these on my head for longer than an hour, as they pinch my ears. These headphones aren&apos;t exactly over the year, but on the ear. But it&apos;s not as bad as when I first received them.

The other issue here is that if you use these with an iPod, make sure that you&apos;re not using an iPod Nano, as the battery will drain quicker with iPod ... &apos;s due to these headphones not being battery powered like the Studio&apos;s. Also, playing mp3 files with these headphones will not unleash the full potential of these headphones because of the compressed state mp3&apos;s are in.

Overall, if you love music like I do and can afford the price tag, do yourself a favor and do not hesitate to get these.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SoundSensation</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Combines Style &amp; Sound to Stimulate Your Ears</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: SOUND, STYLE, STRUCTURE

Cons: No CONS

These headphones are unbelievable! At first glance the price may also seem unbelievable for a pair of Cans but as an avid music listener and self-proclaimed audiophile I can assure you the price is equivalent to the overall product.

Sure some elite Sennheiser sets may sound better but they are not in this price category. I was looking for amazing Sound, amazing style, and amazing structure. This unit combines them all for the ultimate ear stimulation!

Spend the extra $100 and get a far superior product if you are looking at the Dr. Dre Beats Studio vs. Pro. The quality of these are simply unrivaled.

Want to be happy? Buy them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RealityWynn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product, BAD comfort level..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound and Great/Durability Build Quality

Cons: Comfort is a deal breaker.. They hurt your ears after about 40 minutes of wearing them and this is not pain from sound..

First off.. I recorded a video comparing the Pros vs. Studios... (See link below)

Having said that, here is what I think about a week after I shot that video..

Turns out I was initially WRONG about the sound..﻿ The Pros sound ALOT better now that I have calmed down and really took my time and really listened to them.

Now in regards to comfort...Well I just returned my Pros for that reason alone..

I gave them one last go with different variations of how I wore them and they eventually became unbearable within one hour of wearing them.. I do want to note that it was not pain from ... the bass, it was pain on﻿ my ears from wearing them..

So unless they come out with some oval shaped ear cups and Colorware starts to pimp them out, I&apos;m staying with my Studios..

In﻿ conclusion, I do have some feelings for the Studios that will NEVER change..

First one being the way they look and the option to colorware them.. I hope that colorware finds a way to &quot;pimp&quot; the Pros because they might be keepers afterall..

Second thing is the carrying case.. The case that came with the Pros is a complete joke!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>dayday23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>beats pro</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: stylish

Cons: there are heavy

These headphones are great very high price but they are worth it i got them for my 15th birthday. But they are very stylish and very comfortable when you wear them and have great sound . Just a very good headphone over all</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound, but heavy and too expensive</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: good sound

Cons: price, heavy, hot

Good sound, but heavy, too expensive and hot after wearing them for an hour.

I was tired shopping, and bought them in a moment of weakness.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BeatPete</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pro&apos;s over Studios</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I couldn&apos;t be happier with my purchase. I listened to both the Studios and Pros for quite a while at Best Buy and I decided the pros were definitely worth the extra money. Better bass and a much fuller sound. If you want Beats go with pros, you won&apos;t be dissapointed</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>samb2323</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BEST SOUND EVER / WORST COMFORT</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound

Cons: COMFORT

I am a passionate about music in general, therefore I invest in quality products. I have always preferred Sennheiser, Bose, and Infinity audio. The Beats by Dre are by far the best sounding headphones hands down! The headphones are very well made. However, they hurt not only my ear cartilage but my head as well . I wear a size 7 1/4 hat size (average ear size), so basically I have a average size noggin. I can wear these for 30 minutes, then I have to take them off. I like wearing my cans while doing homework, walking to class, or just plain out chillin. For comparison, It is like people that buy expensive furniture not to sit in? These Dre are going back until you improve the ride of your $400 headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>tip12345</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Every thing

Cons: Nothing

These are the best headphones I have ever had! The comfort of these are also really good. The sound quality and bass is also awsome! These headphones are totally worth it!!!!!!!!!! They would be a great christmas present for a 13 year old.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MeForMVP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I see people getting on here and writing about how the beats aren&apos;t worth the money, but don&apos;t let listen to them, that is their personal opinion! I believe they are worth it... It all depends on how you like to listen to music! I love these because of the great bass, sound quality and durability. People complain saying &quot;the bass is overpowering&quot;, when if you have an iPhone/iPod touch, there&apos;s an EQ mode &quot;Bass Reducer&quot;..... and if you didn&apos;t want headphones with this kind of bass, why did you chose to buy beats? It&apos;s what they&apos;re known for!!!
But with the Beats Pro, you will notice music you didn&apos;t know was even in the song, crisp highs, very low bass that will not muffle, and small discomfort levels after extended use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DetroitFire</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, great bang for the buck!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: cabel length

If you are a person who likes his or her music then this is the very product for you. It allows you to enjoy the music as you like it without anyone else sharing the experience with you. I already own some other very high priced headphones that I thought was the best they could be then I tried these just to see if they were ok at best. Wow did I get a big surprise. Great sound and comfort and great value. They aren&apos;t cheap but anything worth having isn&apos;t cheap anyway. Also get yourself a warrantee with anything that cost this much..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>thelander</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pricey, but sound amazing!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound, looks

Cons: comfort, price

I bought these a few days ago, and i love them. the only problem was that they were a little expensive, but it was well worth it. i was on a plane today and i had the headphones on the whole time, and my ears started hurting from the headphones, but i assume that they will need to be broken in. Also, i broke the cable today after having them for a few days, because my computer fell on the headphone jack. If you buy these, get an extra cable off of the monster website or ebay. really good headphones!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Corinna46</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sound made me come out of my skin!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Sound!!!

Cons: The price!

Hey listen, I am by no way an expert, but I have always loved loud, crisp, good music. Even when I was a child I constantly got in trouble for playing the music too loud, when mom and dad where gone!

So, as I said I love it loud. So, after his begging and pleading, I got my son Matty a pair of these, and he plugged these into some sort of sound test, on his Laptop, and gave the head phones to me, to listen to.

I have to say, I literally had to take the headphones off within seconds of putting them on, because the music was so intense that it literally made my skin crawl! And it wasn&apos;t even that loud! But, I love them! I had to put them right back on and listen to the amazing sound that comes out of these headphones! AMAZING! ... r&gt;
If you got the money to spend, these are the ones I would choose! I have never heard music this way! Its a revelation, really! I have never experienced music so totally and completely as I have with these headphones! I love them! Oh, yeah... so does my son! Oh, and I got another pair for me now! Happy Holidays!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>FreshBeats12</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pros vs. Studios</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: durability, wire, sound quality, swag style

Cons: price, comfort, case

I have both the pros and the studios.
I just bought the pros and am very excited !
Here are some comparisons:
1) The sound quality is about the same.
2) Pros wire is thicker and more durable.
3) The headphone itself is more durable
4) The style is about the same
5) The studios are more comfortable
6) No battery needed for the pros
7) Pros soft case seems cheaper than the hard studios case
8) DOES NOT isolate sound
9) A little too heavy
10) Sweet new features like turning the earphones.
Overall, awesome new headphones ; can&apos;t wait for the next invention from Dr. Dre !</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kratosstylez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones for rap and rock</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Deep Bass great sound

Cons: Some distortion and scratching

Awesome headphones, big bass without adding artificial bass boost. An amp is very useful for getting the most out of them. Bought a BOOSTAROO headphone amp for 30 bucks and made a big difference. If using a MP3 Player I recommend the SONY A-Series or S-Series and switch sound setting to UNIQUE. These headphones are great for Rap and Rock. Everything else sounds good, but too much bass for any other type of music that normally does not require alot of bass. No 5 stars because their is some noticable distortion and scratching.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hot sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the sound quality!!!

Cons: i have the white ones easy to get dirty.

You actually feel you are at the studio. No noise interfering, comfortable. Wish my neighborhood best buy would sell the black ones, but the manager said they didn&apos;t. I don&apos;t get that part, other best buy sell all colors.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Matthias101</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These are NOT studio or professional headphones.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Super Durable

Cons: Uncomfortable, Sub par Sound Quality, Price.

When looking at this product as a potential buy, I was intrigued by the claim that these are designed for studio use, and that the headphones would deliver accurate tones when editing and mixing in the studio. When I first used them it was with my iPod, and I can assure you that if this was their primary function, and if that&apos;s what you&apos;re looking for in these headphones, then you should buy them right now. I was blown away by how crisp the songs from my iPod sounded, as if it was the first time I had ever heard the songs. Needless to say, I was itching to use them in the studio. However, when I began using these for such a purpose, it slowly dawned on me that while these headphones are great for casual li ... stening, they have some CRITICAL flaws which make them hard, if not downright impossible (for me anyway) to use for anything other than what I already had done.
The sound quality in the studio, which is claimed to be fantastic, is lacking in several ways: first, they have way to much bass to be able to use well in a studio, and I found that as I was using them, no matter what I tried in the mixer or EQ the bass was too overwhelming to accurately depict what I was recording. Second, the mid and high end frequencies are completely overpowered by the amount of bass in these headphones, making for an unbalanced frequency range that can be crippling when mixing and mastering. Third, the rotating ear-cups, which is a nifty idea in theory, actually made some low frequency buzzing because of the imprecise way the aluminum frame was milled and put together.
While accurate sound in the studio is my number one concern when purchasing headphones at this price range, comfort is about a micrometer below that on the scale of what I want in a headphone. And these &apos;phones are AWFUL. They are EXTREMELY TIGHT, and left me with a splitting headache after an hour and a half of use. If you wear earrings, forget about wearing them while using these for a good while; the small plastic .12 ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>marcelatyourhouse</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Recommended</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Price

If you have the 400$ to spend on them, then do it. Definitely worth it. The sound quality is amazing and they are very comfortable. Wouldn&apos;t go back to regular headphones after purchasing these and I&apos;m no DJ. Primary use is for gym. Very durable and do not move around while running or working out. On top of that, they just look hella decent!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>KnopTix</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overrated</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Save your money, and buy some truly professional headphones. These are all hype and clever marketing. I plugged these in to a $3000 sound system and after hours of tweaking, I was seriously disappointed. If you want professional quality headphones, stick with the professionals.

Pros:
- Built like a tank.

Cons:
- Heavy
- Uncomfortable
- Average quality sound
- Price for components (You DO NOT get what you pay for with these)

If you want some serious headphones in the same category, go get the Pioneer HDJ-2000. Whether you want them to listen to music, or to DJ with, they will serve you very well. Not to mention the fact, the rest of the DJ&apos;s won&apos;t be laughing at you.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>User65</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These sound awesome. They&apos;ve really reignited my love for music. The bass sounds awesome but other genres sound great with the Pro&apos;s as well. I purchased the power beats first for working out. I was impressed but felt that I was still missing out on the full experience a pair of beats could provide, so I decided to try out the Pro&apos;s; I wasn&apos;t disappointed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JosephS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic pair of headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones are amazing. They have great quality in all areas. As far as comfort go, these headphones fit people different. I wear a size 7.5 hat and these headphones can be worn for several hours without any discomfort. These are very well built and feel like they will last many years.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>lil jj aka listen to this track trick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Abt</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MHBTSPOEWH - Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional White Headphones review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Professional Features,Easy To Use,Versatile,Excellent Sound

They are 100% real I am 14 and this is the best [$] i have ever spent. The only problem is the warranty. I am not sure where or how to use it any questions please ask.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW!!! I never knew what I was missing.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones open up the music that I have always listened to a whole knew level. The range is amazing and the bass really kicks. It&apos;s like being in a studio listening in. Can&apos;t wait to let my friends hear what they have been missing. Even though the price is up there a bit I still would by them again.
Everyone at the gym keeps asking about them and take a quick listen. They are rather large but they handle everything with ease. They can also be used as speakers and handles the highest volumes without distortion.

It will be extremely hard to ever go back to regular headphones after experiencing music through these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HDragun</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Out Standing Headphones.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality, durabillity, second audio jack, quality, no batteries needed.

Cons: slight discomfort.

These headphones are just amazing. i had the studios that were defected because it broke in 4 months, but i thought of upgrading to pros. The sound quality of these headphones are just out standing, the second thing i like about these headphones are, they don&apos;t need any batteries for the sound quality it has. The comfort is very good, it can hurt your head after awhile of use, its a little heavy and seems to hurt the top of my ears, thought it may depend on how big or small your ears are. now the best part is, its durability, these are very strong headphones, you can travel with them and you will have a hard time damaging them if you bumped into something. One of the fu ... tures that the headphones has that makes it good for sharing music, is its second audio jack, if you were to listen to music and one of those people who like sharing your music, all they got to do is plug in their headphones into your headset. thought you could also make a chain if they have the same pair of headphones. the coil cord is also pretty nice, if you were used of listening to your music from a ipod or other devices, and plug it in to your pc, and forgot you were plugged in something thats not on you, it wont rip the cord or your headphones away from you.

The bottom line of these headphones, they are very good.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BigZeus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing headphones for any music lover</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headpones may cost a pretty penny but they are like no other and you will have all the quality you could want.

These headphones are absolutely amazing. The sound emitted is of professional dj or producer quality. It brings out every piece of any track and brings forth the vocals in ways that no other headphones can. When you put these headphones on and start to play your favorite songs you will realize you have never truely heard music until that moment.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SantaC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Needed something better</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality in sound and preciseness

Cons: Haven&apos;t noticed a single thing.

I have had a home studio for approx. 6 years. I&apos;m constantly looking and trying find products that produce high quailty studio sound. I am a musician, and sound engineer, and most of the time, never satitisfied with the sound that I hear. I purchased the Phones just the other day.
I had first thought of the Bose headphones, which really sounded nice, but
I wanted something with more KICK, and maticulous discreet sound. I was able to compare the two and our local store, and was totally BLOWN AWAY with the difference in clarity and precise tones I had spent years looking for. I don&apos;t believe I&apos;ve ever been more satisfied with sound I am now recieving. Excellent Product !!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PlayboyMixx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for DJ&apos;s</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Clear sound with lots of bass, metal construction, curved detachable cord, cups can slide up, very attractive looking

Cons: a bit pricey, comfort level is not bad, but nothing spectacular

I&apos;ve been DJ&apos;ing for over 20 years and the Beat Pro&apos;s are the best pair of headphones that I&apos;ve ever used for DJ&apos;ing. The sound quality is really good. Very clear sound with lots of bass. The bass is what really separates these headphones from the sound of other high end models. Over the years I&apos;ve had trouble with the plastic parts on my DJ headphones cracking from folding them up when going to the club. The Beats Pro are made out of metal so they won&apos;t crack like most other DJ headphones (Pioneer 2000 are also made out of metal). Another feature that I like is that the detachable cor ... d has an end that is curved. What that means for DJ&apos;s is that the end of the cord that plugs into your DJ mixer doesn&apos;t stick straight up and get in the way when your DJ&apos;ing (when using mixers that have the headphone jack on top of the board). Because it&apos;s curved, it stays out of the way. The comfort level of these headphones is pretty standard. I also find the white headphones to be unique and very attractive. These headphones are pricey, but not if you&apos;re a serious DJ.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ssmbasketball</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unbelievable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Flip Cups, Durability, Looks

Cons: A little expensive

These headphones are the best I&apos;ve ever had by far. I play basketball so before a game I listen to my music and these headphones allow me to focus. Very good build, love the flip cups, really stylish, just great all around. Dre knocked it out of the ball park with these. Great job</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brad1002</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sceptics Beware</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Build Quality

Cons: Price

This is my best attempt at writing an unbiased review for these headphones. I was a little concerned with the price tag for these babies. However, I have not been disappointed by my purchase. There are many who complain about Beats&apos; sound. Honestly, unless you&apos;re a hardcore audiophile I really don&apos;t see any way that you could say that these sound anything besides excellent. The bass is there when you want it and is booming, no disappointments, the mids are pronounced and clear while not being overpowered by the bass, and the highs are bright and crisp without being tinny. Also, there has been concern that iPods cannot power these headphones. This is false. My iTouch does it just fine. Another factor to consider is sound leakage. The Pros ... leak quite a bit of sound so just be aware of that if you are in public and are rocking out to Ke$ha. On a final note, the build quality is spectacular. A HUGE improvement from the studios (which I would not buy because they were so fragile). So if you have the money buy these and you will not be disappointed. I guarantee it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sai93</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>decent sound quality but comfort ruins the headpho</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the sound quality, the total build of the headphone

Cons: comfort, and the price!

the headphones are not comfortable at all. they hurt my ears and they cannot be worn for long amounts of time. really dont recommend this product. im sorry monster try again!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chaz2272</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Too Mainstream</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: look

Cons: sound quality, bass, everything really

I have 4 year old sennheisers that sound better than these....I remember when these cost 199 when they came out and now their so mainstream the prices are skyrocketed and they sound like cheap skullcandys. All it has for it is the look and the branding.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cjohnson484</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Sound and Unbelievable Comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, Comfort, Flip-Cup, Strong Build

Cons: Price

The wait is over!!! Having used multiple different types of headphones in my life I have yet to find anything that is in near comparison with the Beats Pros. All the way from lows to highs you honestly feel like you are in the studio with the artist. They don&apos;t have noise canceling, but I can&apos;t hear anything but music when I have them on. The ability to have flip cups is almost a necessity, so that you can hear other things around you. I use these primarily for doing homework and watching movies on my computer. With having loud roommates it is very nice to drown them out while doing homework. As far as comfort there is nothing that is even close. While I laid in bed with the studios I was always afraid that I was going ... to snap them in half, but the construction on the Pros is awesome very lightweight yet they feel like they can take a beating with out a problem. I would highly recommend these to anyone who is seriously looking at upgrading your headphones.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>second2n0ne</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>ATTENTION GETTER !!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound Quality

Cons: A bit overpriced

These headphones have an excellent look along with a great sound.
They turn heads and get lots of attention whenever I take them out in public. I am extremely happy with them even though they are a bit overpriced. STILL WORTH THE MONEY. Two thumbs up.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Luke10</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>THESE ARE AMAZING.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything.

Anybody that is looking for quality headphones, this is a MUST buy. The sound quality is unbelievable. Also, the people who are saying it is not comfortable is very weird. I find it very comfortable and I can wear it for hours without any fatigue.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>clay703</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>EXCELLENT PRODUCT</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i got this as a gift for my son and now I want to steal in for myself. The sound quality is EXCEPTIONAL. It blocks out most noise and gives the feeling of being in a recording studio. It seems to be constructed from high grade materials and not subject to easy bumps and bruises from normal wear and tear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Blakmamba240</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones for serious music listeners</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: They have amazing sound!

Cons: Wish they had more colors.

The Dr. Dre beats are meant for people that love to listen to music alot. They are a perfect gift for people who are serious about listening to music. I recommend them for all people.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>angelgaia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound...too much pressure on your ears/head</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound

Cons: Head pressure leads to headache...

I LOVE my Monster Pro Beats, the sound is fantastic but they are overpriced and I kind wished I could take them back because... they put a lot of pressure on my head, around the ears and it gives me a headache if I use them for too long... But the sound is sometimes worth it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AlDM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound and quality.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good looking and high quality.

Cons: A longer extension cord isn&apos;t available, yet.

Unbelievable sound quality for both audio music recordings and for video movies. You can hear so much more individual sound bites, notes and things I used to miss out on. I love them and the new sounds they provide and my wife now wants a pair for herself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BassFlow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>If you make beats its perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound quality

Cons: Price (of course)

My use - I just bought them and my main use is making beats, I am not a pro or anything it is just a hobby and my roommates always complain because for me to balance all the sounds I need to listen to it at full volume, but I can&apos;t bump my beats when they are trying to sleep so I got these to make beats at any time and listen to it with good clarity so I don&apos;t have to re adjust the sounds when I listen to it on my system.

What Sold Me - I was at best buy and trying to decide which ones I wanted and they had a pair of the beats pro that wasn&apos;t plugged in to anything so I plugged it into my iphone and played one of my beats, and it was the best my beat ever sounded I could even hear sound balancing issues that I didn&apos;t hear bef ... ore that I could go back and make sound perfect.

Cons - price, I believe they should be 300 not 400 dollars, I think that extra 100 dollars is just name brand but if you have the money to spend and like good quality music, go ahead and buy them. plus they are stylish.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PJOMan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound! Low Low comfort!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>If you&apos;re going to use these for recording or listening back to tracks the pros are the best headphones out there!! If you wanna listen to these everyday while working out etc please consider the studios. Sound quality is the same in my opinion! However the durability of the pros really makes a huge difference!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>vilfil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great headphones. Sound quality is amazing. My only complaint is the case. It like what the heck I just dropped 400 dollars on them and I get a soft case. I had to buy another case online from slappa for the right case.
Check my channel on YouTube type in vilfil</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AllTheGoodNamesRTaken</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best audio you can get</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: it durable, great sound, comfortable,

Cons: needs a hard case, disappointed its not noise canceling,

Soooo worth the money. Its definately the best pair of headphones you can buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Whit330</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>To heavy for everyday</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Great sound very durable, however the cord is very long and not idle for iPod use . And they are extremely heavy and uncomfortable on head and ears . If you are a casual listener and just using to enjoy music the extra $100. Is so not worth it stick with the studio Or eve the solo both are much more comfortable and sound just as good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>pDavid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound was fantastic

Cons: Little high priced

I own the Studio Dr Beats, Bose Quiet Comfort 3, and Bose Quiet Comfort 15. I compared the the bass, treble, etc with each of these devices, and found that the Dr Beats Pro had the best sound, also it didn&apos;t need batteries in order for it to work. I would highly recommend this product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>doumamai</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Sound Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality, solid heavy duty

Cons: heavy and hard to carry around.

This is one of the best sound quality headphone I have in my life. It will beat the BOSE easily. In addition, it doesn&apos;t feel like my ear were being pressurized like the BOSE does when you turn on the switch to make it quiet. As for comfort, this could be a little heavier compare to BOSE. If all you care is sound quality, go with this. Or, style is also better, in my opinion.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TheGiftGiver</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Maybe the second pair will work</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: appearance

Cons: Only one ear works, waiting for replacement pair.

Comfort, excellent, appearance, great- the question is, do they work? Unfortunately not! Only one ear, the other is silent! I expected better from such an expensive product. Maybe the replacement pair that I am waiting for will actually work! Pricey product, a bit disappointing. Apparently in 7 to 10 days, I should receive an e-mail with a label to return this pair. When the second pair is going to arrive is anyone&apos;s guess. Hopefully, the delivery time is quicker than the first pair. Young man on the Customer service line, was really nice and agreed that such an expensive pair of headphones should actually work.
He had to get approval from someone to send another pair. Waiting for the replacement.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jdip</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Newest dre. Headphones are a step back from studio</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Cord for these headphones is about 25 feet long, be careful not to trip. Only plan on using these while djing because you have no iPhone/iPod song or volume control on the cord. Also no extra cord in case you are not a dj. Flip earphones is not as sweet as you would expect because it pulls your hair. Does leak a lot less sound than the studio beats. Otherwise sound is pretty good. Not worth the extra $100. Still slide off of your head if working out, and incredibly heavy. I will say they are durable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Beats5Bro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Favorite pair of beats</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Looks great, Very strong

Cons: noise cancellation

I own 5 pairs of beats- Pros, Studios, Solos, tours, Mixrs
they are all great, but the pros are probably my favorite
The noise cancellation on the pros is not amazing (compared to the studios) but it is not horrible at all. the noise cancelling is good, but could be better.
some people say they are too big or bulky, but they really aren&apos;t. The case is small and easy to carry, but has no place for the headphone chord
also the carrying case is not a very strong case... it is only a small leather bag, and you cannot fully put your beats in the case there will always be a little bit of the headband you can see.
overall they are a great pair of headphones
they do what they are supposed to do</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MH13</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>worth it but uncomfortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality, ballin&apos; looks

Cons: comfortability

i have the studios and pros and there are some similarities and differences between the two. first, the sound quality seems to be the same. they both go BOOM. the pros definatly are not as comfortably as the studios. the pros are almost on ear whereas the studios are around ear. the pros also seem to squeeze tight together on your ears wich can get uncomfortable. the studios have a nice push to mute button on the right ear which the pros do not. the pros have a cool feature however which is capable of daisy chining headphones together by putting the other headphone jack into the pros so you can share your music. the pros also come with one cord which locks into the headphones and is nice and thick, but is very long and h ... as a weird coiled section at the bottom of the cord. over all they perform similar to the studios but are much less comfortable.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>1of4</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good investment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound quality

Cons: head band tears up to easy. not placed on to well for longevity

if these are anything like the Studios. then Im all over it the the day they RELEASE!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ProBeats</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>&quot;More Than Enough, Less Than A Pound&quot;</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile; Best headphones out there; Consistent; Professional Features; Easy To Use; Excellent Sound

Cons: Absolutly None

I use the product to make my own beats. I also love using them for the music on my IPod, IPhone, Apple Computer, and my other musical devices.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>EmmanuelC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great but heavy...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound/Look

Cons: Weight/Case

Great sound, looks nice (I got it in white), is tough BUT

- it&apos;s heavy, and I&apos;m a big guy with a big head
- the case is not a case, it&apos;s a sleeve. For $400, a sleeve, really?</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ryan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphone.. but</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great sounding, bass is pumping, great quality, looks cool

Cons: heavy, not worth 400 bucks

i would think it is worth the same as the studios but not 400 dollars, great quality headphones: will ot break after multiple uses</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>king415</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>amazing sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound, style, durability

Cons: very expensive, does not come with travel hard case

i&apos;m pretty sure there are better headphones out there, but the beats pro are the best that i have experienced and look better than any headphone i ever seen. very comfortable and durable. the only thing i don&apos;t like, is that it comes with a travel pouch, instead of a hard case.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AWalrus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Ive had 5 pairs is monster headphones and this is by FAR the best sounding and most worth it, they are a little heavy (as to be expected there solid aluminum) there very sturdy and I&apos;m in love. And I doubt I can break them</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>drunkmonkey119</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great for anybody.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound clarity, very durable, comfortable,

I am an avid music listener and now that i have the beats studio pros i can honestly say that i don,t want to use any other pair of headphones again. Im hooked on the Beats.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Baby123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Qulity, Sound

Cons: Price

I love it i bought mines it has Great sound quality its a bit costy but it will pass Great i totally recommend you buy no regrets Trust me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TRESX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for people who realy love music</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the sound and design

Cons: the price

This pair of headphones is real good sound real good and looks real nice the only bad about them is the price but any way they are worthed every dollar.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>VeronicaL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Crystal clear sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Crystal clear sound

Cons: Very expensive

Awesome quality sound.... Great bass, perfect for my dj business.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Junior1981</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Price

Awesome sound and cool style there head turners!!!!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ept78836</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great product, a little pricey</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: sound reproduction

Cons: price a little too high

Have used lots of headsets this one has great low sound and fits/feels snug.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>bighouse427</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love them but 400 really?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durability! and Great Sound Quality!

Cons: Cost

They sound great and recommend them to anyone!!!!! Be prepared fro the cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>bigboog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was very worried about the quality of the sound compared to the price of the headphones. But from the first time I used them I was blown away.
Thank you Dre!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>djCadence</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound quality

Cons: High cost (but worth it)

I dj parttme these headphones&apos; sound is awesome! I highly recommend these headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>eStore.com.au</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product for a great price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have bought products of estore previously, and I have to say there prices smash competitor prices. Bought a genuine Beats pro for 411.00. Can&apos;t beat that!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>UWWisc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound, look,

Incredible sound, look sweet! Def worth it if you got the change.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DjSpeed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones Hands Down</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound,Craftmanship

Cons: Nothin

Very Good headphones,the sound is clea you hear things you didnt even know where in a song.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Monster Beats Pro High Performance Professional Headphones From Monster Pro-tuned Over-Ear - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural - White</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2349614099751042555/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.33&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=Q6SRUMbSFKbF2QWM5oDQCw&amp;ved=0CJIBEPQCMAE4KA</URL>
     <Reviewer>momma123489</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: quality

Cons: brand easily seen so concern over theft

Awesome quality. My son is in love with these headphones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

