<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve Guttenberg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>CNET</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sennheiser HD 650 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2006</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sennheiser&apos;s flagship headphones have high-tech styling, extraordinary bass response, and an extremely comfortable design.

Cons: They&apos;re heavy and very pricey, not to mention ill suited for use with the iPod.

Bottom Line: The formidable Sennheiser HD 650 headphones are fit for a king--and have a price tag to prove it.

We approached Sennheiser&apos;s top headphones, the HD 650, with high expectations, as word of mouth for the product has been overwhelmingly positive. The headphones certainly look the part; the HD 650s&apos; luxurious feel, the thickly padded headband and ear cushions, and the titanium-silver finish leave no doubt--even before you hear them, you can tell these are very special headphones. The HD 650s are pretty big and moderately heavy (9 ounces), but they&apos;r ... e extremely comfortable. We logged many, many hours of listening time and came away thoroughly impressed with their comfort. They retail for $550.
 
The headphones&apos; drivers are hand-selected to ensure precise left/right matching tolerances and feature computer-optimized neodymium magnet systems to minimize distortion. Their lightweight aluminum voice coils ensure accuracy and fast transient response. The HD 650s&apos; 9-foot Y cable is user-replaceable, and that&apos;s a good thing because over the years, cables inevitably break. The cable is terminat ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Richard Black</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>TechRadar UK</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sennheiser HD650</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 2, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The Sennheiser HD650 has been around for a while and has certainly achieved a high reputation among both domestic and professional users.

It&apos;s a smart, no-nonsense model with oval earpieces which seem to fit snugly on every head we tried. There&apos;s plenty of depth to clear prominent ears and the velvet-lined earpads distribute the spring force from the headband, which at first seems rather high, very comfortably. 

We had no discomfort over long listening sessions, though these do seem rather warmer on the ears than other models which give a less firm seal to the head and they sit securely enough to cope with sudden head movements. The lead is highly immune to friction noise, though the headphones sometimes squeak with facial movement, especially if one wears glasses.

Low ... distortion

Peering through the open-back of the HD650, there&apos;s a fine metal mesh, which is Sennheiser&apos;s way of damping the movement of the drivers and reducing resonance. 

Distortion is also claimed to be particularly low, thanks to improvements in the magnet structure, while high-frequency extension is aided by the use of aluminium voice-coil windings. 

Pair matching is claimed to be very good at ±1dB, a more plausible figure than some we&apos;ve seen – bearing in mind that the smallest degree of misalignment on the head (or indeed on a test fixture) can easily contribute a few tenths of a dB of mismatch.

New levels of detail

There is no question that this is a very fine transducer. Like quite a lot of really good hi-fi, it doesn&apos;t always leap out on first hearing as an oustanding product, though it&apos;s clearly highly competent.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joe Minihane</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Electricpig</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sennheiser HD 650</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We love: Incredible sound quality whatever you throw at them, great build quality ....We hate: Pricey, only for hi-fi nuts....Verdict:A stunning piece of kit that&apos;ll bring the very best out of your CD collection These Sennheiser HD 650 cans are all about getting the most out of your vast record collection, even if your got tastes range from Bach to Blur. In fact, the whole idea of these open-backed beasts is to cater for all kinds of tunes. The question is, are they worth that hefty £270 price tag? Read our full Sennheiser HD 650 review now for our verdict. Be under no illusion: if music isn&apos;t the only thing you live for, than the Sennheiser HD 650s are not for you. These headphones are aimed squarely at those who pore over the pages over Mojo and reminisce about the days before music wasn ... &apos;t all downloads and low quality streams. But that&apos;s not to say that they&apos;re absolutely awesome. Plug the Sennheiser HD 650s into your stereo and you&apos;ll soon realise that they&apos;re as good an all-rounder as a fit Freddie Flintoff. We put every genre in our CD collection through them, from bleepy electronica or poseurish New York punk and the results were nothing short of outstanding. Bass heavy tunes were reassuringly thumping, while detailed folkie guitar parts stood out thanks to excellent mid-range and treble. The only thing better are Sennheiser&apos;s one grand HD800s. As we&apos;ve said, though, these are cans very much for audio aficionados. To get the best out of the Sennheiser HD 650s you&apos;ll have to be rocking a decent hi-fi set up. There is an adapter for MP3 players and mobiles, but to make them sing, you&apos;ll want to feeding them CDS rather than shonky MP3s you grabbed while mooching about online. It&apos;s not the only niggle. The open backed style means these are very much for at home listening rather than for taking on long flights and train journeys. Crank the Sennheiser HD 650s on a plane and you&apos;ll quickly be the least popular passenger. Ultimately though, these are quibbles which ignore the Sennheiser HD 650s driving aim. To provide musos with the best quality sound at home. They&apos;re cosy, look the business and sound the right side of amazing. At £270 they&apos;re not cheap, but if you love records more than your family, it&apos;s a price worth paying.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sennheiser HD 650 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent sound quality, comfortable, good bass

Cons: Bulky, expensive, sound leakage

The Sennheiser HD 650 headphones provide reference-quality performance -- at a price. Reviewers describe music as smooth, natural and open. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Firebat5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Accurate and Stunning</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Distinctly non-brittle, and accurate highs.
Perfectly balanced, flat mids.
Bass is accurate, but may lack attack. (could be my amp).

Light weight. Put these things on and you won&apos;t even know they are there.

Comfortable fit. They stay glued to my head (even in head banging sessions), and they don&apos;t give me a headache during long listening sessions.

Open back design. Works well for casual listening when you need/want to hear other loud things (door bell ringing, phone ringing, baby crying, etc).

Price. Paid $350 for mine new. You will have to look long and hard to find a headphone at that price with comparable sound.

Cons: Open back design. If you are listening/working in a loud environment, you will have to depend on louder volumes to attain co ... nsistent non-interupted listening (vs. closed back). Can also be more of a problem (vs. closed back) if liquids are involved.

If you haven&apos;t had the pleasure of listening to a stereo source under headphones this good, do yourself a favor and find a way to listen to these. It truely revolutionizes the experience of listening to recordings. Hands down the cheapest way to get a wonderfully accurate and pleasurable stereo listening experience.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mus1cman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best mid-level audiophile-grade phones available</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Superb sound quality, full over-the-ear design

Cons: Need to be amp&apos;d, sound leakage.

Note to future buyers: These phones do need to be amplified.

These were my first pair of high end headphones I had bought when I was first getting into audio. I had them amplified with a Headroom Total Bithead. (A nice little amp that runs off of AAA&apos;s). They sound awesome. Very neutral headphones. Vocals and individual instruments can be separately heard in clear crisp audio. Very large soundstage as well. These are not bass heavy headphones but hip/hop/rap or techno aren&apos;t Sennheiser&apos;s target consumers. The bass is there just not overpowering like some other phones can be. Sennheiser&apos;s phones have this neutral and well balanced feel that makes it seem like your in a room with ... surround sound rather than wearing headphones.

Last note: I have the sound quality at a 4/5 bars not because it is lacking, but merely because I normally listen to the HD650&apos;s older brother, the HD800s and there really isn&apos;t much of a comparison.

Final note: These phones are the perfect set for anybody wanting to experience the real sound that artists want their listeners to hear.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>strudel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unbeatable for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 18, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sound reproduction is unmatched from anything I have ever heard in my life. All frequencies are reproduced very precisely, bass is very tight and controlled, never boomy of bloated. These headphones will accurately reproduce frequencies I would have thought to be impossible through headphones. Extremely comfortable to the point where you forget you are wearing them after awhile.

Cons: Open design means they do not block sound going in or out. A headphone amp is basically a requirement. High quality media is a must since these will expose every flaw with vivid detail. Expensive until you realize how much you would have to spend on speakers, amps, and whatnot to get similar sound quality.

Anyone I have had who has listen to these is absolutely amazed at the sound q ... uality. The price seems obscene for headphones until you listen to them, then you will think they are a bargain.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superior Unbeatable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I am chuckling as I read the other reviews. I have been an audio junkie for 40 years. I have never heard anything as good as these anywhere near the price range. You can wear these for hours in comfort, too.

Cons: Not really designed for computer junkies. These full range headphones demand more power than most computers put out.

If anyone thinks these sound bad, it is probably the device driving them. Don&apos;t buy these unless you have something with sufficient power. The headphone jack on my home stereo works great, but something like a laptop will need a headphone amplifier.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BUY IT!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Incredible sound detail, expanded base and highs. 

I highly recommend this coupled with the HT Omega Claro Halo sound card which has a built in headphone amp.

If you have the $$$, buy it right now.

Cons: Sounds amazing right out of the box, but a Long burn in time is required (100 hours) for a eargasm experience.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>galpalval</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Slightly bulky, but comfortable.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use my HD650&apos;s every day in radio. I love them! They&apos;re a little bulky, but fit comfortably; sound is full, clear and round. I&apos;m gentle with my cans, but they are designed to take a beating if you tend to be hard on your headphones. I used my last headset (Sennheiser) for 25-years. The product is well built for on air radio professionals.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NeeperVision</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sennheiser HD650 The best I&apos;ve Heard</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Professional Film and Broadcast monitoring. They are very comfortable, you sometimes don&apos;t even realize you have them on. The 650&apos;s reproduce the entire audible sound range. I listen to sound with very high dynamic range (Close lightning strikes, explosions, jet engines, etc) all recorded with state of the art equipment. The 650&apos;s handle these sounds very smoothly and do not collapse at sudden high Db with low frequencies. They reproduce bass like nothing I&apos;ve ever heard. All this; and I haven&apos;t even broken them in yet! (&lt;40 hrs) The only thing I would add is kevlar netting around the cord (I have a cat that likes to chew on cables)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nacnac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These headphones ROCK!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awsome sound quality

Cons: nothing yet

I have gone through lots of headphones but these are the best I have heard for the price. These things sound amazing, the clarity is amazing, each sound frequency is seperated, and sounds like i am sitting in the front row of a live concert. Just beware that these are open aire headphones, and require a high end amp to power them, you don&apos;t want to use these with an Ipod or any other mp3 player because they don&apos;t have enough to power the headphones. I would recommend these for an audiophile enthusist, who enjoys listining music in their home. You can also upgrade the headphone cables because they are interchangable. I would recommend these headphones to anyone who loves good sound quality, and has a high end amp and SACD player.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spiderking</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best headphones ever!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The sennheiser hd650&apos;s are one of the best audiophile headphones money can buy! And I love using them, and they&apos;re the closest thing you can get to natural sound! Get these headphones! Promise you will not be disappointed! Hd650....the best!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent in all respects</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The HD650 is the best I&apos;ve ever put over my ears - and I&apos;ve been an audiophile most of my 60 years. The sound is full and clear (response seems smooth throughout), and their construction seems completely solid. The fit is very comfortable. Worth the cost.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ap34</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Very Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very natural headphone. Extremely comfertable. Everything positive about this headphone that is stated in previous reviews is true. I use these mostly on my computer and have a creative x-fi titanium sound card, and there is no need for an amp if you have a good sound card with you`re pc. Don&apos;t use equalizer imo. Amp is always nice but if you are going to be using these mostly on you`re computer just pair it up with a top of the line sound card. You wont regret it.

Cons: The price is too high. Try and get the best deal you can and it will be worth it.

Really comfertable. You can wear them for as long as you want (12 + hours) and you wont get a headace or have the urge to take them off. They are really that comfertable. Nice to have top of the line headphones. I use thes ... e at home and cant wait to go home to throw these on and listen to music and games. Wish I could hear all sound like I hear sound through these headphones, if that makes sense. As good as headphones get without getting insanely expensive.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MadKat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hey, Nice Cans</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nicest sounding headphones ive ever heard, comfortable. I have it paired with an Asus Xonar Essence

Cons: I honestly dont think they are worth the price tag.
The HD 550&apos;s are probably just as good for less $$

Ive got my 2.66ghz i7 oc&apos;d to 3.82ghz on asus p6t delux, 12gb Dominator mem, 2x 300gb Veliciraptors in Raid0, 1TB wd black hdd, cooler master V8, BFG 285 OXE, Asus Xonar Essence, Lg blu-ray burner and 22x light scribe dvd burner, HAF case, and Corsair 1000w modular psu,Vista 64 Premium, Hanns-g 28&quot; hdcp monitor and dell ultrabrite rotatable 24&quot; in portrait, and Sennheiser HD650 cans. Getting a couple more items from the egg to finish her up. First build- turned out awsome! got almost all components from newegg cause they are FAST and best customer service aro ... und
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Buddy Lee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unreal quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Absolutely unreal quality, the finest headphones I have ever had the pleasure of listening to in terms of accuracy and precision. Being used in a music studio. Used them for gaming once and was literally confusing sound effects as being the real world. (heard banging &quot;in the other room&quot; in Silent Hill 3, took the headphones off to find where it was coming from, after this happened a few times I realized it was the game!) Have never experienced that with any other headphones.

Incredibly accurate bass for 95% of mastering situations. Mindblowingly good for classical, jazz, rock, metal, new age, movie soundtracks, standard dancehall music 30hz and up. (&quot;kick to the chest&quot; stuff, 808 miami bass)

Cons: Not as good for the other 5% for underground dance music, experimenta ... l electronic infrasound bass and things meant to be experienced 120db at 20hz or greater in the real world. Bass may be a little less in sheer volume for some mastering situations such as Drum and Bass or Dubstep where levels above 5.1 AC3 theater reference levels are all but required by the content.

Headphone damage is even possible above reference. :( Don&apos;t know if it was an overenthusiastic volume setting or an accidental burst of sound from the mixer board but looking to replace the now rattling Sennheisers. The Sony&apos;s connected to the same jacks at the same volume experienced no such damage. (and put out greater deeper bass at the same volume, though less accurately)

If Sennheiser made a longer excursion (deeper bass response, louder bass ability, and less risk of damage) version these headphones would beat everyone and I wouldn&apos;t even bother to compare or shop for others, I can&apos;t see how they could be topped.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>space_jaggy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good, but not for me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 28, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very clear sound, the bass is very precise. These headphones are perfect for piano, and great for everything else. The design is very nice and the headphones are comfortable to wear for extended periods of time. They are great for listening to concerts.

Cons: If there&apos;s such think as too much bass, these are it. In fact, when you listen to a track with realistic warfare recorded, gunshots make your ears pop. For some it&apos;s a good thing, for me, I like the style of AKG K701 headphones that only have the very very low tones so powerful. 
Also the HD650s have a tendency to sometimes roll off highs, the bass and fullness of sound sometimes seems to overpower sounds like vocals.

CAUTION! Extremely powerful in low to low-med range. Require an amplifier to sound good (or at ... least loud enough to tell) Beware, these headphones make bad recordings sound horrid, and make good recordings sound amazing.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>loc125</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great SOUND!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: this headphones sound quality is unmatched, i matched this headphones with the FiiO E17 which is also hard to get your hands on, and the sound is very clear and pleasing. Now i can see why this headphones got such a high review, it is worth every penny.

Cons: Price, Newegg has it at retail, dont know why its at this price, they need to give on the price a little!
- expensive
- tight on head, its brand new, i have to wear it in.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Plastic_Druid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Product Review</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sennheiser HD 650 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The sound is amazing. If you really want to listen to music and enjoy the performance of the musicians and timbre of the instruments and the beauty of the human singing voice there is little touch these little beauties.

Cons: Nothing really. They&apos;re pricey but when you look at the build quality and then listen to the brilliant sound you can understand why they cost a lot.

Luscious sound and traditional Sennheiser build quality. If you love music, try these out, but be warned, you won&apos;t want to give them back. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spike Da Peke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The King Is Dead. Long Live the King!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My beloved AKG 701&apos;s inexplicably died recently. I was left with something of a dilemma. I really did love those phones, but they took hundreds of hours to break-in,and even after several years use sometimes felt as much clinical as musical. So, I began to shop around. I looked at the Ultrasone 900&apos;s, the Beyerdynamic T70&apos;s, the Grado RS2i, and finally, the Sennheiser HD650s. Briefly, the Ultrasone 900&apos;s felt poorly controlled, both classical and jazz recordings felt punchy and perhaps a bit screechy. They seem lacking of tightness in both bass and high frequency areas. I very much wanted to like the Beyerdynamic T70&apos;s. But, I must admit to a strong sense of disappointment. Like most phones from that company, then T70 is very comfortable. But, like most closed phones, the bas ... s is a bit uncontrolled. I would never accuse them of being flabby, but coming after the AKG 701&apos;s, they seem to lack precision. The Grado&apos;s were simply uncomfortable. I have never cared for on-the-ear cans and the RS2i&apos;s confirmed my preference. So, finally, the Sennheiser HD650s. I was immediately struck by the musicality of these headphones. Trying them for the first time, I found myself going from one CD to another, one Apple Lossless File to another. I was the proverbial child in a candy store, trying one treat after another. My old CDs and files seemed new: I was hearing new material, unheard lines, staging and detail. The low growling bass and tuba of Wagner&apos;s vorspiel to Siegfried (Karajan and the Berlin Philharmonic, 1969) seemed again terrifying, as they were when I first heard them at a performance of the Ring in Seattle. In Bir??lli and Pastorius&apos;s Stuttgart Aria I felt as if I could see Pastorius dancing across the stage, bass in hand, delivering one impossible riff after another. In Kurt Weill&apos;s Das Berliner Requiem, I can almost see the small, male chorus, leaning forward as they deliver one pensive, pouncing line after another.A great set of headphones re-creates the stage in a new, and more directly accessible way. With these headphones, Sennheiser moved us another step forward into Glenn Gould&apos;s more perfect concert???that is to say a recording. They bring my music files to a livelier, and perhaps more life-like place. There is very little more that I could ask of a headphone. I have one minor criticism: the top surface of the headband seems to be made of a rather cheap glossy plastic. The material seems very much out of place on a [$] headphone.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>well worth it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Incredible sound, extremely comfortable, and pretty. I have these running through a combo amp/DAC which bumped the sound up to a whole new level.

Cons: price i guess, but you get what you pay for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Giznary</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Spectacular</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones ooze quality. From the ultra-light materials (everyone I hand them to says &quot;wow they&apos;re light) to the super comfortable ear-pads (even with glasses on) everything is top-notch. That said it is no surprise that they sound spectacular as well. Though they are expensive (I&apos;m often a bit embarrassed when someone asks what they cost) they are worth every penny for those who love great sound.
Well produced music is positively dreamlike. I&apos;ve found my listening time with Nine Inch Nails has gone way way up for instance. You can hear every sample and every layer.
Layering is a good thing to mention as well. You can hear EVERY layer with these phones. A good visual example (of the sound) would be a diorama. With normal phones you are looking at the sound diorama from ... the front, and the layers make a flat image. With the 650s it&apos;s like you can peek around behind each layer of the diorama, and see each layer completely on it&apos;s own

Cons: I know I&apos;m just an echo at this point, but if you have a beloved recording that is of low quality (and I&apos;m talking production quality here) you may find it hard to listen to. One general example is Rock music (designed to play on very loud, but often low-fidelity speakers) in general takes some getting used to as you hear everything in perfect clarity, and somehow that&apos;s not right! The 650s do not distort with high volumes so songs seem to lose that &quot;loud&quot; sound normally heard in rock music.

Also they are large. Just plain large. I get the occasional &quot;whatever princess Leia&quot; from friends. Usually I respond by putting them on their head and they start to smile, yes they sound good enough to wear in public and not care.
Last they are audio-transparent. If you are listening at lower (safer) volumes you can hear the outside world. This can be a pro (listening for a sleeping baby in my case) but should be noted for those with noisy room-mates or neighbors.

If you plan to go mobile as I did, consider a headphone amp. The 650s sound good without one, but spectacular (in terms of separation and clarity) with one. The headroom total bit-head has worked well in my case.

Lossless audio recommended. Be prepared to feel driven to re-rip or re-buy low quality recordings. Three late nights after I bought the 650s I had a nice stack of .flac rips on my HDD. 

For fun listen to Tool&apos;s &quot;Aenima,&quot; track 7 (can&apos;t say the name here!) at about 1:45 you can hear (relatively clear on the 650s) Maynard saying &quot;consume, be fruitful and multiply.&quot; Even knowing that this bit is there I can&apos;t pick it out on other phones or speakers. Subliminal, not so much on the 650.

Sorry if I&apos;m gushing... I just love these things!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>att</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bass Enthusiast&apos;s Dream</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Going to make this short and to the point, if you are looking for a pair of headphones to put out some DEEP and powerfully accurate BASS these are for you. I have been looking for years for headphones to sound like this with my rap and hip-hop collection and I&apos;ve finally found what I was looking for. Obviously if bass is not for you, just leave it alone in your settings and you will be fine. I don&apos;t want anyone to read this and think the bass is overpowering; it&apos;s only loud because I raised my bass settings and used the bass boost in my X-Fi sound card. That being said, with these settings I can honestly say I am finally satisfied with the bass that comes out of my headphones.

Cons: None

As other reviewers said the sound quality is crystal clear and the headphones a ... re incredibly comfortable. Bass lovers look no further.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Poraim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great for endurance gaming</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I&apos;ve owned many other headphones over the years, and all of them have hurt my ears during extended gaming sessions (8+ hours). The HD650s don&apos;t actually touch my ears, so they don&apos;t hurt. Because of their open design and cloth surface, they don&apos;t make my ears sweat over time (the Bose TriPort causes that problem). After owning them for about 2 years, I can say they are the only comfortable headphones I have ever owned.

Cons: When I first put them on, they fit a little snug, meaning that they put more inward pressure on the sides of the head than I&apos;d like. It&apos;s never painful or annoying though, and over time I learned to appreciate the fact that they never move around on my head.

I use them with an integrated PC sound card, so I&apos;ve probably never heard their full soun ... d potential. They sound good anyway. It&apos;s not super loud without an amp, but it&apos;s enough for gaming or normal-volume music. The pads are replaceable when they get old. Also, I&apos;ve dropped them probably 100+ times, and they work perfectly with no damage. They&apos;re built to last a lifetime.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>andrewbk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic cans, not for the iPod crowd.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fantastic sounding, comfortable

Cons: Large, not very portable

I have had these headphones for about 4 months now and can safely say they are the best headphones I&apos;ve ever owned.

I will start by saying these headphones are NOT meant for use with an iPod or other MP3 players. An iPod only has enough power to properly power small headphones. Headphones of this size need some sort of amplification to truly be taken advantage of.

Once properly amplified these are fantastically accurate and a pleasure to listen to. I listen to a lot of different music from classical to hip hop and I&apos;ve yet to find any genre that these can&apos;t handle.

At first they weren&apos;t the most comfortable headphones ever but the headband seems to have loosened up and I can now listen f ... or many hours without any discomfort.

Bottom Line:
If you are looking for great sounding headphones for use at home and don&apos;t want to spend a fortune, the HD650&apos;s won&apos;t disappoint.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Derek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My opinions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 19, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I am by no means an audiophile so take my opinions how you will. I recently upgraded from a set of Bose Tri-Ports which I consider to be a very nice set of headphones. Here are my opinions on some of the issues that are floating around about these headphones...

The HD650&apos;s require an amp: I would have to disagree that an amp is absolutely necessary. On an iPod, you have to crank up the volume to almost 90% to get a decent punch but any decent stereo should power them fine. That&apos;s not to say it would be a great investment. An external DAC or sound card would be a better starting point IMO.

The HD650&apos;s &quot;color&quot; the sound: If anyone ever tells you this, just laugh and walk away.

The HD650&apos;s sound muddy until around 100 hours of listening: I observed no change in ... sound through the first several hundred hours.

The HD650&apos;s are too tight around the ears: They produce around 3-4 times the pressure of my Bose and take some getting used to but they seem to &quot;loosen up&quot; over time.

Cons: These headphones are so precise with the highs that some types of music become unbearable. For example, if you listen to a lot of sequenced music or music with drum or vocal samples, you will start to notice the &quot;hiss&quot; of the samples when they occur. This is of course a Pro if you think about it. The only other Con i can think of is that you will have to ditch your MP3 collection or at least go through it and weed out the bad quality songs.

As for music choices, I have found that anything goes. The HD650&apos;s handle every genre of music beautifully. Anything with vibrato or synthesizers such as electronic or low strings (cello and bass violin) sound remarkable.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: none

Cons: The bass, mid, high, is very very low qulity. It should only worth $100. returned in 1 week. a lot of $150 head phone is better than this head phone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zman9700</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I, like j, do not actually own these headphones. One of my friends does though. I go to his house sometimes just to listen to these headphones. Right now he is in Europe for a couple weeks and I am sitting here writing this review listening to Daft Punk of these headphones. They are by far the best headphones I have ever heard. I build pretty high quality subwoofers (last one was 400w rms) and I would rank these headphones on the same level as that (in terms of how much I like it, not bass). They do have excellent bass response at any volume level. He has a 
Penguin amp to power them and I am using my X-fi Elite Pro. They are very comfortable. I have been wearing them for almost 3 days straight (and will be wearing them for the next week and a half).

Cons: I have to go to m ... y friend&apos;s house to use them.

I will buy these one day when I have money (may be a while). They are pretty high on my list of things I need to buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It&apos;s got great sound that you can turn up if you need to (it handles lots of power), yet at low volumes it&apos;s still acurate. It&apos;s well made as with all Sennheiser gear. Cord length is perfect, and the cord is quite flexible (but never flex a cord too much). The 1/4&quot; plug by default is wonderfull to see. Anything deserving enough to have this plugged into it should use 1/4&quot; plugs instead of the 1/8&quot; on most consumer level gear. The fit on these are WONDERFULL compared to other headphones. I&apos;ve busted many a headset in my day, but I don&apos;t think I could ever ruin these. As for the sound quality, the bass is exceptional. In fact, there really is ALOT that most people are missing with lesser equipment. Also, I like that if you yank on the cord from the headset, it simply disconnects where ... it plugs into the speaker shroud.

Cons: Cable could have been a bit better quality (silver plated OFHPC at minimum), but it&apos;s better than almost all others out there. Dirt tends to collect easily on the soft plush fabric. One could easily dent the metal grill, but I haven&apos;t yet. It would take quite the force to do, but it still could happen. It wouldn&apos;t affect the sound, however. Not really any issues to be honest.

Excellent sound quality as you probably already know if you are looking at this fine product. Many would ask, is it really worth the money? I would answer in a heartbeat, &quot;absolutely!&quot;
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>specialist812003</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones EVER!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great for music, great for movies. I owned the HD 555 headphones before these, they don&apos;t ever compare. When the volume is louder, the 555&apos;s hissed and popped, not so with these. Watch Transformers 2 at the beginning when the Fallen slams his foot on the ground with any other headphones, you&apos;ll know what I&apos;m talking about. I can hear things on movies and music I didn&apos;t know was there before. Also, these are very well made, nice box, heavy duty cord and the phones are really light.

Cons: Price, but you get what you pay for.
Headphones are a little tight, but hopefully they&apos;ll loosen over time.

These brought together my home theatre.

LG 42&quot; 120hz lcd tv, Sony 7.1 receiver, PS3 slim 250gb, Sennheiser HD 650, Logitech Harmony One remote, Monster HTS 1000 MK III su ... rge protector, Monster Cable HD 2000 hdmi cables
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mochimon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>New Music</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 8, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones are of the upper-most echylon of sound reproduction devices. They reproduce sounds so well that after you buy them you need to start thinking about getting better audio sources(like higher bitrate digital files, digital to analog converters, and headphone amps).

Cons: the head band is a bit tight, and personally does not fit my head perfectly. When i have a headache it&apos;s a bit of a pain to wear these. but people have said i have a big head, so...

The greatest thing about these cans for me is that after getting them all of the music i thought i had experienced fully has become almost brand new. everything sounds so much better that its like rediscovering the music. In that respect they have more than payed for themselves - i have countless hours of ... listening satisfaction from all of my old stuff.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jamescam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>If you are considering the HD650...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Take it from me. Buy the HD600 instead. If you value realism and accuracy like I do, there is no doubt that you will find the HD600 more to your liking. I own both the HD650 and HD600 (retailer won&apos;t let me return the HD650). The HD650 is a good headphone, but the exaggerated lows are unacceptable for such an expensive headphone. The HD600 is cheaper, and in this case, absolutely superior - could not be more pleased.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>j</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: i have never heard better quality from a headset. I do not actually own these, my friend&apos;s brother is an audio engineer and he brought them over. I cannot believe how crystal clear the audio is, highs, mids, and lows! they create a surround sound effect, and are very precise.
i used these gaming, listening to music, and watching movies. i had an available Sony surround sound system set up but i could not take these off of my ears. SO BEAUTIFUL!

Cons: the only con is that i don&apos;t own them. i can not afford it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Avalon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredible!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: After using a pair of $100 Senn&apos;s that I thought were pretty good, I&apos;m blown away by the huge difference these make right out of the box. The sheer fidelity of these &apos;phones is immediately apparent; highs are clearer &amp; crisper, bass is tighter and much more solid, but the mids and vocals are what truly stand out. Very smooth mids with no harshness with any type of music at any volume level, and the vocals take center stage. Well-balanced, revealing, quick response time. It&apos;s like stepping up from a pair of bookshelves/receiver to separates/high quality floorstanders. I have a headphone amp in the mail...will report back when they&apos;ve settled in.

Cons: I have to wait for them to break-in--there&apos;s some edginess to them that should smooth out in time. My last pair of Senn&apos;s we ... re almost returned until mid-way through a track when they suddenly relaxed (around 80 hours of so listening time) and sounded almost completely different.

Well built, solid construction. Nice finish. A tad heavy, but better than being flimsy. Comfortable. Comes with a nifty hinged &amp; padded case. Great service as usual by the &apos;Egg.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shaddix</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good headphones o_ob</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I don&apos;t know much about headphones, I will update this review as I can. These came in the mail two days ago and I&apos;m still waiting on my DAC/AMP so I can actually test them out. I currently have a stock x-fi that i&apos;m using out of my pc. I also have a pair of 595s and they sound about the same as the 650s coming from my pc. I assume the reason for this is because the x-fi is so bad it is limiting the audio so badly you can&apos;t hear a difference. I will update this when I get my source and amp in.

Cons: I will let you know when I get my dac/amp~!

It was tight as hell on my head when I first got them. I put them around a pillow I have overnight to loosen them a little and its better. Do not put them around a box it will mess up the earpads. 

Also newegg&apos;s price for the ... se is a bit high. I got them for about 260 after rebates....
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gipper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Never Been Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I have owned several different Sennheisers over the years and have never been disappointed with any of their product. 

But, the difference between these and their lower end models [ HD 280 Pro, EH 150 ] is stunning. 

Nearly any song that I have listened I can hear notes that just can not be reproduced accurately and/or clearly on most other headphones.

Cons: Not much of a con but these headphones absolutely require amplification before they can live up to their potential. The nature of these headphones means that they are not meant to be directly connected to most any source [ ipod, cd player, etc. ] without an amp in between.

Also, low bit rate audio files or degraded analog sources can sound far worse on these phones since they will pick up on any fla ... ws that are present. This is not a flaw of the headphones just the source audio.

One of the best reference class headphones that money can buy and can outperform other reference grade headphones that cost far more money.

For me, I have no reason to buy any other headphones again..... at least until Sennheiser makes the next in this line.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>teslaguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best headphones.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great sound reproduction. You can hear things in these headphones that you could never hear before.

Cons: an ipod doesnt power them very well, makes lots of lossy music sound terrible and will make you want your entire music collection to be in 24 bit.

BUY THESE.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lou Manchu</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice, but...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simply the best headphones I&apos;ve ever heard, period.

Cons: Require about 350 hours of burn-in to sound their finest.
Require an amp to sound even remotely decent, otherwise the bass is bloated and muddy and there&apos;s no high range at all.
You can hear every imperfection in low-quality recordings. If you plan on getting these, use them with a good vinyl setup or CD setup, or at least make sure the music you&apos;re listening to is encoded in a lossless format. FLAC is best.

Keep in mind that these are 300?, so they require a lot of voltage swing(±2v), but if you balance them this shouldn&apos;t be a problem.
I recommend a good tube amp, such as a SOHA or any of the Millet amps. I use a Xiang Sheng 708B that I&apos;ve heavily modified and it drive the HD650&apos;s without a problem.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones are quite possibly the most comfortable and best sounding cans I have ever had the pleasure of using. I received a pair of these as a gift over the holidays earlier this year and have enjoyed every minute of their use since then. The earpads are extremely comfortable to the point where you really don&apos;t notice that you&apos;re wearing them after a while. In terms of sound quality, it&apos;s really not worth mentioning what is already given. Sennheiser isn&apos;t known as one of the best in the industry for nothing. These are, in my opinion, the best headphones one can own. Note that after their burn-in period you will notice a much better quality of sound, especially in the bass.

Cons: I honestly can&apos;t find anything that is inherently bad with these headphones. Granted, they ... do require an appropriate output source for your audio and are open, which allows environmental noises in, but both of these are required for the quality of the sound.

I used to use a USB headset as I am quite heavily into online gaming. When I received these headphones I purchased a high quality sound card knowing that the cheap one I previously only used for speakers wasn&apos;t going to cut it. I went with one of Creative&apos;s X-Fi cards and (despite a lot of the controversy over their drivers) have found it to be a nice match for the HD650&apos;s. I will note that for my purposes I don&apos;t find myself needing an amp to drive these cans. To my ears, the sound is superb, though I have absolutely no doubts that a nice amp would indeed improve their sound quality. Also, as a sidenote to anyone that does lots of online gaming and is looking at picking these up, I highly recommend also grabbing a clip-on microphone. Newegg used to carry one by Zalman (which is what I am currently using) that works amazing well and just clips on to the headphone cable. Wrapping it around the cable from the clip to the connection on your computer makes for a very nice setup.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking into buying headphones to do ruff mixes when I am on the road. It was between the AKG K 701 and the Sennheiser HD650. I couldn&apos;t be happier with my decision. At first you need to break them in which might take a couple weeks of listening to music. As time goes they get better. I would recommend an external hi-fi amp to use with them. They can&apos;t run off your traditional computer headphone jack or ipod. I wear them for long period of time and are one of the most comfortable headphone to possibly wear. I would recommend this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Really, really accurate. slightly laid back presentation. Superb clarity. Absolutely studio grade. Easily replaceable cord! Trust me, this last WILL make you happy;)

Cons: Note the &quot;studio grade&quot;. I mean that. Imperfections in your source material show up easily. And yes, you will know it&apos;s the source not these phones.

I own an 8 y.o. pair of the 600 model (predecessor, 98% same). Still fantastic, still my reference. I strongly suggest at some point you pick up a quality headphone amp. Really worth it. Can double as an ultra clean preamp.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DejaNoob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I guess i ca...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Once you start you wont stop... When wearing these bad boys you will know that they are there for the first minute or 2 after that you will forget you are wearing them. The sound is too clear if there is such a thing. I went from Bose to these, Sennheiser takes the cake Bose is over rated! The best headphones ever owned and probably ever own.

Cons: I hate all other headphones now they just don&apos;t sound this good. Price is a bit steep but it is worth it once you experience the greatest headphones out there.
The only other con is that I don&apos;t have 2 pairs!!!

I guess i can live with switching these around form Computer too TV for the time being. I will either have to get another pair or a better sound setup. :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tRens</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I got them so cheap I can&apos;t believe it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Well they cover my whole ear... 

When I put them on I immediately noticed a huge difference from my current headset.

I have these and a set of PC166..

Cons: Nothing about the product...

I just wish I could find a microphone that was as awesome.

I ordered these the day before Black Friday. The next day I woke up and while looking around Newegg I saw that they went down 200 bucks due to it being said day.

Contacted Newegg support via email and received my 200 bucks back! lucky me and awesome Newegg.

I wish I had a mic that would attach via USB and didn&apos;t damage my HD650s</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quality Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Really excellent audio fidelity, Modular, Best audio quality for the price range, High quality build (metal, Kevlar, soft, comfortable durable fabrics), Very comfortable and low temperature, really just some of the best headphones in the world

Cons: Price (it&apos;s not too bad if your looking for reference quality), everyone around you can hear you, High energy requirements</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DrizzyDrake</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WHEWW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i got 6 pairs of these for my studio. theyre hands down the BEST headphones you will EVER buy. if it wasnt for these headphones my album, thank me later wouldnt have been as good of quailty as it is.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sound Design Student</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My First Time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 30, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased these headphones for use in my sound classes. I really like these headphones and i am able to wear them for long periods of time with my glasses on. Since they are open ear for production sound they aren&apos;t the greatest since they leak, in and out. Its hard to tell if what you are hearing is from the headphones or just outside noise. For that i&apos;ll just have to buy a different pair that are closed. For my studio classes they are wonderful and i do not have to turn down the volume. Also i&apos;m not isolated from people when they talk to me since I can still hear them...somewhat.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CWoolery</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredibly detailed headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had the pleasure of auditioning a pair of these against my Beyerdynamic DT-770&apos;s and my AKG K240&apos;s. The Dt-770&apos;s took the crown in the bass department because of their sealed nature, but the Sennheiser 650&apos;s were a tad more clear with imaging. My main use for headphones is for studio mixing, so a bright sounding muddy pair of cans is the last thing I want. I would trust the 650&apos;s on a mix any day of the week, and if I ever break my Beyerdynamics I&apos;m definitely buying a pair of these!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tychonides</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>transcendent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones seem to physically disappear once the music starts. There is no barrier between you and what must have been in the composer&apos;s head. Sound is just beautiful through out the entire range of thses incredibly comfortable headphones. I&apos;ve owned professional headphones before but these Sennheiser&apos;s are in a class by themselves.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HD650 / Superb Monitoring Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We have been using several pairs of Sennheiser HD650 headphonesas our very best monitoring reference in remote recording sessionswith the famous, restored Wanamaker pipe organ in the Grand Court of the the downtown [...]/Wanamaker store in Philadelphia. The headphones are driven by nothing less than Grace Design 902 headphone amps.These headphones absolutely rival the sound quality from the very best,customized, fixed-place studio monitor speaker systems at a mere fraction of the cost. They render a brilliant, clean sound that reaches way down to the 16 Hz fundamentals (at zero recording level!) that this huge organ so easily belts out at full tilt. Mids and highs with the HD650&apos;s are as smooth as silk too.The current project is Christmas music featuring the Wanamaker organ accompanied b ... y the Philadelphia Brass. Brass pickup was by anotherfantastic Sennheiser product, a matched pair of the new Sennheiser MKH-8040 cardioid microphones. You may hear the results this Fall when the Wanamaker Christmas CDcomes out on the Gothic Label. The disc may be available in Macy&apos;s stores nationally. Tune in, because every single note on this upcoming album was meticulously monitored by HD650 headphones!Alex Martin, Assistant Recording Engineerdsp Recording/ Chicago
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>notsofast-there</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Get serious, hear?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been using the venerable Sennheiser HD 580 Precision headphones for many years now in recording and studio applications where open-air phones can thus be used. As a recording engineer of some merit, I can easily afford most any set of headphones, (I refuse to call them &apos;cans&apos;) so it becomes a matter of sound quality and comfort, in that order, which dictates the ones I choose. I meant to get the 650s when they first came to my attention, but I procrastinated, as some of us do.I did finally get a set of the HD 650s, which naturally should sound better than the 580s. Did I say sound better? Not to disparage the 580s, which are very good headphones, but this is a good example wherein you most definitely get what you pay for. I have never heard anything so exquisite coming from a set of ... production, professional quality, reference headphones! And I have tried them all. That&apos;s right. All. From the total lack of unnecessary features, protuberances, gewgaws, thick, heavy, clumsy cables and more: from the sheer engineering prowess displayed in the utterly clean sound and the immediate lack of mundane style, these headphones demonstrate the nexus of all that is significant in why do anyone in the recording industry use them at all: they sound absolutely fabulous, are the most comfortable out there and are a bargain for the price. I needn&apos;t go into all the &quot;Wine Spectator&quot;-like reviews and embellish upon the &quot;sound&quot; these headphones make. All I can really say here is how completely impressed I am with every aspect of these headphones. There are none I would rather wear all day long.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>good sound</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best dynamic headphones, along with HD580 and HD600</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Best sound I&apos;ve ever experienced, period. Once I owned a pair of $7K Dyn&apos;s (Contour 3.3), fed through the Creek and Arcam amps. I must admit I prefer the sound of Senn&apos;s.

Cons: Obviously they are expensive. Feel free to get the HD600 and HD580 instead. Honestly, you will not loose much in sound quality, if any. HD590 and HD595 are very good, but not the same as HD580, HD600 and HD650.

These should sound amazing straight out any laptop, PC or MP3 player. To get &quot;the sound&quot;, try a dedicated CD player (or changer) coupled with a decent headphone amp. For a reasonably priced amp, google &quot;PIMETA&quot;. Unbelievable sound below $200. 

And no, you don&apos;t need to give up your MP3&apos;s, unless they are encoded at 128Kbps-fixed or worse. I have mine encoded with &quot;lame&quot; with the &quot;-- ... preset standard&quot; option and I am yet to hear a difference.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NightWoundsTime</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for studios!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2006</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This phone is the absolute best value in audiophile headphones. Beware, though, that it WILL NOT sound good with standard headphone jacks found in and around most studios or professional sound applicatons. Why? Because these are extremely high impedance headphones and require a headphone amplifier to truly shine.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>James</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Make sure this is what you want</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 20, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I was a bit apprehensive about buying these at first. I knew they sounded good, but they are expensive. So going against all judgement I bought them, and have never regretted it. I listen mostly to rock, but also enjoy jazz, classical, and pretty much everything but rap, hip- hop, and yeah. These shine with everything. Rock I have found to be most prevalent. It has the deep bass and the good lows that you want to hear but it doesn&apos;t over power thigh crisp highs of the crashing cymbals, and after that I still am rocking my head to the driving mid-range that is shining. Nothing is left out, nothing is out of balance, when it comes to audio the way it was meant to be heard this is the way to go. You will find that it is worth every cent that you pay for it as well. Considering I would b ... uy them just for the sound, they are also so comfortable. I listen to these whenever I can.

Cons: They will make you hate your stereo. Also MP3, AAC, and WMA won&apos;t cut it, you want lossless. SACD and DVDA are even better. Nothing else can compare, these are the only way you will listen to music.

Headphone amps are expensive but worth it if you want higher volume levels. I recommend LaRocco Audio for that. iPod Classic drives them decently, not loud but an OK listening level, and they don&apos;t compromise quality.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>xyvyx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>ditto</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: crystal clear

Cons: squeezed my head a bit much at first

there are plenty of great reviews here, so I&apos;ll save us both time and say simply: if you have the means, I highly reccomend picking them up :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Newb audiophile</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 24, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I used them everyday since 6 month from now and they are just superb. The only bad thing about them is the cable that somehow always gets stuck on something ha ha ha so strange. As a beginner audiophile they are solid entrance to the audio world.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chazb0t</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I can&apos;t even describe it with words, it is like listening to silk or being in the recording studio when the song was recorded. It&apos;s as if I am listening to every song again for the first time. I just got them this morning and I have spent all day going through thousands and thousands of songs to hear the difference.

Cons: I wish all of my MP3s we&apos;re 320kbps+... it really is true... these headphones are so good that sometimes you can hear the flaws from the actual recordings or from compressing the songs into MP3 format or a smaller bitrate, but it is a minor complaint... and it isn&apos;t the headphones&apos; fault.

I know nothing about music and I am not an audiophile, but I love sennheiser and after using cheaper models HD202s and earbuds and others for years and years on my co ... mputer and Ipods I decided to go all the way and get the best headphones they make... all I can say is wow.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Souji K.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sometimes a ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nobody lies about how great these headphones are. These are as clear as it gets, and accurate for that matter. Incredibly neutral tone with such transparent sound that it made me think my stereo turned on for a second the first time i played something with them. Everything sounds like its supposed to (if the source is junk, it&apos;ll sound so!). They stay clear up to VERY loud volumes, and the only way to pump them up that loud is to use an amplifier anyway. The velvet earcups makes you feel classy the moment you put them on, theyre super comfortable (generally, though sometimes it feels like i can never adjust them and get it right) and of course, they look cool.

Cons: The paint started flaking off on the headband, but whatever, ive had these for a while. The open backs allow you ... to hear everything around you and for everyone around you to join in on your fun (but crank them up and most sounds are gone). Some people may prefer a different (probably warmer) tone, kind of like the bose sound (bleh). People will frequently walk up to me and say HEY ARE THOES SPEAKERS TOO? Once you use these too much, normal headphones make you sick.

sometimes a hair will get stuck between the driver and cause a buzzing sound. Make sure you have a powerful source or an amplifier (a good one, youll notice it if it doesnt sound too great) and theyre kinda heavy so please be respectful and dont drop them!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave-JtFYT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These things shine with a headphone amp!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The HD-650 headphones are remarkable! Their superb clarity, imaging, and comfort make them ideal for...just about anything (except travel)! I HIGHLY recommend using these through a good headphone amp. They take a little more juice than most headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Remarkable!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones are remarkable! Their clarity, imaging, and comfort make them ideal for...just about anything! They shine when used with a headphone amp.

Cons: These take a little more juice than most other headphones. I highly recommend using them through a good headphone amplifier.

Sennheiser has never let me down. I am very happy with this purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HD650</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent dynamic sound, which a lot of space. Open-air, which means you&apos;ll get some decent soundstage with these. The sound has a real texture with these phones, it makes it sound very detailed and smooth.

Cons: Many think they are &quot;colored&quot; and &quot;veiled&quot; out of the box, but after burning them in they sound very good. I&apos;ve purchased an amplifier for mine, which helps a lot. Also, not suited best for hard rock music.

You will need an amplifier of some sort, these are 300ohm headphones. Straight out of your mp3 player or computer will not do these phones justice. Even hooking them to the headphone output of your speakers will help.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Reputation is well deserved</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones do make justice to their reputation. After 100h of burning in, they are by far the best I have tried (and I have been listening carefully to headphones for more than 10 years). You should use a headphone amplifier. They are good without one, but brilliant with one. Also, very comfortable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mcdelaug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No finer headphone exists</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2006</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nearly perfect reproduction of all the detail present in your music, dynamic range extends an octav eabove the range of the human ear for both bass and treble, very comfortable

Cons: high impedance means that you may need an amp to get adeqaute volume from smaller devices (iPod, etc), large size invites ridicule from coworkers, dynamic design allows other sto hear what you hear whether they like it or not

I bought a set of HD 680s several years ago and thought that there could not be much improvement with the 650s. But now that I have had the 650s for seeral months, the improvement is subtle, but consistent. After you listen to these headphones, you will not be able to listen to anything else. Even my home system sounds inadequate comapred to them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Geibys</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones are simply amazing, crisp clear with a great amount of bass, I&apos;m currently using the with the Asus Xonar Essence STX on PC.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GSTER</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One Of The Best Headphones Out There !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>VERY SMOOTH OVERALL SOUND WITH EXTENDED BASS RESPONSE.HIGHS ARE ALL THERE BUT NOT HARSH AT ALL.EXCELLENT DETAIL AT ALL FREQUENCIES.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>musicproducer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BEST PRODUCTION HEADPHONES</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you produce music professionally, these headphones are for you.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Arnold</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT, but no for everyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>One of the best headphones ever, but it is hard to drive. you cannot use iPod or Laptop to drive it. With an dedicated amplifier, it will be perfect.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gamji</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awsome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awsome

Cons: None

Just buy a pair... trust me</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Sennheiser HD 650 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/743847234357497424/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.27&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=2KORUNmgNcfw2QX38YDIBg&amp;ved=0CJQBEPQCMAE4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bojo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Musician&apos;s Friend</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Crap.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2006</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I can&apos;t believe I payed so much for these. They aren&apos;t nearly warm enough for professional studio use, and are severely lacking in pop and verve.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

