<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Computerhobbyist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound; Comfortable; Compact; Good Bass; Lightweight; Good Value; Durable; Stylish

A brisk winter morning. Bright sunshine. Frigid conditions. Snow on the ground. The bus stop. A cool breeze pressing against the face. A tense day ahead. Sudden warmth and comfort over the ears. Sonic accuracy. The morning commute. Relaxation. Perfect. The Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass headphones plunge you into a stunning world of deep bass performance enjoyment. The sound quality coming from these headphones is so good that it will just bring a smile to your face on a cold winter day. To state that the Sony XB stereo headphones are lightweight, snug, and produce natural sound tones from music, movies, and computer games is a profound understatement. This pair of headphones offe ... rs supremely comfortable oversized cushioned ear pads that cover the most acoustically accurate 30mm dynamic stereo headphone drivers on the market. The Sony headphones are compatible with virtually any audio, video, TV, DVD player, VCR, digital video recorder, portable video game system, or computer product that features a 3.5mm or ¼&quot; component stereo headphone jack. The 3.9 ft. Y-shaped durable headphone cord provides optimal length, reduced tangles, and freedom of movement for the Sony Walkman that I have connected to it. This item&apos;s gold-plated L-shaped stereo mini-plug connector offers seamless connectivity to your portable entertainment devices and maximum signal transfer from the source component to your ears. The expertly constructed headband is highly adjustable for maximum flexibility during a lengthy private listening session. I don&apos;t notice any other outside noise distractions while wearing this item, but I admit that I am always engrossed in the music that is playing from these sophisticated stereo headphone drivers. Vocal clarity is superbly transmitted across a lush dynamic audio landscape. Midrange response, where most musical instrument reproduction resides in the audio universe, is nicely-defined, balanced, and harmoniously detailed. This unit&apos;s overall sound quality is warm, delicate during select musical passages, nuanced in the treble range, and not the slightest bit rolled off at the low or high end frequency ranges. If you are passionate about portable musical reproduction, then the Sony MDR-XB300 headphones are the best choice in the over-the-ear headphone product category with respect to its price class. The Sony MDR-XB300 XB stereo headphones offer an audiophile feature set for the budget conscious consumer. Those high class portable audio features include: The Sony Extra Bass headphones sport an attractive appearance with its large over-the-ear design, sturdy construction, adjustable headband for maximum comfort, silver ear cup exterior finish, and a 3.9 ft. flat Y-type cord. The Sony MDR-XB300 headphones feature a sealed acoustic design for improved sound isolation characteristics, direct vibe structure for the highest quality sound output, 3.5mm gold-plated L-shaped stereo mini plug for compatibility with the widest range of portable, MP3, computer, and home audio equipment possible. The Sony Extra Bass headphones provide the following portable audiophile accoutrements: stereo reproduction, 30mm dome type XB driver units, neodymium magnet high-energy speaker drivers, two diaphragms and gaskets for extended low frequency response, king sized pressure-relieving ear cushions, left/right ear cup placement marks, 1.2&quot; ear cup thickness, 3.1&quot; ear cup diameter, over-the-head supra-aural design, Copper-Clad Aluminum Wire Voice Coil, lightweight double-sided flat cord, 1000mW power handling capacity, 5-22,000Hz frequency response, 24 ohms at 1 kHz impedance rating, 100db/mW sensitivity rating, and this unit&apos;s weight is 4.23 ounces without cord. The Sony headphones includes a 90-day parts and labor limited manufacturer warranty, handsome black/silver exterior finish, Sony logo, high quality product packaging with printed limited warranty statement, and it comes with operating instructions. With its excellent...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Shopaholic Depot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best bang for the buck!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These are exceptional headphones in terms of sound quality and price. Out of the packaging they sounded fantastic. The bass on these headphones is warm, clear, and deep. You may find yourself backing off the bass a bit with the eq. They are very comfortable to wear. They fit on top of your ears but the pads are generously cushioned and I can wear them for hours with no discomfort. My main use for these headphones is my Mp3 player. The cord is short and a flat type design. This is actually a positive for me because I hate long cords. Long cords are annoying because they get tangled and knot up easily. I have owned these for 9 months and the cord has not tangled up yet. Thank you Sony for such a well designed cord. The connector is an &quot;L&quot; shape design that mounts flush which is als ... o a very thoughtful touch compared to other headphones that have long connector bases that stick way out. It&apos;s these additional subtle designs that really make these headphones such a joy to own.

Cons: As I mentioned earlier the cord is short. You have to consider what the headphones will be used for. If you&apos;re at a computer, for example, and your CPU is on the floor these are probably not going to reach. I would say these are absolutely perfect for an iPod or other type of Mp3 player.

Don&apos;t let the low cost fool you, these are a great bargain for the quality of sound and comfort. My wife has a pair of Bose headphones. She likes the sound of mine better because of the superior sound of the bass. The Bose have a slightly crisper mid to high freq range clarity but not enough to justify the extra expense in my opinion. The difference is very subtle except for the bass. I strongly recommend these headphones if you are going to use them for a Mp3 or other portable music player. Spending a hundred bucks less than the Bose or other similiar brand names for something just about as good will you will feel like a wise shopper. These headphones show that more money doesn&apos;t always equate to better quality. A definite best bang for the buck. But remember, the cord is short. So consider that aspect carefully because purchasing.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Computerhobbyist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Powerful bass, Lightweight, Comfortable, Great Sound

Cons: No carrying case

A brisk winter morning. Bright sunshine. Frigid conditions. Snow on the ground. The bus stop. A cool breeze pressing against the face. A tense day ahead. Sudden warmth and comfort over the ears. Sonic accuracy. The morning commute. Relaxation. Perfect. The Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass headphones plunge you into a stunning world of deep bass performance bliss. The sound quality coming from these headphones is so good that it will just bring a smile to your face on a cold winter day. To state that the Sony XB stereo headphones are lightweight, snug, and produce natural sound tones from music, movies, and computer games is a profound understatement. This pair of headphones offers supremely comfortable ... oversized cushioned ear pads that cover the most acoustically accurate 30mm dynamic stereo headphone drivers on the market. The Sony headphones are compatible with virtually any audio, video, TV, DVD player, VCR, digital video recorder, portable video game system, or computer product that features a 3.5mm or ¼&quot; component stereo headphone jack. The 3.9 ft. Y-shaped durable headphone cord provides optimal length, reduced tangles, and freedom of movement for the Sony Walkman that I have connected to it. This item&apos;s gold-plated L-shaped stereo mini-plug connector offers seamless connectivity to your portable entertainment devices, and maximum signal transfer from the source component to your ears. The expertly constructed headband is highly adjustable for maximum flexibility during a lengthy private listening session. I don&apos;t notice any other outside noise distractions while wearing this item, but I admit that I am always engrossed in the music that is playing from these sophisticated stereo headphone drivers. Vocal clarity is superbly transmitted across a lush dynamic audio landscape. Midrange response, where most musical instrument reproduction resides in the audio universe, is nicely-defined, balanced, and harmoniously detailed. This unit&apos;s overall sound quality is warm, deli ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Computerhobbyist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>A brisk winter morning. Bright sunshine. Frigid conditions. Snow on the ground. The bus stop. A cool breeze pressing against the face. A tense day ahead. Sudden warmth and comfort over the ears. Sonic accuracy. The morning commute. Relaxation. Perfect. The Sony MDR-XB300 Extra Bass headphones plunge you into a stunning world of deep bass performance bliss. The sound quality coming from these headphones is so good that it will just bring a smile to your face on a cold winter day. To state that the Sony XB stereo headphones are lightweight, snug, and produce natural sound tones from music, movies, and computer games is a profound understatement. This pair of headphones offers supremely comfortable oversized cushioned ear pads that cover the most acoustically accurate 30mm dynamic stereo head ... phone drivers on the market. The Sony headphones are compatible with virtually any audio, video, TV, DVD player, VCR, digital video recorder, portable video game system, or computer product that features a 3.5mm or 1/4 component stereo headphone jack. The 3.9 ft. Y-shaped durable headphone cord provides optimal length, reduced tangles, and freedom of movement for the Sony Walkman that I have connected to it. This items gold-plated L-shaped stereo mini-plug connector offers seamless connectivity to your portable entertainment devices and maximum signal transfer from the source component to your ears. The expertly constructed headband is highly adjustable for maximum flexibility during a lengthy private listening session. I dont notice any other outside noise distractions while wearing this item, but I admit that I am always engrossed in the music that is playing from these sophisticated stereo headphone drivers. Vocal clarity is superbly transmitted across a lush dynamic audio landscape. Midrange response, where most musical instrument reproduction resides in the audio universe, is nicely-defined, balanced, and harmoniously detailed. This units overall sound quality is warm, deli...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The bass is excellent on these things. The mids and highs are mediocre. Pretty much what you&apos;d expect from headphones at this price range. They&apos;re really good quality/comfort for what you pay. They are also quite durable; I&apos;ve run over the cable with my chair tons of times and there&apos;s not a scratch on em. I&apos;ve also dropped them on hardwood floor on numerous occasions and they haven&apos;t been damaged at all. Earpads are nice and cushy, and durable; they seem quite resistant to my skin&apos;s acidity.

Cons: Aside from the solid bass, the sound reproduction leaves something to be desired.

Overall good bargain.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Little John ^_^</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great sound, comfort &amp; design = 1 awesome headset</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this headset lately because i was really loving my music with the extra depth, beat and bass. This headset has fantastic sound and i use quite often now with my phone, mp3 and PC. the price was worth it. i love how the cable is flat making it easy to thread down under my jacket or top and it doesn&apos;t tangle. i must say its not for rough usage, i haven&apos;t been rough with it but it does feel fragile, but, it still has a sturdy design. plus i should add it is very comfortable on the head and the ears, I&apos;m new to this design of cushion but it does add to the sound and feels like any other head set.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Parkay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These Are It !.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Looks,Price,Sound

Cons: Could Fit Tighter. Doesn`t Clamp Tight Enough.

These are very good. The highs, lows and mids are surprisingly strong. But bass is where these excell. Excellent for portables and laptops.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tallydude40</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light. Appear to not be excessively hot on my ears. Comfortable. Good, clean bass (at last). Highs better than expected(may need to adjust sound equalizer to fit taste). Probably not exceptional headphones, but sound great for my Youtube-online listening time.

Cons: Cord a little short, but acceptable. No volume control in cord.

Better than my old Sony MDR-V150 Headphones. Good deal for 30 bucks on sale here.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rezident</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome soft earpads. Phenomenal sound, you&apos;ll be blown away when you put them on for the REALLY reasonable price. Great bass, but also awesome mids &amp; highs too. Pretty good noise cancellation too for ones not designed specifically for that.

Cons: Short cord, sweaty ears. Would be nice if the pads were something not so conducive to my ear sweat.

Buy these headphones and you WILL be satisfied. Guaranteed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>johnneg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound &amp; comfortable fit.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones work better than expected. The bass is deep as are the highs. They fit well and are easy to wear for extended times. They renew my faith in Sony as a premier manufacturer of fine electronics. Would recommend these headphones to anyone seeking the best in portable sound.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cambot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exactly what I was looking for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love/need bass. I bought a pair of more expensive noise canceling Sony headphones hoping for the clear, full sound I eventually found in this product. Definitely a great bargain. The full bass doesn&apos;t come at the expense of crisp and clear highs. I can distinctly hear the full range of sound with these headphones. My only complaint is they can apply uncomfortable pressure and heat to the ears if worn for an hour or more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ray</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Abt</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDRXB300 - Sony Extra Bass Black Headphones review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound,Good Bass,Comfortable,Good Value,Stylish

Used often. Almost too good to be true sound. I use them with my laptop, and get HD like sound from movies and music. I just wish they fit the head tighter. But still is a super upgrade.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Audio Man-Queen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceedes my expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound for the price, and sounds better than some headphones twice it&apos;s price, Bass is amazing in both volume and in audio quality, Mids. and Highs still sound very good. I am very uptight about having very good sound on a budget. These far exceed my expectation I am not just 100% happy, I&apos;m 110% happy. At least with these headphones the marketing isn&apos;t all hype, there&apos;s actually some truth to the marketing. Finally, a very good pair of over the ear headphone for people who love bass but still want clear Mids. and highs, and are on a tight budget. Also, I have a hard time wearing ear bud style headphone , my ears are rather sensitive and get irritated rather easily, even some over the ear headphones will bother my ears. Because the ear cushions are so light and &quot;fluffy&quot; these a ... re very comfortable for me to wear, even for extended periods of time. The flat cable is more resistant to tangling, and appears to be a little more durable than your traditional style cable

Cons: I do wish the cable was maybe an extra 6-8&quot; longer, but this is not really a con, just a personal preference.

To give you an idea of how much bass these headphone are actually capable of putting out.. I have a Sony S-series MP3 Walkman. I normally have the ClearBass system turn to the max level, I actually had to turn this down by one to two levels (depending on the style of music I was listening to). I listen to alot of different styles of music, but I love my Trance music and these are very good for electronic music, or music that is intended to be on the bass heavy side of the low frequency spectrum.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sp25</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Okay for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Bass

Cons: Distortion,Everything Else Including Sound Quality,Size

The only reason I didn&apos;t give these headphones 2 stars was because of the price. As soon as you turn up the volume, the sound starts distorting. They sound like cheap headphones. On the bright side atleast the bass is good...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>CarFreak88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 12, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Unbelievable Bass,Very Comfortable,Warm For Winter

Cons: Not Very Compact

Wow!!! These headphones are amazing!!! I had a pair of Sony MDR-NC7s which had pretty good bass, but required a AAA battery to run the noise reduction, which gave it its rich sound. It also had a problem with sound cutting off when going over bumps in the road while I was on the bus, which is where I used them primarily. The headband was also very uncomfortable after a short amount of time. These new MDR-XB300s have a quality of bass that I believe to be even better than Dr. Dre headphones that cost 6 times as much. I don&apos;t even need a battery to run them. These new headphones don&apos;t cut out on the bus, and as a bonus, they are very effective earmuffs for winter. I was skeptic at first glance on th ... e comfort, but I was gladly proven wrong. They are very comfortable. The only negative aspect I have found is that they don&apos;t fold up in any way. But overall, I am amazed. Two Thumbs up. :) Good Job Sony.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jabbb1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I find the MDR-XB300 headphones most comfortable. The sound reproduction is very clear with minimal inteference in sound. The bass is outstanding, while the highs and midrange are clear. I am very pleased with the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Davy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones for Djing and the bass response is excellent. The construction seems good and the Flat Connecting Lead stops the usual snag ups around the decks! The only gripe I would have is the absence of a 1/2 to 1/4 jack reducer to fit most mixers. Overall they are a good buy!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>pcRUSH</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Product Review for Sony Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these headphones after my skullcandy ones broke. They have the same cons, but these have so much better sound and bass. They cost a lot less than most headphones out there and are prob better than most as well. For $50, this is more than i was expecting. However, after about 30 mins of use, my head started to get uncomfortably hot, and my jaw starting getting sore. Another con is the leakage. I don&apos;t play these on full vol because they are very loud, i play them on about 70-85% vol and people still tell me to lower it because they can hear it and all. I would MOST DEFF recommend these to anyone. However, I would not recommend using these on a bus or something because people can get mad. They are perfect for home or in a car and what not. I wish these were slightly more comfortable ... , but for $50 these are the best headphones available. Inexpensive and amazing.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>WhereThereIsAWilliam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>pcRUSH</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Product Review for Sony Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I often take airline trips that exceed 20 hours (with a stop and layover). I play Drum and Bass music very loud to relax. I have found these to give quite a full range of sound, great for music immersion. Also because I am wearing these extensively, they don&apos;t give that pain on the top and bottom of the ears or the jaw. I can sleep with them on, due to the comfortable pads and music clarity. They also drown out the surrounding noise well such as aircraft engine noise or a whiny boss. Unfortunately these do tend to leak the sound in detail. Sometimes people sing along, sometimes they tap me on the shoulder. Either way, I don&apos;t recommend them for using in public or the office.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jih chop</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MMmmmm comfy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Soooo, soft. Like having your ears gentle pressed between two warm marshmellows (That&apos;s the &quot;keep it PG on the public forum&quot; version, not the example I use for my friends). Seriously, I am retired and spend most days on the PC in EvE-online, like 10-20 hrs! These things are the most comfortable headset I&apos;ve ever owned, and extremely light too. But, not the &quot;so light and cheap they&apos;ll break of you sneeze while wearing&quot; kinda light, these feel pretty sturdy. 
My hearing isn&apos;t great, but I had to actually keep turning these DOWN (via PC vol, no inline) as the bass was so powerful. I eventually changed my SC&apos;s settings for less bass!

Cons: Inline volume would be nice, and a slighty longer cord, but with the price and quality, those aren&apos;t worth losing an egg over.
just a sid ... e note, adn not reallu a CON. . . The earpads are not CUPS that fit over/around your ears. They are actually a disc shaped pad that presses right onto the ears themselves. 
My small ears lay flat against my head and thus, these are very comfortable, but if your ears tend to stick out, these may get annoying in a short while.

NEWEGG ROX!
 When I both my &quot;everyday&quot; headset, AND my emergency backup headset broke within 2 days of each other, I needed a replacement fast. so I went to my local *insert Large Electronics Retailer store name here*, and got the cheapest headset they had, a Skullcandy. They should change their name to skullcrusher! Those things squeeze SO hard in starts to hurt almost immediately! Seriously - PAINFULL! not just uncomfortable. The goodnews is the cheap all plastick build broke in two days - the actual plastic band that slides out for adjustability just snapped! 
That&apos;s when I remembered the Cardinal Rule of PC/electronics buying - ALWAYS BUY NEWEGG!
Thanks to a massive selection and the customer reviews, I ended up with this headset. the most comfortable I&apos;ve ever owned! I&apos;m SO glad I bought two ;)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>monty9balls</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sounds awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones are amazing value for money, the sound is quality, bass is tight and clear but also mid and treble excellent. Has a flat cable which never tangles. Would highly recomend these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>blackberry3322</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Shocking!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sounds Really Good Has A Good Frequency Range

Cons: No Carrying Case

These headphones has a lot of bass. The design of the headphones overall is pretty good. The king size cushions are really comfortable on my ears, and the cord will never get tangle. I first heard these shocking headphones when I was on a trip to Las Vegas. As soon as i pressed play, I knew i had to buy them once I&apos;d get back home. The only problem with these headphones is that there isn&apos;t a carrying case, but that does not take away from the headphones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Christina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>an ok buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>In comparison to my previous buy, these headphones are good quality, have a good sound clarity and good bass.
But I must admit I did expect more, esp for the price I paid which is why it gets 4* instead of 5.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Si</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDR XB300</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>As always from Sony the sound quality is excellent, super deep crisp bass but not overpowering. Only thing that let&apos;s them down is the slightly to slack head band. A little too loose to hold them in place should you lean forward or turn head. The flat wire is a brilliant feature, as it doesn&apos;t snag easily and fits under clothing well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great deal if on sale</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: EXTREMELY Comfortable, if you&apos;re sick of headphones smashing your ears or whatever, these are perfect. They caress ears like an Italian lover on a moonlit night. 

Good sound, and a great deal if you get them on sale. At the full price, I would say maybe shop around a little more.

Cons: Bass is a little too &quot;extra&quot; out of the box. You&apos;ll have to go in and modify your equalizer a little. Not a big deal though. 

The Cord is pretty short. A lot of people have said it, but it&apos;s true. Luckily, the cord length is actually perfect for me the way my stuff is set up. And long cords actually annoy me. But I can see how it&apos;d be a problem if your computer wasn&apos;t right next to you. If you buy these might check out an extension at the same time as you&apos;ll most likely need it. Th ... ey&apos;re cheap though.

Sometimes the cushions can form kinda like a vacuum with your ear, and it makes it feel exactly like you have to pop your ears. Doesn&apos;t happen often but it&apos;s strange when it does.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cpt_Badass</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>would be good at $20</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very comfortable, decent cord length, some bass with tweaking

Cons: There is solid bass, but at a cost. 
The stronger the bass the more &quot;gurgled&quot; the sound. 

That&apos;s the nearest I could explain it. You have to turn up the sound a bit to get the units to respond with audible low frequency bass, but they seem unable to handle multi frequency return. 

Such that when a low note is played, the frequency of that note interferes with the high frequency sounds and creates a gurgling sound. 

I tried all manner of equalizer settings and sound card options, to no avail. I bought these to replace an older semi-aural pair that were uncomfortable. Unfortunately I&apos;ll be returning it soon.

I tried running it through my speakers, through the connector on my sound ... card, and with an MP3 device, all poor total sound quality.

I compared it to my old Sony MDR-V150&apos;s and though they lacked the deep bass, they were leaps and bounds better in terms of total sound quality. 

I&apos;m used to ear canal headphones, but they make my ears itch, so it looks like the search will continue.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kyurama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Eh.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable, good for idle listening.

Cons: Feel flimsy, the cushions barely stay on, retail price a bit high for quality, sound isn&apos;t as good as I expect from sony.

I bought these as headphones to use when i&apos;m practicing with my bass guitar. They don&apos;t pick up the bass frequency my amp puts out, making them rather useless for that. Casual listeners to music may get more use out of them, but for my purposes, they fail rather quickly. I then tried it on my guitar amp, and I only picked up out of the left cup, for obvious reasons. Still an annoyance. Overall, they&apos;re alright, but not for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>GIRLABOUTLONDON</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>House of Fraser</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony MDR-XB300 Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones are incredible for the price they are at, the bass is amazing and the sound quality is also incredible.
If you listen to them for too long they do heat up a little bit, but so worth the money</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Burbaby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Comfy Headphones for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones are very very comfortable! Probably one of the most comfortable pair for under $40. There is definitely no lacking in bass!

Cons: Just like a lot of other reviews, these lack in true intonation quality a little bit. The bass can be a little overwhelming in some songs.

Great headphones for the price. Recommended if you&apos;re looking for an inexpensive pair of comfortable headphones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for casual listener</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I&apos;d say one of the best Sony headphones I ever had. The price was just right for the quality of sound from this. The ear cups are soft and so there was no pressure on the ears. 
Decent noise cancelling. Gives that extra deep bass for people who enjoy bass in everything they want to hear. 

Very comfortable!

Cons: Not really portable, the cord was too short. No stereo adapter to plug in the home theater amplifier. Bass can be overwhelming on some tunes.

Overall good bargain</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>GeekV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sweet Set</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These Headphones do what their name says they do, kick out some serious bass. I had a pair of older sony&apos;s that broke due to an accident. I wanted something a lil better to replace them with and being a big bass head, i gave these lil suckers a try, and they don&apos;t disappoint. The sound quality is great, though the bass can overpower the mids and highs on some music, I like to listen to hard rock, techno, and various instrumental tracks and they are just amazing. In the end for the price you pay, these cant be beat if you like your bass loud and booming.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stu1983</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for Rock, rap, R&amp;B</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing Bass, flat chord, cumfortable, Gold jack, looks GREAT

Cons: OK mids and highs, chord length, warm ears, non folding

i bought these on a whim since my last pair of headphones were lacking bass big time. I am VERY pleased with the Bass with these. the mids and highs are pretty good but could be a lot better. I am no audiophile so this doesnt bother me at all. i Used them to watch a movie on my computer and it was amazing, Use them with my 120GB zune and love it even more. i listen to music at leas 6 hours of the day at work and these are still cumfortable at the end of the day. however, the first few days i used them, my ears got a little warm...but i havn&apos;t noticed it lately. the chord could be a little longer (another foot would be amazing) For the price i would ... for sure get another pair or suggest them to another non audiophile friend. if you want booming bass and dont care too much about mids and highs, these are well worth the price. I wish they were collapsable but i have heard that those brake easily...and these are not my travel headphones so they just sit in a drawer when i am not using them...so no need for collapsing.

not sure what that other guy was talking about but my volume is at 40% on my zune and it is plenty of bass...and the AAA battery...there is no spot on these for a battery, so i dont know if he has another product in mind or what is going on.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>GrantMcD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sweet things for my ears.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Extremely Comfortable,Good Bass,Rich Sound,Very Light Weight.

Cons: No Carry Case.

Been listening to them for last couple of days, been playing a lot of Pink Floyd, Radiohead and Gomez. Brilliant sound on all of them, with the volume up on a bassy track you&apos;ll feel the bass as well as hear it. Small enough to be carried around in public without embarrassment although I would prefer to have been charged a couple of pounds more to get a carry bag with them like you do with the XB500. I was in a group of seven people when I bought these and promptly passed them round so they could have a listen. all were impressed by the sound, looks, weight and size. Excellent purchase, just hope they out live all my other headphones, they appear quite flimsy but there&apos;s a rugged feel abo ... ut them that makes me think they&apos;ll last.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jet300</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>this is awsome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass,Quality

Cons: Cord

These headphones are awesome if you are seeking something with great bass and real good quality at a affordable price. although the cord is a little to short and it be better if the headphone was fold-able but overall this thing is sweet!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>nosheeps</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>don&amp;apos;t go for the 30mm</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Value For Sound Quality

Cons: Not Much Bass

For headphones that are called extra bass they really don&apos;t have that much kick. At least the 30mm don&apos;t. Other wise great headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ChocoMein</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I like them, read this</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Though I have only owned these for a day, I thought I would write a review on them. 
First off, they are VERY comfortable and adjustable for big and small heads; these also look pretty good.

Sound quality is decent, but could be boosted (or you could turn up your music/audio). Cord feels of good quality and isn&apos;t like most cords, it is flat and wide like some pasta noodles. Extra bass is noticeable and nice. However, turning up the volume a bit makes the bass more &quot;there&quot; and better.

Cons: Sound quality could be enhanced a bit. These aren&apos;t as loud as skullcandys and some other brands, but it is satisfactory. Extra bass wasn&apos;t as much as I expected but it is fine with me.

Good buy in my opinion. If you like your music loud and powerful, get these but turn up t ... he music a little. Again, these are super comfortable and that should be a big reason for you to buy. Long use is available without the cost of discomfort.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ELA1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The MDR XB300 deliever great bass with no distortion. They are light weight and comfortable. The mid range and treble are dampened by the ear muffs and you get the best sounding mid and highs by pressing the headphones in closer to your ears. The down side of this is you get tired of holding them. Once you get the headphones situated over your ears, you get pretty good over all sound with GREAT comfort. You do not hear any noise from the head phones when someone is wearing them. When you have them on, you can not hear ANY noise from outside.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kumar773</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfartable,Great Bass

Cons: No Ipod Control And Cord Design

I&apos;ve had these headphones for about a month or 2 now and overall they are very nice. The sound quality is very good, especially if you have some high quality audio/mp3 files. My only 2 complaints about these headphones are that they dont have the ipod control remote on them and i&apos;d like the design more if it was just a one-sided cord. I do like the flat cord though. It never gets tangeled up. Other than that these are some really nice cans and I&apos;d recommend them to any one who is looking for some quality headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ray</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bass Heads, Rejoice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Worth every red cent. Comes real close to perfection. Super bass phones, these surely are. I wish they would fit a little tighter on the head though. If so, they would be a 5 star product. Still, a very good purchase, as far as performance.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>StrayGeek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AMAZING.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very powerful bass, crisp highs, and very comfortable.

Cons: N/A.

I have owned more headphones that I can count trying to find a good pair. But now I never have to search again. These sonys stay on well and cushion your ear great. And the sound is almost at the same level as dr. dre beats, which are 300 dollars. The search stops now.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tinnitus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just right...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: My $15 low-end Sony&apos;s broke so I was looking for a slight upgrade in a replacement and found it with these. GREAT frequency range for the price, comfortable on the ears and very lightweight. Will probably buy a 2nd pair as back-ups.

Cons: Cord is a bit short.
Don&apos;t look like could stand up to very much abuse (not an issue for me).

Tried some mid-priced JVC headphones that were WAY too heavy and clunky...these sound just as good for less $ and are 1/3 the weight. Maybe not for everyone but great for casual use, especially at home.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Heat Filter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Midrange all around</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price! The price is right for such comfy headphones. As the name describes &quot;Extra bass Headphones&quot; is true, these little guys produce plenty of bass. There was plenty of effort in the design, the padding was thoroughly tested to reduce noise and to bring a more natural not-so-direct sound which brings a little warmth to the sounds emitted by the drivers so there is less fatigue and less of a chance for headaches from unwanted frequencies. If pressed harder against the ears, you can appreciate the quality of the drivers with very low distortion even at higher listening levels.

Cons: What is a pro is also a con; the padding. Since these are supposed to be mid-level budget headphones, you will not get the cleanest sound. The drivers are not bad but with so much padding, much of t ... he sound is lost as well as quite a bit of decibels. These Headphones are also tricky if not impossible to get to audiophile quality sound out of them even with a good DSP and fine tuning the frequency bands.

Do not expect to get 40 hours of listening time on your ipod touch like you do with the OEM earbuds. Expect your listening time to be cut to half or less due to the power hungry drivers in these headphones... they are great for on the go listening for short trips without a charger though. Otherwise, have your MP3 player plugged in.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I trust and like newegg a lot more now.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the sound is amazing, like one commentor said, youd expect the higher notes to be drowned out by the bass, but its not like that at all. the bass is great and im hearing notes i didnt even know were in songs. regular headphones sound much worse now.

Cons: a bit small. ironic, i know, but if youre wearing them while watching movies at your computer youd like it to sit over your ears. these just seem to squish them to your head, giving you an ear ache like wearing a hat over them would.

amazing product, good shipment time, and great price. high fives.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nikki</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>should be cheaper</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Given the size of these headphones, one would think the sound quality would be more dynamic. However, unfortunately this is not the case... expensive purchase for an average item</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Slip</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AMAZING</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Amazing sound, DEEP bass. Like, these are super serious. Very comfortable, wear them for hours. I listen to a lot of bass-heavy electronic music so I&apos;ve put them through their paces, speakers sound perfect and the sound is amazing. The casing is a little flimsy and they look kind of like ear-muffs, but for the sound and the price, nothing compares.

Cons: Nothing.

Generously lengthy cord, too. Sweet headphones</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>OAvila</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for on the go</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Supper comfortable, plush ear piece makes them feel incredibly soft on your ear. I wear them for about 2 to 3 hours straight and my ears never begin to hurt, little sweaty but that’s it. Use to have more expensive Sony headphones but the main problem was the extremely long cord. So the thin, flat cord is short which works great with my IPod or traveling with my laptop. Sound quality is great for the price and the overall quality of the headphones is superb.

Cons: Just two cons: 1. They are not great for home stereo system because of the bass and too short of cord. 2. The bass and overall loudness is not as high (loud) as in other headphones i.e. Skull Candy and etc.

Great Value, must buy for IPod or travel.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cedric</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I own the Sony MDR XB500 and I wanted something a little smaller to hit the gym !! So, these 300 are great. There are smaller but still provide a good sound quality overall and good bass. The shipping from B&amp;H was super fast. Thanks !!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good headphones, great price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable, great bass, overall very good sound and clarity.

Cons: Cord is short.

I use these mainly for gaming but I have watch a few movies with them as well. I bought an extension cord for them so I could plug them into the backside audio port on my sound card from more umpf.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnneh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome set of bass headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these set of headphones to replace some older, basic Sony &apos;phones I had since early 2001. I hooked them up to my Sanza Fuze 8GB mp3 player as well as my Alienware m11x laptop. Let me tell you, for being the smallest Extra Bass model Sony offers, these things can pump out the sound! I love them. Playing games such as Mass Effect 2 with a lot of explosions or watching movies gives a cinematic feel. For music, I listened to Iron Maiden&apos;s Aces High. They perform flawlessly. Some users may find the cushy foam headpieces a little restrictive, but the noise canceling function requires this. If one needs a larger headphone jack, say for a 6.35mm stereo, you may have to take a trip to a Radio Shack for the adapter as it is not included. They are a little bigger than most headphones, but I was ... still able to fit them in my laptop bag. They are very comfortable too. Sony, you rock. :)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Toot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Music Lovers!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>A Christmas pressie so I can listen to music whenever I want. Bliss! I like the ear pads and sound but I really wish the lead was a lot longer because I&apos;m restricted where I can sit wearing them. Good value for money though.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not bad for discounted price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: - Good bass for price
- Flat cord
- Cushions are comfortable for long listening
- Cord is the right length for me

Cons: - Lot of things the bass in the headphones can&apos;t handle
- You can feel how cheap they are when they are on your head

A friend of mine has the same headphones, but a higher quality. Not sure if they are on sale on newegg but they were around $100. The difference was better highs, more bass, could handle more songs, and they fitted around the ears instead of resting on top of them (same cushion though).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>sgman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Fine headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I find these headphones to be very comfortable and I can wear them for hours with no discomfort. These headphones actually do a very good job at all frequencies mid and high range not just the bass.

Cons: The cord is short which I knew before I got it, so be aware of this. If you listen to genres of music which tend to have more bass you may find these headphones bass to actually be overpowering, although that may be what you want anyway.

Overall these headphones especially for the price are great! I use them for listening to classical music and Gaming which works great for me because classical can be pretty light in the bass and in gaming for me the more boom the better!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>illusi0n90</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass is really nice, as is the audio quality. Sony is a good brand all-around, hard to go wrong with their products. These feel like a way more expensive pair of headphones, so you get the bang for your buck (always a plus!) Shipping was on time, as usual with Newegg. VERY COMFORTABLE! A big plus, I absolutely HATE ear buds, and lots of headphones can become really uncomfortable after a few hours of use... Not so with these, unbelievable comfort.

Cons: Cord is pretty short, which isn&apos;t an issue for me as my speakers have an audio-out port, but could be a real pain for those needing more length. But I&apos;m not taking an egg off for that, I knew the cord was going to be short.

Would be nice to have a bass throttle, but I have had no issues with the loudness of the bass, its ... pretty sweet. :)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Headcase</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bass is pro.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these for listening to music, PC gaming, and recording. I&apos;d give these a 5/5 any day of the week for all three. The first thing you notice is how comfy they sit on your head. Though they aren&apos;t especially snug, so for people who move around a lot may not like that. The weight is excellent. It&apos;s comparable to putting a marshmallow on each ear, and listening out of that. As far as quality goes, the science behind how they get such an amazing tone isn&apos;t of the rocket variety. They leave an open area in the middle of the foam padding that acts like a giant funnel for the noise to come out, so you get awesome bass. And I mean AWESOME bass. For DJ&apos;s who have a habit to cram the headphones against their head, like their trying to stop water from getting in at all costs will ruin the effect ... of the headphones by pushing out all that open space inside the headphone. The cable length might leave some people salty, if they&apos;re looking for recording use, but I&apos;m quite happy with it. Overall, these deserve nothing less than 5 for 5, especially for the quality you get. Worth every penny.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>little guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>just what i expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: If you like rap music, these cans are for you. But if music is your thing and you want those little details, spend your $$ on a Grado.

a 5 stars VALUE, why? cause you can&apos;t find a better &quot;EAR SOFA&quot; for a &quot;ANDREW JACKSON&quot;,

Cons: bass &gt; detail
no con if that&apos;s really okay for you. but i wouldn&apos;t pay more than $25 for these. MSRP $50 ? ain&apos;t we still in middle of an economic depression.

headphone needs break in to sound right. just hook it up to a quality out put, watch an action movie with it for some time, love will grow on you.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Man_Dog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overall they are ok</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 17, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, the sound isn&apos;t too bad. Lightweight.

Cons: There is a little distortion due to the bass these things can output. 
Headband seems a little fragile.
The cable is a little to short.

Overall not a bad buy, plus there Sony. 
I would recommend these for your ipod or mp3 player, only because of the cable length that they come with.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrKLuTCHe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Cushion is huge and amazingly soft. I don&apos;t know how they did that. Great bass, wide range of frequencies. Nice design.

Cons: Uh.. None!

I don&apos;t have the MDR-XB300&apos;s I have the MDR-XB500&apos;s. I think that they might have misnamed the headphones, I have never seen the 300s.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wyveryx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony&apos;s Got a Winner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 29, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: These headphones can put out...
They have a nice deep rich Bass that really makes you feel like you are in a theaters, while still giving you quality sound. You don&apos;t lose any of the higher pitches either.
The huge cushion ear pads are also very comfortable, and thought the headband is hard plastic is doesn&apos;t ware on you.

Cons: Like any headset the ear muffs will wear on you after about 4 hours, so if you&apos;re a gamer, this might not be for you.
The cord is a bit small, only about 3 feet if that.

I didn&apos;t get mine at newegg, but saw them on a special. As much as I like these I really these, I do think they are worth the $50, prolly around $35 because of the minor set backs of the cord and lack of band cushion.
All in all though, a very good set of headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>norgeswonder</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb sound for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The sound is excellent and the addition of the bass is awsome. It is not overpowering and does not distort the balance of the music, classical pieces sound great. They are also super comfy and soft on the ears.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Iqbal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it !!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 20, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i was looking for a long time to get a good bass headphone... and after a long research i ended up buying this one... its worth the money u pay for.. the sound clarity is awesome and the bass is just amazing... i am not into the techie details.... but i feel these headphones are a great choice...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Julian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDR-XB300 Extra Bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love these headphones. I bought them for skiing and they work perfect. The cable never gets tangled, even when they&apos;re in my backpack. Has a good deep, low frequency bass that doesnt just vibrate your ears with a scratchy sound. It&apos;s powerful and clear sounding. They have a nice ear cusion on them. They start to put a little pressure on my ear lobes if I&apos;m wearing them for about an hour or two but I just have to take them off for about a minute and they&apos;re fine. Overall they produce a nice,clear, and loud bass without the scratchy crackling noise you get with cheaper headphones. The best part is, I bought them for [$]. Way better and cheaper than my friend&apos;s skullcandys</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConoverLaw</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Extra Bass Headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything In This Extra Bass Headphones Is Perfect!

Cons: Did Not Find Any...

This is A+ product. Sony as always has demonstrated transformation of one great idea into one very cool, reliable, and superb product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Francoreviews</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing buy, worth every cent.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Super Comfortable.

Cons: Not Foldable.

These headphones are AMAZING, ive owned tons and tons of pairs but these are one of the best. The bass is extremely great and the sound quality is awesome, especially when watching movies.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>energizer610</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These were not the headphones I thought they were but I must say the sound the headphones produce is fantastic especially the deep bass they produce. They are very comfortalbe as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: SONY MDR-XB300 3.5mm Gold-Plated Connector Circumaural Extra Bass Headphone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The bass is okay but could be improved a lot.

Cons: Not nearly loud enough, I usually listen to my music pretty loud and these are pathetic compared to the last pair of headphones I had. Complete waste of money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DeathAbyss</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome headphones; doubles as earmuffs.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Beautiful Bass,Very Comfortable On The Ears.

Cons: Slightly Overpowers The Other Ranges.

Just got these headphones; wearing them as I write this review. The wires are very well made, no signs of imperfection. The plastic used however wasn&apos;t ideal; there are signs of imperfections, mostly at the edges and the plastic band on top. Looks like the plastic is under stress (faint markings where the parts are pieced together). The bass is very nice, especially for the price right now. Much more comfortable than some of the older models at a similar price range. The headphones rests very comfortably on your ears without hurting your ears. I wear glasses, and oftentimes, when I wear headphones, my glasses gets shifted very awkwardly, but the MDR-XB300 seems to be fine. Oh, and i ... t&apos;s kind of chilly outside; these headphones double as the most awesome earmuffs ever. At least it doesn&apos;t make you look dorky walking across campus.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Andy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>barely satisfactory</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price and local purchase ability. Bought them from a Local Electronics chain.

Cons: Hmm were do I start...I guess I&apos;ll start with that Sony is riding on their name yet again, instead of producing a quality sound product. Granted the price is cheap but no name brands that are cheaper sound better than these plastic cups. I use them for watching movies and listing to music when my wife and children are asleep. The frequency is way to low and the speaker output ohms isn&apos;t satisfactory, besides the fact they sound like they are in cased in thin plastic cups. 
Another Sony audio product that rides near the bottom of the junk pile. I had a pair of Cheap Koss that broke (actually dogs chewed them) So I thought hmm I have a nice Sony 60&quot; HDTV that is awesome, let me try their audio ... product...MISTAKE!! I returned them from hence they came and bought a different brand with higher specs for a cheaper price.

I think Sony makes a much better Video Product than Audio. The pair of headphones I bought at wally world sound much better than these headphones.

I am very much into audio and video, so in todays economy I refuse to buy a product that can&apos;t live up to it&apos;s name in todays market. Especially when there are so many products and companies to choose from.
If you arn&apos;t to quality minded like I am you might like them, but with a name like sony and the money they have you would think a quality product would be second nature.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>gopikrsna925</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>After a long research, I have chosen to go for these among very limited head phone collection here.
The headphones have a nice built and good thumping bass. Using these I&apos;ve heard some new sounds from the same songs I used to hear in my other ear phones, which is great. But, over a period I feel the bass is dominating. Even a mediocre beat gets a rich bass, which I didn&apos;t like and there is also some leak of sound.
Among the current headphones in argos, these are the best. Bass lovers will find them great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AudioScopic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony Strikes Yet Again!! FULL, Clean Sound..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Built Like A Tank,Comfy,Portable Use.,The Thick Sound

Cons: Didn&apos;t Try Them Sooner,Had To Go Through 5 Others First!!

Wow. Truly FULL SOUND. I went from the XB500&apos;s down because of money and the impractical size for my uses- mostly portable, on the move.. and these things sound every bit as &apos;Big&apos; as a 40mm or driver set of phones. EASY. Don&apos;t be fooled by the 30mm setup and the lower sensitivity spec.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mondo16</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>pcRUSH</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Product Review for Sony Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Prior to purchase, i was not sure how the MDR-XB300 would hold up, yet i have had these for almost two years and they are still in pristine condition, despite being used daily in all sorts of conditions. The bass is amazing, and the sound in general far surpasses that of the popular &quot;Beats&quot; headphones by Dr. Dre. The sound, quality, and all around looks are fantastic, and these were a great buy. The MDR-XB300 by Sony is definately worth its price and I would recommend them to anyone looking for a great pair of headphones. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Vicko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Sound !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Every time i listen to music with thess headphones i feel like i m in a club! It s AMAZING ! I use it on my VAIO PC mainly listening to electronic music on Pandora. The bass are incredible as well. I love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sean</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These heaadphones are great. The bass they provide is truly amazing. They are also comfortable to wear for prolonged periods of time. You can&apos;t go wrong with the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DaMirikal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>an audiophiles review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>these headphones are amazing for the price. i also have the 500&apos;s and Sennheiser hd280, Shure srh 440, Philips the stretch and many more.i use these sometimes but not often sense i have the 500&apos;s but when i want a less heavy option i use these. these also do not look very good but its fine i dont really care about looks. for when im in the studio i use my sennheisers or shures. i will do this to review more: bass 10/10 mids 8/10 treble 7.5/10 overall sound 9/10 build 7/10 looks 6/10 overall 8/10 the cable on mine started to short after 3 months so i stoped using them after another 3 months i used them again and the problem was gone?!?!?!? i dont know how but i was happy. over all these are nice but the 500&apos;s are much better i suggest getting them unless you dont want big headphones or you ... have less money. btw if your thinking or getting beats by dre DONT THEY SUCK. get any of the sony mrd xb line there 10x better and cost much less.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RickJessieSpringfield</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones but why dont they fold</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable,Good Value,Heavy Bass

Cons: Are Not Foldable

Really the only thing I could find wrong with these headphones in my opinion is that they dont have the hinge that allows them to be foldable like other models of Sony&apos;s, other then that I freakin love these headphones. The extra cushy ear pads are like wearing a pair of ear warmers it took a little while to get used to them but they are so so comfortable. I love that when you wear them people can you see that your listening to music and not to disturb you unlike those wimpy ear buds. I have been using them on my Ipod touch the past couple of hours and they handled the bass perfectly. I got the entry level pair and am really happy with my purchase. The design is awesome other then my gripe, I really like how the h ... inges that adjust to fit your head are on the inside and the outside band stays solid, oh yeah maybe because I have not purchased premium Sony Headphones in a while I just noticed that Sony has a new flat thin grade of cord instead of the older grade which I think is cool. The form factor is great, buy them!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Scott98</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very comfortable, decent bass for the price

Cons: thought the ear piece material was to slick

I listened to these for about 30 minutes earlier today and thought they were a decent set of headphones for the price. The sound or bass didn&apos;t blow me away by any means, but I wasn&apos;t disappointed with the sound either. I did feel the slick material on the ear piece cushion could cause some problems if you were moving around very much while wearing them. I do have to say though they were extremely light and comfortable to wear. I only tried them out with rap music so I can&apos;t say how they sound with any other type of music.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>paul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I first bought a wirless set of headphones,which failed miserably in the music creation i do,
I purchased these sony headphones after a review i read about them promised a good frequency response, i was not disappointed.
The deep bass they claim to produce is absolutely true , the only niggle i have with them is the length of the cord ,my pc is at ground level and this was a problem ,the 1.2m includes left and right cords meeting a less than sufficient single strip to the mini jack plug,
i had to purchase an extention cord in order to sit comfortably with them.
Apart from that these are an excellent set of headphones for the price and would definately recommend to those who care about the sound quality they listen to.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cathy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>after my husband snapped 2 head candy headphones, had to find a suitable high quality alternative - and these are the ones. Very comfortable to wear and very good quality sound. At a reasonable price, i hope these last longer than the previous ones!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pavi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I been using it for 4 months now, and it turns to be a great head phone. If u r looking for something to listen to music or watch movies on ur laptop its a great headphone, with perfect bass and treble. Cons: Doesn t have control to decrease or increase bass.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mdog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>these head phones are ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>these head phones are amazing, skull candy has head phones with similar prices but seem to be years away. I think that even easily compare to Dr.Dre. durability is good, but i think dr.dre&apos;s are better for durability. plus they wont catch your hair when adjusting them, much like most skull candies do.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ngwo0t</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buy Now</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Exactly what I wanted. So comfortable. Ever sleep on a leather couch, using the arm rest as a pillow? (If you haven&apos;t, its amazing). 

I listen to everything, mostly rock so I was a little scared the &quot;extra bass&quot; would drown out the higher frequency riffs, but this is not the case at all. The rock songs sound incredible and of course the hip hop/dance/electronic/house music all sound incredible.

I was also concerned that I might want the XB500s instead of the XB300s. After listening to the 300s, I am completely satisfied with my decision.

Cons: Cord length MIGHT be a problem for those of you that have your desktop on the floor. I personally have my desktop on my desk, so its not a problem for me.

I would highly recommend these headphones for anyone on ... a budget that wants some quality headphones. Can&apos;t beat the free shipping and $35.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>elroyhisboy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Abt</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDRXB300 - Sony Extra Bass Black Headphones review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Bass

Definitely produces more bass than what I thought I was getting but it&apos;s been a pleasant audio pleasure. I&apos;m glad I purchased these for myself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound for low budget</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The ear pads are like cushions on your ears. They even get more comfy as they age and get a little worn.

Awesome bass and the so far the range in frequencies aren&apos;t that bad, very little to no distortion.

I go on to rip the cord a new one on cons, but in a way it&apos;s also nice if you like to travel. It&apos;s short enough so that when you use these with either you phone or MP3 player that you don&apos;t have to tie the cord up.
To each their own though.

Cons: Super short cord... I can&apos;t even go on to say how much I hate this cord. I had to buy an extender just so I could use it with my desktop and the way my desk is configured.
Also the flat ribbon style is alright up to the point of the &quot;Y&quot; split. But if you are a neat freak it can take some time to figure out how to ... straighten it out.

I wanted to get these back when I tried them Wally World, there were better than my logitechs at the time, and though it doesn&apos;t have a mic for gaming, I found that I use them more so.
They have stood the test of time, dogs, cats, a 3, 4, and 7 year old. Their almost as good as a Timex.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Baboon</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Headset</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Music is very clear, Bass is VERY VERY good. I listen to Dubstep which is mostly a bass dominant music genre, and these headphones produce amazing quality bass output !! I&apos;m very impressed !!

Also, they are VERY comfortable on the ear. I have them on right now and I barely feel them in around my ear. It&apos;s like a custom made ear piece. SIMPLY AWESOME!!

Cons: Cord is pretty short.

Don&apos;t hesitate to get these. Worth every penyy ;]]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>starqueen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>HP</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Like Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve always bought Sony headphones since the 80&apos;s along with my first Walkman. I&apos;ve never been disappointed. Especially with the bass. Music and television sounds great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dan Zerep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love &apos;em</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love these. The only problem is they&apos;re way too comfy that I often fall asleep thinking they&apos;re part if my pillow. Of course there I was sarcastic. But yes they are comfy and sound excellent.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrMusicMan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Set</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased these headphones for recreational use, just to listen to when im at home or travelling. I have to admit sound quality is very good for the price, and i know the point of the product is to have extra bass, but in some cases the base can be a little overwhelming as it starts to compromise the sound quality by being louder than the actual track. also the open cup ear piece allows a bit of sound to escape rendering the product rather useless for professional use.

However, in my opinion, overall the headphones are quality for the money, and im thoroughly enjoying using them! BUY THESE HEADPHONES!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mickeman1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Headphones for gaming and movies on computer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>A great value for a quality product Very comfotable. The other Sony headphones I have start to hurt. There are very soft on the ears The cord is short but not a problem for me. I will buy my secratary a pair for her web seminars.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Michaelg281713</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 30, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The bass is fantastic, the treble not so much. I don&apos;t have a big head so I have to put a headband over the headphones to press them to my ears. Otherwise the treble doesn&apos;t sound great. As long as I put the headband on over them, the overall sound is top notch. I don&apos;t mind the headband, so I would definitely recommend these to anyone who wants true hard hitting headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>In a Cube</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very comfortable, I must wear these for at least six hours a day. The fit is snug but not to the point were you get nasty ear sweat from long term use. For the dollar investment you can&apos;t beat the sound quality.

Cons: Not really a con but a reality, caution is to be used when not wearing the headphones. I will not go as far to say they are made from cheap plastic, but caution should be used when not using this particular product. (I fear the dreaded fall off the desk, move backward to see if they are at my feet but oh no that crunching sound is me buying these headphones again.)

Great gift for a cubicle bound sentient being with a love for music.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>hadden88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great sound , blocks outside noises as well.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>it took some getting used to after years of using ear buds , but if you want great sound and outside noises blocked these work great. i wear while working out to block terrible music at my Gym.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>More bang for the buck</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The MDR-XB300 has certainly performed better than I expected. I was considering the Bose noise cancelling phones, but this set, while not having the noise cancelling feature, is still effective in minimizing external sounds while giving a great range of frequency response and super sensitvity. -a great value for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>blueseadolphin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDRXB300 Bass Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I found a great product on overstock the Sony MDRXB300 Bass Headphones is a great headphones . I though it would not be that great but if you like bass when you listen to your music then you would like this headphones cause they do give you the bass that you like. it&apos;s worth the money and i would buy more when mine don&apos;t work anymore. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mrod76</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Well...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I may not be an Audiophile but these headphones which arrived today have audio the quality of $10 dollar ones. Would gladly return them back if it wasn&apos;t for the fact I ripped the box in which it came in.
I have a 5 yr old USB Plantronics headset which is extremely loud, and in comparison these are just plain substandard for music.

Cons: Everything.

As a commenter here pointed out, Sony has been riding on their name while manufacturing substandard merchandise lately. Tisk tisk.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RemingtonT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>pcRUSH</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Product Review for Sony Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones have pretty good sound quality and delivered their promise on extra bass, but i feel like these headphones are too centered on the bass and that the vocals and the other instruments are just kind of a background to the music. Also, after about 15 minutes of listening, the headphones started to make my ears sore. Even though the cushions are very soft and spongy, they start to hurt after a relativity short period of time. Plus, the plastic headband isn&apos;t the best either. Overall, these headphones would be good if you would use them lightly and if you didn&apos;t want to spend too much money, but choose something else if you are looking for the best overall experience.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Audio Junkie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Budget Phones for Bass Lovers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been buying all different brands of headphones for 10 years now. I have had Skullcandy, Bose, Pioneer, JVC, Panasonic, Klipsch, Monster, Kicker, Sennheiser, and many more. So far, Sony has surprised me in my search for that durable, bassy pair of headphones. It started with the MDR-XB500s, a step up from these, their tight construction lasted through a lot of trips and turns that surronds college life (falls, drops, tripped over wire, and ran over wire). I bought the MDR-XB300s to see if the cheaper end of the line was good. Albeit the sound is good, but the overall bass experience is about 15-20% less than the XB500s, but that doesn&apos;t matter because the bass is really well distributed in this pair. The flat cord is hard to get tangled, the comfortable leather pads produce a snug ... fit to your ear lops, and any musical taste is quickly enhanced with the 30mm drivers. Overall, this pair of headphones is a definite buy for those budget minded audiophiles. If you want to go all out, but still stay in the XB family, look up the XB1000s.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>They are lig...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the package doesn&apos;t lie, the bass is really good! Several times better than my cheap noise-canceling headphones these will replace.

Cons: Comically large foam earpieces: you may look stupid wearing them in public! (unless wearing large headphones is your thing) I bought these for dorm use only, so its not a problem for me.

They are lighter than I expected, though I dont know if this is a good thing or not. They might not be very durable but I will have to see.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>i would buy ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very high quality sound. they perform very well at high and, obviously, low frequencies. i can hear sounds in songs i never even knew existed with other headphones

Cons: none except that, if you have a bassy EQ on and youre listening to music with more than normal bass, the bass can be overwhelming, just change EQ an youre fine though, just a minor detail.

i would buy these again in a heartbeat. i showed them to my brother, friend, and father, all of them want a pair now.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Smart</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Descent headphone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The Sony MDR x300 is presentable, comfortable and good value. but I think the bass levels are so high it eliminates the treble (not very pleased with this, though wont be a problem for most people) . The cable are of good length for use as a mobile headphone (not too long) overall I will recommend them as &apos;worth the money&apos;.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jayne</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Tesco</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Bass MDR-XB 300 Over-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good Points: Great sound and street noise greatly eliminated Bad Points: I have a smaller hear than than the band adjustment allows for.

There is alot of heat from them after a while</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>XRHawk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The 3.5mm is...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound. Sounds almost as good as my 5.1 Digital surround sound system by Sony.

Cons: The cord is not very long but I also use them for studio and live sound. Don&apos;t think thats a very big deal tho.

The 3.5mm is also a 90 degree angled jack.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TheCatford1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Seriously Disappointing...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Bought these headphones after reading good things on various websites. I have to say that while these headphones look good (if a bit big) and offer good (not great) bass response, it is eclipsed by the serious lack of midrange and treble. I had to turn these up really high to get a reasonable amount of volume from them. I went straight out and bought popular German equivalents instead and they&apos;re the best I&apos;ve EVER had! Avoid the Sonys - unless you want expensive ear muffs!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Delilah</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Comfortable and Good Sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass,Good Value,Great Sound,Lightweight,Stylish

Cons: Cord Too Short

I have worn many different headphones, but these are the most comfortable one&apos;s by far, I was rather impressed by the comfort level. The cord is too short though especially if you want to watch TV, but I took care of that by buying a 6&apos; headphone extension cord.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>oleblue41</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>better then I expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sounds good for what I do with them. Main use is for watching tv and playin games on the pc late at night while every one else is asleep.

Cons: after an hour or so they do get a bit uncomfortable, but they are new to my big head.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Braysh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought these for my husband, who is a singer, and has had the same ones for years, which are now falling apart. Although these are domestic, rather than professional, he assures me they are great! Apparantly, they are comfy to wear, and the sound quality is fantastic. This is all good, as my husband is the world&apos;s greatest and biggest critic of everything!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>riki</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>most comfortable headphone ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Affordable,Comfortable,Good Bass &amp; Sound

Cons: Noise Cancellation

i can&apos;t express any thing because this is the best headphone i ever had at this price tag . it is highly comfortable than any other pc headphone as most of the headphone gives lots of pain to ear after wearing for longer times . Gamer like me can use it in counter strike , COD , etc.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SANDEEP2305</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GOOD HEADPHONES go for it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 700,Can Use Them For Long Time,Good Bass,Low&apos;s Are Very Clear,Mid&apos;s,Portable Size When Compared To Xb500

Cons: Highs Are Not Much Clear,No Carry Case

At first i have purchased MDR-XD 200 which were really pretty good especially for Movies and when on my next visit to sony saw these beautifully craved phones and when i listened to a song i felt as if am having woofers around my ears ooooo they r superb , excellent i just scratched my credit card and bought these ..compared these with Apple&apos;s but SONY rocks . But they leave a remark when we talk about high end sounds in films . But i prefer these for MUSIC LOVERS and the ear cups are small in size and we can carry these in our neck without any problem but it would have been better if sony provides carry case and charge so ... me more extra bugs for case.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jordy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony xbass mdr-xb300 headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Before i purchased the sony xbass mdr-xb300 headphones i had the previous model the mdr 200 headphones and i can say that the mdr 300 headphones are a deffinate improvement with a very deep and responsive bass sound i bought them as i wanted a good pair of headphones in which i can listen to my music with a rich and clear sound these headphones tick all the boxes deffinately good value for money very comfortable as well</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>outdoorsportsenthusiast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>music to my ears</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones were a gift for my son. He was very excited to receive them and they work beautifully. As always I am very pleased with my purchase from Overstock.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>cmjo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great deal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought this for my daughter who is a music buff, she had wanted this for a long time but could not afford it, She is very happy and could not believe the price. I am particularly happy to get her away from the in ear speakers. Thanks again Overstock!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jacky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gives your songs a great bass kick.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this set for everything. Listen to music on the train with it (great because it&apos;s inaudible to other people around you at full volume), play my games with it (sound effects are really explosive), use them as makeshift earmuffs in the cold... They&apos;re great, comfortable headphones that give you a real kick in the ears. It&apos;s like having subwoofers mounted onto your head. Can&apos;t go back to anything else I&apos;ve had before. Highly recommended. Wouldn&apos;t go working out with them though, they&apos;re comfortably warm normally - they&apos;ll get unbearably stifling under intense activity.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>djcafe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>like &apos;em so much I want another pair</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Man these are so comfortable and the sound quality is incredible, of course I don&apos;t buy headphones every year so I can only compare to my 10 year old Sony&apos;s. Which is no comparison. Very satisfied.

Cons: cord length. Maybe that&apos;s a pro actually.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>darich8</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great product for the money, bass can be slightly over exagerated at times with very slight distortion on very bass heavy music, but generally quite acceptable audio quality, treble was also a little clearer than expected. Just a shame they&apos;re a little bit CHUNKY, but VERY comfortable. Definately worth the purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Beat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big Impact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight&lt; Comfortable&lt; No Distortion

Cons: The Driver Could Be Closer To The Ear.

I have had them for about a year they are more durable than the beats by Dr.Dre solo which i only had for 3 months, My extra bass are still going strong, only thing i can say about them are they sound much better when the driver is closer to the ear by cutting down the ear cushion they have a sound just like any high end over the ear headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shanhan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I Love This Product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love listening to music and when i got these headphones it has changed the way the music sounded to me. I really enjoy listening to music so much more thanks to these headphones. I love that they have cushion for the ears. All the other headphones that i have used always made my ears hurt after listening to music, but these headphones don&apos;t. i love how the headphones look and feel like they have alot of support and comfort for my ears and head. I can not get over how much these headphones have changed my point of view on headphones. I LOVE THESE!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Emi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Best option</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>its a really good set of headphones, too cheap (i mean, [$]0 bucks?)i would extremly recomend it because it has great noise cancelling and exellent audio qualitybest headphones ive ever bought, exept for the problem that if u look down they fall off</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: -Decent price

-Length was perfect for me

-Overall well made

Cons: -None really, except the metal that connects the ear part to the overhead plastic sorta feels like it might fall off but thats just me.

Would definitely buy another pair of these if i lost/broke mine</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>abcv</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this product and i ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: And The Diver Unit Fits In My Mp3,Great Design,Like The Way The Bass Sounds

Cons: Does Not Fit In My Backpack

I love this product and i would tell any one in heart beat to get this product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sue</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these as a present for my husband, they are excellent quality, very comfortable and he loves them - something about being able to hear very &apos;low&apos; sounds - too technical for me (!), but glad he liked them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Piano Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Highly recom...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great overall response with bass emphasis

Cons: Rumble frequencies below 100 Hz more audible than normal headset - Sometimes annoying listening to TV (wind noise, stupid subdued electric bass improv behind dialog, etc.)

Highly recommended for robust full range stereo audio</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Michelle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Tesco</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Bass MDR-XB 300 Over-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Good Points: Easy to use and comfortable. Good weight and price and good sound</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Luke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The bass in the headphones is great, but there is slight loss in the middle and highs. Also, can get uncomfortable if wearing glasses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Earache8</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Super Bass</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you like bass then these are the headphones for you!! For the price you cant beat these!! Very Nice</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shifty</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The headphones are ver comfy and the bass is amazing</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Weird</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bass, Light, Fit

Cons: Ear phones are weird at the beginning

good set of headphones :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wayne</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Tesco</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Bass MDR-XB 300 Over-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good Points: comfortable easy to adjust to individual comfort good sound reproduction . Bad Points: lacks a volume control</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>diane</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Comfortable to wear light weight, and great sound</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bassallday</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphoness!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great bass, at a cheap price! I crank these headphones and they sound perfect! Good job Sony!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphoness!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great bass, at a cheap price! I crank these headphones and they sound perfect!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>darkzider</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sweet headset</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Fit And Sweet Bass

Cons: Nothing Really

i love them they are great</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>kingkong000</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very nice sound, great bass!

Cons: none</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good purchase</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Excellent product very good bass. Comfort and excellent purchase would recommend</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alec</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>price + quality = success!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Accountant</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great sound!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>they have a great sound, yet their cord is not long enough..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ESB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good service</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Excellent. Easy to find producy on website,
easy to make reservation,
quick and easy to collect</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tiny Tim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent sound Cheep cost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The overall sound quality from the Sony Xbase MDR-XB300 Headphones is excellent and given the low cost = VERY GOOD VALUE FOR MONEY.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Audio</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony MDR-XB300</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>continuing cons: not a good balance of sound. Bass tends to get mushy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roe...</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love NewEgg</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Bought these for my teenager. So far no issues. The sound and fit is great.

Cons: none.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lightweight and nice!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Light weight, nice sound, and it doesn&apos;t put too much pressure on the ears.

Cons: None</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>morris1973</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony Extra Bass Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The headphones work pefectly, are very confortable and reliable. Even better, at a very good price. I take them with me everywere.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Confortable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very comfortable. Could be a little tighter on the ears, the pads are very soft.

Cons: Ears get a little warm on hot days after 2-3 hours use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>h wright</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>best headphones for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great sound feels good on ears even after hours of use</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jaccuu</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great price great buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>great quality especially for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Macmac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent sound!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Brilliant comfort, my step dad loves it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Colin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Xbass MDR-XB300 Headphones - Black.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Could not be more pleased.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nigel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Largely came up to expectations, generally pleased with the product</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Really pleased with the phones. Comfortable to wear and cuts out sounds of the better half....totally.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rollicking Ralph.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Most expensive rubbish ever.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cheap and tatty. No volume control.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nathan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Let down buy the very short lead. Spoils great headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr. Bill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for price!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sounds good comfortable will recommend to co-workers.

Cons: Cord is to short but not worth the loss of egg have jack in front of case.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>anton</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good value for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have found them to be very good and would reconmend them to a friend</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Extreme quality</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>THOMAS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Tesco</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Bass MDR-XB 300 Over-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bad Points: lead not long enough</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR XB300 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/11980510017536031958/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CLYBEPQCMAQ4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jacqueline</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Tesco</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Sony Bass MDR-XB 300 Over-ear headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good Points: comfortable on the ears</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

