<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>stratATK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was previously using the Alessandro MS-1 (like a modified Grados SR60), and decided to switch over to a closed-ear design. As you would expect, it isolates sound nicely, cutting down external noises, and leaks almost no sound. I wear glasses, and find the MDR-7506 is very comfortable for use over extended periods of time (3+ hours at a stretch). The cups fit nicely around my ears. The coiled wire is great. I was worried the 3 m long wire would be clumsy, but without being stretched, it is shorter than the Alessandro MS-1 cable- while having the potential to stretch much further, providing me with more freedom to move around. The sound quality is excellent, although if you are a heavy-bass lover, you might want to steer away from this. That being said, the bass is not weak by any means. I ... f I had to describe the frequency response, it feels like the lows and highs are somewhat flat, and the middle is a raised. As an added benefit, the headphones can fold up for added portability (with a carrying pouch included with the headphones). All in all, I am very satisfied with this product and its value- highly recommended!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>andersdesertfox</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>simply amazing best DJ headphones PERIOD</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After trying many, many headphones for djing, only to be disappointed by distorted sounds, weak isolation, discomfort or a combination of the three finally to have found a pair that has it all. The sounds are clear and crisp, you don&apos;t need to crank the bass or volume to hear what you are doing (soo nice for your ears). The isolation is extremely high so once again you dont need to crank the volume to drown out other sounds. They fit comfortably on your head not to tight or too loose they will not just slip off. This is nice because they dont give you a headache after wearing them for extended periods of time. Lastly the price. Wow such a reasonable price for the quality. I have tried the expensive ones, they always fall down in one of the three categories, but these simply do not i was bl ... own away!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Graz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDR-7506 Sony Headphones for recording</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use them for hours on end recording tracks and mixing. They are comfortable and sound very good - decent bass, mids and highs - very good articulation. The design is very effective at blocking outside noise. They are a bit bulky and you will feel the weight of them which can get a bit tiring after several hours - and you&apos;ll sweat in them if the room isn&apos;t chilled to nomal recording studio temperature. I&apos;ve been using these headphones for years and find that for the price they are an amazing value. I&apos;m still undecided about open-backed vs closed back and I have both. If you are setting up a DAW for project recordings or even going after a serious mix for your next CD, these headphones are a good investment. I do not care at all for the coiled cable - in fact I wish the cabling was st ... raight and a bit more sturdy. Sony has put a lot of effort into making a very good set of affordable headphones. Perhaps they can go one step further and do away with the coiled cable and give us straight cable instead. All it really succeeds in doing is getting tangled up with everything else and causing huge headaches. Great product. I recommend you invest in these and save your money for an expensive mixer or preamp.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paul</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Actually just test on a Ipod and a macbook and the sound still really good for this kind of source. There is enough power to make them sounds good. Even if this headphones will relieve the default of your MP3...if you can avoid MP3. I can&apos;t wait to test them on an amplifier. Easy to tidy and really comfortable. They have a good isolation. Faithful dynamic sound, deep clean bass and treble not aggressive. It&apos;s a good product, good quality/price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex in DC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exception Sound Quailty, Incredible Valu</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this product for audio and video editing applications professionally, but also simply to blast some tunes while I&apos;m hacking around at my desk. The full ear cups are comfortable, durable and, though the isolation is not total, it&apos;s very good. Normal conversation is barely audible with these phones on. Once music is playing, it&apos;s inaudible. To be frank, they don&apos;t look very cool. They&apos;re big and technical. They aren&apos;t very portable, even though they fold. The sounds quality, however, is startling in a sub-$100 headphone. Crisp clear highs, sharp lows with no rumble. If you are looking for a home audio bargain, this is it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tunerguy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still the Best for the Buck</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Over the last 22 years we have chosen these same headphones 3 times. Each time one gets worn out from years of regular use at our church, we do the listening test against other headphones, some 3x the cost. We STILL come back to the MDR7506 every time! It&apos;s not great for external volume isolation, but it wasn&apos;t designed for that. It just simply has the most faithful reproduction - virtually no sweetening in any frequency. NO Headaches from too tight a fit! You can wear them for hours.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tyrone</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Long Term Love Affair</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had these cans for about 7 years now, and they still amaze me with the quality of the sound they produce. I bought them on the recommendation of a friend who is a professional broadcaster. I use them for casual listening, audio editing, and hearing protection. The sound is accurate and isn&apos;t colored at the high and low ends. The clarity is good for critical listening when editing recordings. They are comfortable and I can wear them all day with no discomfort. The isolation is good, and combined with how comfortable they are makes them my first choice for hearing protection when I&apos;m practiceing or rehearsing. They are also nice for those times when I have to play to a click. They are durable and outside of the earpads have held up well through a couple thousand hours of use. You ... can fold them and stuff them in the included bag when not in use to keep them safe and clean. The only downside with them is the original earpads, and the coiled cord. The leather finish earpads make you sweat, and after a couple years they fall apart, but that&apos;s a good thing because you can then get a pair of velour pads from B&amp;H that will make these headphones perfect. The coiled cord is the other negative because of the weight that pulls on your left ear. Unfortunately, that can&apos;t be corrected so you just have to live with it. Still, it&apos;s not enough to stop me from giving them a 5 star rating.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Supergretch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I think I&apos;m in love...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My boyfriend got me these headphones for my birthday after he had recommended them to me months prior. I had been looking for a pair that would a) block out outside noise b) be easy to travel with c) not break the bank and lastly but most importantly, d) deliver exceptional sound quality. These headphones tick all boxes! I can wear them without playing music to block out annoyances but not be completely deaf while running around downtown. They fold up easily and fit conveniently in the travel pouch included, which is the perfect size to throw into my handbag. The sound quality is just great! I listen to a lot of acappella, acoustic, and rock music. Using these headphones has let me hear things I&apos;ve never heard before. The bass with some headphones can sound muddled because it&apos;s so low, bu ... t not with these. Everything is crystal clear and I find myself getting stuck playing and replaying music, rejoicing when I hear something new on my old tunes! I would definitely recommend these headphones to anyone looking for a professional quality piece. My only thumbs down is that the leather pads on the ear part can trap the heat from your head and become too warm over time. I also have the foam replacements that I hear will prevent this (I have yet to try those). This is such a minor detail though that it doesn&apos;t truly affect my overall love of this product. Go out and get a pair, you won&apos;t regret it! Enjoy!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJ Shiva</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Rescue your Sony headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got these based on a recommendation from a friend. My Sony MDR7506 earpads were in tatters, and I was sick of picking little vinyl bits off the side of my face. These were extremely easy to attach. Got it done in 5 minutes (toss the plastic bits; totally useless for Sonys). Now my headphones have better sound isolation, fit better, and most importantly I won&apos;t be picking headphone detritus off my neck for a week. Extremely great bargain that&apos;s giving new life to my otherwise super-dependable Sony headphones!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>W6FG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Comfortable and a good fit.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My Sony MDR-V6 Dynamic Stereo Headphones sound and feel great, but when the ear pads wore out in a very short time I looked for a better pair of replacement pads. The Beyerdynamic earcushions were just the ticket. I wasn&apos;t sure that they would fit, as my Sony headphones are not listed but I am happy to report that they fit perfect. They weren&apos;t cheap but I like the feel and if they last as long, or longer than the originals, I&apos;ll be a happy camper. I use these phones daily for bass guitar practice and my weak-signal ham radio work, so time will tell how well they stand up to every day use. The only reason I don&apos;t give it 5 stars is the price seems high.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>noob music studio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>industry standard</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This product was a great addition to my home recording studio. the clear, crisp and relatively flat sound response let me hear every single detail in my music. good for mixing my tunes. PROs: very comfortable earpads with a compact foldable design! solidly built, representing durability yet lightweight! great sound rendering it to be one of the best value headphones out there! CONs: none</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>soucharenko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For that price it is THE headphone to have. Lightweight and clear sound with a real isolation from the surrounding world. The sound is really profound, you can hear all the parasits of the voice, when they are present. I also like the folding ears making it very compact and easy to handle. I am just a bit concerned about the cables that go to the ears... I found them fragil.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>zac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony mdr 7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was very hesitant about getting these headphones. Not because I thought they would be distorted but because the main reason I bought these headphones was to just personally listen to my music. I know that they are normally for professional use due to their balanced and accurate sound but i listen to a big variety of music. I did not want headphones with a lot of bass for hip hop and rap music alone because it would make my classic rock sound distorted. When I got these headphones I was blown away it makes all my music sound good. Very clear all across the board. The bass, which was the main reason i didn&apos;t continue to listen to my old headphones, is still audible but not overwhelming. A very balanced, crisp, clear, and all around good headphone. Not to mention they are very comfortabl ... e. The only drawbacks are that they have i very ugly but professional design. And that people can hear what i am listening when it is relatively quiet. But that could be due to the volume at which i listen to my music. No huge complaints, all in all a good buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nick Chafin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just buy them</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these for video field productions. Head, shoulders, knees, and toes above the cheap headphones I usually use. Durable, great sound reproduction, easy to hear in loud environments, and fold up to a relatively small size. If you&apos;re looking for a good set of headphones to last you a long time, get these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gregory</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Was not expecting these to sound so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have a project studio going, mostly running a Digi003R+ and JBL LSR4326s, and got these headphones for monitoring and for performers to use. I&apos;m very impressed by how good these sound, yet I don&apos;t feel like they&apos;re all that hyped. Clearly the low end is enhanced, and the mids are thicker than my JBLs indicate, but clarity isn&apos;t an issue. They&apos;re plesantly even. They&apos;re also very comfortable on the ears and barely bleed at all, even when cutting quiet vocals with a sensitive condencer mic. Everything about these headphones has impressed me thus far, and at this price, they&apos;re a great purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>audio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good sound quality, great price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Comfortable, surprisingly well-built for the price, good sound isolation. Sound quality is good- neutral, well-balanced. Not for those who like their base booming.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>*</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Value!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable; Durable; Lightweight; Great Sound; Good Value; Compact; Good Bass; Stylish

I got these for my husband as a Christmas gift and he loves them. He&apos;ll use them while playing games, listeing to music and traveling. He wanted them because he was due for a new set and previously, his good friend bought them and said it was the best[$]he ever spent. So I knew they would be great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pete</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The standard monitor headphone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great for live sound work. Easily adjustable for listening with 1 or both ears. Fits large heads, though might clamp a bit tight if you&apos;re going to wear them for long periods of time. Great isolation but can be a bit hot in the highs for some. Plenty of cord, nice screw-on 1/8 to 1/4 adapter. Collapses into nice bag. Only real gripe is the earpads deteriorate quickly, however these are cheap and easy to replace.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>thomas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great replacement pads for Sony MDR-V6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The factory headphone padding that came with my Sony MDR-V6 headphones started to tear after about 1 year of regular use. After a bit of research, these velour padded earcushions seemed to be the best replacement pads. Here are my thoughts after 2 weeks of replacing the ear cushions.1) Realllllllly comfortable. You can wear these for hours without feeling the need to let your ears breathe for a bit.2) It changes the sound of the headphones. The bass sounds a bit louder and holds more weight to it. The overall tone sounds better in my opinion.The only thing that bothered me a bit about this product was that it was slightly difficult to actually get the pads onto the body of the headphones. But really, that isn&apos;t much of a problem at all.All in all a great product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Prince Henry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t Fault &apos;Em</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable; Compact; Lightweight; Good Value; Great Sound; Good Bass

My twenty seven year-old headphones quit working. So the hunt began in earnest. A colleague has a pair of these and I&apos;ve used them once or twice. My ears are delicate and, ahem, large-ish. So I needed something that would gently surround them while at the same time seal out extraneous sounds. I really didn&apos;t want to shell out $200 for headphones - not sure they would have been worth it anyway. So I took a chance on these. Couldn&apos;t be happier. Even comes with a little string storage pouch. The only caveat is that the intricate folding mechanism should be manipulated carefully. If you&apos;re used to handling semi-truck air brake hoses in the arctic, you&apos;re gonna have to pay special attention here.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Otokomae</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Probably the best headphones for [$]</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am actually replacing another set of high-end Sennheiser headphones with these. I have Grado and Audio Technicas as well, but these Sonys are rugged, accuarate, and the most comfortable headphones I&apos;ve owned. Even comfortable with glasses on! They do emphasize the mid&apos;s (voice) a bit, but have plenty of bass and highs, not nearly as dark as the Sennheisers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>jiffy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 23, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these for monitors when I shoot and edit videos. I thought these seemed light and flimsy, which is how most headphones under $90 feel anyway. But I am going to rate these cans on how they sound. These really exceeded my expectations at this price range (They seem to sound better than Sony 7502). They indeed sound great with rich mids, bright highs, and clean bass. The most durable part I believe is the plug (no joke). headband stays tight and durable. cups are plasticky, light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Trevor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb audio at a low cost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These are great headphones for any type of listening. I love these headphones!! If you want only one pair of headphones for all different types of music these are the ones. It presents an accurate responds on both the highs lows and mids. These headphones show what the audio engineers were intending for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr. T.O.E.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty awesome</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased these headphones because I wanted a second pair of monitor headphones for my studio. The very firt thing I noticed about these headphones is that they are very lightweight and the earcups are EXTREMELY COMFORTABLE. These are very good for recording as the earcups provide a good level of sound isolation. I use these headphones for tracking and editing songs in conjuction with my ATH M50&apos;s that I use for mixing. One thing I noticed when first listening to these headphones is that the mids sounded a little exaggerated compared to my M50&apos;s. But overall, I&apos;m very happy with my purchase and I highly recommend these to anyone whose looking for a good pair of headphones for recording.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Makes a good product even better</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these pads for my set of Sony MDR-V6&apos;s after the stock pads were beginning to wear out (i.e., flake and fall off frequently), and have do regrets about doing so. At [$] they might seem a little overpriced, but I find that their effectiveness and durability definitely make them worth their price. They improve the MDR-V6&apos;s feel on my head and the increased isolation they afford is definitely a benefit. They are somewhat larger than the stock pads, but that does not impact their performance negatively.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>iUDEX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing fidelity. Unbeatable value.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have a set of the Sony MDR-V6&apos;s for video editing, and KRK&apos;s KNS-8400 which I would consider similar. I purchased these as a second set for listening to music and when we have two editors.They are super comfortable for 4-6 hour editing sessions. They have amazing clarity and fidelity especially for this price - I would say they are better than many headphones in the $200-$500 range. They have a very flat signature which is great if you are editing or you appreciate being able to hear the bass not just feel it.They also fold up into itself very neatly in a carry case. The exposed wires always worry me, but I have yet to meet any issues.Compared to the KRK&apos;s, they are flatter in sound (which is a good thing if you are editing). If you have a decent amp (not essential) and equilizer then I&apos; ... d recommend these for listening to music as well.At US[$] they are a bargain!They also come with an exploding diagram showing all parts and how to service them. It shows that Sony still know how to make good gear.Very Highly Recommended.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>SP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Mostly used for sporting events, and ENG where durability and function matter. The muffs fit tight enough to block ambient crowd noise while offering solid sound quality. They sound pretty good on the in-flight sound systems too, but then again, I&apos;m not a recording engineer...but the price point works for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DALPRO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent sound - even better price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lightweight; Great Sound; Comfortable; Good Value; Stylish; Good Bass

These are industry standards and I can see why. You could spend way more and still not top these. BuyDig.com had the best price by a long shot at the time I priced them too. Good stuff!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>aklugs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Work Like A Charm</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Comfortable and great sounding, I don&apos;t think you can do better for the money. I use these with my lexicon onix u42s interface and the sound is pristine with ample highs and lows. Fit well over ear and easily adjust. No complaints.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Amateur Person</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You get what you pay for.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Lightweight

I bought these headphones to use with my Roland TD-10 drum-kit based on positive reviews that I had read in various locations. For the price, these headphones provide decent sound quality and comfort. I was not, however, as blown away by their quality as I had anticipated based on reviews by others. They are a decent product, but you are getting exactly what you pay for... nothing more. I am content with my purchase, but if I had it to do over, I might explore some other options.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>WstlndGrdnr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great, Accurate sound &amp; very durable</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love these headphones. I bought this pair to replace a set that finally died after 10 years of rough use in my travels around the world. They have a flat, accurate sound, tight, closed design, and they fold up for easy storage in a backpack or carry-on. I especially appreciate the bass response on these. I often monitor on small, near-field monitors that don&apos;t produce the low end accurately, but with these I can hear what I&apos;m missing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>MikusN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDR-7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was really surprised at how well this headphone sounds. Deep low end response. Clear mids and highs. They are definitely the perfect pair for audio/video editing. If you&apos;re looking for a headphone to listen to your tunes on ipod - this is not the headphone for you (most likely). However if your looking for a headphone that will reveal EVERYTHING in the mix - you can&apos;t go wrong with these. In my opinion these are head and shoulders above the Senheiser HD280 Pro both in sound quality as well as comfort.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>TiagoRc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I buy these to start my home studio, and i like it. For the price it worth pretty well. The only thing that is not so good is the bass, but of course, this headphone is for monitoring, needs to be balanced and it really is.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lou the sound guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Sony headphone cushion that lasts!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This Beyer headphone cushion is a perfect fit for the ubiquitous Sony MDR V6 and 7506 headphones. They are a comfortable velveteen, effective at isolation and they will not corrode and flake off with use like the Sonys do. And extremely comfortable, even in long listening sessions or live recording! If your trusty Sony phones have gotten flaky and sweaty, these will make a huge difference to you! I own ten sets of Sonys, and still use the first ones I got in 1986 daily, and am gradually changing them over as the original earpads wear out. Totally worth the slightly higher cost! Lou Judson</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Glolini</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this product for field recording and is amazing. Maby if there is traffic or heavy machines does not have a total isolation. But just in extreme cases. The sound quality is perfect for its price. And they are comfortable to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ofir</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony rule!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>just bought Sony MDR-7506 Headphones and i am very satisfied with them! they have best sound with deep bass and treble. they mute most of the ambient noise as well. the negative sides are the cable that is curely and uncomfortable for traveling. Another downside is that they a little bit too tighten on the ears so for long time they not the best option. besides the 2 downsides they are best choice for that price! :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>fintanmason</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent quality for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The headphones are truly professional, giving you the audio quality of the actual recording. Bass is spectacular and they fit perfectly. The only problem is if you wear them for a long period of time; your ears might start to hurt slightly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Exlpaighne</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>These Headphones + B&amp;H Rock!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is my first set of real headphones, so I can&apos;t compare them to much, but man do they sound good! I can&apos;t believe not only the bass, but the clarity of the bass. For the test run I did Dark Side of the Moon, and it was like being a kid again! Plus, I gotta say that I ordered on Monday after the big storm, and I got my cans Tuesday...B&amp;H are a class act in my book!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Poppy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>25 year old Sony MDR-V6 transformed!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Always loved these headphones for their clarity in the mids and highs. Great phones for critical listening, monitoring, recording except for the bass. Although it was always there and was clean, it never came to the front the way I liked it in Jazz, Pop and Cinema. These Beyerdynamic pads have more substance to them...they are more comfortable, much firmer and not soft foam, and provide an open space between the headphone drivers and the ears for the sound energy to accumulate. The result is a clarity and definition to the bass and all percussive instruments that is immediately apparent and quite up front...the way the recording was meant to be heard in dynamic passages. I would estimate that the low end has a gradual rise of +2db. Tympanic response is much improved. Piano very percussive. ... I think Beyerdynamic has proved its point...it knows how to make a fine headphone sound even better. Literally, the Sony MDR-V6 has been transformed. Now the low end has the detail, definition and tympany of the mids and highs. In my view, these pads move the excellent MDR-V6 to the level of outstanding. I had considered buying a headphone with the 50mm drivers to improve the bass (I used to play and love to hear bass runs to this day). I particularly wanted the deepest bass possible for Cinema. Now I think I&apos;ll try these great old phones for awhile yet. What a difference! Highly recommended!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>polymorphism</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality and value for money!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>As an audio researcher, these headphones are very comfortable (especially for long term use). Ambient external noise is significantly reduced and audio quality is nice, crisp, and clear. Very much value for money - highly recommended.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Will</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality at a reasonable price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For the price, and B&amp;H has the best (I know as I checked everywhere), the Sony 7506 headphones are a great quality set of cans. Also, they are completely versatile - use them on your MP3 player, your home stereo or in your recording studio. Not only do they look good, but the feel good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BillVan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound low price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Unusual these days to find a product that performs better than most other units at a fraction of the price. Realistic sound, good durability, also works well in amateur radio broadcast monitoring both receiving weak signals and for final output adjustment when transmitting ESSB. For those not involved in ham radio, ESSB is a extended frequency response using the single sideband mode where audio quality transmitted approaches broadcast quality. Very nice for monitoring any type of audio, smooth base response, balanced highs, exceptional sound field. All opinions are subjective when it comes to audio, but these perform very well for the price point, if you know what to listen for, you&apos;ll be impressed!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JhanJhan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Soooo Soft...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these to replace the pleather pads on my ATH M50 cans. The fit was a bit tight putting it on, but once seated, it looks great. What&apos;s more important, it really didn&apos;t alter the sound other then a little more leakage and less isolation...not a lot, just a bit to be noticeable. What it does for the headphone is make them very very comfortable. No more hot, sweaty ears. :D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Thunderfoot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A reliable product I would buy again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the MDR-7506 to monitor live recording of music with a Marantz CDR310 Pro portable recorder. The music source is usually acoustic with vocal, and instruments range from violins to double bass. I use the phones for subsequent editing and production of a master stereo disc. Compared to the Sennheiser HD280&apos;s I also use, which are more comfortable and block more background noise, the 7506&apos;s render a more accurate and natural, full-frequency sound. They don&apos;t boost highs or lows. They are lightweight but not flimsy, but after a few months of occasional use, the aprons of the ear cushions started to come out of the grooves. I kept pressing them back down with a straight edge until they finally had to be replaced after a year. Replacements are cheap and easy to find. While the HD280&apos;s are ... more comfortable and do a better job of cutting out background noise, I prefer the 7506&apos;s because of their light weight and full, flat frequency response, so I bought a spare pair to avoid stress on the ear cushions. I also like the convenience of the mini-adapter. The Fostex T20R MKll&apos;s were comfortable, but heavy in mid-range, blocked little background, and were not a good purchase compared to the MDR7506&apos;s. There&apos;s no reason to buy anything other than another set of MDR7506&apos;s when I need another pair.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The standard for video production</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I work as a freelance cameraman/editor in NYC. I went for years with cheaper models before buying the MDR7506. WOW! I can&apos;t believe the difference! The sound if incredible. They sit comfortable on ear, and surround it thus providing nice isolation from outer environment. I use it for concerts, interviews, etc. There is nothing better out there for the price. You will not be disappointed....go get em!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>utility project</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>pro sony phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i make my own music at home. i have used the sony 7502&apos;s for years and enjoy them. the 7506&apos;s are a step up. there&apos;s better isolation of sound, better volume and i&apos;m better able to isolate problems in the mix. it&apos;s taking a little getting used to, as i said the 7502&apos;s have been my ears for years now. the only thing i&apos;m not sure about is the fit, the 7506&apos;s seem a bit snug, i&apos;m used to the 7502&apos;s flopping around a little and being loose.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ben U</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Headphones for Field Work</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these for field recording. Three things about these headphones make them perfect for the job: 1. COMPACT: They collapse nicely, with a coiled cable, which should easily fit into your audio kit 2. FREQUENCY RESPONSE: Excellent, excellent, excellent sound. You&apos;ll be able to catch any hums or hisses with these headphones. 3. SOUND-CANCELLING: The muffs on the headphones fit snugly around the ears, and do an excellent job of eliminating outside noises, so you can be immersed in the sound coming through your mics. Terrific headphones at an unbeatable price. A+ to Sony for these.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>michael</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great field headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great headphones! I&apos;ve used them professionally for over 8 years now. When I needed to purchase my own, I didn&apos;t hesitate to order these. For the price they are as good as you can get but I haven&apos;t used a lot of others. Before then we used the Koss Pro4AA as well as some other cheaper ones when the Koss would meet an unfortunate end. Finally, I switched to the MDR7606. It has a great frequency response range. Primarily, I record voice work in the field and these phones have no problem in that range. It&apos;s worked great in the music I&apos;ve recorded, but I wouldn&apos;t be able to elaborate on that as I don&apos;t do that alot. The phones are comfotable and fit beautifully yet are not too large. I never feel like they&apos;re heavy or uncomfortable which is a problem I&apos;ve had in the past. The cushion is gre ... at and isolates sound well. Although not a dedicated sound guy. I am very particular to hear any problems I have in the field, and the MDR7606 does just that. The phones fold up nicely so it packs together in my kit well, which is great as I don&apos;t have alot of help to carry my gear. The cord is long but not in the way. And unlike the others I&apos;ve used, they have not self-destructed. I&apos;ve dropped them more times then I can count, kicked them, mashed them and I have never had a problem. My other phones would only last 1-2 years, these have lasted 5 and counting! Part of its secret, I think, is it is well built and light so upon impact(if it should happen) the parts don&apos;t want to seperate, which is something I&apos;ve seen alot of in the past. Get these phones, a great price for such a versitle headphone that will give you years of use. With the pearson cushion replacement you might never need to buy another.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Van</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Extremely comfty</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The ear cushions on my MDR7506s wore out and I was about to buy the standard Sony replacement ones when a friend told me about these. Long story short: they&apos;re amazing. Not only do these velour pads make the MDR7506s more comfortable, but they also have better sound isolation and seem to make the bass stronger to boot! It feels like a whole new pair of headphones. A must have product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Scott A</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does the job.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this with a Canon 5D and a Canon XL1S to monitor audio. The unit has a nice fit and blocks out external sounds fairly well. While I&apos;m a film professional I&apos;m not a sound expert. I&apos;ve used Sony products for years so my decision was based a little on the brand and the reasonable cost for a good set of head phones. After a couple of loud factory shoots and a few basketball games I can say it works pretty good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jaco D</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t hesitate buying these pads!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought my MDR-V6 exactly 20 years ago, and back then I was blown away by its performance. I&apos;ve tried more expensive headphones and the MDR-V6 can hold a candle to those even if it costs just a fraction of the former&apos;s price. If ever it had an Achilles Heel, it would be those flimsy earpads. I moved to Asia for a while and those earpads were a pain! Not only did they make your ears sweat, they just disintegrated within months of my arrival. Thought it was the weather, but it turns out that those OEM earpads couldn&apos;t take the wear and tear of constant use. I moved back to North America and was thinking of throwing away my V6 when I came across these Beyerdynamic pads. Though the V6 was The Best in my books, these pads just made the V6 Best-er. I&apos;m looking for a second pair of headse ... ts to keep at home (I use the V6 on the road) and plan to get the 7506. You bet I&apos;ll be ordering those pads as well and not wait for the original pads to fail before I replace them.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Truckpile</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Classic Studio Monitors</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound; Good Value; Good Bass; Comfortable

These are the headphones that get used in all the great studios, industry standard, period. These sound amazing, you can mix a whole record on these and just a/b with other produced songs. If you are mixing, producing, or just want to hear everything that&apos;s really in the mix when you&apos;re listening to your music collection, MDR-7506s are a no brainer!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value in headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Comfortable; Good Bass; Good Value; Great Sound; Durable

These headphones are simply the best kept secret when it comes to over the ear headphones. Forget wasting $200 - $300 on Bose QC headphones. These are great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>pa32jock</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sounds great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact; Great Sound; Good Value; Comfortable; Good Bass

Cons: Too Much Ambient Noise

Very good flat sound. It would be nice if a litle more background noise was muted.I would buy them again.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>lee602</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good replacement for Sony MDR-V6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I read that these were better than the standard Sony ear pads (which wore out after just a year of very light use) so I decided to try them. They appear to be of decent quality and look pretty good on the headphones. They fit well and were fairly easy to put on. However, my ears don&apos;t seem to fit in them quite as well as in the original Sony pads. Otherwise they are quite comfortable. Hopefully they&apos;ll last longer than the Sony pads.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spook0987</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great sound definition; Versatile; Compact; Durable; Easy To Use; Clear Sound; Lightweight

I use this Product to Mix records with. Iam a Professional DJ with over 33 years of Experience
in mixing cutting scratching and thease are the only Units since the Mdr V6 type that help in being able to tell what is on beat and on key in any mix.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>rob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>works well</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The headphones are used for monitoring location sound recording, and mixing audio for video. Headphones are well built, the cups rotate and are comfortable to wear, and keep out most of the background noise. It would be nice if one of the cups would flip completely up and out of the way, leaving one ear uncovered. It sort of does this, but not in way that is comfortable long term. The coiled cable will stretch out enough to allow movement around the gear, and short enough (when coiled) to not get caught underfoot or on the tripod. Audio quality is excellent, with more bass than one might be accustomed to when coming from an open-back headphone. I very much like that the cups fold up inside the headband, making the headphones into a small, compact package for storage/packing away.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Biff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great versatile pads</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Put on my Ultrasone HFI580s Fits like a glove. Very comfortable and feels light on my head. Much much better than the stock pleather pads it came. One thing I didnt like is that it slightly changed the sound quality a bit. That is expected because these pads arent made for my headphones. The highs became just a tad brighter. But it doesnt bother me. Overall great purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>spliffs.up</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>something worth buying!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>their easy to use.. they really block out all the noise, and with the music playing. you wont be able to hear anything.. i love them and im glad i bought them. only thing about them that i didnt like was that the bass isnt as laud as i thought is was going to be. be overall a good purchase</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>12st</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Cans, Good ISO, not rugged</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i used this product for mixing live recordings down to 2 channels on the fly. the cans provide good ISO making it a breeze to check signal quality. they fit snugly and are comfortable, but i ended up returning them because of the size and some concerns about ruggedness. i travel to gigs on a bicycle and found these cans a bit bulky and the earcups are full of a liquid that i read can be pierced and leak. Before i had a chance to find out, i sent them back. i think the ISO can be replicated with a good pair of IEM&apos;s like the ETY&apos;s and a gun range ear cover over the earbuds. i have never found hearing protection with a liquid filling at gun ranges. i believe these ear covers can be found in the $10 ballpark.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Rice Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good All Purpose Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have used these headphones for many years at many job sites. They have decient bass and good overall sound. Though they are not great headphones (and not many are) these are great for DJ work, Live sound mixing, or even to use to monitor a recording. They are comfortable and fold into a nice compact unit. Be aware they do not block out as much external noise as some other headphones, but they do enough to get the job done. Overall great product for a good price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gal With a Guitar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great quality, Great sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I haven&apos;t had these headphones for long, but I am really happy with their performance thus far! They do a great job of sealing the sound in, but don&apos;t hurt your ears when you wear them for an extended period of time. They are conveniently designed (I like the way that they flip so you can listen without putting them on your head. I would recommend them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stebaht</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for all listening</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>These phones are fantastic value. Transparent sound for music, clear precise bass, accurate sound repro. I use them for listening to music, movies and gaming. The cord is a little long for commuting and mobile listning but its great that its long for sitting around your desk, lots of movement. to thats a pro/con. But they are wonderful all around phones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ReDcOX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The studio standard ~ great in the field</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use it for listening to the audio recording while in the field for video production and for the audio and sound mix in the dit suite. This Sony can&apos;t be beat for value and performance.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mad_crease</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Initial Thoughts</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I presently own 2 sets of Sony&apos;s V6 cans. As that&apos;s all they ammount to after the garbage pads available through Sony wear down (2-3 months). I use them daily 4 to 5 hours for editing sound and training videos. Enough background. After reading and listening to others rave about these pads, I opted to give them a try. Cons : I was a bit dismayed when I looked at the flimsy and cheap looking replacements. The Sony&apos;s at least have some feel to them. These are thinner and really offer no more physical confort for my use. I also noticed a high end drop/clipping. This is usually above 16khz where I start to notice it. There is no instructions to NOT use the plastice spacers with my V6&apos;s, but that was easy enough to figure out. Pros : no sweating.. PERIOD. no ear itching from sweat at all. Also ... it does dampens ambient noise to a degree, and that in itself is a big bonus. The pads are easy to put on if you just work around the ear flange and slide the pad as you go. Now that I said they look flimsy and cheap looking, they are not to bad. When compared to the Sony replacements, they are miles beyond. I will see how they hold up. As for losing the high end, Its because the foam filter rests on the end of the speaker and muffles the higher frequency oscilation of the cone. I&apos;ll try and modify the plastic disc as a bridge to keep the pad off the cone. I saw someone else post about cutting the Sony pad from the old ones. I&apos;m not sure, but even if I am not able to regain some of the upper end, I&apos;ll continue with them. For now, I don&apos;t have to pick black bits of crumpled plastic/vinyl from my shirt, ears and sound board from the deteriorated Sony pad covers. If these hold up past the 4 month mark, I&apos;ll get the other ones equipped.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Captain SmashFist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The only headphones I like to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a sound engineer and a musician and I have been listening to everything I can on these headphones since 1999. Got some in college and they&apos;d get used afew hours every day. For my ridiculous amount of wear and tear they last about 2-4 years (I think that&apos;s amazing). Whether I&apos;m playing bass in the live room with the drummer or having to edit tracks and not bug anyone, these are the only headphones I reach for. I&apos;ve probably had 5-7 pairs and love them and will keep getting them/replacing them if they break or blow up (and they take abuse pretty well), I hope Sony never discontinues or changes them. For anyone using them casually I&apos;m sure they&apos;d last a long time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr. K.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Good isolation, very good quality, great price. I own 5 pairs and use them in my recording studio with no complaints. Very comfortable, especially for multi-hour sessions. There are better quality headphones but for substantially more money. Great buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mixup</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still the best</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Sony released a couple new models to surpass the quality of the 7506, and reviews have been lukewarm. At [$] these are a bargain and are far better than any $300 Beats headset.They are still the standard with most of us pro film sound recordists.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sufjan Fan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for entertainment as well!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great value; Durable; Beautiful Sound

Cons: Initially defective

I bought these headphones for generic music listening and entertainment purposes. The initial pair I got were defective (lost sound out of one ear after 15 minutes), but Adorama replaced them without any question. The new pair I got works great and sounds beautiful. Way better sound than a lot of more expensive stuff.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>ojo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Performance Claims
    
    Headphones Type: dynamic, closed
    Magnet type: Neodymium
    Speaker size: 40 mm
    Frequency response: 10 Hz - 20 kHz
    Impedance: 63 ohms at 1 kHz
    Sensitivity: 106 dB / mW
    Rated input power: 500 mW
    Maximum power input: 1000 mWPlug: Gold-plated, 3.5 mm, with an adapter for 6.3 mm
    Cable length: 3 meters (twisted structure)
    Weight: 230 grams

Headphone sound analytical, with a slight bias in brightness. Low-frequency case some forced, but it worked fine - feel the depth of bass, there is practically no mumbling. Mid-range is applied gently, naturally, without whistling. Vocals perfectly distinguishable. High frequencies slightly podyarcheny,possible to monitor a given range.
Stereo is wide enough ... , and for closed headphones - or just a luxury, is the effect of shallow depth of the scene. Attack of the good, the sound is felt only a blur in a very complex record. The dynamic range is wide, listening to classical music on the 7506 is nice.Detail at a high level, the smallest details of tracks can be heard.
Genre preferences, I find I can not, headphones do a good job with all the genres, they are universal.
The only moot point is, in my opinion - dryness filing. There is no &quot;punch&quot; is the presentation of information - and nothing more. On the other hand,for the &quot;studio&quot; headphones is more plus than a minus.
Use the MDR 7506 with low-power sources, I would not recommend.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leecast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Industry Standard &amp; Time Proven</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I needed a decent set of headphones for my studio and did not want to break the bank. I did my homework on these, and a number of audio/video professions I know love Sony headphones. They all mentioned the flat response and being able to trust these in terms of bass level. The coiled cord is nice, as well as the fact that it can plug into both 1/8 and 1/4 headphone jacks due to the adapter is comes with. Beyond that, they fold up and come with a decent Sony bag to protect and transport them. I do professional voice-over work and have a good set of KRK studio monitors I use for mixing. These phones are great to wear while recording and give me another sound perpective to experience when trying to listen to things in multiple ways. This helps ensure a recording that will sound great on al ... l kinds of systems. In short, these are great for the money. They are lighweight, comfortable, compact, and seem to reject background noise well. Unless you are looking to spend twice as much, and move into something like a Beyerdynamic DT 770 Pro, I would suggest strongly considering these.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HatesNoise</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Cans for Most Purposes</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use them for practicing guitar and listening to music. They are very comfortable to wear and have a natural, balanced sound. Their compact design and foldability make them good for travel.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Decker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I Love The Smell Of New Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Well I am going to say that I am in radio and I have used these headphones for years. I have also seen them on more heads than I can count. I use them for at least 5 hrs everyday. They are light weight and have a great sound. I take them with me if I have to be another studio. Don&apos;t leave home without them.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kuledud3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sweet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these expecting something pretty good but not amazing... Well these are amazing. I was considering Beats br Dr. Dre.. No these sound just as good for a way cheaper price. If you are debating between beats, or any other over ear headphones for that matter, with these? Choose these, you will not regret.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>RRRobots</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Loving these headphones!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After dealing with some of the more stylish headphone brands that ended up sounding ok but falling apart fairly quickly, I decided to spend a bit more and give the MDR-7506&apos;s a go based on the hundreds of glowing reviews here and elsewhere. I&apos;ve had them for a couple weeks now and love them, these are by far the best headphones I have ever owned. Everything sounds crisp and clean, there&apos;s a decent amount of bass, but it&apos;s not overemphasized. I&apos;m not as knowledgeable about the different aspects of audio as some reviewers here, but I can explain it this way; in the past I was constantly mucking around with the EQ in my player software, now I generally don&apos;t have to because things just sound right. The MDR-7506s are also darn comfortable. I bought a pair of Garfield earpad softies from the ... get-go, and with those on I haven&apos;t noticed much discomfort, even after extended use. The headband conforms to my skull well and adjusts easily. It&apos;s got kind of a ratchet thing going on, everything locks into place and stays that way- one side isn&apos;t slowly slipping down or anything like that. The rest: the cord is plenty long, but coiled so it doesn&apos;t get in the way. Everything seems well made and sturdy- I don&apos;t feel like I have to handle the things with kid gloves (not that I&apos;m throwing them around, either). The phones have a little hinge on each side so that they fold up nice, making them pretty compact for travel or whatever. I find myself liking the way they look more and more- they aren&apos;t stylish, but they are designed with kind of a perfect utility.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>xBLACKMAM8Ax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wow!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I sold my Bose QC3&apos;s and decided to go with these after a good music producer friend of mine steered me toward these. I love the sound and they are very comfortable. The bass doesn&apos;t get distorted like the Bose and Beats By Dre. This set is the BEST BANG for the BUCK!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hutch Video</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use these for video editing. Good, clean sound and comfortable to wear for long periods of time. The material that covers the padded earpieces seems to be coming loose after only using them a few times... I don&apos;t know if it is poor design or the way I handle them??? but that is the only problem I have had. Overall nice, professional product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>PeteTheBeat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best I&apos;ve used</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact; Great clarity; Comfortable; Great Sound

I am a drummer. When one of my bands practices or plays out, we record the session with a Sony PCM digital recorder. I use these Sony headphones for mixing and editing the tunes at home and while on the road for my regular job. Their clarity and bass-response is amazing. They are the best headphones I have used to date.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>T-Money</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Quality that lasts 6 years!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Versatile; Durable; Clear Sound; Easy To Use; Lightweight; Compact

I picked up my first pair of these Sony&apos;s 6 years ago when I started college. The audio quality stayed the same over the 6 years of use. The seals to my ear got worn over that time, but they still got the job done the entire time.Best [$] I have ever spent on an audio product and I instantly knew I wanted a 2nd pair when they broke finally.I would tell anyone who was looking at getting noise cancelling, high def, or any kind of headphones to get these ones. The cord is awesome and very lengthy, the quality of the audio is amazing, and the portability of the product is that of any other recording headphone.Plus - if you take care of them you will get a great 6 years out of them or more. On mine, the pin brok ... e where it holds the headphone to the arm that wraps around your head. I could&apos;ve fixed them - but decided 6 years for [$] is well worth the product.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beyerdynamic Earcushion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The cushions on my DT250&apos;s had become real funky from extended use so finding these replacements was great. Identical to the originals with a tight-napped textured surface that&apos;s soft but still seals well enough to give adequate isolation on closed headphones. Quality is typical beyerdynamic, fitting and snapping into the headphones perfectly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Deppy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>now the ears can breath &amp; bass sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Purchased these recently with the free shipping and I would like to say the delivery was very quick. Put them on my Sony MDR-7506&apos;s and do not get the ear forecast of hot with a chance of sweat. These definitely keep the ears much cooler &amp; comfortable. The bass seems to be deeper and not as pronounced as the original Sony&apos;s, which is one of the reasons I loved the sound from the Sony&apos;s. I noticed that the fabric between the speaker and my ear(separate piece with the Beyerdynamics) on these seem a bit thicker than the Sony ones (which are connected to the sony ear cushions). I may cut out the Sony ones and try them in place of the Beyerdynamic ones to see if this will help the bass sound. Will post If I do this. Installation simply requires slowly stretching them over the earphone ... s then I carefully used a guitar pick to push it into the crevice. Also, you don&apos;t need to use the plastic inserts that came with the product. Very happy doing business with B&amp;H.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dr. Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Replaced My Sony MDR-V6 Pads</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is definitely an upgrade in more ways than one to my Sony MDR-V6 headphones. First of all the comfort factor, I can wear these all day with the Beyer pads, where I could go no more than an hour with the stock Sony&apos;s. I even forget I&apos;m wearing headphones. These go around my ears instead of on. This being my second replacement set of this headphone model, my originals finally gave up the ghost, after 15 years, I know these phones and the old pads very well. Next, the bass response tightens up, outside noise levels decrease and the overall sound of already great headphones improves. This is the best upgrade to a piece of equipment I have made in a very long time. I&apos;m smiling.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Flt Girl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exellent Quality Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very happy with my purchase of the sony mdr-7506 headphones. It was delivered on time and was properly packaged and sustained no damage. These are the first pair of over-ear headphones I have bought. I use them to listen to music/movies on my computer. I find the sound crisp but also with full bass. The best of both worlds in my opinion. I would recommend this product to friends and family.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>deadhead</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>solid phones..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quantifiably artticulate; Compact; Easy To Use; Clear Sound

Cons: Best choice for the money

I own a pair of Beyer Dynamic DT 770 - I love them, but they&apos;re a little &quot;warm&quot;.... luckily I have a head phone amp that allows you to control bass, treble, balance &amp; gain on each channel - so I can roll off a little of the low end. I bought the MDR 7506&apos;s as a gift for my son&apos;s home studio and he LOVEs them. Very even response across the frequency spectrum. No wonder they are the &quot;industry standard&quot;. Highly recommend the 7506&apos;s. Can&apos;t go wrong. Buy &apos;em. :D</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Franck Bender</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been using this product for about two weeks, mainly on my laptop and on portable media players; they sound even better with my Fiio E6 portable headphone amplifier (less than $30). I find the sound not too bright but rather neutral, I think they sound great and seem very durable, except for the earpads, but obviously that&apos;s minor. They are hard to beat for the price, especially with the overpriced gadgets that are invading the market nowadays. I know some people don&apos;t like how they look, so you might want to actually see what they look like on someone before committing. I myself love the vintage look, and I love that I won&apos;t be buying a new pair every 6 months. I use them with the velour padded Beyerdynamic earcushions (originally replacements for Beyerdynamic DT 250 and 280; item BEE ... DT250V on here), and they are very comfortable, not too clenching (and I have a large head). These earcushions are a great upgrade, they don&apos;t stick to the ears when sweating (like the pleather originals do), they are more comfortable, and I even think the headphones look better with those. These are great headphones of professional grade, for all of us who refuse to buy shiny overpriced gadgets. They&apos;re a great buy for under $100, and are flat out better than some $200 headphones out there.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Morten</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Clear &amp; Superb sound!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Excellent studio headphone! Crisp &amp; Clear sound. I use it for DJ&apos;ing as well, and just love it. Beats those bassheavy &amp; muddy DJ-models by miles. Pure quality from Sony with an unbeatable price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DeCA Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony&apos;s MDR-7506 Headphones...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>What can I say -- I like them! They are light-weight, sound is very good, reduces exterior noise, and fold for easy storage or transport. I use them for editing video/audio clips -- cuts down the ambient noise, and I don&apos;t disturb those around me. Tried a few others but for the price a very good choice for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JacksonBauer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Improvement to Sony MDR-V6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I recently purchased these earcushions for my Sony MDR-V6 headphones. They were very easy to install and they have vastly improved the headphones. They are much more comfortable--I can now wear the headphones for hours without any discomfort or hot ears. The headphone isolation and sound quality seems to have improved.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>XEMENES Productions</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Nice Set of Cans!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This unit is a must have for professional use, especially in video/audio production, It provides quality sound at an affordable price. Great bass and ambient noise come with these. We use these on video cameras, so we love the coiled cord, something we didn&apos;t find to much of on other products up for sale. The only thing we have a minor issue with, which we can find on many sets of headphones, is the moisture build up after wearing them for so long. So get the Garfield Headphone Softies to keep you nice and dry.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>OriginalAdric</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After using various consumer models of Sony headphones, I&apos;ve found my favorite. For the price, they sound great, and the inclusion of a service manual is a real winner for me. After having all my previous Sony headsets break on me, I really like being able to replace broken parts myself instead of having to buy a whole new headset.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brian that guitar player</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is my first set of real headphones, so I can&apos;t compare to much else, but I know what I&apos;m hearing out of these cans, and that&apos;s goood clean sound! These are more flat response, but not overly sterile...i use them both for listening and small time home recording. Very nice sound spectrum. For the price range, these rock! [...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ted the cameraman.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Studio Monitor Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For any field monitoring use these headphones are the way to go. I am an owner operator video DP that also subcontracts sound engineers, I have tried many other headsets and it always comes down to, well they are OK, but not as good as a set of MDR-7506&apos;s So then I ask, why not just get them in the first place? Sonically they are un-matched, and because they are closed you can easily isolated what you are recording from background. Anyone who is seriously recording sound owns a pair of MDR-7506&apos;s. The only compaint is the wire used in the curley cable is difficult to solder, so many times a repair becomes a replace.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A quality replacement option</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased these after reading that they would directly replace the extremely aged cushions on my Sony MDR-V6 headphones. Great material (velour over vinyl something), easy installation. Noted that sound quality actually appears to have increased, more than likely due to the slightly increased depth and density of these cushions over OEM, increasing the physical distance to the ear but also creating a more quiet environment within the cup. On that note, the cushions are more firm/stiff than OEM, changing the feel of the headphones slightly as well (at least as of about 1.5 weeks after install). Overall, these appear to be a quality option for replacement and this reviewer at least is planning on changing out the pads on other headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hawaiian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this product when I listen to music. What&apos;s great is I can tune everything out, every noise. I like how loud the headphones can be, and the beats are awesome. I don&apos;t like how I can hear bass. If I&apos;m listening to music and it has a lot of bass the headphones don&apos;t really put it into my ears.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jay Alexander</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Value with full display packaging</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable; Lightweight; Clear Sound

Cons: none

You get a truly reliable full spectrum reproduction of sound. Allows you to use your mic effectivly with no second guessing about fidelity.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones for monitoring audio on location for film shoots. The sound quality is superb. You can hear almost everything. They&apos;re very comfortable and adjust to fit most head sizes. And they fold up nicely for easy storage with the rest of my audio kit. Would definitely recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alterego</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best pair of head phones I&apos;ve had</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought these mainly for my recording class, though I was needing a new pair as my old ones managed to break in half. These headphones are made from metal and plastic so hopefully that won&apos;t happen again. The folding function is nice, and the threaded 1/4 adapter is a plus. All sound frequencies are crystal clear, playing guitar through these direct from the amp gives me great sound and range. My only concern is the small wires at the folding joints, which overtime I bet will be the point of failure when I lose sound in one ear. Folding joint + small wire...hmm... Other than though this is a great pair of head phones, definitely worth the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Josh the Procrastinator</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stunning</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>When I first heard my teacher spouting off about this product I wasn&apos;t really buying into it, but since it was required for class, I bought it. It turns out that everything my teacher said was true. It really plays music they way it was intended to be heard. The pure sounds of the song without the enhancements or overkill of bass. These headphones are absolutely stunning and I would recommend it to anyone who appreciates high quality sound. You really get the bang for the buck on these Headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dan the Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Like Pillow on Your Ears</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great product and well worth the investment. Fit very well and firmly around ears for my Sony MDR-V6. Material is very durable and workks wonders. As other customers have said, because they are a little deeper than the vinyl stock earpads that come with sony headphones, there is a slightly better bass response with my headphones. Easy to install, too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JackHalfaPrayer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic no-mod solution for MDR-7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use SONY MDR&apos;s for pro music and sound design work. The factory model comes with crummy earpads that degrade quickly and wear thin. These pads not only fit the MDR-7500&apos;s perfectly, they&apos;re also more comfortable and cancel out significantly more incoming external sound. And they&apos;re built to last. I&apos;d pay twice what I did.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jacob49</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones: would want volume cont</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Sound; Lightweight; Compact; Comfortable; Good Value

If I was doing this over again I would want a volume control on the device. Too often I have to adjust the volume on the source to a point that is almost impossible to set.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>connor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>:/ hmmmm idk</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these headphones at a local music store and they were on sale for[$] originally 130 which I soon realized was not the case. I listened to them in the store and they sounded amazing some of the best. When I got home I plugged in my 30$ ear buds and compared the sound quality and there was not much difference in sound quality besides the bass. Needless to say I was disappointed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Phantompwr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got these as a headphone reference when mixing music and audio for video, and I am planning to use them in the field doing on-location sound in the future. It is my first time using this popular model of headphone and I can see why they are popular. I was blown away by the sound quality. The bass reproduction is especially good compared to some of my other headphones, and it has more ambient noise reduction than the AKG and the cheaper sony models I have (though not nearly as much as the metrophones). They are pretty light for the size, and I have been able to wear them for a good amount of time so far without discomfort. I seem to have a sensitive head so it is tough to find a good pair of headphones that are comfortable, but these seem to do the job. I&apos;m very happy with my purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim the Runner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Used as replacements on ixos dj1005</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 2, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It is difficult to find replacements for earcushions on headsets out of production since manufacturers do not list dimensions of their earcushions. Nor they provide any scale on pictures of replacement cushions. So for the most part it is trial and error process. After extensive search online I&apos;ve decided to replace earcushions in my ixos dj1005 by ministry of sound by these. I was nervous that the replacements may be too small, but I managed (barely) to fit them on the earcups. Hopefully, velour will last longer than leatherette cover and won&apos;t flake.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mat Schranz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had heard so many great things about these headphones online, so I decided to try them out. They have great sound with nice bass depth and rich clearity. A welcome addition to my growing home studio. Mat</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome replacement for Sony MDR-V6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Like most folks, I love my Sony MDR-V6&apos;s. The old ear cushions were disintegrating and I tried these - WOW! They fit great, were easy to install and sound better than the originals. They seem to have a tighter cell foam that keeps out more background noise and better captures the headphone sound. A bit more bass, etc. Very nice. Excellent upgrade.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>C-Money</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Earcushions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>To be honest, I didn&apos;t pair these ear cushions with any Beyerdynamic or Sony product. I actually used them with my Ultrasone Hifi 780. The fake leather pads wore down after about two years, so I did my research and found these. The benefits are: 1. The comfort is fantastic, gone is the plasticity feel, the sweating, and pain from the old leather stock pads. 2. The bass will be deeper, more of it, and it will have more punch. 3. Mids will be better defined and easier to place the instruments. 4. Highs will loose some harshness and yet be clearer and with more detail I own three pairs of Ultrasone&apos;s and the sound quality I got from these pads was definitely a major step up from the stock pads. A MUST HAVE FOR ULTRASONE HIFI SERIES</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Soren</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound, amazing value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I used these to replace the flaking ear pads on my 6-year-old Sony MDR-V6 headphones. Installation was a little tricky but didn&apos;t end up taking that long. They&apos;re a bit firmer than the Sony ones, feel a lot nicer on my head, and provide a lot of isolation. Bass is a lot deeper and treble is smoother. A really great upgrade for the money, I would tell anyone to do this right away with their Sony headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>AudioGuy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use is for general music review and audio editing. They are a light comfortable pair of headphones that have great quality surround sound with a good price. Have a slight high buff up compared to other headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Head Phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Probably the most common choice for location sound guys working with film crews. Flat frequency response, non-hyped sound and durable construction. Just be careful with the coiled cable, when it gets overly stretched, it loses it&apos;s ability to coil up with time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great accessory for Sony Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased the Beyer ear cushions to replace the cushions on my new Sony MDR7506 headphones since they are reported to be an improvement over the originals. They fit well on the product and fit well on my head. They are comfortable and the sound isn&apos;t affected. They are certainly designed to long outlast the Sonys. Fabric has much better wear properties than micro thin vinyl film. The only negative quality is their ability to attract lint:-) I&apos;m very happy and the installation was painless. Just take it slow and don&apos;t use sharp objects to pry them on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jazz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent as expected</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I believe that every recording studio I have ever worked in in 25+ years of my career has at least a couple pairs of these. There is good reason for that. They are very neutral sounding with very little emphasis anywhere in the frequency range. Maybe just a wee bit bass heavy but that is common with any closed-back set of headphones. My only gripe is they are a bit fragile.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Matt the Sound Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Replacement for the 7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Finally decided to replace my worn out, stock 7506 headphone cups. As I mainly do production sound I wanted a more durable replacement, that also was less hot and sticky on warm shoots. So far these have fit that need perfectly. They don&apos;t seem to alter the sound to a large degree, although some comment on more bass etc. My only qualm is that the velour material isn&apos;t very soft, and tends to produce a crinkling noise when moved. I&apos;ve heard that the material softens up with time, and during recording the crinkling isn&apos;t a noticeable.... The quality is outstanding though!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Toto</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Industry standard</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These are THE headphones to get for good reason. Used by professionals and amateurs who appreciate good sound. I am a nature sound recorder and these are comfortable, compact, easy to carry, and have a manageable cord. I&apos;m using with a Sound Devices 722 and an Olympus LS10.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Matt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I&apos;ll never buy another headphone now that I have these</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 27, 2007</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought a pair of MDR-V6 headphones on Amazon andliked them for the first hour of wearing them. After that,the stock cushions were so thin that they pinched the edgesof my ears which became really hard to bear and I had tooften take them off. Then, I found these cushions, andeverything changed.Not only are the cushions thicker, so your ears aren&apos;tpressed against the metal coverings on the speakers insidethe &apos;phone, but your ears never feel sticky like they didbefore with the stock cheap leather-feeling cushions. I canwear these things for hours and my ears are prettysensitive; I can&apos;t wear on-ear headphones because they startto hurt after more than a half hour. I&apos;d say my ears are alittle bigger than average, too.If you&apos;re listening to music from a computer, MP3player/iPod, or any oth ... er low- to mid-power source, theseare the headphones for you. The bass with the cushions wasa little bit light for me, but it is with every headphone Ilisten to. In my sound card mixer on my PC (Sound BlasterAudigy2) I turned up the bass and upped the treble a littlebit too, and now they sound absolutely perfect. I ownseveral pairs of headphones, and I always, always come backto these every time now that I have these cushions. Theyare a MUST-HAVE if you own MDR-V6 cans, period. Expertise: Just your typical audiophile Problems Encountered: When you get these ear cushions, they are -only- thecushions. There is no fabric between the cushions,where your ears sit, to cover up the speakers on the insideof the headphones. Instead of leaving the speakers exposed,I simply cut two oval shapes out of some black fabric I hadlaying around and put it between the headphone and the earcushions. Took me ten minutes to do, and now everything&apos;sperfect. I suppose you could leave them the way they arenow, but I liked the all-black look.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Iron Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, great price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones for video production/editing and sound recording. Nice clear neutal sound reproduction and the ear pieces do a great job of blocking out noice. In addition, I have found them very comfortable to wear during long editing sessions. The fact that they fold in half makes it convenient when travelling or packing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mkramer40</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What goes in, comes out..... that&apos;s good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Used most often with an Ipod, there is plenty of volume. I think the bass response is just right for this use but if the recording is poor, do not expect these phones to save the day. Just know that owning and useing these will be like a relationship with your best friend because the truth will always be told. I can live with that. Flat out truth in sound reproduction.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>guitar man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones while playing my guitar and in recording music. They are superb professional quality headphones that are quite insulated,keeping out most all sounds. The sound through them is incredibly clear and crisp, and they are so comfortable that I have worn them for hours wihout any discomfort. I sometimes even forget I have them on.[...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Mount</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again and again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones are durable and produce great quality sound. And the price is very reasonable. These are the only headphones we buy for both our sound boards and all of our Aviom monitors.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Local Motion on WIOXradio[@] 91.3 FM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Puts you in the music.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these in a radio station broadcast three times a week. The sound is amazing. The price can&apos;t be beat. They are a little heavy but I got use to them quick. [...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sash</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best headphones for the price!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve tried many headphones, but quality of these headphones are superior to many. Structurally very durable and have a very comfortable fit on the head, long cord and flexibility in transport.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>C-Swa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Have bought unit before Good Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The MDR-7506 headphones have a great sound. I understand from the specs that the bass response rolls off, but only for really low frequencies (Lower than bass guitar, think pipe organ). This unit has a fairly flat response which I need for mixing my own music. I appreciate the long coiled cord so that I can walk around &amp; continue hearing. I also use this for general Music listening. The fact that this headphone collapses is a plus for travel and the previous headphone set held up for about 3 years so far. I am not brutal with headphones, but 3 years is pretty good in my opinion. The ear cushion pads wear out, but can be replaced by ordering directly from Sony. The downside of this unit is that it is a tad uncomfortable for prolonged use. I have learned to live with that. I pur ... chased a new unit because I seemed to me that the previous headset had developed a slight buzz on one earphone, but now I am thinking that something else in the audio signal chain is responsible for the distortion.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big Al</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Truly a great buy...would buy again!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>There is not too much I can fault with these wonderful headphones. I was looking for comfort and neutral sound quality. ie. flat response curve, I find some headphones have too much bass or it is extremely bright. I ran some white noise thru it for a good 100 hours, and it made a improvement on the sound quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ryo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product, poor quality control</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Great sound, not too tinny or to bassy, more neutral than my Bose set. 1/4 jack was faulty right out of the box. Easy to replace but annoying for a supposed high quality set of headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JonBrennanMusic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>7 years and running, love them</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I work in a variety of areas, classical music recording, film composer and sound design for video. These headphones continue to amaze me after 7 years of using them on an almost daily basis.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Guillaume</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones period</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphone, all day long at work, while i&apos;m on the bus and listing to music at home. They are comfortable, they sound perfectly good. For that price they are a steel. They produce crystal clear sound that is very balanced. I will recommand those to anyone who wants to buy headphones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these headphones at the recommendation of a friend and I&apos;m really happy to have followed his advise. They provide really good acoustics for the money you pay. I also own a pair of Sennheiser HD595 which cost more than three times but the sound is not that much better. I have not seen any major flaws with the Sony headphones yet, but I have only used them for a few days. Overall, they are very good value for the money you pay.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Luke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Top of the line headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Beautiful product. Incredible sound quality, people clamor to listen to them. Very lightweight, comfortable to use (even more comfortable with pearstone velour pads, $). Very mobile, as they fold up compactly. The cord can get a little annoying because of its length, and they&apos;re not the best-looking headphones, but these are very minor gripes. Altogether I recommend them immensely.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sideways George</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great set of head phones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been shooting video on-location for over 20 years and these are the standard set of headphones for the video industry while shooting on location. The bag is just a little small and I wish that I could find a safe place to put the 1/4 adapter. Today almost everything is now a mini plug. I guess I could put it in my audio bag, but I&apos;m use to having them on the headphones. I know that over time the ear muffs will start to fall apart. This set has been around awhile so that is how I know. They do sell a spare set or an upgrade, but I just wish they were sturdy from the start. So if you can afford the spare set, get them. Regardless a great set of headphones and the price is very competitive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>roguebardmedia[@]</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this while editing video and adding a little extra polish to the sound in sound booth. Compared to the PC speakers I was using before the quality of sound is leaps and bounds above. Has a little more bass than I&apos;m used to, but it&apos;s not objectionable by any means.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shinsah</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best pads for Sony MDR-V6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>All you do is take off your old Sony MDR-V6 pads and slap these bad boys on and you&apos;re set. It comes with a circular cut out overlay you put on before you put the pads on. I have found the pads that the V6 come with hurt your ears after you&apos;ve worn them for a while but these pads are great. I can wear these velour pads forever and my ears will not hurt at all. Not only does it take the hurt away, it provides awesome sound and a deeper bass. Highly recommended replacement pads for Sony V6.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marty</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony 7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this for many critical sound applications like monitoring recordings, mixing and live soun. The sound qaulity is fantastic. They are great for everything I need headphones for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Clinton Yates</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect fit</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got these after finally giving up on finding them pre-attached to the Sony MDR7506 themselves. The installation was in fact far easier than I thought and I&apos;m going to get another backup pair just in case. They&apos;re soft, simple to attach and good looking. No brainer if you&apos;re tired of the plastic deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Giloun</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No difference with MDR-V-6</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I A-B compared the MDR-7506 and MDR-V6 and I cannot find any difference between the two regarding the sound and build quality. Both are made in Thailand. The only differnece is the marking and the colour of the plug. Of course the price is different with 7506 more expensive. Both are great can for the mony but why pay more for the golden coloured plug!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Oscar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Best There is (Under [$])</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Picky with my Muzik. I&apos;ve had these for about 8 years from B&amp;H NYC store, never failed. My workhorse. I actually compared these to ([$] Grado, Sennheiser &amp; AKG). I use these on MP3s, iPods, Computers, as a monitor in recordings, just about anything related to sound. I would not settle for a mediocre headphone, so I went to B&amp;H as they have a listening station with headphones of all sorts. I listened to all, one by one. These stood WAY out for: 1-Acoustics, 2-Fidelity 3-Bass/Treble peak, 4-Definition of sounds, 5-Comfort. Simply The Best (IMHO).My thoughts: I hope Sony NEVER discontinue these, as whenever my current pair of MDR-7506 die, I hope to be able to buy (The Same MDR-7506) again. Won&apos;t buy another pair now because there is no sign of these ever failing even after about ... 8 years- That&apos;s Right!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Daniel in Zion&apos;s den</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDR-7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>While i am a music addict, this is my first investment into quality headphones. i enjoy a wide range of music with a strong focus on massage/yoga/spiritual to downtempo/IDM/ambient. i wanted these headphones because i listen to such artists as Shpongle, Bluetech, Desert Dwellers, Gaudi, Thievery, and so forth. These headphones are great for picking up the detail and movement of the music. While it took a little getting used to the size and feel on my ears, they keep getting more comfortable. They were definitely worth the investment. B&amp;H had the best price by the way ;-}</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>B Squared</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still Crazy After All These Years</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve used MDR-7506&apos;s on location for decades and owned a dozen of these when I had a studio. They used to cost only [$] a pair, but are still a great value at the current price. I love them on location because they are LOUD, bright and clean. The new ones have better tonal balance with a nice tight bass that was lacking in the older models and they are still LOUD. The only problem I have is keeping my sons away from them, so I&apos;ll be buying another two pairs for Christmas. Yeah, the construction could be better, but if you take care of these cans, they&apos;ll take care of you for decades too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>DJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones, great deal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 24, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones for DJing and they&apos;re the best I&apos;ve come across after 10 years of doing it. I started out with a pair of 7506s and they lasted me a good 7 years, so they&apos;re very robust. I then tried Technics headphones and was very disappointed. When it was finally time for me to get another pair of headphones, it was a no-brainer...7506s all the way. You will not be disappointed with these, they sound great; they have great range and clarity, and they&apos;re comfortable to wear for long periods of time. I definitely recommend these headphones!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>radioops</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sound, durability issues</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Our radio reporters love these for their robust sound. Caution: if they get extremely heavy use, as they do in a broadcast studio, the exposed wires can get stripped as they rub between plastic parts. The wires are not replaceable. A little judiciously applied electrical tape can prevent the problem. Also, the pad covers will wear out more quickly than you might expect (they are replaceable.) But all in all, great phones.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>BillyMystic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphone, as simple as that.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this headphone primarly on my bicycle for listening to music: I&apos;ve tested around 10 different headphones (AKG, Beyer, Philipps, etc.) and it&apos;s by far the best: closed (so that you don&apos;t hear car noises), very comfortable and a very-well defined sound. Perhaps it could be better with slightly more bass to compensate the (quite weak actually) wind noise. I also use it my humble home studio: especially when recording (so comfortable) and mixing. It is a good reference when you want to compare your mix from your speakers to headphone. I would definitely buy one again if needed. I actually did, the first I bought was 18 months ago and eventually had a bad contact problem at the end of the cord. This is not surprising since I use it everyday, stick the coord with my mp3 player in my pock ... et, etc. I know simply use it at home with no problem at all.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>mewcomm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>They&apos;re been around for what? 20 years?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>There&apos;s a reason Film and Video Audio professionals have used the 7506 for many years. They&apos;re flat out excellent. Closed ear isolation, good freq. response, durable, comfortable and moderate price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>HVB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Top Quality Headphones!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For the money and quality, you can&apos;t do much better than this for under $100 bucks! I used these heaphones out in the field while recording a wedding...great way to monitor my sound!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Works Great!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>[...]very comfortable and is great for a simple pair of monitor headphones. As I am not an audiophile but rather a sound engineer I prefer the best raw sound as opposed to the highest fidelity. These phones work great for giving you a raw sound without too much bass. A more accurate sound is what I work with, and these deliver.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Garrett the Visual Storyteller</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than the stock earcushions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I wish I had bought these long ago. Firmer foam means my ears don&apos;t get squished. This also means I can wear them longer. Not super easy to stretch the material around to install them. Hopefully that means they are less likely to come off.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cop Cameraman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>MDR - 7506 Small, easy and good quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These headphones have good consistent quailty and take a beating! They are easy to fold and store in small spaces for transport. I carry my own pair everywhere I go to keep my ears familiar with the same sound quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>robotuprising</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great, comfortable Earpads</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these earpads to replace the low quality cushions on the Monoprice 8323 headphones. They are super comfortable, and they make the headphones able to to be worn all day without fatigue on the ears. I&apos;d reccomend these to anyone with compatable headphones who are looking for a much better listening experience.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>marcifer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great headphones for a good price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I shopped for the MDR-7506 at the recommendation of a friend who uses them for studio work. I now know why, because they are unbeatable for an accurate reproduction of the sound without adding any strange effects. I like them much better than my Bose Tri-Port On-Ear headphones. Based on another reviewer&apos;s recommendation, I did play them for about 200 hours at different volumes and a wide variety of music to burn them in. Some say that&apos;s not necessary or is mythical, but I am certain that it really loosened up the low-end bass--amazingly. Maybe I over-did it, but I&apos;m very happy and think I&apos;ll get another pair and leave them as-is. These are used in many studios and will be a great addition to your collection. Check it out, Jodi Foster uses them as a radio host in the movie, The Brave One. ... They are comfortable, reliable, and it doesn&apos;t take a lot of power to drive them. marcifer
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Elray</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Workhorses</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I work in the film business and took a survey from sound mixers/recordists and they all suggested these as the workhorse of the industry. I purchased them and I am very happy with what I hear. It turns out my wife who is a singer and radio host also prefers them to my other headphones and I can never find them. I am happily buying another pair fortunately they are affordable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stefan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best value, hands down</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I just came out of a sound mixing studio session. The engineers had them as well. That has to say something. For the cost / sound and comfort, I&apos;ve yet to come across a better pair of headphone. Only downside is the pads might come apart 2 years in. But that&apos;s 100 of hours later...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Digeeedad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Terrific headphones... great buy!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2009</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had my set of the Sony 7506&apos;s for about a month now, Definitely happy with the sound, from highs to low end. I use them for editing music videos, watching movies and hooked to my IPod. All applications work great! Movie soundtracks seem to have an almost surround quality to them using these headphones.... definately NOT just left right and center sounding! I have a rather large head and ears and I found that these phones were hurting the edges of my ears a LOT! I adjusted/bent the very malleable headband and that helped a lot. I also ordered and installed the Beyerdynamic Padded Earcushions for DT250/DT280 offered here. Would HIGHLY recommend switching out the ear pads. WAY more comfortable and seemingly a bit tighter bass!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alison NYC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Earcushions to Prevent Exhaustion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought these to up-grade from the set that comes standard, which are just ok. These make it so that I can mix sound for hours without my ears aching and are totally worth the extra 20 bucks I paid</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Soundmama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Old Sony&apos;s</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 23, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve listened to music, voice-overs, film clips and yes, absolutely nothing with these headphones for 6 years now. They are nothing short of pure transparent sound - all I need in a headphone. I&apos;m a picky listener, too. There have been times when the music runs out and I just keep wearing the headphones. They are very comfortable and block out a lot of office noise without being fancy noise-reducing headphones. My only gripe is that they smash my hair like any fitted phone would, so half the time I wear them around the back of my head resting on my neck, which works fine. I love them and would buy them again in a heartbeat for much more money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ottosamm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Purchase ..Right PRICE!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Hi everyone, I&apos;m starting to build my home studio..so I need it to buy a Good headphone so I choose the Sony mdr-7506.. I don&apos;t regret it at all ..sound great .. for instruments,vocals.. The only things that I wish they came with a case or something not only the leather bag... but anyway its great.. I also saw other mdr-7506 on other websites but many of them are Chinese fake...with very low prices so ..watch out! I rather buy on a place where they guaranty the product... Well bottom line I recommend the Sony MDR-7506 to any musician on the way to glory!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>155</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Schzam Sam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cord Problems</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i use these headphones to listen to my i-pod and do music assignments on Smart Music(music program). the sound is amazing, and the headphones muffle noise but don&apos;t completely block it out. making it useful for anyone who needs your attention. the fact that these headphones can also fold into a small bag is great for storage, and for finding them easily. the only small problem is the length of the cord, whenever i&apos;m listening to my i-pod i have to stuff the cord in a pocket otherwise i can trip on it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>156</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Travis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 2, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These legendary headphones are a great but for anyone in the audio industry. The only problem I have seen is the ring on the mini plug tends to disconnect, leaving you with signal only in the left phone. Easily repairable with a new mini plug. Also, the wires in the cord are notorious for breaking. Once again, due to the great user-serviceable design, just swap it out. Overall great design, beats the hell out of the competition.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>157</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alan Tay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Sound Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is my first pro monitor headphone that I use for my video works. I will never go back to using consumer grade hifi headphone for sound monitoring when shooting video! Awesome sound quality. It is very comfortable on the ears for extended use. Audio is an important part of video work. MDR 7506 has quality sound performance without break your bank account for any videographer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>158</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doctor Quarky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Too Small</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Bought these to replace MDR-7509 headphones. The MDR-7509s seem to have an earpiece diaphram coating which changes rigidity with use. Takes about 30 minutes daily operation to loosen them up to acceptable distortion for use. The MDR-7506s do not have this problem. Much better audio with the MDR-7506s. However, the MDR-7506s ear pads rest on the outer edges of my ears and are uncomfortable. They are too small for my ears. The MDR-7509 ear pads are larger and fit around my ears. I had expected the MDR-7506 ear pads to be as large as the MDR-7509s. So I have another item for my junk box. The MDR-7506s would be fine for a person with small ears.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>159</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tension Studios</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great replacement for my Sony MDR-7506</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Just as all the other reviews have said, these are great replacements/upgrades for your cans. Smooth and reduces sweaty-ear syndrom. A little patience is recommended for putting them on, but fit fine once they&apos;re on.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>160</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Grobe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Huge improvement in comfort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My MDR-7506 are over ten years old, and now made new again with these cushions. They look and feel way better, thanks to the velour cushions. The material that actually touches your skin is way nicer than that awful plastic. The best part, however, is the shape and material of the padding. It is a little more firm than the cheap yellow foam that Sony provides. They are also a bit deeper and maybe slightly beleveld to provide a larger diameter where it touches your head. With the old pads, the phones were always partially ON my ear, and hurt after longer listening periods. These pads fit fully AROUND my ear, and the overall experience with these headphones is twice as good. So if I had to get a new pair of Sony phones, I would replace the pads immediately. Hint: use a butter knife ... to install the lip of the cover onto the earpiece. Took 3 minutes.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>161</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>LOUK.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use these headphones running sound during live productions. They work great!!! I also use them during my down time to listen to my mp3 WOW what a great sound, heard things didn&apos;t know were there... Great frequency response...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>162</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>The TV</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great product for a great price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the headphones for my computer at work, as well my computer at home. I needed something with great sound that was light weight. I would wear headphones for hours and be uncomfortable at many points in the day, now with my MDR i really don&apos;t have that issue, especially with the deluxe pads.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>163</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Happy Camper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My MDR-V6 headphones are alive again!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 18, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These Padded Ear cushions brought life back into my MDR-V6. Owned MDR-V6 headphones for over 20 years. The original pads had deteriorated, thereby reducing sound quality. Excellent fit for MDR-V6 headphones! Now I hear deeper bass and crisper mid range and treble. Highly Recommended! Thanks to those who suggested these fantastic replacements.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>164</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>el Negro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>These are amazing earphones, so good that I swear my audio track quality has improved just because of the clarity of the sound while I&apos;m shooting. I now see why they have become legendary. I do have one gripe; the cord is WAY too long for my liking. It must be 12&apos; when uncoiled. As I&apos;m monitoring off the video camera, 2 feet would be ample. I wish the cord could be interchanged easily.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>165</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>the russellator</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Back for more, my 3rd pair!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Durable; Compact; Clear Sound

This is my 3rd pair of these headphones. My first pair lasted 15 years, the second was permanently borrowed by my children &amp; so I have my own for use in the studio for my radio show. In this business we have plenty of great options but hands down these Sony headphones produce a clean and clear sound.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>166</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>JimBob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great replacement</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2008</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Went through two sets of ear cushions for my Sony MDR V6. Coating kept on deteriorating. These replacements fit right on. Although sometimes not shown in product pictures, they come with separate center inserts to span the open space in the ear cushions. They seal out outside sound and are very comfortable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>167</ID>
     <Item>Sony MDR 7506 - headphones - Ear-cup, Binaural</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4374892795300801355/reviews?q=headphones&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=667&amp;bih=625&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=VaKRUO_LBqbU2AX_lICoDA.1351721563172.29&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_KORUOWcCYqM2gWGyoDADA&amp;ved=0CKABEPQCMAI4FA</URL>
     <Reviewer>Eagleman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Headphones I ever owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: I love the sound these headphones produce. I&apos;m a musician and I&apos;ve used quality headphones all my life. I usually spend $150-$225 for new headphones every 5 years or so. At almost half the cost, imagine my surprise when I discovered these HP&apos;s have a much broader range of sounds than my old Sony HPhones. Great Headphones at a very reasonable price.Comes with a nice long coiled cord, as always with Sony.Cons: The ear cup is a little smaller than my previous 4 or 5 Sony Headphones. These are comfortable, but they do not &apos;enclose&apos; my ears, instead, they kind of sit &apos;on&apos; my ears.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

