<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon PowerShot SD1300 IS Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent image quality, solid build quality, clear, vibrant LCD screen

Cons: No optical viewfinder, lacks HD video

The Canon PowerShot SD1300 IS is a great ultra-compact camera, according to reviewers. In one test, it beats under-$180 competitors from seven different brands. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TygrTat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent buy...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: many features, auto exposure, presets, battery life (Li-ion), easy to use on &quot;auto&quot;

Cons: A little difficult to find certain settings when you want to change them manually, and video not the best

While it&apos;s no SLR -- it&apos;s packs quite a punch regardless.

I bought this to replace my Canon PowerShot A590IS because I was going through AA batteries like crazy. I decided to stay with Canon because of all the features that they include in these little guys -- you have almost complete control over your shoot. From exposure settings to white balance settings (tungsten, cloudy, fluorescent, et...), even custom lighting/white-balancing that you can set to whatever you like. There are also preset settings like &quot;portrait&quot; which will blur the background so the subject is the m ... ain focus, &quot;night&quot;, &quot;indoor&quot;, &quot;kids/pets&quot;, And THEN there&apos;s &quot;low-lighting&quot; &quot;snow&quot;, &quot;beach&quot; &quot;foilage&quot; etc... they&apos;re all included on this camera too.

The &quot;auto&quot; setting is amazing by itself, but if you want more control there is a &quot;manual&quot; setting. However, you do have to do a little exploring to find certain features (hence the 4 instead of 5 for &quot;ease of use&quot;). The book that comes with it is extremely lacking. No manual, just a &quot;getting started&quot; guide. Should be included, but they at least offer a PDF (full-manual guide) that you can view and/or download from Canon&apos;s website.

Picture quality....amazing! Auto Exposure does an amazing job of compensating for those bad lighting situations.

Battery life -- AWESOME! I used to have to bring two or three diff. sets of batteries for only a couple of hours of shooting (photos alone) with my older PowerShot. With the rechargeable battery Li-ion, I can go on several shootings (different days) without ever getting &quot;low&quot; warning-- and that&apos;s mixing it up using both photos and video.

Video -- not so hot (not terrible either), but this is a digital camera, not a digital movie camera. The largest size is only 640 x 480 px and you need really good lighting. But with video editing software it&apos;s really easy to fix the lighting. Zoom quality is horrendous, but if you&apos;re looking to take great quality home videos then you should buy a video camera. lol

Completely a ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>garyb2008</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A promising new Powershot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 4X optical zoom in a small size. Great pictures. Good shot-to-shot recycle times.

Cons: No optical view finder. Care needed in focusing under low light conditions. Battery life?

I bought the SD1300IS the day after it was put on display at my local Best Buy store. My aim was to replace an older but still faithful Canon A-540 (10,000+ shots) with something smaller and with Canon&apos;s updated lighting, program and sensor features. So far, after over 200 pictures and video clips, I have not been disappointed.

I spent time up-front going through the operator&apos;s manual page by page (camera in hand) learning how to utilize the SD1300&apos;s features and controls. It has paid off due to the differences between the my old A and the SD ELPH series cameras.

I have noticed the ... SD1300 recycles faster between shots, especially with the flash on. I do miss the mode dial on top of the A-540.

The SD1300 seems to not focus well in some lower light conditions unless you &quot;prefocus&quot; first by depressing the shutter button half way.

Battery life seems shorter than the A540 (had rechargeable AA&apos;s) but not all bad with a &quot;useful&quot; battery monitor display. A spare Canon battery is much more expensive than rechargeable AA&apos;s.

The Low Light setting appears to have promising capabilities during poor lighting conditions but I am still experimenting with the results under varying situations.

I have owned several Canon &quot;point and shoot&quot; cameras over the years and this one promises to be a good one also. I can only hope it is as reliable and rugged as my A-540 has been.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pamalamb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good pocket camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Body Color; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Easy To Use; Great Zoom; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact

Have not used it a lot since bought it. Some party pictures. Like it so far. Good price [...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gret Little Every Day Shooter</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I started out shooting 35mm film 10 years ago. About 5 years ago I switched to 1.6 crop digital. Very recently I bought a SD1300. My wife calls it my toy camera., I wanted a more convenient camera. The day after I received the SD1300 I put it through it&apos;s paces. I took back lit, wife in front of window night snapshot, ie fill flash worked fine. We went to the park I took a shot with the setting sun behind her using ???2 exposure compensation brought out the shadow details in PS using curves. Would have preferred fill light with RAW editor but curves was almost as good. Took a macro shot of a flower in the park. Took landscapes with tree line in middle ground and building in background, worked fine. Shut-off flash, set ISO to 400 and took low light shots. I was able to take fairly sharp sh ... ots at 1/8 sec. With the exception of bracketing, saving RAW and a meaningful DOF pretty much came close to my other cameras. After all it&apos;s about the size a pack of cigarettes and weighs less than 5 ozs. The major paradigm shift is the DOF. Pretty much everything is in focus. Background blur is not possible. After I did some quick calculations I figured out why. Large format uses f64 for a lot of DOF, medium format 32, 35mm 16, 1.6 crop 11. Since, the size of this camera is so small 5-20mm equals 28-112 35mm. Holy cow batman, that&apos;s a a multiplier of 5.6.. So on this camera f2.8 is roughly the same as f16 on 35mm and f5.9 is f32. So, the camera always shoots wide open, as it should. I spent my life in aperture priority on my other cameras. But here it&apos;s always wide open. So, that&apos;s not part of the equation anymore. My one complaint is the algorithm that it uses to set exposure. It changes ISO as much or more than shutter speed. I find that annoying. So, I suggest that you set the thing in the middle setting, P or camera mode as it&apos;s called. Pick you&apos;re ISO and White Balance and let the camera decide the shutter speed. I&apos;d also suggest that you turn on iConstrast and set folder names to daily. Start with ISO at 80 for bright lights and work you way up as the light diminishes and shutter speeds get down to around 1/8. I also set focus on the middle with small rectangle. As I&apos;ve said with the widest aperture at f16 pretty much everything is going to focus, so don&apos;t get to carried away with focus. With the AIAF one of the main, if not the primary purpose, of this camera is party snaps (birthdays, anniversaries, graduations, holidays, dates, special events etc..) and vacation snaps. For these it works perfectly. Would you get better images with a DSLR with several lens? Of course you would. How much better? In most cases not a whole lot. Is it worth one the cost and the effort lugging all that equipment around? Only you can decide that. For me when I&apos;m spending several grand to go on vacation, let&apos;s say in Europe, I&apos;m taking my full DSLR kit. When I&apos;m going to my niece&apos;s birthday or to a New Years Eve party or a walk around town the DSLR stay&apos;s home and I&apos;m taking the SD1300.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Campjeep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>IT IS CLASSY AND IT TAKES GREAT PICTURES</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am going to try to share what I have discovered about this camera. These are just my thoughts. Some things I am compairing to a canon SD1200 and the SD940. The flat button arangement is the same as the SD1200 all but the power button on top is larger and easier to turn off and on,I like that but be carefull it does not come on in your pocket. I have not had any trouble using any of the buttons even with my big old hands. I like that the mic for the video is in the frount of the camera instead of being on the top like the canon SD940,it picks up less noise being in the frount. I like the func menu(where you set iso, white ballance, my colors) better than the SD940 because it lets you set things with one less step like the SD1200 and it has a better color skeem(the color of the menus) than ... the canon 1200, that just me though. I can not tell any differnce in shot to shot or flash shot to shot times between the SD1300 and the SD1200 which is 1 and 1/2secs to 2secs with out flash and 3 to 4secs with flash on(up to 6secs for full flash recharge). Shutter lag is good for a canon point and shoot but if you prefocas that will help even more. I never tested the continuous shooting( but see my battery test) but canon says it is 0.9 per sec where the sd 1200 is 1.4 shots per sec, if that is important to you. I did test the battery by using continuous shooting with the flash on and got well over 400 pictures and still had 3 bars left on the battery icon and it was taking 1 picture every 2 seconds or less if that helps you out on the continuous shooting part and when I turned the flash off it seemed to be very fast. I am getting about the same image quality as the SD 1200 which is very good for this size point and shoot camera and getting a 2.7inch very clear LCD screen and a 28mm x 112mm lens a little better (than the 35 x 105 on the SD1200). This is just me but I would stay away from the auto mode indoors(it works good outdoors in bright light though), it seems to want to use a very high iso which makes your picture look grainy or snowing looking, it would be ok for 4x6x prints?. I use program mode and set the iso to 100 or 200 iso (if possable).For some reason canon has done this wih all thier newer point and shoot cameras the last year or two, I know (it is a bummer)... With the SD1200 and SD940 I would use program mode and auto iso but when trying to do that with the SD1300 it wants to go to 500iso some times where the 1200 and 940 would go to 250iso ,go figure? A lot of the review sites blow thier pictures way up and look for defects,your likely to only make 5x7 or 8x10s and not see (what they see). If you are going to make larger prints you could go to a canon S90 or the bigger G11, but much more money I know!&gt;Just keep the iso down and you will do good...) Just a thought I wish they would of stayed at 10 megapixles because of the small sensor... The SD1300 has a touch more style, larger LCD and a little more virsatle lens, but the 1200 is also a very good camera. Try (neutral) in (my colors menu) and see what you think with your indoor shots of the kids if your not happy with the default color? I posted some pictures on this site for the SD1300, theirs just not much color her yet but they will give you some idea untill some one can post some good pictures. I mostly take pictures of bear in the smokey mountians (CADES COVE) and love chaseing the grand kids around taking their pictures
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>audioj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent pocket camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features, price, battery life.

Cons: Can&apos;t think of anything.

I have a full-featured DSLR camera, but for small parties or get-togethers with friends it&apos;s too cumbersome. This camera is a great alternative and offers excellent features in a small package and for a decent price. For casual photography I have enjoyed this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mark</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love This Little Point &amp; Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Large Clear LCD; Nice Body Color; Easy To Use; Good Image Quality

Cons: Slippery in the hand

Love this little camera. Great looks, great performance, cheap price. Plenty of megapixels and a great LCD for so little money. Takes great pics, especially with the flash--doesn&apos;t blow out your subjects. I&apos;m using primarily as a point-and-shoot party camera and it&apos;s perfect for that. Only con is the ergonomics in your hand. Nothing to really grip it with and so it&apos;s a little slippery. I&apos;d recommend getting one of those straps where you can pull the bead down to make it tight around your wrist. My last little Canon came with that kind of strap, but sadly, this one doesn&apos;t, and needs it. Otherwise, bravo Canon!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pradeep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have to say the feature performs as expected. Obviously it&apos;s not going to do much if there is a lot of camera shake, but it does the job for what it&apos;s intended to do. Picture quality is excellent. It does well in Low light as well. Manual settings do just as well as auto settings. I like the playback button that lets you review pics rather than having to switch the camera into another mode. When taking multiple shots the lag time between pics is minimal. Videos work well with it but there is that pesky no in and out zoom during a video. Sound quality was surprisingly good with video mode as well. It takes outdoor video well with little wind noise. I was a bit cautious about buying a camera with no viewfinder as my last camera had one, but let&apos;s face it, I hardly used it when I had it. In ... sisting on a camera with a viewfinder also significantly limited my choices for point and shoots. I&apos;m satisfied with no viewfinder and this camera is exactly what I expect in a good point and shoot. Battery life is great! Even under moderate to heavy use it lasted all night and part of the next day.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>watergirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>can&apos;t beat this compact for price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact; Easy To Use

Cons: Some yellow indoors; Colors may wash out

This camera is incredibly light and stylish. It is one of the few left with wide angle in this price range. It can take incredible pictures and is great for travel, especially outdoor shots. Downside: you really need to frame your shots and play with the settings in order to get truly great pics, but that is true with any camera. It is easy to use for beginners who just want to point and shoot, but watch indoor and low light shots. Bad shots will show on the lcd and the camera won&apos;t settle when you half press the shutter if it can&apos;t reach a good speed in that light. Overall and amazing camera for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>2doodle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>cannon power shot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is easy to use, has a nice view screen and the rechargable battery feature is very nice. The Auto feature tends to take darker indoor photos than when left on regular camera feature. The slim size makes it easy to carry around. The photo&apos;s were very clear and colors were true. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>alpinehammer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Powershot SD1300 IS 12MP Digital ELPH</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Image Quality; Large Clear LCD; Small / Compact; Easy To Use

Cons: Lag / Shutter Delay

a great camera all around. My fat fingers just barely work on it. the functions are intuitive. a spare battery in the package deal would be a plus. good Canon quality; my 3rd.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dean</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pocket camera... does a great job</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I use this camera to capture some quick pictures on the go. Its very light, and usually you can&apos;t even feel it in your pocket. Its a little different from its earlier SD versions which had a viewfinder, this one doesn&apos;t. Also, This has 3 modes, autofocus, video and other programs. So if you switch on your camera only to review pictures, the lens would still come out and you have to wait for it to retract after a minute.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great base camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price! Great Pictures!

Cons: Auto-focus not always the best in low light

Easy to use with good picture quality. Focus is not always consistent but when it&apos;s on, its excellent. Excellent battery life and the provided software is good quality and useful.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little Camera for your pocket</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Good Image Stabilization; Short Lag Time; Nice Body Color

This is the best little camera I have owned. Light weight compact and love the color. Takes great pictures for all settings.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Happy Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Body Color; Short Lag Time; Good in Low Light; Great Zoom; Good Image Stabilization

Bought this for my 11 yr old. She loves it! It&apos;s small enough to carry in a pocket, but takes great pics. Just point and shoot. She&apos;s enjoying taking video with it also.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rubeezy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty legit camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color; Great Zoom; Good Image Stabilization

Cons: Lag shutter delay; Poor Flash

This camera is really easy to use. Typical canon features. Nice and compact. The battery life is pretty excellent, especially if you don&apos;t playback your pictures a lot. I&apos;m satisfied with it because I&apos;m mostly taking family pictures and the quality is awesome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Peace</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Super camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization; Nice Body Color; Great Zoom

This camera is great- many features, zoom and wide angle worked well. I took most of my pics using the kids/animal settings since the lag time was shorter. Lower light images came out so-so but I am not that great of a photographer so I may have been pushing the limits of phorotgraphy in some pics (night time of the moon). Friends who purchased products at local stores were impressed with all the features this camera came with for the amount of money that the camera cost. [...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Caribbean Cruiser</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon SD1300 camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization

We just came back from a 7 day cruise where we used this camera extensivly. It work perfect every time. I&apos;m not camera expert but we took over 400 pictures and a few videos and have no major issues. As with any compact camera, the size can feel alittle small in your hands but it wansn&apos;t major for us. Battery life was great. I noce package.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Campjeep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is classy and it takes great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very good image quality; Good Image Stabilization

Cons: NO CAMERA IS PERFECT

These are just (my thoughts) I hope they might help a little. (Some things) I am compairing to a canon SD1200 and the SD940. The flat button arangement is the same as the SD1200 all but the power button on top is larger and easier to turn off and on, I like that but be carefull it does not come on in your pocket. I have not had any trouble using any of the buttons even with my big old hands. The SD1300 is very easy to use. Some will miss the viewfinder that the SD1200 had and some will miss the HD 720p in the movie mode that the SD940 has, The SD1300 has 640x480 at 30fps like the canon SD1200 G11 and S90. I like that the mic for the video is in the frount of the camera instead of being on the t ... op (where I put my finger) like the canon SD940 SD970 and others, it picks up less finger movement noise being in the frount. I can not tell any difference in shot to shot or flash shot to shot times between the SD1300 and the SD1200 which is 2secs with out the flash, and 3 to 4secs with the flash on, (( up to 6secs for full flash recharge )). Shutter lag is good for a canon point and shoot but if you prefocas that will help even more. I never tested the continuous shooting( but see my battery test) but canon says it is 0.9 per sec where the sd 1200 is 1.4 shots per sec, if that is important to you. I did test the battery (NB-6L same battery as SD1200) by using continuous shooting with the flash on and got well over 400 pictures and it was taking ( 1 picture every 2 seconds or less in the continuous mode if that helps you out on the continuous shooting part) and when I turned the flash off it seemed to be very fast. In real life your get around 300 to 350 pictures with some of them using the flash, your still need a second battery for a backup. I am getting about the same image quality as the SD 1200 which is very good for this size point and shoot camera and getting a 2.7inch very clear LCD screen and a 28mm x 112mm lens a little better (than the 35 x 105 on the SD1200). This is just me, I am no expert but I like using the program mode best and try not to use the auto mode indoors ((auto works good outdoors in good light tho) auto seems to want to use a very high iso indoors which makes your pictures look grainy or snowy looking on larger prints, it would be ok for a 4x6 or 5x7 print?. I use program mode and set the iso to 100 or 200 iso (if possable indoors), (I like 80 or 100iso for the best image quality if you have anough good light indoors or outdoors ). For some reason canon has done this with all there newer point and shoot cameras the last year or two, (I know it is a bummer) and again this is just me), You might be happy with the pictures you take in auto mode... With the SD1200 and SD940 I would use program mode and auto iso but when trying to do that with the SD1300 it wants to go to 500iso some times where the 1200 and 940 would go to 250iso ,go figure? A lot of the review sites blow there pictures way up and look for defects, your likely to only make 5x7 or 8x10s and not see (what they see). If you are going to make larger prints or need a better low light camera and still stay in a point and shoot you could go with a canon S90 or the bigger G11,but (much more money I know)! Just keep the iso down and you will do good...) Just a thought I wish they would of stayed at 10 megapixles because of the small sensor. The SD1300 seems to have a nice sharp lens but highlights sometimes tend to blow out in very bright sun as with all small cameras this size, you can see this in some of the pictures I posted on this sight for the 1300. But to be fair my G11 does this also. No problem with red eye in pictures useing the SD1300. The menu screens are easy to read... The SD1300 has a touch more style, larger LCD and a little more virsatle lens than the SD1200, but the 1200 is also a very good camera. The SD1300 does have a weak battery door cover like the SD1200. Small enough to carry every place you go for those spontaneous grandkid pictures...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shutterbug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good value</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I am an advanced amateur who also just bought a Canon EOS T3i SLR. I bought one of these (silver) for myself as pocket camera to use when I didn&apos;t want to schlep my SLR..like to dinners or other events where the SLR would be too bulky. I also steered my girlfriend to get one to replace her old broken camera and, so far, she is happy with it. The reviews were very good on [@] and I am generally happy with the camera and the pics. It is small, light and the screen is big. I wish it had a viewfinder for sunny days when it is hard to see the screen. The 28mm equivalent wide angle is good for squeezing people into those inevitable group shots. Like in all point and shoot cameras, I don&apos;t like the lag between pictures or the shutter lag. (That&apos;s one reason I have an SLR too). My only complaint i ... s that it may not focus on the subject you want and there is no manual focus.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tytyrox</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality and image stabilization.

Cons: Not as many features as you would like.

This thing is the most powerful little sucker I&apos;ve ever owned. Picture quality is the best I&apos;ve ever used out of a point and shoot (I&apos;ve used about 15 other cameras). I&apos;m on a yearbook staff so I have had the oppertunity to use many cameras. Granted this camera doesn&apos;t take slr quality pictures, but it&apos;s the best you will get from a point and shoot.

There aren&apos;t as many features on this camera as i would have liked. There is no HD video which almost made me chose another camera. There arent that many scene modes either, I think there are 5. Also there is no charging the battery in the camera, but the picture quality make up for all of that.

Side note: there is a cable th ... at allows you to see your pictures on the t.v. it is a nice addition to this amazing camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KelseyG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small size, great photo quality, long battery life, great price and value, easy to use!

Cons: Not much zoom.

I absolutely adore this camera. I&apos;m a student with very limited funds, so I can&apos;t afford a really fancy expensive camera. And you know what? I don&apos;t even need one, this camera does the trick. It is compact, fast to use, simple to figure out, and takes great quality photos.
When someone stole this camera from my coat one night, I cried--then went and bought the exact same one from Best Buy. I didn&apos;t even look at the other options. This camera is everything I need.
Someday, I would like to buy a higher-zoom camera for taking nature photos, but for now, this one does the trick.
Good work Canon--you made a great camera for a low price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a solid point &amp; shoot. Great for the pocket, although I have an older one (400 series) which is heavier but has a solid metal body which I prefer. The 1300 is slimmer, much lighter, but I haven&apos;t dropped it yet so I can&apos;t comment on its durability in that regard yet (my 400 survived numerous drops and still works well). Traded up because this was reasonably priced for double the image resolution. Still won&apos;t replace my DSLR, but for casual parties, discrete tourist photos, or just keeping in a backpack it takes great pictures. I do wish there was less lag, but you can&apos;t have everything. For the size and the price it was a great purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MEB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect camera for intended use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking for a decent point and shoot to use during the times i did not wish to carry my full body DSLR and lenses. I did not want to spend too much money on it as well. I was very surprised at the good quality of the images and how great it shot in low light without the use of a flash. Very responsive and very good battery life. Extremely pleased with the quality for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nadine35</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been searching for a good camera, that takes good pics as well as easy to use. Also, one that uses a USB plug. I had bought a canon before and I love the quality. However, it&apos;s uses AA batteries. Which was a Hugh problem, I would constantly buy batteries. I hate that. So I set out to buy a camera that I didn&apos;t have to buy batteries. This canon is the BEST, picture quality is great the colors are vibrant and clear.Also, very easy to use! I love this camera. So does all my friends! A great buy for the price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Greyhair</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Will buy another one just like it soon!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Large Clear LCD; Small / Compact; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Quality

Was a gift for my wife to take on a skiing trip. Used it for casual shots around the cabin as well as scenery shots while driving in the mountains and shots taken while actually skiing down the slope. We could not be more pleased with everything about the camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sudhakar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>my canon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Quality; Good Image Stabilization; Large Clear LCD; Easy To Use; Small / Compact

[...]i liked my camera very much. this is my 3rd one from canon and its really gr8</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big Red</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Camera for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Good Image Quality; Good Image Stabilization; Easy To Use; Fast/accurate auto-focus

Cons: Limited Zoom

Nice camera! Good deal for the money</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>frugalwifeandmom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Thorougly pleased!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s a great camera. We&apos;ve had Sonys before, but have had problems in the family with 3 different aging Sonys getting finicky. My MIL has had her Canon for 4 + yrs and no problems so we made the switch (along with other recommendations). I wanted a view finder, but this camera does not have one. It&apos;ll be fine as long as Canon is the reliable camera it&apos;s supposed to be. The LARGE LCD screen is great and can really be a good way to show off pictures too! What&apos;s also neat is that if you rotate the camera when reviewing the pictures it&apos;ll rotate the picture too... it knows it&apos;s down from up. The pictures are good quality and the video is also dramatically better than our previous camera. Be sure to get a BIG memory card though! 8GB is what we got, and I&apos;m glad we didn&apos;t get anythin ... g smaller because we&apos;re using this as a video camera too. Why carry around 2 pieces of equipment? For us Overstock was truly the best deal price wise and they had it in stock! We love our PowerShot! ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>longbeachmama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love My Canon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking for a camera that had advanced features yet with a high emphasis on being user friendly. This camera is great for both. Its slim design is a bonus. Captures crisp images, but I am still learning how to reset it for lower lighting situations. Great value for the price. I purchased the Overstock.com extended warranty that I thought was reasonably priced. When the extended warranty runs and the camera runs its course I know I can trade it in at Canon with their loyalty program. Canon cameras rock!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BestBuoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera for a novice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small, stylish, fast start-up.

Cons: Lack of scenes, can&apos;t control focus point easily, no manual control.

I&apos;ve owned this camera for a month and have taken just over 500 pics, mostly outdoor scenes, some macro indoor and out, kids indoors. So far I&apos;m disappointed with this camera.

I like:
it&apos;s size and feel, quick start-up, plus 1 face timer is pretty cool, custom timer, internal battery for keeping settings when removing the battery,

I don&apos;t like:
Canon&apos;s function menu structure (I guess I&apos;m getting used to it), no key customization, that it doesn&apos;t remember focus settings when powered off, it&apos;s difficult to focus where you want, aperture seems too narrow, even on infinity focus it has to find something to focus on causing a lag, has very few scenes ... (no sunset filter, no flowing water shot), can&apos;t force where you&apos;d like it to focus.

I guess Canon doesn&apos;t want to put these features in a sub-compact camera, they probably want you to buy an SLR for $500. Or maybe I got spoiled with these features on the two previous sub-compacts I owned (Casio Exilm&apos;s believe it or not. Loved them.)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization

Cons: Limited Zoom

It was a nice photograph. You will get the value for the money you spent. I wants to go for small and handy camera and this fits perfectly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brickyard</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Photography is my hobby. I take this camera when I travel due to it&apos;s size and weight. The photos and videos I&apos;ve taken to date have produced good to very good results. It thin, light with a large screen and is a good value for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mathematics01</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great, Easy-to-Use Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, best deal, sturdy, takes great pictures, loads quickly

Cons: doesnt stand up well, falls over, no panoramic setting, deleting unwanted pictures takes awhile

I bought this camera after seeing how nice my neighbor&apos;s was. Their camera had only 10 megapixels, so It was nice to see that I could get the 12 megapixel camera for even a cheaper price than they got theirs. (Their camera was an older version) I took this camera on vacation and it took abcolutely stunning pictures of all the scenery. It had a really nice feature that let you change the color to sepia or black and white before you took the picture, which I liked. It was also very easy to figure out how to use, I didn&apos;t read the manual at all and I already feel like a pro. However, I was disappointed tha ... t you only have two choices when it comes to deleting photos: delete them one at a time, or delete ALL of them all at once. my old camera (which was a sony cybershot W150) let you select only the images you wanted to delete, and the deleting process wasnt so time-consuming. I liked how the Sony cameras now have the Panorama setting to take panoramic pictures; sadly, this camera does not have that feature. Overall, very good, very durable piece of equipment which I hope will last a couple years.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera Very Happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization; Short Lag Time; Very happy so far

I love that it is small enough and had the belt carrying case. Can take it anywhere and it is so compact. It is so light you can have it with you where ever you go so you do not have to miss a shot</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>solcloud</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for Family photo work!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, Ease to use, Price

Cons: short bettery life

I purchased this camera for family photo. It was great Price and features.
This will be best choice if you have to choose camera.
only one bad thing is short bettery life, but it is enough for a day.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>J Martinez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this as a mother&apos;s day present for my mom, and after a short tutorial she was taking decent pictures. The shutter release delay is small compared to some other cameras in the same price range, which is very important to me. You can also shoot short video clips.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rob the Collegian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>SD 1300 Good Option, not Best</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Good camera with useful functions and easy interface - battery has good life. Takes a moment to focus, lighting difficult to gauge and is sometimes inconsistent. Overall quality is good, size is convenient, and interface is very workable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jazzgirl22</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great first camera!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sharp images and color quality. Does particularly well taking pictures in the dark! Long battery life, too!

Cons: It&apos;s starting to malfunction already

I never had a camera before. All I knew is I didn&apos;t want one that would distort colors or give me something grainy. I shopped long and hard starting off with SLR cameras knowing they had the best quality... I bought one and felt it was too pricey. I didn&apos;t get my money&apos;s worth- so I sent it back right away. I bought another- a hot pink point-and-shoot from Samsung. It was fine until one of its reviewers brought to my attention its off-colored photos. I thought I could bare it because the camera itself was such a pretty color, but after taking a few pictures, I couldn&apos;t stand it. I&apos;d bought a new shirt and put on some othe ... r whatnot for a great photo (loving the color of everything) and all of the colors came out darkened- almost sad-looking. The pictures looked cold and lifeless. I took that in a very well lit area, too. Pictures in the dark were out of the question. I sent that one back. FINALLY I came across this beauty! It was much smaller than the others. I worried about trading out my old camera for one that had .3 less pixles, but I thought to give it a try for its high satisfaction rates. It turned out to be my best first camera ever! The colors are warmer, I can take pictures in the dark (without always having to use a flash or special setting). Pictures come out a little grainy sometimes- but only sometimes! Most of the pictures I&apos;ve taken with this have come out fantastic!! I love it when my targets move, because sometimes even that&apos;ll turn out pretty cool! After all of my shopping, I learned to trust what the people say and that Canon truly is a great camera company. Keep in mind that I bought this before Canon produced it&apos;s 14 pixel series. If you can, I suggest you tried one of those, but if not, you wouldn&apos;t be sorry with this one. I&apos;m very happy with it and definately got my money&apos;s worth! :D
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Campjeep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is classy and it takes great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Takes great pictures; Good Image Stabilization; It is easy to use; Good battery life; Has good zoom range

Cons: NO CAMERA IS PERFECT

These are just my thoughts. Some things I am compairing to a canon SD1200 and the SD940. The flat button arangement is the same as the SD1200 all but the power button on top is larger and easier to turn off and on,I like that but be carefull it does not come on in your pocket. I have not had any trouble using any of the buttons even with my big old hands. ((Some will miss the viewfinder that the SD1200 had)). I like that the mic for the video is in the frount of the camera instead of being on the top (where I put my finger) like the canon SD940,it picks up less noise being in the frount. I like the func menu(where you set iso, white ballan ... ce, my colors) better than the SD940 because it lets you set things with one less step like the SD1200 and it has a better menu color skeem (the print color of the menus) than the canon 1200, thats just me tho.. I can not tell any differnce in shot to shot or flash shot to shot times between the SD1300 and the SD1200 which is (1 and 1/2secs) to (2secs) with out flash and 3 to 4secs with flash on(up to 6secs for full flash recharge). Shutter lag is good for a canon point and shoot but if you prefocas that will help even more. I never tested the continuous shooting( but see my battery test) but canon says it is 0.9 per sec where the sd 1200 is 1.4 shots per sec, if that is important to you. I did test the battery (NB-6L same as SD1200) by using continuous shooting with the flash on and got well over 400 pictures and still had 3 bars left on the battery icon and it was taking 1 picture every 2 seconds or less if that helps you out on the continuous shooting part and when I turned the flash off it seemed to be very fast. I am getting about the same image quality as the SD 1200 which is very good for this size point and shoot camera and getting a 2.7inch very clear LCD screen and a 28mm x 112mm lens a little better (than the 35 x 105 on the SD1200). This is just me but I would stay away from the auto mode indoors(it works good outdoors in good light tho), it seems to want to use a very high iso indoors in auto which makes your picture look grainy or snowy looking, it would be ok for 4x6x prints?. I use program mode and set the iso to 100 or 200 iso (if possable).For some reason canon has done this with all thier newer point and shoot cameras the last year or two, I know (((it is a bummer)))... With the SD1200 and SD940 I would use program mode and auto iso but when trying to do that with the SD1300 it wants to go to 500iso some times where the 1200 and 940 would go to 250iso ,go figure? &gt;&gt;&gt; A lot of the review sites blow thier pictures way up and look for defects, your likely to only make 5x7 or 8x10s and not see (what they see). If you are going to make larger prints or need a low light camera you could go to a canon (S90) or the bigger (G11), but much more money I know!&gt;Just keep the iso down and you will do good...) Just a thought I wish they would of stayed at 10 megapixles because of the small sensor... The SD1300 has a touch more style, larger LCD and a little more virsatle lens, but the 1200 is also a very good camera. You do not get a SD card with the camera and if your new to this digital camera stuff remember to low level format the SD card. &gt;((I carry my camera in a little phone case that has a belt clip not a loop for fast &amp; easy on and off the belt)) I definitely recommend picking up a small camera case for protection. 
I mostly take pictures of bear in the Smokey Mountians (CADES COVE) and love chaseing the grand kids around taking their pictures.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nikki</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this camera!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera in March 2011 and I get a lot of compliments on the quality of my pictures, the ease of use, and the features for this camera. I also love the fact that is has a rechargeable battery. I use it for both business and pleasure. I would definitely buy this camera again. It s cute and light weight and just perfect for me!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Baiana</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great buy for awesome shots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Very easy to use, and produces great, clear shots. Auto-focus takes the &apos;thinking&apos; out of shooting. The image quality, even in shooting concerts + video was incredibly sharp.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Deecoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Office Depot</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>After struggling to find an easy to use digital camera I went with the Powershot. I was very happy with the photos it took. They seemed to snap quickly (not quite quick enough sometimes for my kids, but better than most). However after 2 months the pieces that close to cover the lens became detached and would not always reveal the lens...which of course means no pictures.

We sent the camera back since it was still under warranty, only to find out that the warranty did not cover that part of the camera. Now I may have kids, but I keep my camera out of reach. Frustrated by the fact that it would cost as much to fix it as it would to buy a new camera, we went ahead and ordered the same camera again. It had good ratings, and we figured that the lens issue was a fluke, and after all we w ... ere happy with the actual pictures.

I got the new camera today, and the microphone does not work. Already scheduled to return it. Fool me once... I guess I had this coming. Now I&apos;m back in search of a good, affordable digital camera. I&apos;m beginning to believe this does not exist.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Haywoody</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Point and Shoot

Got my Canon to give me a smaller camera to carry in my pocket while duck hunting. Good, handy size, with excellent pics. Just point and shoot. Even did a video while Goose hunting in Maryland. Got good vid without having a big bulky camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ProudPapa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great job again BuyDig !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice Body Color; Easy To Use; Small / Compact

Cons: None

Bought this for our 12 year old daughter. Love that it[...]has its own rechargeable battery and she, of course, loves the color.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>brilin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>CanonPower shotD1300IS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great little camera with easy to use point and shoot features. Can customoze your picture taking very easily. Light weight and handy to keep in purse.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Liz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera weighs next to nothing and takes fabulous photos. Its easy to use. Even I was able to load up jpegs onto my computer and email them with ease. Its simple, yet taken off AUTO setting, this Canon can do a whole lot more for more serious photographers.It even shoots a movie or self portraits. I highly recommend this Canon. Its a winner and moron proof.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jomoin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use and takes good pictures.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use and size.

Cons: Lots of options to choose from... can be confusing.

I&apos;m very happy with this camera, so far. I&apos;ve used it over the holidays and on vacaton. It&apos;s best to take a moment to think before you click....you need to focus the picture well and set the frame. Really easy to use and fits well in my pocket or purse.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Disneyseeker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera but grainey picture</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, easy to use, long rechargeable battery life

Cons: viewing screen grainey

I love the size of the camera. The viewing screen is extremely grainey but the picture doesn&apos;t come out grainey. Some of the pictures are blurred but that could just be the user who is in error.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Michiko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large Clear LCD; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact; Good in Low Light

I&apos;m a big fan of Canon cameras. Owned a older one for years. This one has great picture quality, and great lighting in low light. Still learning how to use all the features.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photographer in Crisis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not a lucky brake</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Nice Body Color

Cons: Poor Image Quality; Shows an Error

The camera wasn&apos;t working properly when I received it. It showed constantly an Error message. Very blurry pictures. I had to return it and I am afraid to purchase the same one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>grabj</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice little addition</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Bought this for my wife who normally uses my SLR backup - Canon 40D. She wanted something small enough to carry around in her purse for snapshot type of pictures. It is taking her a it of time to get used to not looking through a viewfinder, but other than that she is pleased. I was worried about noise levels with all those pixels being squeezed into a samll point and shoot sensor but the initial photos look great. It certainly is compact and simple to use. Wold prefer a viewfinder but they are hard to find in these little cameras.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lorie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s an awesome camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome Camera; LIGHT COMPACT; GREAT PICS; Cool color

Cons: Don&apos;t know any

So far, I really like it. It&apos;s small &amp; compact enought to carry anywhere. It takes great pics &amp; has cool features.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cirano</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pictures, easy to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera as a Xmas present for my girlfriend whose old camera took really awful pictures. This tiny camera delivers pictures with great colors, it&apos;s easy to use, and has a stylish design. In addition, at this price is was a total bargain.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mikey25</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for quick startup time and amazing pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Photo quality, fast start up, and battery life.

Cons: Nothing

This camera is the best point and shoot camera I have ever used for several reasons. Number one, it feels and looks great. It starts up and is able to snap a picture within seconds which is great for action shots one when your trying to catch a moving target. The battery life is great, lasts several days with moderate use and 2 days with heavy use. The pictures taken are great as well. Many people comment on my pictures expecting a larger and more expensive camera to have taken them. The cannon name is also a plus! I would recommend this produce to anyone who is looking for a great price for a great product .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>aprilmommy0205</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So small</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Image Quality; Easy To Use; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Small / Compact

I have a Canon DSLR that I love. However, it is bulky to carry around for everyday photo opportunities. I purchased the Canon PS 1300 for the Canon name/reputation and its size. The camera seems so small compared to the DSLR. It will take some getting used to, but I have been very happy with the images captured thus far.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>abbeyrs123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great camera, nice quality and easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: nothing

love this camera. its small but powerful. takes excellent pictures in macro and many different features to it. great battery life and nice compact charger. great for a beginner or someone who would just like a nice small digital camera to take around instead of a digital SLR.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VixenTheCat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Buy the Sony Cyber-shot DSC W330 instead!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good picture quality, easy to use

Cons: Squeaky winding noise when it not doing anything

First off, after having this camera for ONE DAY, it made a &quot;squeaky-winding&quot; noise. Even when it was making videos. I know that making videos is not the purpose of this camera, but it should not be doing that. Then, I went back to the store to exchange for the same one and the guy there said that another one was doing it, so I just exchanged it for the Sony Cyber-shot DSC W330. Which is a much better camera. I was specifically looking for a camera with auto-focus and I didn&apos;t realize that the Canon one didn&apos;t have it when I purchased it. So I am much happier that I got the Sony camera.
...but, the pictures turned out pretty good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gifter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Got this camera as a gift for my mother. She needed something reliable and simple to use yet. A professional photographer myself, I knew Canon would be a quality product. It did not disappoint. My mom loves it, the compact feel and quality photos and video. The rechargeable battery and image stabilizer were what hooked me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DaisyLou</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality and size of camera.

Cons: No instuction booklet w/ the camera

For the money, this camera is awesome! The picture quality is great and it has many features. My only complaint about it is that it does not come w/ an instructions booklet. You have to go online and download it if you want it. With so many features, you have to have the instructions to figure out how to maximize the camera&apos;s functions.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sternlax</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Super Compact - full of features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s a really handy camera to have on me at all times. I usually shoot with a Canon DSLR. This gives me a lot of the functions I find on my D40 but in a point and shoot. I&apos;m pretty happy with it. My last canon point and shoot lasted me 8 years. When you think about it, the cost over 8 years is pretty nominal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Picture pertect</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Good Image Quality; Easy To Use; Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color

I have the Canon SD1200 IS and like it a lot. A friend liked it a lot and asked me for one. Since it has been replaced by the Canon SD1300 IS picked it out for her.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tinydancer2426</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been using every type of camera out there in the world, and this one is great for the price. It&apos;s lightweight, small, and has a nice range of features for a point and shoot. I haven&apos;t been able to use it a ton, but so far it has been great! ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>camillesau</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I actually researched this camera for a friend. I saw the photos it took, and bought one for myself. The camera is small, lightweight, and takes very good shots. In my opinion, one of the best P and S out there. As with all P and S, a bit of flash lag, but not much. Good color balance, anti-shake and zoom. Sturdy little thing, and fits in a pocket.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dean</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Camera For Point And Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization

Perfect camera for point and shoot without complicating the settings. Very compact and easy to handle.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Squiggy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>No Bad for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good Image Stabilization; Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color

Cons: Zoom lever

Nice camera for the price. Zoom lever is alittle difficut to use being on top with the picture shot button. Takes some getting use to.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rjwin1967</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A very good little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use and it&apos;s features.

Cons: PC software. Some won&apos;t load. We use file manager to download pictures.

This camera makes good pictures easy. If you want a compact camera that takes very clear pictures automatically, then I&apos;d suggest looking at this one. Even the macro setting is automatic. Some of the software wouldn&apos;t load after trying several times, but to be honest, we didn&apos;t need it anyway. The computer&apos;s file manager will get you access to the camera&apos;s memory and any image editor will work then. We were going to buy a Sony rated at 14 megapixels, but after comparing it with this one, we chose the Canon.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ScottyB980</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small size

Cons: nothing so far

If you are looking for a small camera that takes good pictures this should be a good fit. I had a Canon camera before this that used AA batteries and it was very bulky compared to this camera. You can easily take this one with you in your pocket. It shoots faster than my previous camera too. It&apos;s not an SLR camera but meets my needs for most situations.

I used the fireworks mode over the fourth and it worked pretty well. I also use the kids &amp; pets shooting mode with continuous shooting and it is fast enough for me especially when there us a lot of light. The quality of pictures is good too.

Over all I would recommend this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JennyH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color; Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization

This product is great, I love it! It takes great pictures! I got everything in the deal[...] I LOVE THIS CAMERA!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bell</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Short Lag Time; Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization; Good in Low Light

this is a great camera and I would recommend it to anyone. It is easy to us and sharp looking.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ksch411</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, would recommend</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I would recommend this camera. It&apos;s compact size is PERFECT. It fits inside a little clutch or your back pocket. I got the chocolate color and absolutely love it. The quality of pictures is excellent, and response time is fairly fast. I am getting some blurred pictures but it&apos;s probably because I haven&apos;t played with the settings enough yet. I would highly recommend! ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Can&apos;t go wrong with the SD1300 IS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The best part about the Canon SD1300 is that it works right out of the box. Great crisp photos. Everything is intuitive and you can give it to your grandmother or an experienced photographer and get great pictures. If you want to utilize the more advanced features, like forced flash, it&apos;s a simple setting. A very minor nit: I wish they would put the battery alignment arrow on the camera body, not just the charger. Although you can&apos;t put the battery in backward, it would make it easier to align. Enjoy this great camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ASL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera for Personal, Amateur Photography</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy-to-use, Quick snap-time

Cons: Wouldn&apos;t recommend for photography enthusiasts

I bought this camera to take pictures and videos on vacations. It has served this purpose perfectly. I like that quick response time from the time you press the snapshot button to the time the picture is actually taken. Pictures are clear and there are plenty of options to customize your shots. I would definitely recommend this camera to someone who needs an everyday-use digital camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>justjessica</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I&apos;m in love</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Takes great pictures, battery life is awesome

This is the best camera I have ever owned. After going through 3 nikon&apos;s I decided to try another brand of camera. I played around with this one in the store and fell in love with it. I got it home and took a ton of pictures and they all turned out great because of the auto focus. I haven&apos;t charged the battery in 3 days and it&apos;s still fully charged and I use the camera a lot. It&apos;s easy to use and I would definitely tell anyone to buy it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AnonymousDC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small slim size, lightweight, silver color, nice shape, good looking, excellent battery recharger without cord

Cons: Nice if it were easier to use and less expensive

This is a great little camera! I love the small size. It is light and can easliy fit into a handbag or pocket. I was delighted to see how thin and small it was and that the camera was not heavy to carry around. The silver color is nice. A friend recommended this camera to me. Photos are clear and good. I would recommend it to others. There are so many digital cameras and choices out there it can be confusing, but thankfully a close friend identified this camera as an excellent one. It is well worth the money to buy this excellent camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jeep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>IT IS CLASSY AND IT TAKES GREAT PICTURES</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: A very good 2.7inch LCD, 28mm wide angle lens and 4x opticl zoom

Cons: No camera is perfect

. The flat button arangement is the same as the SD1200, SD940 all but the power button on the top is larger and easier to turn on and off, I like that but be carefull it does not come on in your pocket. I have no trouble using any of the flat buttons even with my big old hands, that&apos;s just me though. I like that the mic for the video is in the frount of the camera instead of on top next to where your finger sets like the canon SD940 and SD1400, it picks up less noise (from your fingers) being in the frount. I like the func menu (this is where you set iso white balance,my colors) better than the SD940 because it lets you set things with one less step like on the SD1200. It also ha ... s a better color skeem (the color of the menus) than the canon SD1200, again thats just me though. I can not tell any differnce in shot to shot or flash shot to shot times between the SD1300 and the SD1200 which is 1 and 1/2secs to 2secs with out the flash and 3 to 4secs with the flash on(up to 6sec for a full all out flash recharge). Shutter lag is good for a canon point and shoot but if you prefocas that will help even more. I never tested the continuous shooting(but see my battery test) but canon says it is 0.9 shots per sec on the SD1300 where the SD1200 is 1.4 shots per sec, if that is important to you. I did test the battery by using the continuous shooting mode with the flash on and got well over 420 pictures on a freshly charged battery and still had 3 bars left on a the battery icon and it was taking 1 picture every 2secs or less if that helps you out on the continious shooting part any and when I turned the flash off it seemed to be very fast for a small canon point and shoot. I am getting about the same image quality as the SD1200 which is very good for this size camera, your getting a larger 2.7inch very clear LCD screen and a 28mm x 112mm lens, a little better than the 35 x 105 on the SD1200. A lot of review sites blow their pictures way up and look for defects, your likely to o ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Squinty</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I bought this once before</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I loved the compact size and great quality pictures with my SD1200. Too bad I dropped it out of my car. This next generation is better with more pixels and telephoto. Wish it had a viewfinder, but most cameras this size and price don&apos;t have one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Crafty-Lady</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For the quick shots because it&apos;s so small and handy, it was a present for my wife and she loves it. Her photos are clean and sharp. She also used camera video to shoot humming birds feeding from our garden deckand placed the video on her FB page. Have not heard any negatives about her camera to date. She has been using her camera for 3 weeks now.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ybkay</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great and easy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this from everyday shots of my kids to trips to the zoo and capture great shots of animals in their element. Recently just took some awesome skyline pics of Chicago from Lake Michigan. One slight problem is that when pulling camera from case the lens sometimes gets stuck if I accidently push the on button while gripping the camera. This results in a lens error but doesn&apos;t seem to damage camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mom the bomb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good things do come in small packages.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large Clear LCD; Good in Low Light; Easy To Use; Good Image Quality; Great Zoom; Nice Body Color; Small / Compact; Good Image Stabilization; Fast/accurate auto-focus

Cons: Lag / Shutter Delay

Although, the auto focus feature is a nice adddition, it takes a little getting used to. The picture in the LCD display at first is very pixally however, after the shot is comprised the image turns out beautifully. Great little camera and at a great little price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Property Manager</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought several of these for our staff to take property photos. We don&apos;t need a monster slr. We just need small cameras that take good pictures and have plenty of battery life. The PowerShot SD1300 IS fits the bill.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>aim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>decent for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Good Image Quality; Easy To Use

Cons: No Viewfinder; Lag / Shutter Delay

It&apos;s a little slow in taking pictures. That&apos;s my only complaint.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>anonymousnonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Gremlins</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>This is our second PowerShot. The first broke after several years of use. Since we liked the old one, we figured the newer model could only be better. Wrong! Soon after purchase, the camera started to have periods where the pictures would be completely washed out. Other times we had issues with the automatic white balance. Other times pictures would come out very fuzzy as if the autofocus is not working. Also, when you are indoors/dimly lit areas, it took the camera an eternity to focus and take the picture. We thought that we just happened to get a lemon. Unfortunately, my mother-in-law who purchased the same camera is experiencing similar problems.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>momof3crc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect, compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been pleased with this camera. The battery life is really long which is a plus for someone on the go! The picture quality is sharp. I can also say that there isn&apos;t as much lag time between taking continuous pictures as there has been with older models of the same camera. Canon is always my go-to brand, and I haven&apos;t been disappointed with this one. My highest quality pics are taken outdoors, but the flash is pretty powerful for a compact camera. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hegde</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent choice as the first camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Easy To Use; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Stabilization; Good Image Quality; Nice Body Color; Large Clear LCD

I bought this camera for my husband, who is new to photography. This is a good first camera to introduce him to photography, because of ease of use and image stabilization. Compact size and silver color looks cool and makes it easy to carry wherever you go. This camera gives the maximum bang for the buck.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nikkiparty</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love this camera....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Short Lag Time; Large Clear LCD; Great Zoom; Easy To Use; Good Image Quality; Good in Low Light; Small / Compact; Nice Body Color

Cons: Have not found one yet

I have not read the directions yet to know how to fully utilize all the features. I just started pointing and clicking and started figuring some things out along the way. I love it. My photos are very nice and I am impressed with the camera and would definitely recommend to friends and family. I has all the features I want and need. I especially love the rechargeable battery and charger and the timer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Here Fido</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Crisp and simple camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Quality; Large Clear LCD; Easy To Use; Small / Compact; Good Image Stabilization; Nice Body Color; Great Zoom

camera takes excellent color pics. Always takes sharp pics. does not have a ton of feature options to deal with, just point and shoot.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>red7399</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Loved my canons until this one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: love the ease of use is great. switching from modes

Cons: turns on too easy

I have had a couple different Canons. I got the sc1300 is in July 2010 and now its Feb 2011 and i have had to replace it 2 times because of a &quot;Lens error&quot; which is a manufacters defect. Which i think happenes because it can be turned on too easy in your pocket and when the lens doesnt open it breaks.
I will not be replacing it with the same model again..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>decent camera, okay shots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: fast to take pictures

Cons: sometimes pictures not so great you have to aim for your good shots

after hearing rave reviews and not liking a sony cybershot i went with this camera and although each had their strong points this camera had less weak points if that makes sense. good battery life, decent pics. the automode always trys to focus on the wrong thing tho</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Most excellent, simple, easy camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is easy to use.

Cons: Rechargable battery as opposed to direct charge.

Photographers destined to become great in the future and are building their skills now, or those who have no patience for all of those confusing settings and buttons will love this camera. The video option recorded some priceless tender Christmas moments, and the zoom, some beautiful 1st birthday, cake in the face, frameable portraits. Amazing quality for a simple to use camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bmartiny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for a really good price. Easy to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simple operation, sharp pictures

Cons: So far nothing, Love it

I bought this for a gift to my dad who is 80. He loves it and finds it easy to use. It takes great pictures, and the battery holds a charge a long time. So far it is all good!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AliceBlueChgo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, ease of use

Cons: .jpgs are very large.

It&apos;s easy to use! That was my basic objective, along with being compact, and it meets both those criteria.

I&apos;m still trying to figure out how to use some of the features. Also trying to figure out why the .jpgs are so big.

I bought this for travel, have another digital when I want to take trickier shots. Love that this fits easily into my purse.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TwoCollegeDaughters</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for my daughter who is at college</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Takes great pictures

My daughter seems to always lose her camera. I was determined to by a good quality camera at reasonable cost. This camera is perfect for her. The small size is perfect to fit in her purse. It is very easy to use....she started using it the first day without reading directions. I would highly recommend this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GrannyDebB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good camera for a point &amp; shoot!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simple and good pics

Cons: would prefer AA or AAA batteries for ease of replacement in a pinch.

Was looking for small and simple. This camera filled the bill! Very happy with my purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kazz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, picture quality

Cons: nothing

Especially for the price, I am very pleased. Some internal memory would have been nice, but with memory being so cheap now, the trade-off in order to get the great pricing I think is a great deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>From one who likes simplicity.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great compact camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Good Image Quality; Large Clear LCD; Easy To Use; Fast/accurate auto-focus

Cons: No Viewfinder

We have other Canon Cameras and needed one to use for job pictures. This meets our needs and takes really clear pictures. Great small camera for a point and shot user.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hulagaga</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Little Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I needed a digital camera to move into the 21st century, but didn&apos;t want to spend too much. This is an easy-to-use camera for a novice like me. It&apos;s small, yet the pictures look clear and sharp. [...] the price was comparable to other sources.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BriBCN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent quality pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love the clear quality and color of the pictures. The camera is easy to use and my photos require little to no touching-up once they are uploaded onto my computer. The only thing I would say is that whoever is taking the picture needs to make sure the camera focuses before taking the shot or else the picture can come out blurry. Otherwise, a great little camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love my pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large Clear LCD; Easy To Use; Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact

It&apos;s great for family events and vacations. My vacation pictures are always great looking and family members have told me they like the pictures that it takes. It&apos;s very good on low light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Carissa the Gifter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good starter, but not for larger hands</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small and compact; Large viewscreen; Excellent Quality Picture; Easy to use

Cons: Small Buttons

I bought this camera for my dad -- a novice who has larger fingers and is inexperienced with digital cameras in general. The menu system and functionality was user-friendly, but the shutter and zoom buttons were a little small for him to use well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MisterBrady</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Yellow!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use with lots of features

Cons: Image colors were bad

I quickly and easily went through the camera settings and was able to set it up to my liking without reading through the manual. Lots of great settings even if you want to &quot;dial in&quot; the right balance for each shot, but also has lots of &quot;auto&quot; features which most will find handy.

I took several images with this camera when we first bought it and had terrible results with the image colors while using the flash. The subject of the image would look fine, but the entire background looked like it was painted with a yellow/orange tint.

I could turn the flash setting to &quot;off&quot; and get better results, but then it seemed like the image stabilization suffered (I don&apos;t think I developed a twitch). This camer ... a was for my wife who will do nothing but use the &quot;Auto&quot; settings (including flash) so I had to return it and try another.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kiwi1712</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Extremely Happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Haven&apos;t found anything yet

After buying a panasonic and hating it, I returned it and bought this instead. I am SO GLAD I did. This camera&apos;s picture quality is just beautiful! I am so happy with this camera..the design and features are great and easy to use as well. Would definitely recommend this camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ash1313</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is overall good, especially for the price! The zoom is very good as well as the quality picture. NOTE: This does NOT come with a memory card. This may explain why the price is low. . . .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ktlew</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent value; easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have rheumatoid arthrits. I found the camera easy to hold and use. opening the battery/photo card space and removing/placing them was no problem. Instructions were also easy to follow. Pictures are true to the original with good clarity. colors were also true. I&apos;m enjoying my new camera. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Clicken</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization; Large Clear LCD; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact; Easy To Use

Cons: Lag / Shutter Delay

Great camera. Just point and shoot.
Great deal! Came with 4GB SD Memory, Camera case, lense cleaner.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>batdaddy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Staples</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just What I Was Looking For</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good Image Quality; Large Clear LCD; Nice Body Color; Small / Compact; Easy To Use

Cons: LCD can be jittery in sun

I wanted a camera that took quality family photos, but wasn&apos;t going to break the bank. This camera fit the bill nicely. Pictures are very clear whether using the Auto or Manual modes. The videos are great and it is so easy to use. I am very happy with this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>salma shamel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Colors</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Very practical camera, easy to use, great price for what you get. The only disappointment was the difference between the colors on the pc screen and the camera, colors became less vibrant, and not so good in low light. Other that that, I would definitely recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bubbasmom1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the money!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality.

Cons: Would prefer camera had metal body instead of plastic.

I love this camera. I read many reviews after my sony of 7 yrs shot craps before making this purchase. I above all wanted a camera which took great pics at an economical price. I&apos;ve had it a little over a month and am very pleased with the pic quality. I struggle sometime with downloading the pics but I know it will get easier with repeated use. I am very much a novice at photography but enjoy the candid shots of friends, family , pets, etc. So far I am exremely satisfied with my Canon. I even recommended it to my son who is in Okinawa. Very much worth the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Some chick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Short Lag Time; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact; Large Clear LCD; Good in Low Light; Good Image Stabilization; Nice Body Color; Great Zoom

Cons: Limited Zoom

I bought this camera to replace my old Canon that had a fried processing unit. I LOVE this camera!! The &quot;Auto&quot; function is awesome, and the zoom is mostly what I prefer it to be. Can&apos;t complain too much about the macro setting as I&apos;d need a different camera and lenses to do the zooming I tend to do (see pictures). I&apos;ve found no faults with it... just love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>muffins</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for beginner photographer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use just point and click-it focused for me

Cons: nothing

I bought camera right before I went to Alaska. I used AUTO setting as I was afraidI wouldn&apos;t remember correct setting as a moose ran by. The pics were great . I received many compliments from more experienced photographers on my pics</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stanleylm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best, most intuitive compact camera we have owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use. Screen visible in sunlight

Cons: It is the best compact I have owned

Through loss, theft and whatever we have owned several compact cameras. The last one, a nikon cool pix. They have all been marginal. hard to see screens in the sunlight, to complicaed to remember the controls.

The Canon SD 1300 IS has solved all of my complaints in a elegant, easy to use package. The screen brightness can be adjusted so the image is visable even in bright Italinan sun. All of the controls are very easy to figure out, without carrying the manual around. Pictures are great as to be expected.

I love this camera. Have not even liked the ones I have owned in the past.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KasperPD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I like it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, easy to use, design...

Cons: Nothing so far....

For $150 it is a great camera. The most, the picture quality. It is really easy to use, and it fits perfectly in my hand. Good battery life. I just love it.

My former Canon had a problem with the CCD (image sensor), and Canon sent to me a refurbished camera free (newer model), even when my warranty was expired for more than two years. Time later, the CCD of the second camera got broken again. Canon addressed the problem, and I hope by this time they will had corrected it definitely.

They treated me well, and both cameras took great pictures, so I wanted to trust them one more time. Hope everything will work well this time.

Best.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Little Freddie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A neat camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good in Low Light; Great size; Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization; Great Zoom; Easy to use on auto mode; Nice Body Color; Sharp Pictures

Cons: No panorama stitch

I just received the camera a few days ago. Have used it for pics of grandchildren (inside the house) and some outside test shots. The low light pictures are really nice but make sure your finger does not cover the flash. I bought it for an upcoming trip to England. The manual shows the camera will do a lot more than I thought and I look forward to learning more. I will use the &quot;auto&quot; mode mostly. I bought the leather case too and rec it as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for real estate use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Wide angle lens and long battery life

The wide angle lens is advantageous for real estate photos, and the quality is excellent. Battery life is outstanding!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mojoge</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I really love this camera! It takes great pictures and is very easy to use. I especially like the auto mode since I&apos;m not into setting a camera manually just yet. It seems very sturdy and well built. I would recommend it for the price. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Priscilla Lipshitz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE THIS THING</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this as my personal quick shot camera for parties, events and such. The images are crisp, clean and contain wonderful color. The delay for focusing is minimal so you&apos;re able to take your quick photos. Easy to carry and durable enough to survive my purse. I haven&apos;t found anything I do not like about it yet! So glad I purchased it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Roy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great housing for starting underwater photography. If you already have the Canon SD 1300 camera this will get it safely underwater. Very simple to use, just drop in the camera, close the back and go. So far I have used it on 6 dives in the Turks &amp; Caicos up to 90 ft. deep and not a drop of water inside. The internal flash works ok but to get true colors, I think the external flash is needed. I plan on making that my next purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>vedral</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Beautiful pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Recently used it along the California coast, Hearst Castle, and 2 weeks later Lake Tahoe. The pictures and videos it takes are fantastic, and it&apos;s slim line feature, make it easy to carry around. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fencer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Slow Response Time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good picture quality and easy user interface

Cons: Slow response time

One point that has not been brought out in these reviews is the really slow response time to taking a picture (latency). This camera takes a photo 1 - 2 seconds after you press the shutter button, making it unusable for any action shots, and most normal point-and-shoot shots. Returned the day after I bought it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Battery Genie customer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good replacement battery for Canon S90</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very good product. While the Canon battery has a one-month warranty, these have a lifetime warranty. Lasts as long as the original Canon battery that came with the camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big Camera in small package!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had this camera for 3 weeks now. Iv&apos;e taken great pictures and videos above and below the surface. This camera has so many wonderful features that I haven&apos;t even used yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bestmom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good deal!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Great Battery Life; Nice Body Color; Good Image Stabilization; Good in Low Light; Short Lag Time

Cons: No view finder

This is my first digital camera so I don&apos;t have much to compare it with but I do not have any complaints so far. Love the brown color and everything else about it! It does not have a view finder, just a screen and I was wondering how bad that would be on a sunny day but it&apos;s been fine so far. I think it&apos;s a good deal for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shop til you Drop</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best point n shoot camera I&apos;ve owned!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good in Low Light; Nice Body Color; Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization

Cons: Limited Zoom

I have owned several point and shoot cameras and this one is the best I have owned so far. This is so easy to use and takes great shots! The picture quality is great for the price and it is small enough to carry with you at all times. So far, so good! Very happy with my purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>skipbank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a very easy camera to use. It is my first digital camera and I am happy with it. The only disappointment I have with it is that it does not have the feature to pick out one color in a shot and have the rest of the picture come out in black and white. I am not sure what that feature is called, but I do know that the Powershot SD1100IS does have that option. This was one of the reasons I purchased this camera. The description did not have a good detail of the enhancements available. I assumed it would have the feature. Don&apos;t assume! I should have called customer service. Overall I am very happy with this camera. The battery lasts a long time. (A BIG plus!!!) ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lifeinpictures</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good handy one..worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good Image Stabilization

Just started using it, so far like it for the use. I needed a small one which can go into my pocket when I really do not need to carry my bulky SLR around. Pretty impressed by the picture quality and ease of handling. Cannon brand..makes it feel better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doug the retiree</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>PowerShot SD 1300 digital camera by Cano</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We use this camera for family events such as birthdays, Christmas and other holidays. We also rely on this camera for recording our travels, both domestic and foreign. The camera is lightweight and very slim. It is so easy to carry in its case or in my pocket. There is really nothing about the camera that I do not like.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Warden</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>[...]</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We bought 3 of the cameras for our real estate appraisal office. We need cameras that take a beating since we use them all day every day. So far these SD1300&apos;s are hitting the spot. They&apos;re simple to use and have just the right amount of features. You have the auto mode which is great for everyday use and then the program mode with just the right amount of shooting modes. I can&apos;t stand the cameras with 40 different shooting modes. I don&apos;t think there is a reason to have 4 underwater modes and 3 different portrait modes... that&apos;s overkill. The only complaint I really have is the lack of a view finder, which was scrapped for the larger LCD screen. I know it&apos;s not as popular as it used to be, but the screen is not bright enough to out shine direct sunlight, so a viewfinder would come in handy ... . Basically, if you&apos;re looking for something to get the job done and don&apos;t want to read a dostoevsky novel to understand how to use it, then this is the camera for you.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hinda</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again &amp; again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I absolutely LOVE the Power Shot SD1300. I am a person who does not like change, BUT, I was talked into trying a digital camera and once using the Power Shot SD 1300 I never looked back. I hike with my dog up in the mountains of NYS and always have the camera at my ready..I was able to get a Red Tail Hawk awaiting it&apos;s prey up in a tree, etc. and other facinating and fantastic sights with Mother Nature. The clarity of the photos, the easiness of the use and the understanding of the camera makes it the absolute best for me. While in N.C. I dropped my Power Shot SD1300 and it broke. I immediately contacted my niece in Suffern, NY who through B&amp;H ordered me a new Power Shot SD1300 ..[...]. I cannot praise this camera enough. It is GREAT!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kortez73</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I owned a Canon camera before and I needed to update. This one is nice and small and easy to use. Takes a much larger card that is so tiny you wonder how it can hold so much more. Amazing. Great pictures.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Larry Sr.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Compact Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Short Lag Time; Good in Low Light; Small / Compact; Good Image Stabilization; Large Clear LCD; Good Image Quality

Cons: Limited Zoom

Just what I was looking for in a compact camera when we cruise. When we get off the ship I needed something small that still takes great photos. I&apos;m a Canon fan anyway as I have two other Canon cameras. This one fits in my pocket, or in my wife&apos;s purse. Indoor low light photos are very good. Turned out to be a perfect fit for what I wanted.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Du Haus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Solid Canon quality and great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Good Image Quality; Short Lag Time

While I&apos;m no expert on camera performance or technical details, I can say that this is a good quality camera in this price range. I owned a Canon SD750 that was stolen. prior to this, and the SD1300 seems to be compare quite well with that gem. Navigating the features is very similar to the 750 but will not be too tricky for someone completely new to the layout. Good picture quality and a super-fast start up make it an ideal camera for the casual user like myself.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mackdiddi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera for Vacation</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Takes great pictures.

Cons: Price was dropped by another store as clearence alot cheaper by 50%

Just got back from 7 day Cruise. Bought this camera for 99.99. Used this camera as the primary camera for all pictures. Used this in day, night , outside, inside and several different lighting conditions. You can&apos;t go wrong with this camera. It is quick and easy to use. Read the instructions and you will not have any problems.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BarbH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, quality

This is the best camera I have ever purchased. It&apos;s actually my 3rd one. I had one for myself and one for my daughter. She lost hers and I replaced it for her. The price is great for the quality of photo!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>stowlind</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The only thing I do not like about it is the way it works with people moving. It always is blurry. Other than that, its a great camera. Takes nice pictures and videos!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Randy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great first underwater camera experiance</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought this housing and the Canon SD1300 camera to take down to Cozumel. Great pictures and video from such a simple package. Scuba diving down to 100 feet and it worked great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>oreokooky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Horrible picture quality.

I was an instant fan after I got my first Canon camera. This is the 2nd Canon I have purchased and was immediately disappointed. My 890IS was infinitely better at taking pictures and video and gave much higher quality. I have not taken a single image with my 1300IS that I have been happy with. Everything comes out really blurry and/or LOTS of noise. The 1300IS video so far has been VERY unreliable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>crymine</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use and takes great pictures

Cons: Have no complaints yet

This is a great camera. That is easy to use as soon as you get it out of the box. Leaving the setting as is takes great, clear pictures. Its very easy to use and the quality is great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AnoniMouse</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fair entry level unit, but you grow beyond it fast</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>A good entry level camera for casual users, or a &quot;disposable&quot; backup cam. Very good outdoor shots, but indoor shots can be less than great. The flash can be overly strong for many shots. The processing/saving lag is surprisingly long.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nikalaus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use

Cons: Loved everything about it

It&apos;s compact, easy to use, pictures are fabulous! First camera that I have ever bought that came with it&apos;s own battery charger. It is very fast.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fvdn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great general use camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lighting, color, sharpness

Cons: Nothing that I can think of

We love this camera. I bought this camera in a hurry and at the last minute as I had left my digital SLR at home for an event. The clarity and lighting of the photos are brilliant - I now use it in place of my SLR for family pics and events.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Camera challenged person loved it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use and the directions are easy to understand

Cons: You need to purchase a SD card.

I bought this as a christmas gift for my sister. She is technically challenged and just now learning to use a computer. So now she has a digital camera. She loves it. Though she hasn&apos;t uploaded to facebook and shared her pics I know she will soon. She said the camera is easy to use and understand. For her that says a lot!!! And that says a lot for Canon as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>biatro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: picture quality and price

I used Canon Cameras throughout the years and i was always very satisfied. I bought this camera on a black friday deal, after i broke my older Canon. I am very pleased so far. It takes great pictures and it is very easy to use for soemone who wants nice pictures but not something too sophisticated.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wisconsinmommy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Price, Nice Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Time between pictures &amp; time to focus are slower than I would prefer. Sometimes I miss the picture I&apos;m trying to get.

I had a camera that I loved and I miss things about my old one, but this camera is a good replacement. Easy to use, easy to learn to use, good pictures. I have found that it is more important to &quot;half push&quot; the photo button for longer on this camera than on my last one, as I end up with out of focus pictures more easily, but if I take the time to let the camera focus, the quality is great. I also think that the focus and recycle time takes longer with this camera than others that I have used.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ZTAKPsi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small and great quality!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Great Zoom; Small / Compact; Nice Body Color; Good in Low Light; Good Image Quality

Cons: Lag / Shutter Delay

Got this to keep in my purse and just have on hand while wandering around NYC on a daily basis. There are always good shots to be had in the city, and this is a great camera to just have in my purse that doesn&apos;t take up room or add extra weight. I&apos;ve always loved Canon and this camera doesn&apos;t disappoint!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jpwnvmz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty Good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It is a good camera. My favorite feature is that you can turn it to see the picture vertical. We are taking this to Hawaii so I may have a more thorough review after our trip in March.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mvargas26</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good upgrade camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features and picture quality

Cons: start up time a little slow

I had an older canon and I found for the price this was a great upgrade that won&apos;t hurt your pocket too much. Good size camera that packs a lot of punch. Well worth the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rep164</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love how tiny it is!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I haven&apos;t had a chance to use my new camera a ton yet, or really play around with the features, but so far so good. my boyfriend used it a bit and in some settings had problems with yellowiness/off colors and a little blurriness, but in normal conditions and outdoors it works great so far! and it&apos;s so tiny... after my last camera (also a canon, which I loved but it was stolen from me) I didn&apos;t think they could keep getting smaller but they have! doesn&apos;t feel cheap or fragile though which is nice. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>viper318z</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera, great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great pics and easy to use

Cons: none so far

I was always been a canon fan and my SD700 finally gave up after 5 yrs. After researching and reading several reviews, i decided to get this camera. I had it for a month and i must say i love it. It takes great pictures, easy to use and got a good price deal during christmas sale.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bose</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good cool product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Short Lag Time; Large Clear LCD; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Easy To Use; Great Zoom; Good Image Quality; Small / Compact

I use this camera when I am not into serious photography. I usually carry my SLR always but wanted something to go in my pocket to take some casual photos so I got this one. I have used it during the holiday season took some pictures. Quality is good and the flash is really powerful, if you are planning to take pictures inside a room.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot ELPH SD1300 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Silver)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/2409922947907404805/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLsBEPQCMAA4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kimmy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>pleased but not too pleased</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice variety of settings; Really good close ups

Cons: No color swap; No color enhancer

I really miss the color swap and color enhancer. please bring it back!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

