<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Josie Reavely</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>TechRadar UK</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Canon G1 X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The new Canon PowerShot G1 X - commonly shortened to Canon G1 X, or even Canon G1X - occupies the top spot in Canon&apos;s prestigious G-series compact camera range, offering a truly impressive array of high-end features. 

Launched at CES earlier this year, the new digital camera is aimed at advanced photographers in search of a high-quality, take-anywhere primary camera and/or backup for their DSLR. 

To that end, the Canon G1 X is packed with advanced technologies designed to deliver the very best performance.

It may not be the compact system camera (CSC) that everyone was expecting to see from Canon, nor is it a direct replacement for the highly popular Canon PowerShot G12 - rather, it&apos;s something in between. 

As such, it&apos;s difficult to slot the Canon G1 X into any ... one particular category and so - as Canon is keen to point out - it&apos;s just as tricky to determine natural rivals for this new camera. 

The Canon PowerShot G1 X&apos;s specifications make for very impressive reading. It boasts a 14.3MP CMOS sensor that&apos;s almost the same size as an EOS DSLR&apos;s, sporting a pixel structure and size that&apos;s equivalent to that on the entry-level Canon EOS 600D&apos;s CMOS device.

The latest generation Digic 5 image processor drives this camera&apos;s performance and promises to deliver richly-detailed shots with well-controlled noise, while the Canon G1X&apos;s fast, 4x optical image stabilisation (IS) zoom lens incorporates a new design using Ultra High Refractive Index Aspherical (UA) elements for supreme image quality.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff Keller</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>DCResource.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DCRP Review: Canon PowerShot G1 X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent photo quality, with low noise until highest ISOs; Solid build quality, with lots of dials and direct buttons; Optical image stabilization; Super high resolution 3-inch rotating LCD display; Optical viewfinder is always a nice touch; Full manual controls, including RAW support; Smart Auto mode picks a scene mode (and the proper IS setting) for you; Tons of scene modes and Creative Filters; Dynamic range correction and HDR features improve image contrast; Customizable button, menu, and spots on mode dial; Handy electronic level; Built-in neutral density filter; Redeye not an issue -- if it does become one, a removal tool is available in playback mode; Records Full HD (1080/24p) video with stereo sound, use of optical zoom; Very expandable, with optional external flash, lens h ... ood and filters, underwater housing, and wired remote

Cons: Expensive; Likes to clip highlights; Lens on the slow side at telephoto end; AF performance needs improvement; Long minimum focus distances mean frequent switching between normal and macro AF when subjects are close; Design annoyances: bulky body, lens visible through viewfinder, can&apos;t access memory card slot when using tripod; Movies are a bit choppy due to 24 fps frame rate -- no manual controls available; Unremarkable burst mode; Below average battery life; Full manual on CD-ROM

if you&apos;ve got $800 burning a hole in your pocket and want a semi-compact camera with D-SLR image quality, then look no further than the Canon PowerShot G1 X. It&apos;s not for action photography (due to its sluggish focusing and burst modes) nor is it great for close-ups, but for virtually every other situation, the G1 X delivers. I&apos;m hopeful that Canon&apos;s next large sensor camera will have a faster lens, snappier performance, and improved battery life, but for now, the G1 X is easily good enough for me to recommend.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Audley Jarvis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>TrustedReviews</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Review: Canon PowerShot G1X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros:Class-leading image quality for an advanced compact Impressive high ISO performance Super sharp lens that captures lots of detail Vari-angle LCD screen adds flexibility Useful built-in 3-stop ND filter Cons</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bestcovery.com Expert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Bestcovery</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ranked Fourth in Best Low Light Compact Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Canon&apos;s G-series PowerShot cameras reached an evolutionary peak with the G12 model, combining highly refined DSLR-style controls on a (relatively) compact body surrounding a 1/1.7&quot; image sensor. One of the main criticisms leveled at the G12 was that it was &apos;too much camera&apos; for its sensor, referring to the too-small image sensor for a camera...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shawn Barnett</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Imaging-Resource.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon PowerShot G1 X Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div style=&quot;display: none;&quot; class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quite a bit smaller than large-sensor mirrorless or SLR with similar lens
Lens is fairly sharp (except corners at wide angle), hits a good sweet spot for zoom range, and bright at wide angle
JPEG mode automatically corrects for distortion, aberration
Tilt/swivel LCD adds protection, makes framing awkward angles easy
Excellent high ISO performance for a compact
Large sensor and relatively fast lens allows shallow depth-of-field at wide angle
Nice, camera-like interface with lots of external controls, including twin dials
Two custom settings groups make it easy to save setups for specific situations
Dedicated movie button makes spontaneous video easier (but no crop preview until recording starts, unless in Movie mode)
Very good low-light performance 
Good ... flash range from built in flash, hot shoe for external strobes
Adjustable JPEG noise reduction 
14-bit RAW files 
Fair selection of creative options
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon PowerShot G1 X Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large image sensor and excellent photo quality, full HD (1080p) video, low noise at high ISOs

Cons: Sluggish autofocus, no dedicated ISO button, poor macro shooting

Canon&apos;s G1 X intuitive and fun The Canon PowerShot G1 X earns excellent reviews for its combination of outstanding image quality and compact design. This somewhat compact camera sports a large 1.5-inch CMOS sensor (the same one you&apos;ll find on many DSLRs), along with a 4x optical zoom, vari-angle LCD, optical viewfinder and full manual controls. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photoman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A step up for point-and-shoots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The biggest attraction with the G1X is naturally the larger sensor and the fact that it&apos;s a CMOS sensor, as opposed to the usual CCD found in point-and-shoots. This holds out the promise of noticeably improved image quality, and the possibility a photographer can use all the camera&apos;s features, rather than having to work around its shortcomings. A quick test of a gray, white and black subject at the main ISO speeds, with high noise reduction on, shows the sensor to produce greatly reduced noise, especially in the high- to very-high range. Where previous point-and-shoots would begin exhibiting noise as low as ISO 200, the G1X holds up remarkably well even at the higher ISOs, and this bodes well for improved image quality, as well as for low-light shooting. Before talking good and bad point ... s, let&apos;s say what this camera is NOT. It&apos;s not an SLR in disguise, nor is it intended as an SLR replacement. So comparing its performance to an SLR, and especially complaining about that, seems wrongheaded. But it CAN and should be compared with previously-released point-and-shoots, representing as it does a step forward in that category. Having said that, here are the things I like about the camera: 1. The large, flip-out LCD view screen; Canon seems to be listening to customers who find this a huge bonus and it&apos;s a good thing to continue. 2. Anyone notice that the aperture closes down to F-16 -- two stops more than previous Powershots, including the G-12? This gives the photographer more flexibility with both exposure and Depth of Field. Very nice to have! 3. The shutter speed and F-stop settings are controlled with separate wheels -- more like a pro camera -- rather than one toggle switch. This allows you to work faster when adjusting exposure. 4. The Exposure Compensation dial is on an always-ready dial with a very sure grip -- no need to access a menu. And here are the things I dislike: 1. The position of -- and lack of protection for -- the video-engage button makes it too easy to accidentally trigger the start of a video. I&apos;ve done this several times and it wastes space on the memory card. AND it&apos;s annoying for someone who doesn&apos;t use a still digital camera to shoot videos. 2. The standard lens cap setup -- with the cap tethered to the neck strap -- is a clunky throwback to previous G-series cameras. The cap is necessary for lens protection but swings around awkwardly. Better to remove it and consider a UV filter and filter adapter to protect the lens, since there are no blades to do that automatically. A filter setup could be considered a plus, actually, and more like a pro setup, but then there&apos;s the price tag for the adapter plus the filter. 3. I do like the popup flash, but the flash menus need simplification. Too hard to sort through them, as is true of other Powershots. 4. Like many of its predecessors, the macro function on the G1X is disappointing. You can really only get close enough for true macros with the lens at a wide focal length, and than may not give the desired framing or Depth of Field. Thus, if you want to shoot close-ups, this is not really the camera of choice. And that&apos;s too bad. Overall, though, there&apos;s more to like about this camera than to dislike, and it does represent a groundbreaking step toward improved cameras for people who want decent quality digital shots, say, on vacations, but are loathe to lug around a heavy SLR and several lenses. I can place myself in that category and I&apos;m looking forward to what the G1x can do on my next vacation come this June.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gary</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Use of Adobe Photoshop CS5 RAW with G1 X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Latest Adobe Camera Raw 6.7 for Photoshop CS5(Adobe Labs - Candidate Release) as of March 5, 2012 will take care of converting the RAW files taken on the G1X Camera. Beware that this download for Adobe Camera RAW 6.7 is still in the testing stages and has not reached the Final Release point. It is working for me with PS CS5. Poor Macro focusing distance is disappointing. Close focusing speed is disappointing. Optical Viewfinder is disappointing. LCD color and clarity is great. Majority of function settings is good to great. 4X Zoom is poor for the price. Battery life is very very poor, especially with use of LCD, and this is evident in the lack of available Canon NB-10L Batteries on the market as of today. Other G1X owners have probably had to purchase 1 or 2 spare batteries for t ... heir G1X camera; not a bad idea but the availability is lacking even direct from Canon USA which makes me wonder if this camera is going to survive. Why no printed user manual provided with the camera was a surprise and mystery to me. Very cheap of Canon not to provide a printed user manual with this camera which they have done in the past.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>viktas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love IQ, learning curve needed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>love this little camera. Honestly I hate point &amp; shoots. but this little guy has some serious potentual. First off IQ especially with flash is top notch. And that&apos;s just the pop up flash!! menu is intuitive comming from a 7D and currently using a 5Dmk3. AF is terrible compared to DSLR&apos;s, incretibly slow. set center AF point and optical zoom instead of using digital zoom. helps get best IQ and with composition. leave AF assist beam on. test 430 ex ii and works great. lens is sharp through entire range. remember to hold it steady. don&apos;t just rely on stabilizer. was shocked to see ISO 1600 being geat, 3200 being good (and 6400 usable is printing 5x7). this is all with out shooting raw and not applying any noise reduction software. Video quality is stunningly good!, surprising 1hr 1080p ... with 16gb card. didn&apos;t see limit, ( maybe because this is a point &amp; shoot ). read audio is bad, didn&apos;t test. Hated handling nex 5n, almost fell out of my hands just trying to pick it up. I have American large hands. This is the body for Professional Photographers Point and shoot with normal sized hands wanting to use full manual. love the articulating screen. incredibly useful. this camera feels small in my hands, but with good grip and ergonomics for its size. it is not big just a tad bit heavy. Price could be lower, but there&apos;s nothing that handles this good with this iQ period!!! the Nex has better IQ 15% better but seriously bad ergonomics and not for a Professsional wanting to shoot in full manual and no hot shoe! I chose the 5Dmk3 because it&apos;s by far a better all around body then the D800, this is a much better all around point and shoot then the nex 5n.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gardenjim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wickedly sharp optics</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m probably exactly the guy Canon had in mind when they dreamed up the Powershot G1X: I do most of my seriousl shooting with a DSLR, but wanted a much smaller, high-quality camera that I could take anywhere, or use as a backup for my DSLR. The G1X shoots raw files, so whatever I take is publishable, so I lose nothing in that regard. Its high-quality optics and extra large CMOS sensor give me crisp images that can be cropped hard if needed, but still retain incredible sharpness. In my experience, color rendition is a bit on the cool side, but white balance is adjustable. The lens has an 28- to 112mm zoom range (35mm equivalent) plus a limited macro range (at closest focus tele macro, you can almost fill the frame with an 8 1/2 by 11 inch page; at wide, you can more than fill the frame with ... the same page). In other words, the camera is set up to do all the basics extremely well; if you want something with extra telephoto or macro capability, buy something else (but lose the advantages of the extra large chip). I&apos;ve read complaints about the optical viewfinder. While it&apos;s true that I use the LCD for composed shots, the optical viewfinder works fine (and zooms right along with the lens) for grab shots of people and animals. The menus are well-organized, intuitive, and have on-screen help that makes it quickly apparent what each item does (if you can&apos;t figure it out yourself). The camera is made like a fine Swiss watch???very precise and solid. My only complaint is that when the electronic level is calibrated to be perfectly horizontal in the landscape (horizontal) position, it&apos;s off in the vertical. When I calibrate it for vertical, it throws off horizontal leveling. The G1X can be customized lots of ways???it takes a 240-page pdf file to elaborate on all the possibilities???but you&apos;ll soon have it set up for the way that best suits your shooting style. Since I&apos;m a still photographer, I don&apos;t use or care about the camera&apos;s video abilities, so you&apos;ll have to read different reviews that cover that. This camera is perfect for me. My advice is to carefully read about its feature set to decide whether it&apos;s for you. What it promises, it delivers, and then some.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ProMom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent.... But.....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Image Quality is AMAZING

Cons: Price, weight, MACRO, Zoom

First let me say.... I am one of those &quot;horrible&quot; people who, when new camera technology comes out, will sell my old equipment to upgrade because I can&apos;t resist the newness. That being said - I previously owned the G12... which is an AMAZING little camera. I love it. but the allure of the bigger sensor and HD video (along with a few other minor details) wooed me into purchasing the G1X. (Also - another side note - I am a professional photographer who wanted a camera that I could pack around when I didn&apos;t want to carry my &quot;big guns&quot;. And the Canon G Series is the BEST way to go - if you are in the same boat. It is NOT a DSLR... so please do not even try to compare it to a DSLR. It is what it is.... an outstanding ... &quot;carry around&quot; camera when you don&apos;t want to pack the DSLR).

So here is a basic overview of what I think of the G1X - and especially comparing it to the G12.

VIDEO: Outstanding improvement. If video is important to you - then you might consider the G1X. The video is excellent quality and I am more than pleased with it. Sound is great and IQ is great. I have one little complaint - and that is - that the zoom in video mode is painfullly slooooowwww. Other than that - it&apos;s great.

MACRO: Okay... so here is my biggest complaint. If you are serious (or even interested in) shooting in Macro mode... this is NOT the camera for you. Turn around and purchase the G12. (IT does a good job with Macro). There is NO macro capability and I think that it&apos;s even a bit of a joke that &quot;macro&quot; even shows up when you get close to something. It WILL NOT focus on what you want it to focus on. Canon... You NEED to fix the Macro on the G Series. End of story.

IQ: Well - I think I already wrapped this one up. Image Quality - especially in low ligh (I do not - ever - shoot with flash. So low light capability is a MAJOR deal for me) is absolutely amazing for a point-and-shoot camera.... and I gues that&apos;s all I can really say about that.

Even though I don&apos;t shoot in &quot;Auto&quot; mode.... ( ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ImageTree</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Disappointed is How I Would Put It. . .</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been leaving my DSLR at home on vacations and taking my point and shoot taking jpeg images with fair results. But I would like to get RAW files and improved image quality and size. Along comes the G1 X. Love the idea of RAW and all the manual features up front and easy to access without menus. After reading early reviews, I decided this camera has most of the features I am looking for: articulated LCD, RAW files, rangefinder viewer, external manual controls, electronic level and a hot shoe. I thought I understood it was bigger than a point and shoot, but hey, I have big pockets just not deep ones. Although you might think I have deep pockets for what this camera costs so for what his gem costs. If it hadn&apos;t taken me so long to get this camera on the road to really put it to t ... he test as a vacation camera, I would return it. One of the first things I discovered is how annoying the lens cap tether is. It takes you free hand to keep the lens cap from flopping around while you try to frame up a shot or change from horizontal to vertical. The other very annoying thing is the instant video button placed right next to the the thumb rest. It didn&apos;t take long to discover that the camera loves to shoot wild video of the ground, sky, and blurred landscapes. I wasted a lot of battery power and card space accidentally pressing the little red record button. You think the engineers would have put a menu option for deactivating this little red annoyance for those of us who have big fat thumbs and don&apos;t spend a lot of time shooting video we&apos;ll never use. Maybe a a disable feature can be included in any new firmware upgrades. The macro feature is not happening with this camera. The larger sensor is a trade off I guess for being able to close focus. I could use my 58mm screw on close-up lenses if Canon every gets the filter adapter available. While the 28mm eq. wide angle is passible, I miss the longer telephoto of my DSLR or even on my PNS. Not because of magnification, but for limiting the angle of view. So I guess I&apos;m stuck. After all the bad reviews I&apos;ve seen here, it will be hard to sell this camera for anything but a big loss. I&apos;ll buy a neck strap and put it around my neck on the next vacation to keep from stretching out my pocket and make room for my PNS back up camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>roguery</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My new Stealth 24p HD wonder cam</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So far, so great! Photo&apos;s look really superb. Even DOF suprisingly good bokeh but you have to zoom the lens all the way out with the subject in focus up close. Amazing. But I bought this point and shoot for it&apos;s video capture capabilities. The only thing I DON&apos;T like is that (like on SLR) you have an actual 24,30,50,60 locked in screen that you lock in what setting you want. This doesn&apos;t have that. Just say&apos;s when you are in HD you are in 24p and when in SD you are 30p. kinda lame if you ask me. In my first initial video tests I notice some rolling shutter problems. But the image itself? unreal. Great lens, great DIGIC 5 (new look)...which im really liking. The point and shoot options on this camera are so fun. I wish I had these goofball options on my 5D. This camera is such a STEALTH ind ... y film cam. No one will think you are shooting 24p HD...in let&apos;s say a STADIUM for a crowd scene. haha. I wish the zoom was a little farther. I am very impressed with the W I D E on this puppy. totally great as is. Although it has built in ND filters (which is cool). I have ordered the filter adapter and ND filters. I will definatly use this on corporate ENG gigs as well. Thank you B&amp;H for your customer service rep&apos;s telling me about this camera. Bang for the BUCK superb and great EMERGENCY back up for DSLR filming or EXTRA cam on music video, ENG, DOCU or even stealth shot on Indy feature with the 24p. So far, loving this puppy. (way better than my g11 for photos and as good as my 7D, 5D with nice glass photo&apos;s = )
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fwguam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been waiting for a high quality pocket camera with good manual control for a couple years, Canon G1X is the right one. Here is the pros and cons: Pro: - Sensor size. I simply do not believe in nail size sensors. - Size and weight: It fits in my hand, and feel good for the weight when taking pictures at low speed. - ISO: Very good at 1600 - Silent on movie mode Cons - Slow focus. I have not found manual focus, will do more research. - Macro is a joke. - OVF is useless. Others - White balance is about average</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jerry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Don&apos;t pay attention to bad-mouth reviews</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Too many reviews treat this camera as one to replace a Canon 7D or Canon 5D, and, therefore, complain about its shortcomings relative to those cameras. That&apos;s just dead wrong. That is not what this camera is about. I use a camera for scenic views in places like National Parks, and to record memories of interiors of museum, castles, art galleries, Bhutanese temples, Papua New Guinea long houses, etc. during my travels to the far corners of the earth. It is perfect for those activities. It has a huge sensor with pixel density roughly the same as that of the Canon 7D, and a high performance Digic 5 processor. It has an excellent stabilized lens. It has an excellent artuclated screen. It has a poor view finder. It takes brilliant pictures in outdoor settings. It takes totally usable pi ... ctures in the dimmest of lighting at ISO settings up to 3200, and quite acceptable pictures even up to ISO 12,800. It is the perfect camera for those environments. It takes HD video. The lens is somewhat slow, but its high ISO capability makes that not an issue. It is bigger than most compacts. I need to use hiking sticks to walk, so I use a belt attached device that holds the camera comfortably in a locked state, and releases rapidly for use. Its weight is totally tolerable for this transport method. I will use it where lugging my Canon 7D is just too taxing. It uses a contrast focusing technique that is not the fastest, but focuses perfectly for my uses. If you are into sports photography, or photography of any rapidly moving objects that you want to focus on qickly, and hold the focus, this is definitely not the camera for you. If you are into macro photography it is also not the camera for you. It has poor close focusing capability. It has a fixed 4x zoom lens, 28 to 112, so it is not great where large zooms are required.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RCKADBARY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Impressive features in a small package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Even though this camera offers many advanced features, its use is intuitive. I was able to take full advantage of this fantastic camera with minimal reading of the well-written manual. Pros: Very good low light use Full Automatic mode can be use 95% of the time. The high resolution allows for extreme cropping, without losing quality. Response time, from power on to first photo is very fast. Comparable to most DSLR cameras, both in quality and price. This camera offers too much to be considered a point and shoot. Cons: Minimal optical zoom(but offset by high resolution). Relatively heavy for a point and shoot. Video quality is just ok.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pixel Dude</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Almost Perfect Grab and Go Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been using this camera for about six weeks and I find it is excellent as a grab and go camera. Wherever I&apos;m going and whatever I&apos;m doing, this camera has been great for taking along for any unplanned photo op that comes up. While not tiny like a point and shoot, it is small, compact and light and easy to carry along in a small shoulder bag, backpack, satchel, etc. It is well balanced and the size is just right for easy handling. Image quality has been excellent with sharp pictures across focal and aperture ranges. I have mostly been shooting in Raw, but JPEGS have also been quite good. The external controls and menu system make it easy to take full control of image making. The G1X has a quality look and feel to it. The fully articulating LCD is a beauty and very useful for ... all kinds of creative shots. The camera does have a few weak points. I miss the excellent macro of my old G11, but I can manage without it. The simple optical viewfinder is pathetic, and it seems a good EVF should be possible and included at this price given what other manufacturers are producing. Shutter responsiveness is also rather slow and is not competitive with CSC offerings. Overall, I really like the G1X for its simple all in one portability and great image quality. However, improvements I would like to see would be the inclusion of an EVF with info display, quicker focus and shutter response, and a 24mm focal length at the wide end. That would make it a truly perfect grab and go camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Orchid Enthusiast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb step-up from Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The fold-out LCD Screen is very bright, clear, and so very convenient for shooting at odd angles. The size, shape, and weight are great for someone who prefers a smaller, lighter camera with great capability. This is a fantastic find either as a back-up for SLR, or as an almost-SLR. Image quality and ability to shoot in lower lighting conditions is superb. On the not so upside, the Auto Focus in Macro mode is not as easy to use as my PowerShot S50, surprisingly. At least, the manual focus is easier. Occasionally hitting the Macro focus button and have to re-select. On the more fussy end of my nitpicks: I had read that the front dial and shortcut buttons were user-assignable, but I&apos;m rather disappointed with the selections. If this is important to you, download the User Guide from Ca ... non and make certain that you read up. Wish the Zoom was a bit higher, but honestly, it&apos;s quite good.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is solidly built. The larger sensor enables low noise at much higher iso settings than typical point and shoot cameras. Although it will not fit in a shirt pocket it will fit comfortably in a large jacket pocket. The only annoying feature is the video record button sits very close to where you would normally rest your thumb. This causes inadvertent video recording. Canon needs to update it&apos;s software to deactivate the video record button.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wisching You the Very Best!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far, so good...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I replaced a G12 with the G1X on Friday. I&apos;ve taken about 100 comparison photos of a scene similar to my test shots of the G12. Different weather conditions but so far the images are well saturated, clean and seem to have much more shadow detail. It is bigger compared to the G12, mostly in thickness. The lens is really huge and closed sticks out a half inch. The lens cap is very good since it doesn&apos;t have a built in cover. It is very easy to handle. The body seems to be much better thought out as though they hired a Nikon guy to give them ergonomic pointers. The dedicated movie button is really handy and the controls are similar to G series cameras. The sound is bad, bad, bad. Really bad and there isn&apos;t a way to add an external mic. Lots of zoom noise from the lens. BIG DISAPPOINTMENT! ... However, the 24p setting gives a nice MOV video file which shouldn&apos;t be compared to a true HD camera but is easy to edit. RAW is not currently supported in Photoshop or ACDSee Pro. Zoom Browser is the only way to view the files. The CR2 vs. JPG thumbs seem to be very close in tonality and luminosity. Flash coverage seems about equal to the G12 although detail is better and noise is lower. I used it in the WP-DC44 underwater housing which is much bigger than the WP-DC34 for the G12. Buy a WW-DC1 Weight Set if you don&apos;t already own one. This camera will be difficult to keep submerged without ballast. Flash coverage with the new housing is better than it was with the G12 largely because the flash has an attached diffuser tunnel that focuses more light were you need it. Bottom Line: if you are used to the G10-G12 series, you will start running with this right out of the box. The files are huge compared to those (about 11-14 meg) when shooting at highest resolution. One cool feature is variable aspect ratio imaging. I tend to use the 24x36 aspect to keep my full frame and pocket camera (ha! definitely won&apos;t fit in your pocket!) images similar. You will probably like this camera a lot after you get used to the size.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gizmo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>OK, here&apos;s the deal with this camera. I shoot MMA Fighters full-time for a magazine. The G1X is my temporary backup camera &apos;til I get the Canon 1D X. My main camera is the 5D Mark II which will turn into my backup camera. I sold my old 5D to get the G1X. Now your probably saying What are you doing using a point-and-shoot for a backup camera? I&apos;ve found the image quality is on par with my old 5D and maybe a little better than the Canon 7D. It&apos;s got great high ISO rendering. I always wanted a compact camera for personal use and for times when I don&apos;t want to carry around my heavy camera bag. Like times when I go mountain biking. There is no other compact camera I could live with as far as image quality until this one. My biggest complaint is that it&apos;s so small that I don&apos;t have a very big ar ... ea to put my right thumb when holding the camera. Just takes a little getting used to. I love how the rear viewing screen flips out and flips around. This is my seventh Canon camera with my first back in 1985. The first G1X I ordered had a spot on the sensor, so I returned it to B and H and they sent out the replacement. I&apos;ve never had to send a camera back and the replacement I received seems to be just fine. So one faulty camera out of seven is not too bad. I bought the Lowepro 60 AW camera bag which fits like it was made for this camera. I can just strap this bag to my camelback shoulder strap and go mountain biking. When I want to take a shot, it&apos;s right there. I wouldn&apos;t want to use this camera as my permanent backup camera, but I believe I could get the job done with this camera if my 5D Mark II died on me during a photo shoot . . . which has never happened. Even when I get my permanent backup camera, this G1X is always going to be with me because a compact camera that delivers a quality RAW image is awesome!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Aviation Shooter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My Constant Companion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I hate being without a camera, but the bulk and weight of my DSLR is a bit much when not working. Not eager to surrender the benefits of shooting raw images, point &amp; shoots didn&apos;t made the grade, until I discovered the G1X. And it gives me HD video! It never leaves my side, and my wife is starting to get jealous.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rlsm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>not for me...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I returned my camera after trying it out for 10 days. The screen was difficult to see in daylight, the viewer is small and useless and the plastic parts are just not solid. The photographs were good but the macro feature was bad. For the money its not worth it. As a pro I thought this might be a great walk around light camera but I am now going with the another brand. Canon could have put a lot more work into this one and I&apos;m going to get the lumix.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GD the Farmer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My wife love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>(1) Great for people together in side and out side, photo quality are no big different with Canon 60D or 7D. (2) Easy use for less photo experince person. (3) Allow you feel good for camera size and color, I mean little pro. ... (4) Macro function is very bad, my wife&apos;s only complain.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kyle I</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big Image, Little Package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to be a compromise of my SLR and Point-and -shoot. I wanted a smaller camera that still shot RAW and maintained exceptional image quality. In the week that I&apos;ve used it, I&apos;ve been very impressed. The image quality is better than my older SLR and the video is awesome. My only complaint is that lack of zoom (longest focal length is 60mm) and the auto focus can be a bit inaccurate at times. But for a fixed lens it&apos;s pretty good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SkullCreekMedia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon G1X is a big disappointment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>First off don&apos;t believe all the expert reviews. I have read a lot of them over the past few months. I believe some of those writers at the review sites haven&apos;t even seen one. The G1X is supposedly geared to the more professional market as a backup and more portable and discreet camera with high quality images. With this in mind the operation will of course take some getting used to. I am a photojournalist working in some extreme conditions and this would theoretically be a great fit as I always have to have a camera with me. Upon opening the box, to my surprise and disappointment I found that this [$] camera does not come with an owners manual and we all have to occasionally refer to the manual. It comes with a CD to down load it so while you are dealing with extreme conditions with yo ... ur new G1X in your BDU side pocket or trying to be discreet you will have to carry your laptop with you for any questions and there are defiantly some. Trust me, just viewing you photos is a challenge in itself. Come on Canon not even an app.I am shooting in Raw which is why I bought this camera. It seems that many of the reviewers have obviously not taken any photos and tried to open them in PhotoShop (CS4) because it can&apos;t be done. So much for targeting the pro market. The only way to open them is to use Canon&apos;s Digital Photo Professional software. Here is the trick, You either have to download and install all the useless stuff on their CD to get a usable version of DPP (there is no custom installation) or in my case I went to Canon Service and Support site and downloaded an upgrade to the DPP version I already had and was using flawlessly with the Raw images form my 7D. The 7D Raw images open in Bridge and Photo Shop with no problem. You can open the G1X Raw images now with the upgrades DPP and do some very basic editing then using the batch processing, save them in tiff (80mb) to a file and then open them in bridge and Photo Shop to work on them which is a real pain but can be done. If you plan to travel with the G1X , don&apos;t plan on using just any coffee house computer etc. The main reason that I will be returning this thing, is that my wife loves to accompany me on location and while she can handle any situation that comes our way, she is not a photographer, but will shoot some great grab shots that I may miss as long as the camera is set to Auto (green) and I can cleanup or crop later as long as the info is there. So another important reason that I wanted this Camera is that I can hand it to my wife and off we go. Not exactly, the G1X will not shoot in Raw while set to auto or any scene modes. This camera is a total disappointment for the niche I hoped to fill . Nice design too. When you look through the viewfinder you see the barrel of the lens in the lower left corner.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>endoman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Terrible Macro and Autofocus poor.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I would only recommend this to a friend if they don&apos;t want to use its macro function or other fast or close up focus situations. I used the G10 first and then moved on to G12 and was very happy with both cameras (although G10 did give me a focus problem later in its life with complete motor failure with its zoom/focus drive)... but I was generally happy with having these models, especially the G12 where I was able to capture HD footage. When G1X came out I was very excited to get it because I wanted the Full HD capability as well as having a high quality point and shoot to capture macro shots of run of the mill products. The macro autofocus on this thing is simply horrible. I don&apos;t know why others don&apos;t have a problem but I&apos;ve used professional lighting then held an object at arm length di ... stance and moved it in and out and about at different distances and the focus failed on me 1 out of 2 times. That&apos;s terrible. I bought this because I didn&apos;t want to whip out my DSLR and Macro lens every time I want to shoot some stupid thing close by. The HD footage is good but again, for close ups, the focus is not good even in video. So, you&apos;ll have to see what you really will use the camera for. If you need it for close ups then it won&apos;t be that good. I had heard about this problem but frankly didn&apos;t believe it. It appears that in my experience, there&apos;s something is wrong with this camera that was not the case with G12 and G10. I don&apos;t know why... maybe the sensor size is screwing up the camera&apos;s focus.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>kelpman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera with some minor issues</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a fan of the G line of Canon cameras and really like the G1 X. I did find there was a small learning curve and have had to refer to the manual more than with the other G cameras. I&apos;m currently using the camera on a ski trip and still haven&apos;t gotten things dialed in. Although, I am asking it to do a wide range of tasks (action, scenic, closeup, balanced flash). I also keep running into little issues such as it&apos;s easy to accidentally turn the viewing screen off. Another feature that&apos;s irritating is the placement of the video record button. It&apos;s lies right under where my right thumb rests and it&apos;s very easy to accidentally start recording. However, all the small things aside, I think the G1 X a great travel camera and I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll use if for years to come.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>profesorromek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this camera - MUST HAVE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was amazed by this little camera. Initially i was expecting to be just a regular point and shoot camera, but it turn out that it was actually better than my Canon 50D + 24-70mm L F4 (I&apos;m not even mentioning the size difference). Low light performance (without a flash) is just outstanding , i can say outpacing my Canon 50D. The lens is very good and give you enough coverage for almost anything (FYI- F2.8). I was reluctant to spend that much money on a point and shoot (you can actually buy Canon rebel T2i with that price), but i can tell you its worth every penny. The biggest reason? - THE SIZE OF THE CAMERA. You can take this with you on vacation or anywhere else, shoot great pro DSLR quality photos, and yet it can fit in your pocket. So, buy this!, enjoy vacation without carrying DSRL ba ... g and camera + lens on your neck. FYI. My friend have Sony NEX (which supposed to be compact DSLR), and after seeing G1X, he is selling SONY and buying G1X...now that is something....
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>s2hrts</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>canon g1x</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Image Quality; Good Image Stabilization; Good in Low Light; Large Clear LCD; Nice Body Color; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Short Lag Time; Small / Compact; Great Zoom; Easy To Use

This is a great camera. I&apos;ve had it for about a month and it is exactly what I had been looking for – a camera I could travel with that has the performance of a DSLR and the size of a compact. OK, a large compact, but a compact nevertheless. It is the perfect complement to my 7D. I had been looking at the ILCs, but I didn&apos;t like two things about all of them: you&apos;d have to buy a second set of lenses and they are all too big with a lens attached to carry comfortably, and with the exception of the Sony, the sensors are too small. Also, I wanted an OVF. 
The IQ is beautiful and the glass is ju ... st what I expected from Canon. The photos are beautiful, sharp and highly detailed. In full auto mode the focus is pretty slow, but switch to P mode, get rid of the facial recognition and the focus speed is more than acceptable. Actually, it&apos;s quite good, not 7D good, but good. 
When I read reviews from others I often think that they forget that this is a point and shoot and not a pro DSLR. Easy to understand because the photos are so good, but remember this is not a DSLR, it just produces DSLR like photos. I don&apos;t shoot video, but the video I have shot just to try it out was excellent.
 This is a camera I can hand to my wife for her to use or I can pack to take on trips and have a high quality camera with me without the hassle of traveling with a large camera bag and lenses. The fact that it has both a pop-up flash and a hot shoe was another reason I liked this more than the ILCs. I use the camera in full manual mode almost 100% of the time. And that may be this cameras&apos; best feature – it can be used by beginners and pros alike and they will both be happy with it and the results the G1X produces. This is a perfect camera for a beginner who wants to advance their skills and not have to buy a different camera as their skill set grows. The G1X has a nice heft to it, fits the hand beautifully and has excellent build quality. 
On another note, this was the first time I&apos;ve ever bought anything from Adorama and I am extremely happy with the experience. Manny, the associate I dealt with, was knowledgeable, friendly and answered all of my questions. 
Bottom line – I am extremely happy with my G1X and I recommend it every chance I can.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Musicman5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>awesome images</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I try to carry a camera with me all the time. This camera replaces the G10 or 40D that I used to carry around. So the increased size of the G1 X was not a problem for me. The larger sensor and better ISO performance were what attracted me and they both deliver. Great images. The poor macro performance does not concern me either as I will not use this camera for that. The learning curve is kind of high for this camera. The lack of a printed manual is a big downer for me. When I get a new camera I carry the manual around with it for weeks until I have figured out how everything works but you can&apos;t do that with a PDF. It has steepened the learning curve, at least for me. But the images I can create with this camera justify the price of the G1 X and that is really the bottom line for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RedsockBluesock</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Everything I wanted in a camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I like to have a camera with me most of the time and this often means the camera has to be able to take some abuse. This camera is sturdy and solid. I&apos;m not worried about putting it in my backpack or jacket pocket without a case. I&apos;ve taken a couple hundred photos over the past few weeks and they are crisp with excellent color. I had the G9 and the controls and menu layout is almost the same so I was up and running in no time. I often shoot in manual with raw and the larger sensor really helps the overall quality of the final image. I really don&apos;t have anything bad to say about this camera except that it isn&apos;t small... You can&apos;t tuck this discretely in your shirt or pants pocket but that&apos;s where I put my (camera) phone and I didn&apos;t buy this camera for the size I bought it for its quality a ... nd capabilities. I feel I got what I paid for and more.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave in NC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon G1X - excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I just got back from a European trip where I used the G1X extensively. It more than surpassed my already high expectations. Color is very good, noise is very low (even to ISO 1600), and the Image Stabilization works great. I was able to take sharp, handheld images at 1/10 of a second. The camera is easy to operate and the rotating screen is very helpful for shooting at unusual angles. The G1X is noticably heavier than the G12, but this is OK given the quality of its images. I also used a 270EX for fill flash, and the camera metered the flash very well. Canon has a winner here in my opinion. I only wish the widest setting were somewhat wider, but that is really for DSLR&apos;s and super-wide lenses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>johnny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera at a good price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use the G1X for fine art/street photography. The ginormous sensor renders crisp detail overall. It does very well in low light. I love the wider range of f-stops than previouly available in the G-series. The shutter speed settings moved to the front of the body with a seperate wheel was a great idea. . Two drawbacks: 1. the macro setting isn&apos;t very macro; I like playing with macro from time-to-time but the G1X doesn&apos;t cut it there. 2. Adobe Raw doesn&apos;t recognize the Raw files so I&apos;m stuck using Canon&apos;s poor substitute software. . This is exactly what I&apos;ve been waiting for since I began shooting digital -- a high end camera with good glass, a good sensor, complete manual controls, about the size and weight of a 35mm film rangefinder and is affordable. . I definitely recommend the G1X. ... Bravo, Canon
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Watergirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect compact camera for me.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am an enthusiastic amateur photographer and wanted a walk about camera that primarily provided good images. Canon has always served me well with previous cameras and this G1 X is the best yet. It does not easily fit in my jacket pocket but that is ok with me. I read about some of the things that bothered others about this camera but I have not found problems. Image quality is extremely impressive - that was most important and I am thrilled not to have to carry around extra lenses to produce great shots. Love the HDR feature, HD video, and I have have good success with close-ups. Low light hand held shots impressive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photos by Joe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this thing!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera as a travel complement to my Canon EOS 7D, and I couldn&apos;t be more pleased with the image results. Image quality and compact size were my requirements, and the G1 X fits the bill perfectly. Focusing is fast and accurate, and the controls are intuitive for out-of-the-box shooting. I added a Canon Speedlite 270 EX II flash which I had originally thought would be useful on the 7D, but this compact flash is more appropriate for the G1 X.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hawk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I do a lot of photography. I have a 7D, G11, S100 and now the G1X. When shooting groups and lots of close-up couples I have to go to AUTO so it will automatically go to macro mode to get the shot. If I am in P it will miss focus because it doesn&apos;t focus close. Aside from that I love it. Bokeh is better than expected as is picture quality. I shot a lot of wet downtown night shots. Fabulous whether shot manual or auto or night mode. Some tripod and some hand held and all will look good in a 16X20 print. I shoot high ISO a bunch and I believe this is quite a bit better than my 7D even with the update on the 7D.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Matt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Rock solid, easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Putting a G1 X inside this case is about the cheapest way to get DSLR image quality in a wet environment. It&apos;s surprisingly solid, easy to install the camera, and all the camera&apos;s functions are accessible. I wasn&apos;t aware the manual controls would be accessible, but using the S button on the camera while using up/down and left/right direction controls allows you to change aperture and shutter speed in manual mode. Also, the Pelican 1450 isn&apos;t really the best fit for this case. The Pelican im2075 is a much better fit: a little taller and good gaps on the front, back, and sides. The 1450 is too big and barely gives the case any headroom. I&apos;m very glad I bought this case. I don&apos;t dive much, but this will be great in the rain, at the pool, or out sailing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big Disappointment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>What a hugh disappointment! The camera is heavier and bulkier than the previous G-series cameras. You might just as well buy a good SLR for this price if you&apos;re willing to carry around this much heft. Although it promises a lot of interesting new features, most of them only work if you&apos;re using JPEG, not RAW. It is also VERY confusing trying to figure out which features work under what circumstances, and since they no longer include a printed users guide you have to wade through a PDF on your computer to figure out under what circumstances the features you want to use will operate. It has a longer zoom lens, but you can&apos;t use it for getting in close, only for long distances. It has a new variation of RAW which Adobe doesn&apos;t currently support so you have go use their proprietary software f ... or decoding. It includes tons of gimmicky features for kids who think it would be neat to turn grandma blue, but major compromises for those who want to do serious photography. I wish Canon would realize that there are a lot of serious photographers out here who would like a small carry all the time camera and do need or want all the stupid tricks that they keep loading onto these cameras. I sent this one back.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shutterbug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon almost built a great camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Canon almost built a great camera with the Powershot G1X. Most of the features are very good except for the macro mode. I used both the automatic focus and the manuel focus and did not get clear images while in the macro mode. I would recommend this camera to anyone who is not concerned about taking macro photos. As for me, I will wait until Canon is able to correct this flaw in future models. At that point I will own the G2X or the G3X.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Little Person</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It is a great camera when you don&apos;t feel like carrying around a DSLR. The pictures have amazing qualities. It is great for a light, fun day out. The only thing that I didn&apos;t really like is the battery life. Other than that this is a really good camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dig6</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty Sweet</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have had a PS G10 &amp; I liked it. So I thought I would try this. It is a bit bigger but I love the hand hold on it. Picture quality is good. The macro on it is a little bit disappointing. I mainly got this to carry around instead of my big dslrs. I ordered the water case for it so I am pretty excited about that. The video quality is nice!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>La Photog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon G1X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Very unhappy with the JPEG file size - seems to max out at 2-3 MP. That&apos;s pretty weak for a 14 MP camera. For me RAW has always been a storage and a workflow hassle. My G10 puts out 6-7 MP in the super Fine JPEG mode . It seems Canon got rid of this mode 2-3 years ago. I do a lot of post processing, and the more MP I have to work with (without going to RAW) the better. 6-7 MP for the G10 seemed to be a good solution. Also when I went to download the RAW converter from Photoshop, that was a hassle. Even though the web site said it covered the G1X, it didn&apos;t. After a few futile attempts to download and reload, it seem that the info was wrong and that the current Beta version does have the correct converter. The software that Canon provided (Zoom browser), I didn&apos;t bother loading. Fo ... r the G10, it was lame, and I never used it. Viewfinder was useless - didn&apos;t frame correctly and part of the frame is obscured. Lens cap is a nuisance. On the plus side when I did a side by side comparison with the G10 : at 100 ISO - very much the same at 400 ISO , G1X is better at 800 ISO G10 is useless - G1X looks great at 1600 ISO G1X still looks really good
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ray the photo bug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>G1 X is in a class all by itself</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>AWB is superior to my old back-up, the G-11. It gets excellent low light pictures even when the ISO is at 1600. As a rule I always shoot in P mode with my G-11, never in auto mode: however, with the G1-X, I still rely heavily on P mode, but have found that in Many instances, the Auto mode does a great job. Extremely pleased with the G1-X and heartily recommend it to everyone - great pro back up camera. Cons .. it only has a 4X telephoto. Overall, it is an excellent camera for the Buck and that larger sensor is superb. The movies I shot with it are great. Another Con: to big to carry in trouser pocket. Thanks Canon</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>johnh.ivanhoe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Top of the heap.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This little camera is a huge leap forward, and combines all the features I have been hoping for some time! Solid build, high res swing-out monitor,all new f2.8 lens,APS (almost) sensor,14 bit RAW, and Full HD video, and new Digic 5 processor all make for fantastic image quality. The in-camera HDR works well in contrasty lighting. Battery life is excellent, and the weight won&apos;t give you fallen arches. The FA-DC58C filter holder is a flimsy piece of junk, and the camera seems to have lost a bit of it&apos;s macro capability from previous models, but a close-up filter can help a bit. I hope add-on converter lenses become available, as with previous models.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>John</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>World&apos;s best compact camera?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to pull out when I didn&apos;t feel like loading up my EOS 1DS Mk iii with the right lens. I am shocked at how close it comes to the image quality of $10,000 worth of EOS and lens. It is so close, that I have stopped after I made a test shot with the Powershot. It is probably the best compact camera in history for non-moving subjects. Incredible image quality. Good dynamic range, auto bracketing, full manual mode, operates similar to EOS. Uses EOS flash accessories. Shoots raw. I don&apos;t use JPG or vidoe so can&apos;t comment. The built-in flash is adequate for outdoor fill flash so long as you cut it back a stop or so. This is an expensive camera for many and has limitations (not fast enough for sports or kids) but it is my favorite causal camera ever.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I Like it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My main camera is a Canon 1DsMarkIII which takes great images. The G1X is the 3rd Point and Shoot type of camera I have tried. I wanted one for those times I did not want to carry my 1Ds. The other two cameras, Canon G12 and Fugifilm X100 had awful image quality. The G1X has very good image quality which is the main asset I wanted in a Point and Shoot. I shoot only in RAW and these images combined with the new adjustments in the LR4 Develop Module keep me happy. There are of course things that I do not care for, but there is always a compromise to be made. Great: Image quality Fully manual or auto Size, not too small and not too big Can use my Canon flash High ISO is very good Not so great: Focusing time Battery life View finder (I hate holding a camera at arms length to take a pho ... to.) Lens cap could be one third the thickness so it would fit in a pocket easier. f/2.8 available through complete zoom range. Again for me the main thing I wanted was good image quality, I can work with the other short comings and this camera has good image quality.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DDB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, lacking DOF/flash features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I tried this camera out for a few days, but I ended up returning it because it didn&apos;t meet my needs. I didn&apos;t find a review that spoke to the features that I was interested in, so I&apos;m going to provide a few comments here. First, if you&apos;re looking for a high-end compact camera, this is a great choice. The G1X takes nice images and is well built. I was looking for a specific set of features (which it ended up not being able to fulfill) so I returned it. 1. The hotshoe doesn&apos;t work with the PocketWizard FlexTT5. Perhaps PW will address this with a future upgrade, but I couldn&apos;t even get basic functionality out of this combination. I do a lot of work with flash, and I was interested in a Canon compact that would allow me to work with PW&apos;s without having to bring a 5D. So far, this isn&apos;t it. ... 2. The depth of field control is more substantial than previous G-series cameras, but the depth control across the zoom range isn&apos;t anywhere close to an SLR. I realize that SLRs have larger image sensors, so it&apos;s not a fair comparison. However, for the G1X, the size of the maximum aperture quickly decreases across the zoom range, so the lens is at least f/4 at a 50mm focal length (35mm equivalent). (Don&apos;t quote me on that exact relationship, but the max aperture gets considerably smaller as you start zooming the lens.) As a result, it was really hard to blow the backgrounds out of focus. (I realize the Fuji X100 has a smaller sensor, but I found the X100 to have a shallower depth of field than the G1X at the equivalent focal length.) As a final comment, the AF is still similar to previous G1 series. It&apos;s sufficient for landscapes and adults, but there is absolutely no way it&apos;s going to keep up with small kids. I realize the compacts use a different AF detection scheme that SLR&apos;s, but the AF speed on the G1X isn&apos;t much different from the G10 or 11. Anyway, these are my quick comments. If I were looking for a compact camera, I wouldn&apos;t hesitate in buying one of these. However, I was looking for something portable that would work with my PocketWizards and/or a allow a shallow depth of field. The G1X has neither so I returned it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ted</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>G1X - image quality is it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>First, the service at B &amp; H is absolutely the best. The camera itself has some quirks - lousy viewfinder, lousy macro mode, less than state of the art autofocus. But if you&apos;re looking for DSLR-like image quality in a Canon G series camera, the G1X is for you. I can put up with the annoyances when a camera puts out the IQ this one does. I love the swivel LCD, the great auto white balance, the great high ISO performance and the general feel (very similar to the other Canon G series cameras) as well as the image quality, and the camera is very adjustable. I use it for mostly nature/outdoor/landscape stuff when I don&apos;t want to lug around my big camera and for this, it&apos;s just fabulous.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Varago</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not for everyone but</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>If you want GREAT IQ this is it. MY G1X came in on 2-9-2012 and have taken over 1000 pics with it. If you want a FAST camera then its not for you, the focus is not fast but it does the job, I would not call it slow. Shot to shot is slow and dont even talk about macro. I have a 7D for speed and macro but the funny thing is the G1X has as good if not better IQ at high iso it really is that good. The 4 stars and not 5 is for the speed of focus and MFD. I do weddings and portraits and this is now my backup camera to my 7D. Its far from perfect but the reason for a camera is the picture and for this its very very good. The video is good and it will focus while in video mode, you can also zoom in video and its nearly silent. I use raw with my 7D but I am finding that may not be needed with the ... G1X the jpg&apos;s out of the camera are as good as I can get with LR4. Dave
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>BEST CAMERA EVER!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am just a weekend/vacation photographer of my friends and family. The pictures taken with this camera are beautiful in color and clarity. I really like that it takes good pictures without using a flash even in shaded areas. It is easy for me to use! My only complaint is that it is heavier than my point and shoot digital camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fastfwd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Impressed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have used the G6/G12 and like to carry them in a belt bag while riding my motorcycle to get landscapes with the bike which is the primary reason for sticking with a Powershot Series. I&apos;m not really financially in a position to buy the glass for a DSLR either quite frankly. I am pretty pleased so far with the trade up to the G1X. The layout of controls and menus are very familiar making it easy for me to just pick up and start using for the most part. I&apos;m still experimenting with it, but have already taken a few shots that I think really justify the upgrade. The level of detail is just amazing! I&apos;ve been testing it out with low light subjects and pulled off some pretty amazingly sharp handheld shots too with low ISO. I&apos;m guessing the image stabilization might have contributed to t ... hat ??? it was turned on. I haven&apos;t really even needed to rely on the higher ISO quality for quicker shutter speeds yet, but I&apos;m sure that will be very handy at concerts, etc. with moving subjects. If I were to critique it I might confirm that the battery life is less than my previous G Series. Although, after turning off a few options and turning down the lcd brightness I did squeeze out about 175 individual shots (jpeg + RAW creating two files for each). I didn&apos;t even look at the battery level, but it was still going strong. I&apos;ll have to pick up some extras. It is just slightly larger than my G12 and it feels great in my hands, but I am still searching for a bag that will be less bulky like the one that I carried my G6/12 in. I may get the lens hood for it and just use the bulkier new bag possibly.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good at what it&apos;s designed for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Clearly not a replacement for a DSLR but as a travel solution to avoid taking all your gear it&apos;s great. As it&apos;s been already said, some limitations but overall I like it. The flip screen is actually useful sometimes to shoot holding the camera low or high, the DOF wide open over the whole range is nice, good for most situations, not really small like the 100mm @ f2.8 would be. The lens is very sharp in my tests. The auto HDR works, only on JPEG, but comparing RAW adjusted in CS5 and JPEG, the JPEGs are 90% spot on, due to latest DIGIC 5 Image Processor I presume. Noise at high ISO minimal (up to 1000).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VIDCON</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>VIDEO (RAW-NO EFFECTS) canon G1X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>here is a video I shot walking around with the G1X handheld entire time (raw). This camera is NOT the 5D or 7D etc. But bang for the buck (features, HD video, Photos, IS, ISO, quality) it&apos;s realy quite nice and fun to own. I&apos;ve now had for 4 months and still like alot. :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>David</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Confused on G1X Reviews</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I have been shooting a 5D and 5D MK II since each of them came out and was getting tired of lugging around the whole kit when on a travel holiday. So I purchased a G1X with high hopes. I chose to want to believe the rave reviews by pros and semi-pros and ignore some of the complaints about the AF system. As a loyal Canon user, I hoped for the best. Fortunately the G1X was not available in time for my trip, so that I took the 5D MK II and got wonderful photos. I have specific complaints about the camera after taking about 100 shots. 1. The AF seems sadly out of whack. Even after I figured it out, it was hard to get a correctly focused shot. 2. The close focusing distance is not good. 3. The so-called manual focus isn&apos;t really manual. It still relies on using buttons to operate. 4. Althoug ... h the time delay between focusing and shooting is low for a point and shoot, it still is disconcertingly long. 5. Placement of so many buttons on the back of the camera in close proximity to one another caused me to be continually hitting the menu and various other functions accidently. Not a good thing. I would really like to know why highly competent photographers like the camera so much. I know others have similar complaints to mine. Are pros able to make the AF system work better?
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>no</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The perfect camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am 78 yrs old. Years ago I had 4x5 and 8x10 view cameras and my bag was about 70 lbs! Later I got digitals and lenses and the bag was 10 lbs - ponds which started to be heavier and heavier each year... Last month I met a pro photographer in Washington DC who said he has found the perfect camera. Afer some test I bought the G1X. Is it perfect? For me it is. I travel and photagraph a lot. The G1X has everything I need : all the controls, a nice zoom, and above all a superb quality of images (color balance, crisp images which can be printed up to 24 x 16). The body of the camera fits very well in my hand. For people interested in video, the G1X is outstanding. I only regret that the lens does not have a slightly wider opening (say 24 instead of 28) and finally the eye viewfinder is very ba ... d. . Highly recommended!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GSZ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best bridge I could think of</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It is very complete, no thrills and easy to use camera that offers excellent value return, little if ever noise, excellent color separation and excellent aspheric lens. The sensor if quick and adjusts perfectly to light change. Good video and a screen that tilts, adding to the ease of use in special shooting conditions.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnny G.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect....for me!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this as my carry-around camera and although it has some weaknesses, the superior image quality from the large sensor far outweighs any shortcomings. Canon nailed this one as far as I&apos;m concerned...I don&apos;t want to mess with interchangeable lenses. The biggest draw-back for me is the lack of close focus in the Macro mode, however, the image resolution is so high that I can get superior results by cropping. Great in low available light, too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big EZ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Best Point and Shoot Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is the first point and shoot camera I have owned and I was waiting to buy one that gave me the same quality images that I got using my DSLR cameras. I shoot all the time and almost every where I go and I needed a smaller camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BillFe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lightweight alternative to the DSLR</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s small, with great image quality, unobtrusive for street shooting, my favorite activity. The G1X is worth the price. I shoot at the wide end (28mm equiv) In a future update I&apos;d like to see a 20mm or 24mm equiv. at the wide end. I can live happily without the tele.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brian J</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Secret weapon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>replacing my G11. Nice image quality in a pinch. I carry this in my waist pack when I&apos;m carrying long lenses on my main camera. If I need a wider shot in a hurry, this is always ready faster than switching lenses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Aurelius</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High expactations, mixed results</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I was very excited when hearing about G1X launch - I was looking for a relatively compact backup to avoid carrying my 5D/7D on every business trip. I bought it as soon as I found it in retail and after 1st hour of playing with it I was puzzled. The sensor provides really great IQ, with little noise and very crisp output also in JPEG. But the way it feels in operation is a letdown. I still have in a drawer my first digital camera - a 11 years old Powershot G2. The G1X after 11 years feels as fast as the G2. Do I need to say anything else? It is a real pity, becoause this camera could have been THE backup for SLR. Regretfully it cannot be.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chris</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have owned a number of G series cameras including the G12, and the G1X surpasses them all. Beautiful photos, loads of creative control, all in a compact package. I also own a 60D and the quality of the G1X images is very close to SLR. I agree with some reviewers who say that performance and macro may be lacking, but if you are looking for a compact and portable camera that takes outstanding pictures, grab the G1X. I love this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ElyRocks</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the serious &apos;prosumer&apos;!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large sensor in point-and-shoot (fabulous low light work!)

Cons: Cost

Great camera but ONLY for someone who a) knows how to use the array of manual controls to control your image, and b) will only use &apos;P&apos; &lt;.01% of the time they&apos;re shooting. If you don&apos;t fit those criteria, save yourself a bunch of $$$$ and get a simple point-and-shoot. If you want near the performance of an SLR in a point-and-shoot body this is the camera for you. A few nits, but no show-stoppers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Worldly Travel Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A good holiday/vacation camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Small size relative to an SLR yet takes practically the same quality of photos. It&apos;s easy to operate but if you&apos;re looking for zoom then unfortunately this doesn&apos;t have much of it...only 4X optical.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jammin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The camera I have been waiting for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have worked in Glacier National Park and now I work in the Bob Marshall Wilderness Complex as a fire lookout and have helped out with numberous wildlife studies and this camera suits me perfectly. The camera is light-weight, easy to use and takes great pictures of landscape and wildlife.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pete</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good product worth the cost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The adapter fits snugly onto the G1X. My circular polarizing filter screws firmly into the adapter. I have taken about a thousand photos and videos in New Hampshire&apos;s White Mountains and whale watching out of Plymouth, MA with excellent results in that the polarizer works as expected and there is no looseness or play in the adapter. The combination of adapter and polarizer on the camera fits perfectly into the leather case sold separately. One cannot use the lens cap that came with the camera once you attach the adapter, which is no problem as the case protects the front filter and I no longer have the bother of fiddling with the lens cap. I keep a cleaning cloth in my back pocket when shooting and clean any dust particles from the filter as required.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bullfrog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The almost great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Canon started to make a great camera with many great features. They fell short of this goal with the G1X. The focing in macro mode (both automatic and manuel) is difficult to produce a clear image. Over-all I was happy with this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brandy k</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Auto focus for close ups is louzy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to replace my g11. I use it to take photos for my companies catalog. It is useless at close range. I really just thought my camera was broken but turns out it isnt. I have the canon s100 as well, its much smaller, and honestly takes better photos, also has a very cool slow motion movie effect that the G1x doesnt have</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ryman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Camera is AWESOME!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>AGREE, DO NOT listen to the NAYSAYERS. I love the 5DMII, I love the 7D..and the G11 (gives average photo&apos;s). I shoot mostly Video, but like to rip off a few pics now and then when the mood is right. And this new g1x doesn&apos;t dissapoint. NO, it lacks in a few area&apos;s. But geez, for [$]! It&apos;s a bargain. My video looks crisp. Pics look so great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mac the Photog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The package I&apos;ve been looking for!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use it when I&apos;m traveling light (much of the time), but want photo quality equivalent to my DSLR. Things I really like: small size, weight excellent low light level performance useful eye level finder for action shots well selected zoom range great optics excellent video performance when needed a full spectrum from auto to manual operation Not so great: I wish the macro capabilities weren&apos;t quite as limited. However, I have yet to actually miss a photo because of the macro limits.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>PowerShot G1 X Digital Camera by Canon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is for personal of home use. It take high quality of photos andf is easy to carry. The photos are great, but videos are so so. It is not priamrily a video camera anyhow. It is also pricy of course.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great sturdy travel camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera for four reasons: (1) Great image quality (2) backup for my dSLR&apos;s (3) sturdy build (4) travel when the dSLR&apos;s are just too heavy. Also, I like it much better than my G12 as it has more projection on the hand grip, which the G12 lacks and is hard for me to hold steady. I also find the G1X OVF very useful in bright mid-day light which can often blank-out viewing the subject using the LCD. I usually avoid using digital zooms, but I am astonished at the image quality when using the tele-converter or digital zoom on the G1X. It also has a much better control wheel on the back than does the G12, as the G1X control wheel has a study feel and projects out from the central func/set button, making it easy to use. Even though I own the G12 and SX40, I still found a l ... earning curve with the GX1, and much that is not mentioned or discussed in the manual. Owning and having used the G12 and SX40 has been helpful in this regard. Overall the G1X is a great camera that is well made, easy to hold steady and has amazing image stabilization and image quality. I highly recommend it !
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>limin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great image quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Have only used this camera briefly but I can tell the image quality is wonderful. I will enjoy having this camera with me when I&apos;m not carrying my DSLR and even when I am. It will allow me to take some panoramic shots when I have a telephoto on my main camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Leica S2 Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Elegant Design, Power Features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Although I just received the camera, I have begun using it regularly; I shoot about 8,000 images a year across equipment. The G1-X is about the perfect point and shooter for the advanced amateur or working pro who does not want to carry around DSLRs every moment. I use Leica S2 equipment. The G1-X is elegantly designed, of quality construction, and creates images even better than those from the G12. The controls are logically placed, the viewfinder and flexible LCD screen accurate, and the fit and form very good in my hands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Willie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Home Run</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Unlike so many of the flimsy difficult to manage tiny cameras out there, this one is build solid and a pleasure to shoot with. For me, and I expect for many others, the joy of using a well constructed camera is as close to important as the actual pictures. But don&apos;t fret, the picture quality will blow you away. The color saturation and sharpness are indistinguishable from those taken on my D300S, and the movie button allows me to catch kid moments that were previously lost while fiddling with buttons/menus. This is a perfect camera for those who want an old school beautifully built machine with film like quality -- all in a portable package that won&apos;t disappoint.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Snappy Dad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Rekindling the joy of photography</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>5 years ago, about when my first child was born, I got into photography with a Canon G9. I have since bought two DSLRs but I&apos;ve missed the grab and go portability of the G series. I just got my G1X last week and have really enjoyed the combination of compactness and impressive image quality. I&apos;d been dreading the shutter lag/poor auto-focus (especially after reading the early reviews) but was pleasantly surprised that I could still take sharp pictures of my extremely mobile kids. Center focus + servo/continuous AF was perfectly usable. Some things I did wish the G1X had: -- Back button focus -- Optical or electronic viewfinder with focus point confirmation Otherwise, the G1X is just a perfect camera for traveling or spontaneous shooting.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GRAYGHOST</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT RESOLUTION AND PHOTOS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>THIS CAMERA WILL BE MY CARRY CAMERA WHEN A DSLR IS TOO LARGE OR HEAVY ETC . COMPARED TO THE D200 NIKON, PICS AT 1600 ARE MUCH BETTER. THE RESOLUTION IS EXCELLENT ON JPEGS AND RAW (CS5)FILES. IN MY SHORT TIME TO USE IT THE CONS ARE:LIMITED AREA TO GRIP WITH RIGHT HAND BUT MUCH BETTER THAN MY OLD G11: SO FAR SOME JPEGS SEEM 1 STOP OVEREXPOSED--EASY TO FIX. OVERALL, HAPPY WITH SIZE, FUNCTION, PICS, WEIGHT ETC.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>deLeonStrong</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The jury is still out but so far so good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>PowerShot G1 X Digital Camera by Canon has it issues with performance as you must have read about already. What do you expect with a 1st version of product in a new category? If you look past some if the flaws, the camera produces some quality photos. I have ONLY used this camera for stills since some of its pre-mentioned and reviewed flaws. So far I have been happy with the results. That said, for what it is, the price is too steep but I needed a quality camera with a point and shoot size for under $1000 and this seemed to be the best of the worst options.I have many Canon products and I have been happy with all. I would recommend this camera to the above average photographer but if you can wait, hold out for the 1st revision in this category.Nice Durable &amp; Easy to use Product!Rec ... ommend = Yes.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alexander</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The good idea but quality not</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>So Canon again made lens without UV filter on board and we need to use external filter holders... This is sad. I bought this adapter and i was in hope that will be solid metal but unfortunately this is weak plastic. And not strong at all. So be careful with this adapter. This is not the same quality like G1X camera...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dolph</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fine addition to the Canon line up</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a wonderful camera for the times when using your full sized DSLR just isn&apos;t practical, and without sacrificing many of the features you&apos;re accustomed to from it&apos;s bigger brothers. It&apos;s loaded with all of the great features that you&apos;ve come to love from the G Series.In my opinion, the full sized sensor is the biggest plus with the G1X. That being said, the one big disappointment is the cameras inability to get in real close with the macro feature. Something I used often with my G9, but I&apos;ll get over it. Throw the G1X in your backpack and you&apos;ll have a nice back up camera that can get some quality images.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>atort</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice try!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I just received this camera today and have been an extremely loyal avid user of the G9, G10, G11, and G12 series cameras to the point of having two G10&apos;s and two G12&apos;s still. This is a creative camera for me and largely a macro tool that I use while out and about and this G1X&apos;s macro ability is rubbish! It has a range of 7.9 in. as opposed to the 0.4 in. of the G12...seriously I&apos;m dumbfounded to what Canon was thinking when making this enormous leap?!? Surely they had to know the macro ability of these Powershot G series cameras were a BIG part of why so many loved them. Truly disappointed and just saved me $1000.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>humrick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Nice!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Th G1X is definitely not for everyone. But if you desire highest quality image from a carry-around camera, this is it. Image is phenomenal, I have shot ISO up to 3200 with minor PS noise cleanup. Past 1600, no PS needed at all. My other cameras are 5DMk2 and 7D but cannot lug them around all the time. This fills in perfectly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spaceman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect companion to my EOS-1D MarkIII</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this camera as a companion to my full size Canon DSLR, but also as a replacement for it when I want great images and features without all the size and weight. It does use its battery quicker than my G10, so I recommend getting a spare when you buy the camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>banknote</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best P&amp;S out there</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Bought for the wife to replace a G12 - with the new lens and larger sensor this camera takes very good pictures and the video is quite good - however the hot shoe design is defective in that if you use an external speed light it disables the internal pop up flash function (disables in menu - small micro switch in hot shoe sticks - use tooth pick to free) if you own a EOS 5D Mkii you will notice this camera doesn&apos;t come close in picture or video performance but then what can you expect from it&apos;s design and price point. When you consider the alternatives like the Sony NEX7 that over heats taking video and the NX210 that takes superior pictures (larger sensor) but very poor video this is the P&amp;S compact camera to have at this point in time because while it&apos;s slow to respond (focus and wri ... ting to disc) it simply works well for pictures and video.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>frankc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Looks, protects and fits great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I prefer using the glass protectors as they resist scratches much better than the plastic ones. Note that this protector attaches to the bezel around the LCD screen, not directly to it (leaving a slight gap between the protector and the LCD). At first I thought it would be better to have the glass cut a little smaller so that it would fit inside the bezel directly to the LCD to avoid any issue with the LCD latching shut when turned facing the camera and closed (due to the extra thickness), but then realized that doing so would make it very difficult to remove later on if necessary. Also, I&apos;m glad to say that the LCD does latch shut when closed facing the camera - something that my G12 would not do with a similar protector.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Little Dog Photos</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect fit for the G1 easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Be sure to read instructions and prep the gasket. I was surprised how well and easy to use it was. If traveling on a plane store unlocked as the change in cabin pressure will make it hard to open if the case is locked closed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bearington</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>superb camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The Canon G1X is easy to use, professional quality, and captures amazing events and landscapes superbly. I used the camera while traveling through France and captured part of the Tour de France. The speed and digital resolution produced fine quality photos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RobW</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Companion Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My G1X is second camera (to 7D), replacing my G10, which in turn replaced G7. Image quality is outstanding. On a 10-day trip recently with both 7D and G1X I, much to my surprise, found the choice between images from each camera surprisingly difficult. Very low noise and excellent color performance. I can understand some of the comments re start-up time and focus performance is slightly below what I would have hoped, but for me these are minor compromises in the performance of an excellent camera. Don&apos;t really understand review comments re battery performance, as I&apos;ve not been able to stress it so far, and I&apos;m a self-confessed hog who then has to spend far too many hours sorting through the results. VIdeo performance is stunning. I loaned my wife the camera to try HD Video while i was using ... the 7D to capture stills, while our daughters were zip lining in rainforest area. Results were impressive, with the video image quality and stabilization outstanding. Very flexible camera in a small package and a very worthwhile upgrade from the G10. I see a few niggles reported, and a few I agree with, though I&apos;d certainly buy it again as-is. Of course, if Canon are able to deal with them via firmware in the same way as the firmware upgrade about to be released for my 7D, then I&apos;ll be a delighted owner indeed!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Don</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>By My Side</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>No, I&apos;m no going to use this to cover sports, music or major news events. That&apos;s what my DSLR&apos;s are for. But it&apos;s great to have a high-quality image from a camera that I can live with at other times. I like having a viewfinder but wish it was a little larger. Quicker shutter response and focusing speed would be nice. Otherwise, it&apos;s exactly what I wanted.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sunny62</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great take a long when DSL is too much</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a good choice for someone who is used to high quality images, but needs a smaller than DSL to take along. RAW-not much more needed to be said. If your shooting micro, bring your DSL-not this.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Imagetree</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It works</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I got the filter adapter so I can use my 58mm close-up lenses and polarizer. It was a quick twist to put on and the lenses work fine. I think for what it is, this adapter should have been included with the camera and not be an expensive add on. If you have a G1X, and want to use a polarizer or other types of filters, this is a only good way to do it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>save your money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Lens hood is poorly designed, its fine when shooting but when you want to reverse it when the camera is not being used, it must be removed as it will not fit over the lens barrel.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Muckle John</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Flimsy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>You&apos;d think that Canon&apos;s accessories would be the best, but you&apos;re better off buying after market. Their adaptor rings for all of the G-series are made of cast plastic, never fit snuggly onto the camera and easily accidentally unlock. This one is no exception. For such poor quality, you&apos;d expect them to charge less.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Javier</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon vaporware?</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve gone from the 350D to the 5D MKII. But for a recent strictly tourist trip to Paris with my wife I chose to travel light, so I bought the G1X. The G1X is a FANTASTIC camera.But as for any street-outdoors good photographic endeavor, it needs a polarising filter. And this is where Canon drop-to-drop accessories availability policies are unacceptable: to attach a polarising filter to the G1X you need this Out of Stock thing. And it is not available with B&amp;H only, I searched all photo stores in Paris and I couldn&apos;t find it.So there&apos;s when a $ otherwise remakable machine fails, because it lacks a cheapo plastic accesory.As ever, Canon cannot do it absolutely right.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JohnL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Does the job</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>This accessory is needed to mount 58mm filters and items such as close-up adapters on the G1X. It does its job with those attachments, but I am not sure about its longevity - it appears to be made of plastic. I have tried it also with a Canon 0.7x wideangle attachment, which is considerably heavier than a filter, and it still works, but appears to flex very slightly under the weight.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hoff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great lens protection</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After scratching the lens on my G9, I was really happy to see this adapter on the G1X. I already had an assortment of 58mm filters making this camera even more versatile.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Laurence</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice addition to a DSLR.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Image Stabilization; Easy To Use; Large Clear LCD; Small / Compact; Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Good Image Quality; Short Lag Time; Nice Body Color

This is a good addition to a DSLR and not replace one especially during times that having a full sized DSLR isn&apos;t practical or not allowed e.g. in certain venues like concerts, museums or dining out, etc.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>planthi80</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I was expecting more from Canon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>General work...either it was hunting or slow to get in focus. pointless viewfinder and short battery life. Otherwise great build quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CLEVELAND CLICK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>G1X BLOWS HIGHLIGHTS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Lag / Shutter Delay; Short Battery Life

CAN&apos;T BELIEVE CANON WOULD LET THIS GO TO MARKET.
OTHER COLOR PROBLEMS AND WHIT BA.L</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Skycam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>user unfriendly</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Protects body but is not easy to access camera functions while attached. A transit case only not user friendly while attached.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>angelo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great small camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I gave this camera as a gift to my brother for his wedding. he really enjoy it. Very nice camera, with a lot of great functions in a small pack.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gilikas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>macros and battery life is bad...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>As the camera is very good quality overall. However, the macro feature, and the battery life is very very bad.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>QfromCali</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great camera! Tons of features. Beautiful pictures. Bought this camera to take along when my 60D is just too big.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mel Taff</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Buy.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>New camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am very happy with the new Canon G1X. It has all of the feature I have been looking for in a point shoot camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gold</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Images</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Nice layout ,Sharp lens. Good image Quality</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photo Doc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use it when I don&apos;t want to carry my 5D Sharp photos,excellent colors.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JoeRoth</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding follow-on to G12</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great point and shoot camera. Big, bright LCD screen.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>photobill</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent camera !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The picture quality is great , but sometime the focus is a hit and miss .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Thebighumm</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Canon G1X - its a yes from me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Yes go ahead and buy one, if you need DSLR features in a compact package and don&apos;t want to pay excess luggage on the flights.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zockmister</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My wife and I are first time camera buyers. This product really has been simple and easy to use. We are incredibly impressed with the picture quality as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tin can</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>cannon G1x</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>takes good picture</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MKSutton</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Another Canon Winner, The PowerShot G1 X</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Outstanding new addition to the PowerShot line. Great resolution! The new big sesnor produces outstanding images! Canon Rules!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cush</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple, easy, and well built!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been using Aquatech cases for my SLR&apos;s and now I&apos;ve changed to this. It is super easy to utilize all the functions of the G1X.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tod</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb image quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Image quality has been improved---great deal of manual flexibility---superbly built.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>prosumer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>finally, everthing in one small package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>awesome picture quality and unbeatable low light/high iso performance!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>wolfyfoto</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Big enough that it&apos;s easy to use but not so big that I don&apos;t wanna carry it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tony</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Made by Canon</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Works well</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mdenhof</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Glass LCD Screen Protector for Canon G1x</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Quality seems fine. So far so good. One of the 4 edges has little surface area to grip to, based on the shape and fit. But it still grabs and is holding.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Norman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>True Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: - Great support for the camera - Ultra lightweight Cons: - Too many buttons to unbotton before operating the camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Benjidog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Handy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Handy. Easy to carry in camera bag. Info at your finger tips.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Frankm6</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Hope it does its&apos; job</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If it keeps the scratches off I&apos;m happy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fotonomad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Overpriced and cheaply made</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Why is this a $30 accessory instead of a standard item included with an expensive camera? Canon got greedy - and it&apos;s not even well designed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simple attachment for added impact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Adapter works great for the addition of a UV or Polarizer filter.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ahmed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent experience</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Unique product in terms of quality and performance Recommend to buy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>virgilet47</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s very a pro-product. I am very satisfied with this product</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PDG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great quality in a small camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is the back up camera that i have waited for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Canon PowerShot G1 X 14.3 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4544704004186079471/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.13&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=s4-RUIbNEKOM2gWR-IGgCQ&amp;ved=0CKMCEPQCMAc4Hg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ojo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>computeruniverse.net</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Kaufempfehlung</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Another &quot;new&quot; :) qualitatively modified G12.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

