<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica D-Lux 5 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very good image quality, stylish design, full manual controls

Cons: Pricier than most compact cameras, no viewfinder

The Leica D-Lux 5 is an expensive compact digital camera that reviewers say is a good choice for enthusiasts and serious photographers who don&apos;t mind paying more for the Leica brand. The 10.1-megapixel camera includes a 3.8x optical zoom and plenty of manual controls to suit discerning photographers. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cowboy Bob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The One to Buy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a semi-professional photographer who needs a good quality, small camera to use for scouting or when hiking. I first bought the Leica V-Lux 30 because it has a long zoom and lots of bells and whistles. After one day, I returned it, since it&apos;s basically an expensive toy. I spent the extra $50 for this baby. And I&apos;m glad I did. First, keep in mind that it&apos;s a point and shoot. It cannot compete with my Canon 5D MII and L glass for long shots or very soft bokeh/DOF. You can&apos;t get narrow DOF with a lens this small and relatively wide angle of view. It&apos;s also a zoom, so DOF increases as you rack it out. That being said, color rendition and sharpness are amazing for this type of camera. There&apos;s a nice warmth to the shots as well, with very nice skin tones. I haven&apos;t noticed much of any shut ... ter lag, either. I shoot in RAW, but there are plenty of creative options if you shoot JPEG. Be sure to upgrade to Firmware 2.0, as the difference in AF and options vs. 1.0 is sizeable. Finally, I can&apos;t put this baby down. It feels great to handle. Solid and sturdy, yet not heavy. I also bought the Lumix version of the EVF. Same as the Leica for about half the price. Invaluable here in Colorado, since the combination of bright sun and my eyeglasses makes using the LCD screen basically impossible half the time.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>5 out of 6 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>The traveller</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best P&amp;S for maximum creative control</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Here goes my first review of any product ever :)I bought this camera about 3 weeks ago and have been taking many photos with it. I spent a good 1 month researching between the Leica, the sony Nex-5 and the canon DSLR rebel T2i. I mainly was looking for a camera that gave me a lot of creative control and was compact as I travel a lot and decided on the leica for the size and control. The camera is very easy to learn and there are a wealth of options to choose from! I have realized that taking many photos and playing around with the different settings help you recall which feature to choose to get that perfect shot. I would also highly recommend the Photographers guide to the Leica D-Lux 5 book that you can find in [...]. It showed me a lot of features that I didnt know of the camera that ar ... e an absolute delight to have! I highly recommend High Dynamic in the my film selection. The dynamic black and white setting is very nice even with high ISO setting. This camera is great for candid shots during street photography. Honestly I would encourage to take this camera everywhere and take pictures wherever and whenever. you would be surprised at how many great expressions of people you will find. My previous camera was a P&amp;S Canon SD-850IS and that camera had almost no creative control. I felt very limited by it. Another huge feature of this camera is the 720p HD video capability. The video is very crisp even at night. The dial on the back of the camera for changing exposure, shutter speed and aperture is a huge step up from the D-lux 4. Also, the inclusion of Lightroom 3 (~$250 value) is a huge benefit for those people who like to develop their photos afterwards. The macro feature is fantastic on the camera! I took a few shots of food and it turned out really well! Actually there is also a food setting on the camera so that is also a useable option!The camera is an investment but the camera will give you good returns with great photos and style to match. I personally didnt care for the red dot appeal when I bought the camera...but I must say its starting to grow on me :) Some things that bother me are that the camera will not save all my settings in the my custom mode. I keep having to change ISO and other fine tune settings repeatedly every single time I go back. This gets mildly annoying but their are plenty of other features that make up for this annoyance. As an added bonus, the Leica customer service is very good and correspondence is very quick and timely. The best 2 features I would say for this camera is the ease of use and the wealth of creative control. Looking devilishly handsome helps too hehe :) My advice is that you should experiment with all the options to see what settings you like best.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>7 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>earthtorachel</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVIN IT!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Best point and shoot I&apos;ve ever owned. Defintely not pro grade. I couldn&apos;t use this with clients but am very happy with my purchase for home use. The images are shockingly sharp and we are still playing with all the features. Great for photographing our personal life and so much better than lugging around our mark II and lenses and not being able to put them down. This little Leica fits right in your pocket it&apos;s so small. Wish it came with a case but other than that, it&apos;s well worth the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>6 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Not404</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The Leica DUX-5 exceeds any reasonable set of expectations. But then again anyone who would buy a camera of this caliber most likely does not have reasonable expectations. I typically carry 40 or more pounds of Nikon gear on trips to Europe and going solo with a point-and-shoot took some weeks of self-convincing. But for my last trip to Spain and Portugal that is indeed what I did. And although I had a small number of wish I had my Nikon with me now moments the DUX-5 came through. For some time I have been looking for a point-and-shoot for this exact situation and have used the G 10 for a number of years as an alternative to the Nikon. But I wanted something more than the G 10 was providing seeking the holy grail of a point-and-shoot who would come close to the Pro gear I typically c ... arry. A friend of mine had a DUX-5 in Brazil on a recent trip which produced wonderful images so I broke down and bought the Leica. On the negative side as I alluded to above the DUX-5 in certain highly technical situations is most likely not going to meet the requirements of an advanced photographer. For those of us who have taught our muscles how to stabilize a large and bulky camera the DUX-5 is sometimes annoyingly too small. Even a small handed photographer might find this problematic. I like the control features on the camera but in a number of instances I found that they were easily moved by mistake while handling the camera. If you do not splurge for the electronic viewfinder framing a picture is sometimes difficult. And if you happen to be wearing polarized sunglasses while shooting viewing the picture in the LCD display can be maddening. Indeed I found even without shades in bright light situations the LCD display was difficult to use. But the positives are all of five-star caliber. Notwithstanding the easy movement of some of the control switches by mistake, the control layout is very intuitive and changing configuration is quite easy. Indeed the control layout is probably the closest to a professional grade camera of any point-and-shoot I have used. Soft menu configuration is excellent and much more intuitive and easy to control than most cameras I have used. There are a number of very interesting options one of them being aspect ratio bracketing. For those who bracket and take multiple frames of a picture regularly this feature is quite nice. Color rendition is exceptional. I shoot almost exclusively RAW format but with other settings the feature set is rich and as with many of the current generation of cameras deeper than most photographers would typically use. Image quality was also excellent far superior to any other point-and-shoot I have used. For fun I had my son use my G 10 and he took many of the same photographs that I took. Comparison of the images supports the fact that rendering of the DUX-5 is top-tier. Almost the entire set of image issues that I found on processing revolved around image quality resulting from camera stabilization which I attribute to what I outlined above - that profile of the camera is small. This undoubtedly might be rectified with more experience using the camera. All in all if you are seeking only a point-and-shoot solution to your photo bug the DUX-5 is an excellent and superior choice. But alas if you are seeking a point-and-shoot which really can match Pro gear (as I noted probably an unreasonable expectation) I might stick to cheaper and almost as excellent point-and-shoot options. That said if I don&apos;t have my Pro gear with me the DUX-5 is now always within easy reach.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>4 out of 5 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnw2k</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Beautiful Little Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is an exceptionally versatile and good quality point and shoot camera. It was a gift for my friend who loves taking pictures, wanted more control over the creative process sometimes but also wanted a compact, simple to use snapshot camera that she could carry everywhere. So far she is very happy with some great pictures of friends, kids and a weekend in San Francisco and Marin. While simple to use there is another side to it that has a fairly steep learning curve- there are so many pre-sets and features. The controls are also small and not entirely intuitive or similar to SLR bodies but are sturdy and reliable once mastered. The printed manual shows you the controls with brief outlines of function but assumes you know something about photography; I haven&apos;t spent time with the on line ... offerings as yet. Overall this is a very good camera, solid mechanically with good internal software, low shutter lag and a nice set of features. It doesn&apos;t try to do &apos;too much&apos; as some of the more extreme of the point-and-shoot lot I looked at before choosing this but has a very nice balance of capabilities.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>MN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty Good Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera for my trip abroad because I wanted to pack light. It served its purpose during my trip. It&apos;s light and small. Easy to carry. Takes good photos (but noisy when set at high ISOs). I like the raw file settings. The battery life is good. I didn&apos;t recharge it during my 2-week trip. I haven&apos;t downloaded the Lightroom yet, but it&apos;s a good deal that it comes with the camera. I didn&apos;t give 5 stars because focusing with this camera is not so intuitive than I hoped. It&apos;s more expensive than other point-and-shoot cameras, but if your budget allows, it&apos;s a good camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>schirgotis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Point and Shoot Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been looking for a point &amp; shoot camera for several years, a camera that I could always carry with me where ever I go; I finally found that camera. Currently I shoot with a Nikon D700 and thought I would never find a point and shoot that would satisfy me, even when I only want to catch a snapshot. I was wrong, the Leica D-Lux 5 has blown me away and in some situations it has been a pleasure not to have to fidget with all the setting in order to get a really nice picture. I have taken the camera out a few times since it arrived, I shot poolside in bright sun, I shot inside a very old dark theater trying to capture the ornate decorations and architecture, I shot at a marina in bright sun and out at a park on an overcast day. I also shot indoors during daylight hours. All of m ... y shooting has been with the flash off using the various settings form manual, S, A, P, Scene, Color Pallet and Snapshot mode. Loved the majority of the photos taken. I have the camera set to highest resolution and largest format. Although I tried I Resolution and I Exposure, I quickly turned those settings off. I do have I Zoom on and Digital Zoom off. The pictures have been awesome. The camera is very easy to use. If you are familiar with a DSLR it&apos;s not too difficult to figure out how to setup this camera. A few things I had to look up in order to understand what they were and how they work. I still need to understand how to use B&amp;W modes; although I have tried them I haven&apos;t been that impressed and preferred my conversions. B&amp;W film have come out too dark, out of all the B&amp;W settings I think I like Dynamic B&amp;W the best so far. And did I mention how quiet this camera is? My daughter was with me one day and wanted to know when I was going to start taking pictures. I told her I already took about 50 shots, she was surprised because she was standing right next to me and didn&apos;t hear a thing, very nice when at an event and you want to be discrete. Shutter is a little slow although I wouldn&apos;t really call it shutter lag, you would not really be able to use this for continuous shooting and get the results you would expect from a DSLR. The LCD is very difficult to see in bright sunlight but if you know how to judge you can probable get by in bright light, I think I will probably buy the Panasonic EVF because it is suppose to be the same as the Leica but a lot less expensive. As far as the camera itself, I hear that the software delivers much better / natural colors than the Panasonic LX 5 so I was willing to spend the extra $$ for this as I want to use this camera as a Point &amp; Shoot and don&apos;t want to shoot in raw. I want to shoot in jpeg, I want to shoot fast, I just don&apos;t want to miss the moment when I can&apos;t have my DSLR with me and that&apos;s what I got. The skin tones are awesome right out of the camera, a beautiful camera that produces beautiful results. I am loving it, now I have to make sure I still take my Nikon D700 out on occasion, just kidding, each has a purpose.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Frank C</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Takes exceptionally sharp photos for a small camera. I also use a Canon 5D Mark II, but wanted something for times that I didn&apos;t want to carry the heavy camera and lenses. The Leica is perfect for that. I took some flower close ups in macro mode on an overcast day, without a tripod, and the sharpness and color were excellent. I found it pretty easy to use right out of the box, but it does take a while to learn all of the features. Overall I think its a great value even at the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>jmpdctr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Within its fairly narrow performance envelope, this is a wonderful camera. The optics are excellent, the color perception is exquisite, and the relatively large LCD has better resolution than any I have ever seen. It has capabilities that rival my Canon 7D, while being small enough to carry in a pocket. Its lens is HUGE for a pocket camera. The limitations are the obvious ones. You can&apos;t change lenses, and this camera is designed to do near macro, people, and landscapes. WIthin that performance envelope, it is actually superior to the 7D, my Canon 50D, my Canon 95s, and absolutely the Nikon Coolpix. My 5D is better, but not in the same class from a convenience standpoint. (for that matter, the 7D is so much lighter and more intuitive than the 5D and the 50D that I have actually qu ... it using them.) Admittedly, I have not tried to blow it up greater than 8X10, where I routinely take the 7D to 20 x 30, using the right lens. That said, it is still slow compared to a full size DSLR. It does allow excellent AV, P, and M use. It is not easy to manually focus, and some of the more advanced capabilities are not particularly intuitive. The hot shoe is kind of ridiculous, since most external flashes will be much larger than the camera itself, and defeat the purpose of having a pocket camera. Other than that, this is a pocket size camera which takes pictures that are as good as, or even better than a full size, medium-high performance DSLR. Overall, I love it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>7 out of 7 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dave</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera in December 2010 because I wanted a compact camera to take on vacation from CT to Arizona. I didn&apos;t want to lug the Canon DSLR across the country. When it arrived, I was surprised how solid it is. Solid but small enough to fit in my pocket. Perfect for a trip. The camera is simple to use, takes fantastic photos and since I got it, I haven&apos;t touched the big DSLR. I think this camera is perfect for just about anything except fast action. It even has a macro setting that actually performs darn good. It ships with Lightroom 3 which you download after registering your camera. I would have given this five stars, but I didn&apos;t because of two reasons. it doesn&apos;t ship with a users manual book. You have to download it onto your computer from a cd. I prefer a book to c ... arry with me should I need it and the buttons are a bit small. I am adjusting to the size of them, but it is taking a while. The camera takes beautiful pictures though and that is what I bought it for. I am very happy with it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Yorkshireman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Zen style looks and sharp photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The Leica D-Lux 5 handles well, has simple controls and produces very sharp color true photographs. The screen at the back is large and looks great in low light but is not easy to see in strong light. The loose lens cap is very annoying and should have been supplied with a lanyard. There is no Leica case available for this camera as yet, which is unforgivable in a product launch. Getting the included Photoshop Lightroom software was an incredible hassle, with no guidance provided at all in the box, manual or on the web site. Even the vendor had no clue how to get it. Poor product launch organization again!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mauricio Arruga</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My first compact camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 8, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a DSLR user who doesn&apos;t bother to carry a Nikon D40 in most places I go, still I wanted a point and shoot camera that could fit in my pocket. After reading a lot of reviews I finally chose Leica D-Lux 5. I don&apos;t think it&apos;s true that Leica D-Lux 5 is an overpriced version of Panasonic LX5. I got what I paid and the Adobe Lightroom 3 worth the difference of price between both cameras. Last weekend traveled with my wife and my son. For the first time in two years I left my D40 home (with a bit of remorse in my soul). I had the chance to shoot in overcasted and sunny skies, at day and at night and all sorts of conditions. I shoot in Manual Mode, Shutter Priority Mode, Aperture Priority Mode, Auto Mode, Scene and so on. I tried all the color schemes, I filmed I did everything I could ... with the camera. The result was an 8gb card filled with great great pictures. I am very pleased with the results for each condition I submited my exposures. This is compact camera with professional quality. At first, my only concern was the poor user manual. But if you are going to use as point and shoot the user manual has pretty much all information needed. If you are an enthusiast or a pro, you&apos;ll know where to find what you need. This camera grabbed me at once.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Per</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I take the camera with me everywhere, it is so small and great just for that! Also it takes RAW images which I prossess in PS. Images are very sharp, colors great, and I am totally satisfied with everything this camera can do. I have not used the Video option jet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Maria RW</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good, but not worth the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I broke in my new Leica in a recent Paris trip. It proved easy to use and somewhat more powerful than the average point and shoot for its size, but I was disappointed. I used to have a Leica minilux zoom 35mm, so that is my previous comparison point, and this one did not fare well against the old analog. The minilux zoom had amazing image quality and range for a point and shoot, it compared very favorably to a 35mm SLR. I bought this digital Leica because I had read that it had a good range in low light, and it does not! Lots of noise in low light situations. This camera costs roughly twice as much as a decent digital point and shoot and it does not deliver twice the power. I also expected a more rapid shutter speed: it is good but not great, takes too long to record, particularly ... if you shoot raw. At this price, you want great and this does not deliver.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>4 out of 4 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>MJL</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Ultimate Point &amp; Shot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is my second D-lux and cannot keep my hands &amp; eyes away from them. The Image Quality is in par with my dSLR or Medium Format systems, and acceptable even for publication or stock photo purposes. It shares some Panasonic DMC-LX5 accessories which is an economical option to get backup batteries or such. This is a Point &amp; Shot so people are more candid towards it. However, I do not carry the camera strap and cover the red dot when traveling to avoid unwanted attention.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>RF</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Results</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is my first Leica and my first point and shoot camera, usually I use a DSLR Canon 5D (difficult camera to take to restaurants or any kind of get together). What is so great about this camera: 1. Portability 2. Looks 3. Manual Settings 4. Light 5. Flash 6. RAW format 7. Quick shooting and easy to use 8. Lightroom included (software) 9. Wideangle lens 10. You will always receive a Wow! That is an amazing camera! Not so good: 1. Other camara exactly or almost the same but different brand + half price 2. No grip 3. No Leica lens adaptors 4. Poor optical zoom 5. Poor digital zoom quality Hope this works for you.. If you ask me, should I buy this camera, I would say, DEFINETELY.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>CL DeLancey</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ideal for a good amateur photographer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I wanted a camera I could control, which these days eliminates the vast majority of compact, pocketable cameras. The choices were pretty much narrowed down to the Canon S95 or the Leica D-Lux 5/Panasonic LX5.I almost bought the Panasonic for the same reason everyone else does: cheaper price for the same camera as the Leica except for JPG treatment, Adobe LightRoom, and the warranty. Turns out that warranty is worth a lot. I live in Europe and needed an international warranty, which Panasonic does not provide. That made the decision for me. Having now shot more than 500 photos with my new Leica, I am simply delighted with it. Its low-light capabilities are second to none, and have opened up whole new worlds for me in terms of no-flash photography. I can take glorious photographs inside chur ... ches and cathedrals, and snap off quick shots in restaurants and my own home, all without a flash. In fact, I&apos;ve used the flash exactly twice so far, both times for photos taken outside after dark. Bumping the ISO up to 800 still yields clear photos, and the stellar image stabilization means that handheld shots of even 1/20 of a second can turn out sharp.The macro capabilities are also out of this world, which is a delight since I take photos for botany identification purposes. And I am very pleased with the color tones and light handling. The Leica even performed perfectly in one of the most challenging light situations of all, a shot of a harbor through a blindingly white arch, outside on a sunny day. Faced with such a dynamic range of light, the Leica came up with the perfect shutter speed to complement my aperture choice, capturing the darker harbor without overexposing the arch.The four aspect ratios are also a joy, allowing me far more latitude in my framing choices. Each has its benefits, though I find myself using the 16:9 more often than the others. And did I mention that the video function works like a dream as well?My only complaint so far is that moving the thumb dial can be a bit of a labor if I&apos;m going from one end of the aperture range/shutter speed to the other. It would be nice if a fast spin allowed greater jumps in values, rather than just plodding through them number by number. But that&apos;s a pretty small quibble for such a fantastic camera. I&apos;ll be hanging on to this sweet thing for years to come. Buy it if you can.Note: I added the Franiec aftermarket grip and find it really does enhance the handling. It&apos;s much smaller and MUCH cheaper than the Leica version (only [$]), doesn&apos;t block the battery/card slot, and still lets you easily pop the camera into a jacket pocket.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Saltfly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>SUPERB CAMERA!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It is hard to find fault with this camera. The lens is every bit what a Summicron should be, producing very, very sharp images with excellent color and tone rendition. The screen is bright and there are more than enough features for most types of use. Another winner from Leica.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dani</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love the new Leica D-Lux 5</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been delaying the purchase of a new camera, waiting for a pocket size camera with a great lens and lots of features. When I read the specs of the Leica D-Lux 5 I jumped on it. The lens is amazing, really fast, crystal clear images, beautiful results. The user interface is extremely friendly, it took me few minutes to learn the basics. What&apos;s bad? When you use a really high ISO (12800 or 6400) the digital noise is noticeable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>aid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Satisfied...so far!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>i&apos;m yet to fully learn the camera but i really like the pictures i&apos;ve taken so far. i like to travel and smaller cameras work well for me (it&apos;s hard to take a picture with my face on it with a dslr). i have a micro-4/3 and another good point-and-shoot. i&apos;ve been comparing the raw pics side-by-side using different shooting modes. i&apos;d say that they&apos;re all good but i really like the ones i took with the leica. i&apos;ll be on vacation again pretty soon and i&apos;ll definitely use the leica this time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photo Fanatic</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceptional Camera!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As a fairly experienced non-professional photographer, this camera has all the features needed to produce excellent images. I was particularly impressed with the bright images produced without a flash, even in low light situations. Although the Leica is listed as a point and shoot camera, it is far from it. It has numerous features lacking in the Canons and Nikons that I&apos;ve had. There are a few minor issues that one should be aware of. The free Adobe Lightscribe software takes over two hours to download and Leica allows only two downloads. My first effort failed and I was reluctant to try again since a second failure would eliminate my opportunity to download the software. Fortunately the Leica web site provided an email address for reporting problems. Within a few days, Leica responded t ... hat they had reset my free downloads back to two and I was able to successfully install Lightscribe on my laptop. Secondly, while using the Leica features is intuitive, the operating manual provided on a CD is over 220 pages long so priniting it isn&apos;t an option. Nevertheless, the Leica is a solid, beautiful camera and highly recommended.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>John, artiste peintre</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Expensive, but well worth the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use my Leica D-Lux 5 for artistic purposes only. As an oil painter, I use my Leica primarily for two reasons: 1) To generate ideas while I am traveling 2) To take images of my oil paintings when they are finished for my web site and other promotional activities. It has been said that the most difficult (almost impossible for numeric cameras) is to capture colors created by oil paints accurately. In the past I always used my traditional camera with slide film and special lighting in order to accurately generate the colors I achieve on my palette. The film, developing and scanning are relatively expensive and are also time-consuming. With my leica, finally I can achieve colors that are almost perfect, and with very little revision/editing I can acheive the same result, without spending a ... fortune on film, developing, etc. Thus, for me the Leica D&apos;Lux 5 is perfect. One additional feature which works extremely well and is extremely practical for me is the auto-focus. At 50 years old my vision is not perfect, thus I always had problems achieving a correct focus. That issue is finally resolved for me with the auto-focus, and my current photos are all perfectly in focus! The only negative things that I can say is that the manual is really long (it took me a week to fully read and understand), and that the camera is made in Japan not Germany (however the quality is A+). Hope that my comments help other artists/oil painters come to the same decision. Buy this camera!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>jo jo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Learning to love my Leica !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking for a camera to replace my old and well used Lumix. My Nikon is a bit bulky and too obvious to carry on day to day outings. I like to carry a compact camera in my bag, but also want quality images. Sooo, I decided to purchase the little Leica and hoped it would meet these requirements. On my first outing to our local Royal show I popped it in my bag and snapped away at the various exhibits - when I thought about what I was doing and the light conditions, etc , I achieved some excellent shots. Now I need to continue practicing ... it is simple to use and easy to recharge with the plug prongs built in to the charger. Is it worth the extra money ? Maybe, maybe not - but so far I am liking it. The lens cap is a nuisance as mentioned by many, but then again my Nikon has one to ... o and I usually leave it off anyway!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Old Age Nexalist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Fast lens; Small / Compact; Fast Shutter Speed; Easy to Use; Excellent Image quality; Good in Low Light; Excellent controls; Large Clear LCD; Good Image Stabilization

Cons: Grip handling

I bought the D-Lux 5 because I developed hand tremors and didn&apos;t want to always carry my Nikon D200. Using other point and shoot cameras I was down to 1 in 5 photos. The Leica has exceeded my expectations, in fact I&apos;m almost blown away by the image quality in a camera this small. I&apos;ve tested it up to iso 3200 (definitely &quot;grainy&quot; but still usable. Have found that the combination of iso 400 and f3.5 works very well if my hand shakes, esp. if I shoot a burst. Depth of field at f3.5 is exceptional. The wide angle + 16:9 format is great and the full telephoto is good for people shoot ... ing. In short,
I think I&apos;ve gained another 5 years of photography with this purchase, when I was just about to give it up. Very pleased with the camera and the service from Adorama. FYI, I purchased the Panasonic viewfinder which works fine and helped me achieve a steadier shooting platform, and just purchased the grip accessory for the same purpose. Finally, the bundled lightroom software is excellent and work the $$$.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>DB</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great bet for the size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve stayed away from compact point and shoots since the limited creative control, but I wanted something for an upcoming trip that would be easy to carry and fit in a purse, and the D-Lux 5 seemed to be the best choice. Granted this doesn&apos;t quite equal the level of control of a full DSLR kit, but it&apos;s a great bet for the size. And much better to haul around then 20+ lbs. of gear. Haven&apos;t played with all the features, but a few first impressions: Pros: -Portable. This goes with me everyday while the bulky DSLR stays at home. -Manual controls are always a plus in my book. -Fast lens for a compact camera, and I love how the D-Lux 5 handles low light. Cons: -I&apos;d love a bit more zoom. It&apos;s only 90mm. -Expensive, but the download of Lightroom bridges the gap between the Leica and the related ... Panny. -The traditional lens cap is going to get lost sooner or later
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Desert Runner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Compact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Just used the D-Lux to take 500 pictures on my holiday. Great quality shots. I used mostly the snapshot mode, and haven&apos;t had enough time to figure out the other features yet, and it has lots of them. I bought this instead of an DSLR because of the size,but a viewfinder would be nice in hindsight, especially outdoors in bright light. That said this camera is what I wanted, lightweight, compact, and awesome pics.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jamie F</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy with purchase so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have bought this camera to use on a holiday to Europe. Main influences when purchasing was size/portability and picture quality. I chose this over other compacts based on the pictures it produces. Very good macro mode also. Also liked the ability to zoom during movies unlike some other cameras competing for same market share. So far I have only taken a few test shots but I am very happy with the performance. Will probably post up another review in a month or so after using extensively overseas.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Fimbulwinter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not a Toy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this after realizing that the Canon G10 I used as a backup camera was not getting along with me. I wanted something that I could slip in a pocket, but when set correctly could take professional level photographs. I figured that, if the D-Lux 5 didn&apos;t do it for me I was simply not point and shoot material. Truth be told, this camera is a lot more camera than a P&amp;S. Getting a grip on all the setting variations takes some effort, but once mastered is is as superb as the name Leica promises. It comes at a dear price, but it&apos;s really worth it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Billy1956</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stunning image quality.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve owned a couple point and shoot cameras and wanted something that provided better image quality and I got more than I could ask for with this camera! The images are amazingly sharp, color is brilliant, it is small enough for my pocket and a breeze to use. I carry this as a sidekick to my Leica M-6.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Francisco the traveler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera delivers excellence</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For the price, I expected excellence and this camera delivers. The good: the camera is solidly built, has outstanding image quality (the best of any camera that I have ever owned or tested). The color representation is outstanding and the lens delivers fantastic sharpness. The not so good: there is a very slight distortion on the edges at the widest angle, which is typical on 24mm lenses. Also, the camera has a lens cap, which makes it tedious when you need to take a quick picture. However, because the image quality is extraordinary, I&apos;m thrilled with my purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica D-Lux 5 Rocks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I find myself grabbing this camera more often than my Nikon D2x. Ease of use is simple; point and shoot if you like or set your own preferences. Great low light abilities. And the video feature was a great surprise. Shot a musical scene in a school play and posted on Facebook. Sound and picture were excellent, beyond expectation. Great little camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>RixPix</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lives up to the Leica name</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera produces high quality images and 720 HD videos for a compact. The 16:9 image option is very useful for HD video edits. The controls are easy to understand and are versatile.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>KJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Takes great pictures, the quality rivals that of my DSLR. However, I find I have trouble getting the focus point I want sometimes. I think I need to read the manual a little more and figure out how to choose the focus point. Can also be slow to record image. Other than that I have no complaints. It is in my pocket 90% of the time!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Akemi-M</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Real Winner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have a D-lux 4, and an M9. The D-Lux 4 was great travel companion and the D-Lux 5 is even better! The optical quality, sharpness, and color are outstanding. I could go on and on about this fine tool, suffice to say the image quality is just impressive! The layout is logical and easy to work with. The build quality is outstanding. This works for 95% of my shooting and produces excellent 12x18 images. Some may complain about the lens cap, but I personally have no issues with this. Lightroom download is a real benefit.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Stephen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to have a small point and shoot camera to leave in my truck, but after seeing the results from it I will be using it quite a bit more than I expected to. Leica has created what I can only say is an amazing little compact camera. It is better than I expected and I would highly recommend it to anyone seeking above average results from a camera you can slide in your pants pockets. From basic point &amp; shoot to full manual settings, you can have all the control you want. For me, from the blazing fast focus in all light levels and very pleasing exposure results, I will probably shoot 99% of the time in snap shot mode. Really, it&apos;s that good and for those wanting even more it is right there for them. Fun, easy, and remarkable results equals a great camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nawaf Alkhashab</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An Excellent Quality!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got this Camera from BH .. And it&apos;s a very good Compact quality.. it&apos;s not like another Compact Camera .. Leica d-lux 5 a perfect Camera in Size , Price and quality.. thank you bh for this camera and you have a good service i&apos;m from kuwait and i&apos;ve got this camera in 5 days!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Iaia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s a great camera for a compact!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had it recommended by a friend of mine that owns a D-Lux 4. I fall in love with it so, i purchased the D-Lux 5. I am very satisfied with it! The lens quality is astonishing and has all the features that any photographer needs from a small and powerful machine like this. I would definitely recommend it!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leonie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I did a lot of research before buying this camera. I wanted something that would take great pictures with some freedom for me to play with settings. But I have young children so I wanted something compact that I could keep in my bag to capture special moments. I&apos;m still getting the hang of the advanced settings but it is a really easy to use point and shoot. You don&apos;t have to be a pro to take a good shot with the D-LUX 5. I&apos;m really happy with my purchase and loving I paid a little bit extra for the Leica rather than its Panasonic twin.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>LPeng</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is the best camera I have so far. I just got it on my hand for two weeks, so far it is amazingly good. I love the pictures taken at low light, even at auto focus the quality is great. It simply works!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pete</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Camera I have ever owned!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Photography is a serious hobby for me and I have used Nikon, Pentax, Cannon and 3or 4 small digital cameras over a 30 year period. This D Lux 5 Leica is hands down the best camera I have owned.....I love it! Excellent in low light, the colors are brilliant and it&apos;s compact and easy to carry around. I have been hiking in the mountains, on the streets of New York and this camera lives up to it&apos;s 5 Stars for me. Worth every dollar!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>finally I have .. a LEICA</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have TONS of NIKON equipment and I started in the mid 70s with NIKON. I still love my NIKON equipment BUT I have always taken small digital cameras with me on trips too. This would be my third small digtial camera in I&apos;d say over 8 plus years. I had been with someone that had this model on a recent trip where a small digital camera was THE way to go and was very impressed so I am now .. a LECIA owner. It&apos;s a GREAT camera. Very German in all respects. THe controls SEEM simplistic BUT one can do all kinds of complex settings if you desire. If I was not so invested in NIKON for now well over near 40 years - well perhpas Id be LEICA ALL THE WAY. PS the suggested reviews below with PROs and CONs suggest how waterproof or how you might use this camera underwaterr - I WOULD NOT SUGGEST TH ... AT. I own Sea n Sea cameras and in fact my current small digital that this replaced IS rated for about 30 feet underwater. DON&apos;T TAKE YOUR LEICA UNDERWATER - no siree. You&apos;ll REGRET IT BIG TIME
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ross</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I should bought this a long time ago</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>For a long time,I had other digital point and shoot type cameras but never been satisfied by the result. I went to Europe and came back dissatisfied by the pictures that I have taken. I finally got a Leica that I can afford for everyday type use. The first picture I took is my bookshelf, a row of colorful cacti and I cant believe that the colors were so realistic, same color as what my eyes would see. I know then that this was the camera for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>MM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW what a camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am an amateur but my SLR is a Nikon D300. This little camera is always wanting to jump into my pocket. The image quality is superb. Don&apos;t hesitate to spend the extra money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>vanessa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>pretty, easy to use, basic camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>this camera is simple with a little bit of fancy and takes beautiful photos. i bought it right before i went on vacation, learned the basic settings in the airport and was ready to take pictures right away. its light and small, easy to carry, perfect for travel. it also is just so pretty. the limited zoom is the only drawback.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>ProfBif</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>D-LUX 5 Digital Camera (Black) by Leica</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I upgraded to the Leica D-Lux 5 from the D-Lux 4 for the 24-90 mm zoom lens. It gives me greater flexibility in my photography. It is compact, flexible and easy to control; it takes great pictures too. I spent the extra dollars over a comparable brand for the Lightroom software that it is packaged with and the fact that It is a more aesthetically pleasing camera that feels good to hold. It is a great second camera for the serious pro.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>TMC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica Winner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Upgraded from D-Lux 3 to this D-Lux 5 and just returned from a trip to France using it extensively. It&apos;s handiness and brilliantly-conceived (and not yet fully mastered) layout, controls and capability helped produce some fine photos. The low-light capability (f2) worked impressively in churches that did not permit flash. The image stabilization software worked well. It is perfect stowed in a belt pouch.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>GKexactly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love my new Leica D-Lux 5</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is my point-and-shoot camera that I keep around for general use. I actually wear it hanging around my neck on its strap--everyone comments on the nifty, retro old Leica look. And the pictures are astonishingly good, even in low-light conditions. Colors are vivid and pop. The camera is fast to respond when powered on. I couldn&apos;t be happier with it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>hitors</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Choice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The camera value for what it cost, the vendor recommends me a panasonic that is identical and it really is, the panasonic has leica lenses... but.... i am really happy with the camera, its small enough to carry on a trip, it passes unnoticed when its neccesary and causes stir on a party.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Erin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great graphic quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>it has great graphic quality for small camera like this. the color of pictures is very natural, just like what we have seen. moreover, it is much easier to carry with than DSLRs.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marcus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is pretty much my dream camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have been waiting for this camera to come out for a while! Finally, an affordable Leica, compact but with a sensor the size of a full DSLR, &amp; it shoots in RAW. It&apos;s a sweet little honey of a camera! Although there are many excellent shooting modes (Dynamic, especially, which really saturates the color nicely &amp; pumps up the contrast a bit, it seems, to sweeten the drama of the image), I usually shoot in the Standard Mode (or Dynamic, if I can&apos;t help myself) &amp; then do all my image work in Photoshop. Since it shoots RAW, all the data is there, unadulterated, to work with, which is amazing. The only negative I think of is that it is so small &amp; SO smooth in texture that it could quite easily slip from my grip. I never pick it up without having the loop around my wrist, &amp;a ... mp; thankfully, as I HAVE lost grip on it &amp; it would have otherwise dropped! I purchased the hand grip, which is a marked improvement, but I wish it had been designed into the camera. I purchased the brown leather camera case, which is a sweet-looking thing, &amp; I always have it looped through my belt wherever I go. The hand grip, however, screws into the bottom of the camera as an accessory, &amp; the camera won&apos;t fit in the case with the grip on, meaning I must somehow carry it along with me in addition to the camera, attaching &amp; re-attaching it as necessary. This is less than desirable, even a bit annoying if I am to be honest, but it really is my only complaint against the product. It&apos;s a LEICA, after all! Which means, of course, GREAT GLASS, &amp; all the elegance &amp; mechanical perfection that comes with its reputation. I LOVE this camera &amp; highly recommend it!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>doppelgaenger</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>More than merits the praise</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As a beginner to photography I did my fair share of research to help push me towards my first purchase. My enthusiasm allowed me to comfortably avoid the most entry-level options and upon reading many favorable reviews, the Dlux5 just stood out. The inclusion of LR, which i do not own, solidified the choice. I want to have my camera around with me whenever i&apos;m out of the house and this portable p&amp;s allows me to do just that. the retro design appeals to my personal tastes and i love just looking at it. i wish i was a photogveteran to explain the intricacies but there is plenty of that online. Image quality is fantastic and large aperture (f/2) is a bonus, as is the interesting 1:1 aspect ratio (square frame). If you don&apos;t have LR, there should be little to dissuade you from purchasing t ... his little Leica.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>bagcie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>super love this cam</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love my c lux 3 but i love this cam even more. i use it to take random photos and it gives me very good results. i&apos;m so impressed with this camera. the photos are crisp and clear and the color is amazing. i have just use the program mode and i&apos;m really happy with the photos taken. i&apos;m glad i bought it. i love LEICA!!!! LEICA is the BEST!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chris</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small and powerful</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great for snapshots. Compact size makes it a great discrete shooter. On the other hand, its small size and heavy optics can make for awkward balancing that does take some getting used to. The image quality makes up for this, amazingly little noise at high ISO.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>sr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great walk around compact camera, shoots very well in low light and has a nice wide angle for landscapes. The different color settings are pretty handy, i love the b&amp;w film grain. It also includes a download of adobe lightroom. The two minuses are: the lens cap is retro cool and also retro inconvenient; there should be a printed instruction booklet instead of a cd that can&apos;t be copied.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Udoindesert</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>tiny and handy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>That little gem was a birthday gift for my wife. Using bulkier cameras I was (am) amazed how relaxing the handling of this little camera is while introducing it to my wife. That&apos;s this sort of walkaround camera even every serious photographer should be reaching for. Stunning picture quality which I did not expect from such a small sensor, good feeling about its craftsmanship are immediately obvious. Definitely a clear hint to its origin.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>BJH</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superb Point &amp; Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have owned the D-Lux 3 &amp; 4 and loved them both but the 5 continues the quality I have come to expect. I am a part time pro photographer and have owned dozens of digital cameras over the years and the D-Lux is my favorite compact camera by far. I own Hasselblad and top of the line Nikon and this supplements them perfectly. I prefer using the D-Lux for all my macro photography and even sold my Nikon micro as this does a much better job. Kept in top shape the camera retains its value too as I have just sold my D-Lux 4 for a very good price. Highly recommended!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marcelo Best</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica D-Lux5 - A true Leica...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>... in diminutive size. The lenses are of the highest quality. Scene selection and controls are much more advanced than those of previous models. One big draw back is the lens&apos;s cap. It doesn&apos;t make any sense to have a removable lens&apos;s cap in a point and shoot camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice P&amp;S camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Amazing exterior, functional, and easy to use. However, due to it&apos;s a digital p&amp;s camera, the image performance is not as good as my expectation. Sometimes, the pictures captured are not very sharp, there is blurred portion caused by failure to focus the right way but not handling motion.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leviolonist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Little Leica impresses</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this dapper little camera for street shooting and snapshooting when traveling light. I fitted a Leica digital eyelevel finder onto it and wouldn&apos;t use it without this wonderful little device. The camera is feature-laden, fast, with 24mm-90mm zoom (available in STEPS just like analog Leica lenses!) and rapid-fire motorwind. Worth every penny. A perfect companion for the Leica V-Lux 3.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lamar the traveler</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Little camera when you get to know</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this when I dont want the extra weight of the DSLR. I shoot in RAW and manual a lot and the in=mages are amazing. I wish it zoomed more, but otherwise I love it</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sara the Viking</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth the $$$$ DSLR Quality in a P&amp;S</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Just got back from a trip with this camera. I usually bring my Canon 10D SLR and the Leica D-Lux 5 took pictures with equal quality without carrying around a bunch of lenses and a much larger camera. Super crisp photos and to be able to come home and use the complimentary Adobe Lightroom makes it even better!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>CindyJo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica D-Lux 5</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I haven&apos;t had the camera long but I already love it. The picture quality is great and I love the size. So far I haven&apos;t found anything I dislike about this camera. I am really impressed!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>5fingercrawl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Pretty good point and shoot camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Over all a good little camera. I bought it because it can shoot RAW files and it is small camera easy to carry around. The only complaint I have is there has been noise in the shadows and skies of some images.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leslaw</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>D-LUX 5 Digital camera is fabulous!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Very handy to use in travel, and casual photography. Not a bulky camera, which means it can be stowed away and retrieved quickly. Beautifully made. Very solid. I will enjoy using this camera! I would like to see a better grip, a bigger grip, or at least a choice of a bigger grip.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Charles</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great, small camera. Just what I need</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use my Leica D-Lux 5 as my wide-angle camera when using my DSLR with a telephone lens. It&apos;s an excellent quality camera for its small size. It&apos;s a lot better than carrying two large DSLR cameras.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Russ the mad photographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>quite a little dynamo</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use it to take snapshots, street scenes, portraits. Soon I will experiment with the macro option. The only drawback thus far is having to take the lenscap off to view pictures.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>raintjw</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice photo camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Clear pic, and most importantly, there is a leica on the machine which makes me feel so good. Pro: clear, sharp photo, manual control and leica brand Short side: Lense quality not as good as that of DSRLs, the lense cap is the one of inconvenient design which should be improved by the manufactory.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Archi-Andy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>You get what you pay for</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great colour and white balance though every photo I&apos;ve taken so far. I&apos;m an architect and I love how detail is picked out in the shadows and comparatively &apos;bright&apos; areas of each building shot I take. This camera is also portable enough to take away camping snapping the family in the countryside - doesn&apos;t take up much room! Win!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Thiago Brazil</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>it is so perfect.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The photography qualities of this product are amazing. The control of aperture and speed and ISO etc, makes me remember my father??s old cameras, it is the perfect camera for someone who wants to express criativity, not just point and shoot. The HD video is also fantastic. I will never leave this camera at home.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>MJ in MA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lovin&apos; It!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bring this camera with me everywhere - I had found that there are times when a digital SLR is just too much to bring and wanted a great quality point + shoot that I could control (I can do what I want with it, when I want) I spent a lot of research and am having so much fun with the D LUX 5! This camera is awesome with great features like multiple exposure, panorama assist, very crisp macro, multiple aspect ratio, could go on but it also shoots RAW which is the icing on the cake. This camera is very intuitive and has great quality optics. I know, the price is up there but it is a wise investment especially of you want a great performing camera that will hold it&apos;s resale value.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>John</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Thing in a Small Package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is one great little camera. I use this camera to photograph thing I see daily. I went for a walk in a airport hanger. The low light photos are really good. I did some window light photos of my cat and the light and detail are amazing. I am always happy with with a Leica.The only thing I don&apos;t like about this camera is the lag time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Artichoke</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT...But I&apos;m worried...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Good Battery Life; Easy to Use; Good in Low Light; Large Clear LCD; Preset zoom stops option; Easy image review; Fast Shutter Speed

Cons: Poor Image Quality

RECOMMENDATION WITH RESERVATION. I use this for EVERYTHING. For the past three years I have used a D-Lux 3 for everything and have been enchanted (understanding its inherent limitation--i.e. small processor) and have gotten astounding results, including large exhibition prints. After reading a professional review, I decided that the 5 sounded great. It is, in every respect, EXCEPT..., I am worried that mine is defective because the images do not seem as sharp. I hope it can be fixed. So my recommendation is without reservation..., unless it cannot be fixed. If that&apos;s the case..., I don&apos;t know ... what I&apos;ll do. So this is a cautionary. I wish I could file a follow-up report later.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>3 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>RJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Happy</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have purchased many high end cameras over the years - going back to film. Spent a lot of money and liked all of my cameras, but I must say I love the Leica D-Lux 5 more than any camera I have ever enjoyed, the fact that Lightroom comes with it is amazing. If you want a small camera that delivers superb photos than do yourself a favor and buy this great camera. I have three friends that have seen the results and they are buying the Leica....</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sigi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>my third Leica D-LUX</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is the most recent addition to my D-LUX3 and D-LUX4 collection. Leica (or Panasonic for that matter) is getting better with each model. I am using the D-LUX5 for all but the teleshots (done with my V-LUX20). Great quality in construction, optics, and electronics! I shall never touch a bigger camera again (gave away my Canon equipment to a stronger person ...).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Desmocrat</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best of the point-n-shoot cameras</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The LEica D-Lux 5 is a great little camera. I&apos;ve dealt with carrying some big glass around as I tour the world trying to capture the images for my next book. Not to say that the Nikon D2X and the Hasselblad 500C are not great cameras, but when I&apos;m at 15,000ft in the Himalaya or in the sweltering heat of Cambodia, I want small, compact and able to deliver results good enough for publication.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>srgilmore</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Point &amp; Shoot Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I know there are cheaper alternatives out there, but a Leica is truly something special - even if it is just a point and shoot camera. The controls are beautifully laid out and intuitive. Very nicely designed camera. Only complaint - it doesn&apos;t come with a wrist strap (just an over the shoulder strap). I ordered a Nikon wrist strap for $5.95 from [@] as a result.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Arrowhead Man</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Super Duper D-LUX 5 Leica</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After owning the D-LUX 4, This D-LUX 5 has quite some improvements with a myriad of operator selection settings and then some. It is my favorite Camera for all purpose use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jens</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big camera quality in a compact body</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After much consideration, I decided to take the plunge and buy a compact Leica. I wanted a compact camera, I can bring with me wherever I go, without compromising on image quality and functionality. A week after delivery I have to say, that the D-Lux 5 delivers way beyond my expectations. It is a fabulous little package, that really performs as well as any large camera. Picture quality and ease of use are simply stunning![...]</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ed Beltrao</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Quality Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought the D-Lux5 to register moments of a motorcycle trip to Patagonia. I kept it in the bike&apos;s tank bag and would wip it out easily whenever there was something to record. Amidst all the wind, rocks and dust on the roads it never skipped a beat. It&apos;s rugged despite its small size.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Libai</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Leica Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you cant afford a M9. Get D-lux 5! Cheaper camera than M9 and works so well! It&apos;s silly to carry big cameras hanging around. Cool outlook and enormous functions in this little thing! Love it so much!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sunny</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful Leica product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I love almost everything about this camera , the almost is because the battery life is quite poor. I wish I would have ordered a second one (battery) ...Other then that I have no other complain .</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Guyde</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Latest of a long line.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a ret. mag. photog. tired of lugging equipment I had the D-lux3, D-Lux4 and now the D-Lux5, they all turned out top quality images.I upgraded to the 5 for the longer zoom, square format and easier operation. Needless to add, that I love Leica products.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>H</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent w/warts (hdmi cable spec)</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Fast Shutter Speed; Small / Compact; Easy to Use; Good Battery Life; Good in Low Light; Large Clear LCD; Great Resolution

hdmi cable not included with camera package. hdmi spec not shown in user manual. not easy to find correct hdmi cable. Its a not a standard hdmi nor a mini hdmi. No indication of correct hdmi to buy in Leica User Manual.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>lolo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>must have camera for every day recording</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Leica Dlux5 is my second camera owned Dlux4 debating between vlux 30 an dlux5 opted to second one for its sharpness and high iso use mainly for street photography concerts and travel wish had longer zoom</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Harry O</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>D-Lux 5 is a great traveling companion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I went back and forth on a number of compact digitals to keep alongside my 35mm mainstay --- I am thrilled withe the D-Lux 5 --- Must admit to paying up a bit for the leica name but am happy with the ultimate experience --- Just back from Paris on the camera&apos;s maiden voyage and it performed beautifully--- Would like a little more range but am not willing to compromise quality, so am satisfied with what I have for now ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tomes</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>FANTASTIC PURCHASE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For someone who does a lot of Urban Travelling and Exploring this camera is great! The Lens options leave a vintage look to each photo! super cool! I Love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ann</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Love this camera, the lens and color of these photos is AWESOME!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>YM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Compact and nice</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I like the product because of its light weight and good image quality. Although the IQ can match the DSLR, but it&apos;s a camera you can carry whereever you go.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeremy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The perfect compact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>&gt; great range of manual settings &gt; compact, sleek design it&apos;s a LEICA</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>gmaynez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camara!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>it is a great camara, easy to use, and easy to carry. a good option for a pocket camara with all the functions of a pro.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>lemurina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I used to have a canon but was to big so i decided to trade it for this beautiful small camera, if you are into design and quality this is the camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>esy0345</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Leica D-Lux 5</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Improvements to D-Lux 4 are worth it with increased zoom, click wheel, video button, and better low light processing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>ezoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I can`t really used to it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>I thought it would be easier to use a small camera but i couldn`t really get used to it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>0 out of 3 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Donald</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would recommend this camera !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Fabulous camera for a compact. Excellent lens in available light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is great. We absolutely loved it. As my father always says - buy a camera from a company that makes lenses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jthar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>compact yet powerful. would make a good backup to a dslr.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>tommy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A MUST BUY!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If your looking for a stylish compact with great quality and the d-lux 5 falls into your price range, just buy it. You wont be disappointed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>jim the runner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small but mighty</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Travel light and takes great pictures equal to my Nikon slr&apos; Zoom is somewhat limited have to use your feet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>LeicaLucky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>screen is large and easy to read. The camera is very intuitive.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shura</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>excellent compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>very good in low light conditions</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>ejnieto</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought it for traveling and it&apos;s perfect! Great quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>M</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Compact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great travel item</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>eK</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s great pruchase!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Found what I looked for. Fast and safe transaction. Great product!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>Andy the Brain</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Classic camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Classy camera with high performance results.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>weili</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>no bad</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>good quality</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>cd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>unique product w yearly advancements tha</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>professional documentation for marketing products artistically daily as journal indoors available light is waesome capability over previous</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Leica D-LUX 5 10.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/4449042713339896779/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CNUCEPQCMAo</URL>
     <Reviewer>jespinosa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It is the difference....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Beatufil and interesting with the right zomm range for a compact Leica.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

