<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff Keller</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>DCResource.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DCRP Review: Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very good photo quality; Monster 24X, 25 - 600 mm Leica lens; Power OIS image stabilization, with &quot;active&quot; mode for movies; 3-inch rotating LCD with 460,000 pixels, good outdoor/low light visibility; Full manual controls with RAW support, numerous ways to adjust white balance, two types of bracketing, and a customizable button and spot on the mode dial; Intelligent Auto mode does it all for you, including scene selection, face detection, blur reduction, shadow brightening, and smart sharpening; Robust performance, especially focusing and shot-to-shot speeds; Lots of scene modes and special effects, with 3D still capability; Intelligent Resolution sharpens photos, and gives you a 1.3x boost in zoom power with a minimal drop in image quality; Super fast burst mode, with ability to shoo ... t at 5.5 with continuous AF and 12 fps with single AF; Intelligent Dynamic brightens shadows (though not in all situations -- and it does nothing for highlight clipping); Records movies at 1080/60p with stereo sound and continuous autofocus using AVCHD or MPEG-4 codecs -- full manual controls available -- optical zoom and image stabilizer can be used while recording; Support for external flash, external microphone, conversion lenses and filters, and a remote shutter release cable; Above average battery life; HDMI output

Cons: Tends to clip highlights; Images have yellow/brownish cast in artificial light -- still no fluorescent white balance option; Some redeye -- no removal tool in playback mode; Long write times after a burst containing RAW photos is taken; Rainbow effect on electronic viewfinder can be distracting; Can&apos;t access memory card while camera is on a tripod; No composite A/V cable or Mac software included; Full manual on CD-ROM (it&apos;s not very user-friendly, either)

The Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 is a very good super zoom camera, and one that should be high on your shopping list. If you&apos;re a beginner who wants something simple to take photos and movies with, it can do that with ease. Enthusiasts will be pleased too, thanks to the full manual controls, expandability, and RAW support. Negatives are few, and are mostly related to highlight clipping, color accuracy in artificial lighting, and what you&apos;ll find in the box.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>4 out of 4 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Imaging-Resource.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div style=&quot;display: none;&quot; class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent 24x zoom covers 25-600mm
Optical Image Stabilization
Solid build
Stereo microphone
Articulating LCD
Electronic viewfinder
Power switch instead of a button
Built-in hot shoe
Two zoom toggles
Lens hood included
Rear dial is great for quick adjustments
Nice, big shutter release
Dual-speed zoom lever
Top-deck Movie Record start button
High quality Full HD video at 60p
High speed video
12 fps full resolution continuous mode
Mode dial is packed with 14 modes
RAW and RAW+JPEG capture modes
Good battery life
EV control is easy to access
Auto white balance does well
More sophisticated noise suppression system
Fast autofocus
Fast shot-to-shot cycle time
Mic/Remote socket
HDMI port
Good print quality, ran ... ging from 16x20 to 5x7 at lowest and highest ISO settings

Cons: Tends to blow out highlights
Tripod socket too close to battery/card door
Zoom range not as generous as some competitors
Lens hood gets in the way of the flash
Uncorrected RAW files have lots of chromatic aberration, and geometric distortion at wide-angle is strong (typical of long zooms, though)
No sweep panorama mode
Incandescent white balance is a little warm

Review Posted: 11/15/2011_
If there&apos;s still an argument to be made for the small sensor digicam, the most compelling would have to be the one made by the megazoom models.
Thanks to the relatively small size of the sensor itself, you can enjoy the most versatile lenses ever crafted. From a true wide angle that embraces a small room to an impossible-to-keep-steady zoom with a macro that makes small things visible, the megazoom delivers in one lens what no other camera can.
The drawback to this magic, however, is also the sensor size. Packing a lot of photo sites onto such a tiny imager means that the more sensitive ISO settings will deliver too many &quot;false positives&quot; per pixel, generating what we call Noise.
Compounding the problem is that image processors have become as cocky as an adolescent with car keys, smoothing out that noise at the expense of detail. Last year&apos;s FZ100, Panasonic&apos;s flagship megazoom, failed to earn a Dave&apos;s Pick for just that reason.
So how did Panasonic do with this year&apos;s top-of-the line FZ150?
*Look and Feel*. First of all, let&apos;s applaud the company for sticking to a well-conceived design that is also solidly built. The Panasonic FZ150 body is nearly identical to the FZ100 with only some silkscreening omitted, a larger stereo microphone grill, and a new side lever on the outside of the lens barrel which can be set to focus or zoom so you can put your left hand to use. Small refinements.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 24x zoom lens, supports RAW format, hot shoe for accessory flash, excellent video quality

Cons: More expensive than cameras with better features, so-so image quality

Among mega-zoom digital cameras, the Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 earns numerous recommendations for its 24x zoom lens and excellent video quality. This 12.1-megapixel camera has a number of features not commonly found on mega-zoom cameras, including a hot shoe (for an external flash and other accessories), and it supports RAW file format. ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Addicted to Pizza</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Addicted to Pizza</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been looking for a camera that takes great quality photos yet compact enough to carry around; this camera is the best of both worlds. I&apos;m what you would call the casual hobbyist photographer. I actually have 2 cameras, a full size SLR and this Panasonic. For years, I carried around a compact point and shoot camera mainly out of the convenience but I was rarely satisfied with the quality of photos. The outdoor daylight photos were good but indoor photos and low light conditions were awful but I also didn&apos;t feel like carrying around a bulky full size SLR when I&apos;m traveling, hiking etc. The problem with the point and shoot cameras is that there is no ability to adjust the settings such as the Aperture (lens opening), Shutter speed (Length of time the shutter allows lig ... ht to travel through the lens) or the ISO/ASA (film speed). Basically, the right amount of light needs to travel through the lens to prevent over exposure (too light) or under exposure (too dark). The point and shoot cameras have specific settings i.e. portrait mode, sports mode, night scenes etc but the problem with this is that the computer and sensor in the camera is controlling all of the settings and it often leads to poor quality shots. This is where the Panasonic FZ150 comes in. This camera is considered to be a compact SLR and it takes excellent photographs. It starts with a high quality Leica lens which delivers phenomenal colors and sharp pictures. This camera allows the user to manually adjust all of the settings mentioned above but it&apos;s much smaller and lighter than the full size SLR&apos;s. This camera also has a large LCD screen to review your shots and it also shoot 1080 HD video. If you&apos;re not worried about bulk, size or cost, then I would recommend you go with the full size SLR&apos;s because nothing will compare when it comes to professional looking photos. If you want a great camera that shoots all around quality photos, at a good price, and compact size, then this is the camera for you. The only drawback is that the lens is fixed on this camera, meaning you cannot switch out to a different lens for situational photography but with that said, the vast majority of folks will find that this camera and lens is more than you need. I would also recommend you buy a spare battery and a clear lens filter for around $15 to protect the lens; if you scratch the lens, your camera is done. I&apos;m really pleased with this camera and would recommend it to anyone who finds themselves in a similar situation as mine.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>roycebarber</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>fz150</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: This is ALMOST a pro camera. It does EVERYTHING a pro does, but has a lower cost light sensor. This is the BEST!!!

Cons: I compare it to a full professional camera, but it costs half as much, so the light sensor isn&apos;t pro.

I LOVE IT!!! The fz150 is a hybrid bridge megazoom. Hybrid referring to the light sensor. Bridge means it&apos;s between a point and shoot and a pro camera. Mega zoom means it&apos;s lens reaches far further than other cameras (there are a few other megazooms but their image clarity isn&apos;t nearly as amazing as this one). The light sensor is amazing for not being pro-price-range, it&apos;s some kind of hybrid sensor which is better than other point and shoots, but it&apos;s not a full professional sensor because it costs half as much. This is an incredible travel camera fo ... r me because the lens is built in and i don&apos;t have to carry anything but a CPL day-filter for super bright days. I can add lenses to it, easily, but they must go on the end of the permanent lens. Also, the close-up &quot;macro&quot; shots are incredible, I can print a poster of a penny. I can get way up close on anything, to the point of touching the lens itself (i do use a protective lens filter so i don&apos;t scratch the lens!!!), providing there is light to take a photo. I highly recommend this camera for serious photo takers. A professional photographer should use this as a travel camera because it&apos;s light-weight compared to the huge gear you&apos;re used to carrying around and this camera has as many features as the pro cameras. The video quality, and the video features, are breath taking. I make blu-ray videos for my buddies and this is the v-logging camera of my dreams. :D

if you&apos;re a child who doesn&apos;t care what the camera does, get something pocket size and cheaper. but if you need superb pixel clarity, then get this camera. if you&apos;re a super professional, then spend 2 grand more and get a super pro camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Joe</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Early Impressions</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am replacing a Canon VIXIA HV30 for family photos and videos, as well as occasional second camera angle in 2-cam shoots. I&apos;ve only had it for a week. The Panasonic delivers a lot for the money both in video and for stills. It delivers very good video quality, but not as easy to operate as dedicated video cams. The zoom for instance is 2-speed, not continuous; there&apos;s no iris ring. Focus is electric and not too precise. For family photos it appears more than adequate. I had been looking at the $1,000 range of DSLRs with interchangeable lenses, but really didn&apos;t need more than a zoom, so saved a lot. They didn&apos;t seem to provide more video functionality, and the kit lenses were quite slow. The viewfinder is ok, but I find I&apos;m using the LCD more. The fold out design is very functional, but y ... ou could break off the screen if you weren&apos;t careful. Wish you could monitor the audio while recording, and adjust the levels. Really if one is serious about quality an outboard recorder would be needed. Also would be great to be able to monitor video through the HDMI port while recording, but no luck there. Haven&apos;t tried the AV output whether works while recording. The cam will record AVCHD continuously for as long as chip and battery hold out. Highest quality, 1080p/16 gig chip runs about an hour and 15 minutes. Recording of concerts and plays would be practical. If you&apos;re used to a real prosumer video camera you&apos;ll have to scale down your expectations, yet it&apos;s still a lot for the money, and careful work should yield surprising results. The still pictures are excellent for my use because I don&apos;t print bigger than 8x10, and scale down a lot for email and web. The steady shot in the lens really does work well. The cam feels a little frail and light, but everything works and if you don&apos;t drop, it should keep going. All in all I&apos;m looking forward to getting to know this little cam better. I think it&apos;s going to work out fine.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Pizza guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect compromise</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>For years, I&apos;ve struggled with and contemplated the convenience of carrying a smaller point and shoot camera vs. carrying a bulky/heavy full sized SLR. The problem is that the smaller cameras are tempting to take on vacation because of their size but the picture quality is often dissapointing and fails to capture the true ambience of that moment. Conversely, the full sized SLR cameras take excellent pictures but it&apos;s size, weight, not to mention cost, make it less appealing to haul around. This is where I introduce the Panasonic FZ 150; it&apos;s the perfect compromise of both worlds. By no means am I a professional photographer but the problem with the compact point and shoot type cameras is its&apos; inability to make separate or manual adjustments to the Aperture (opening of the lens), ... shutter speed (length of time the lens remains open during a photo shot) and the ISO/ASA the (film speed rating). I realize that compact cameras have task specific settings i.e. portrait mode, scenery mode, night time mode etc but these modes rely on the camera to make all automatic adjustments and it rarely turns out the way you&apos;d like. You will notice that even on these specialized modes, the picture is often grainy, too light or too dark. In short, ideally, the right amount of light has to travel through the lens for the right amount of time, with the correct depth of field in order for the picture to portray what the human eye sees. With that said, a high quality point and shoot cameras does a descent job in daylight but night time and flash photography is dicey. I&apos;ve owned many cameras throughout the years but so far, this camera is the best compromise for size, weight and picture quality. It starts with a high quality Leica lens. The optical zoom is impressive and the clarity rivals that of the full size SLR&apos;s. Most importantly, this camera is capable of separate and manual adjustments to the aperture, shutter speed and ISO/ASA settings which means that I choose the factors that dictate the picture quality. Additionally, this camera is capable of shooting full 1080i HD video and the quality of the video is impressive. This camera has all of the manual adjustments available on a full size SLR. The main difference is that the high end SLR&apos;s have greater range of adjustments and more specialized capabilities for professional photography. If you&apos;re like me, casual photo enthusiast, you&apos;ll probably never need that range in flexibility. Also keep in mind that the lens on this camera is fixed, meaning that you won&apos;t be able to change out to a more specialized or specific lens for longer zooms, wide angles etc. In conclusion, if size, weight and cost is of no concern, then get the full size SLR. At the end of the day, the picture quality from the full size SLR is the best. If you don&apos;t care about picture quality but just want something simple to take casual photos, stick with the compact point and shoot. If you&apos;re in the market for a mid sized, well priced camera that takes excellent pictures, then look no further. I hope this helps.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Picky camera guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product and inexpensive</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m really impressed with this camera thus far. This is the perfect compromise between the compact point and shoot models and the full size SLR&apos;s. The point and shoot cameras have limited flexibility in terms of adjusting the camera&apos;s settings such as the Aperture, ASA/ISO and Shutter Speeds. The ability to adjust such settings makes all the difference in the world between quality photo shots and poorly exposed shots. Generally, I found that the pre-set portrait, scenery, night time and sports settings on point and shoot cameras often yield mediocre results and even worse in low light conditions. With the full size SLR&apos;s they take awesome pictures but I find them to be a bit bulky and heavy to lug around, especially on hikes and such. I&apos;ve been looking for a slightly m ... ore compact version that&apos;s capable of taking high quality pictures. This Panasonic camera is an excellent all around camera. It starts with the Leica lens which is high quality and capable of taking fantastic photos. The color presentation is fabulous, clarity crystal clear and it&apos;s really easy to use. Best of all, it&apos;s capable of the finer adjustments comparable to that of the more common full size SLR&apos;s. Another bonus is that this camera has dual capabilities as a video recorder with full 1080 HD quality videos. If you&apos;re a casual photo enthusiast like me but want a camera that&apos;s capable of taking great photos without the inconvenience of bulk and $$$$, this camera is a great alternative.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: - Good picture quality
- Can take RAW images
- 1080p 60p with no limits on how much you can record (only limit is battery and memory).
- Not much noise in shooting night shots.
- Build quality is nicer than some competitors
- 460K LCD
- nice grip and fits nice in my hands.
- Comes with hood and neck strap; isnt bad at all.

Cons: - Not many creative filters (HDR/Selective color or Color Accent, etc.)
- 24x Optical zoom seems low compared to 35x and others.
- EVF is a bit laggy but thats just me.

Not deducting any eggs because of picky cons. 

I commend Panasonic for listening to reviewers and buyers to improve the image quality and features on the new FZ150. 

Hoping that they add creative filters/features to new Super-Zoom.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Senior Citizen Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Exceeds expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I have been looking for a possible replacement to my heavy and cumbersome DSLR equipment to take on mountain hikes. Having previously owned two earlier Panasonic &apos;super-zoom&apos; FZ models, I had an idea of what to expect regarding user functions and how the camera fundamentally would operate. Thus, this purchase decision was easy (given B&amp;H&apos;s easy, no-fuss return policies). Image quality is excellent; clearly exceeded my expectations. I shoot only RAW. The FZ150 gives me what I want. With a remote control port, I can use this camera just as I would use my heavy, expensive DSLR equipment. I am very pleased. The lens is really good. The image stabilization system works terrific. The adjustable (position) LCD is a nice feature. Video looks great (albeit I have not used it much). Just a f ... ew complaints. The size of the 4-way controller on the back which gets heavy use is too small. I&apos;d like it to be a little bigger (to be fair, my hands are very big). Also, when reviewing images, lens barrel retracts to the off position. This can be an issue (pinched fingers) with the supplied lens hood if the hood is mounted in the reverse (for storage) position. Viewfinder diopter adjustment will not lock; it can get out of adjustment too easy. Would also prefer a manual zoom control.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wudce</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Point and Shoot Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: All the functions of a DSLR in a point and shoot packet.
Great photos even in low light.
Good battery life.
Easy to use and understand.

Cons: Price. Close to that of a entry level DSLR
Lack of F-Stops, 2.8-8.0 W, 5.2-8.0 T
This is not really a con, mosty me but the thumb wheel on back which controls your EV, Aperture and Shutter speed took some getting use to I got a big thumb.

This camera is about as close as your going to get to a DSLR in a point and shoot camera but the cost being so close to that of a entry level DSLR may make some past it by. It&apos;s really up to you want your wanting to do. For me I&apos;m happy with it and it dose all I want and then some. As a side note I&apos;v not done enough video recording so I can&apos;t comment on this yet. Once again thanks ... Newegg for quick shipping!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best of all for all</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I like this camera and have been comparing it to others for a year. I recommended it often when asked what camera to get. It has setting that makes it an excellent point and shoot. It also has controls for many features found on DSLRs. I finally bought it for myself and used it at the McChord air show. Shot fast action at 12 fps and made high definition videos as well as snapshots of family with planes. Comes with software that is outstanding for making slide shows to DVDs to share. Camera fit in a cargo pocket and performs like a big camera with a telephoto.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Komondor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What a change</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this in a wide variety shooting condition. What an improvment from my FZ28! Longer and wider zoom, but the compactness feels great, especially I travel alot with it. Love the very large articulated screen. Great HD video indoors and outdoors. Better controls, overall it is really great. Would be nice to have a larger sensor, but I do not print anything larger than 8x10. Battery life is OK, but probably will need a second battery for long trips.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bone Daddy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Almost Perfect!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Having gradually stepped up from the Lumix LX1 (as an early adopter) to the LX5 in search of the perfect one-lens run-and-gun camera, I ordered the FZ150 for the 24X zoom (this is a fantastic lens!), the dedicated mic input (the RODE VideoMic is perfect on this!) and the hinged screen/EVF option (love it!). Those amazing features are more than a fair trade for the increased bridge size, when using it as a travel shooter. The ergonomic &amp; utilitarian design of this camera is fantastic -- except for ONE boneheaded thing: the tripod mounting screw socket is located very close to the battery/SD card door hinge, as opposed to in the center of the camera, under the lens. This prevents ANY changing of batteries or loading/unloading of SD cards when the camera is on a tripod or attached to a qu ... ick-release mount. This oversight is baffling, considering the location of the tripod socket on both of my LX models allowed the door to open when mounted. Completely detaching the camera to check the memory card in the middle of a shoot is pretty obnoxious, having not had to before. Other than that, though, it&apos;s a great camera for the price. Oh, and the Lumix DMW-LWA52 wide angle conversion lens (marketed for the LX5) works on this camera perfectly -- without an adaptor or having to switch to manual focus!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>stnwll</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High end point &amp; shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Simply the best point and shoot camera on the market at this time. I purchased this camera specifically for the video capture capabilities. 1080p at 60fps. I&apos;ve shot quite a few videos and all I can say is WOW. Very good quality even in low light. Photo&apos;s are fantastic and the zoom is quite good at 24X although not as high as some of the competitors. One feature you won&apos;t find on the others is 220fps high speed video, great for perfecting that golf swing and the ability to capture non-compressed (RAW) photos.

Cons: I have yet to find a real flaw with this camera. The software that comes with the camera isn&apos;t the greatest but it is functional. You have a choice between Apple&apos;s mpeg4 mov files or the new AVCHD mts formats. The latter of which is difficult to edit without some sp ... ecial tools.

Even though this is a bit higher in cost compaired to the FZ47, the new sensor does a great job in noise reduction. The friends that have seen the videos taken from this camera have all commented on the fantastic clarity. The optical stabilization is nothing short of amazing. If you&apos;ve ever tried to hold a camera still by hand for more than 15 minutes you&apos;ll come to appreciate how well this stabilization works.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>BlinkDog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One of the best superzoom midranges.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>So far I&apos;ve mostly taken photos of birds, but also planes, helicopters, and indoor, static product shots. The thing that makes this camera is definitely the zoom, but also the great lens from Leica. No distortion or fringing. This camera is super easy to use and understand to take basic photos, with a ton of modes for getting creative or helping get the shot right. Very intuitive and plenty of easy-access buttons to get to the function you need right away. The only negatives I have to report so far are the low resolution of the electronic viewfinder makes it a little hard to judge focus there; things are a bit grainy in the EVF, and the fact that you only get a video signal out the HDMI port in playback mode. Would be nice to capture live video direclty to the HDMI output port.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Liz</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I haven&apos;t had much time with the camera but am slowly learning the different features. I have been able to take indoor shots without using flash which I love as I am not a fan of bright flash. The zoom works very well and has allowed me to take close up pictures of the grandchildren without being in their face. The video is truly sharp. My only complaint is that the tulip shade showed up in some of my shots when not using the zoom. If you don&apos;t want the weight and hassle of a dslr then this is the camera for you. I read multiple reviews online and this was the highest rated for a reason.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sailor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fourth Panasonic camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Travel, portraits, and art photos are my uses of this camera. My first Panasonic camera was the FZ 30. I bought the FH 20 to travel light and the TS 10 for snorkeling. After using the FZ 150 for a month I agree with the positive reviews. Pictures are sharp, new features are excellent, access to these features are easy, intelligent automatic and the multiple positions of the screen are helpful. Two negatives: The compact design causes buttons to be pushed accidentally. The barrel zoom and focus has been replaced with a single switch that is close to the manual switch. In a rush it is easy to push the wrong one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Shines</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>At home and travel. Compare to typical DSL, FZ150 is light weight and small enough to carry around. Easy to operate. Fast recharge. Great in low light. The flip/ turn around 3 monitor helps to take group pic. Take crispy clear pictures. The zoom really worked. beautiful body and strong built. The price is reasonable with all the features and the quality. A best camera I ever owned. I recommand it to anybody who likes to take photos. Good job, Panasonic! I will buy another one for my daughter.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paula</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Bridge Camera ever</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is easy to use and has so many different options...I read tons of reviews before deciding on this one and im glad i chose it. Pictures come out clear and the burst mode is a big bonus on this camera. I love that the back flips out, and the zzom is amazing. This camera will get to go where my DSLR isnt allowed like concerts. I cant wait till the next one to use it there! Good in low light too!!! Battery life is VERY good also!!! I havent tried the video yet but when I do Ill come back to let you know how it works...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>suzannehy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Overstock.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love the zoom, be aware of focu</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m a camera enthusiast, and usually stay with Nikon and Canon cameras. I have multiple dSLRs and purchased the long-awaited Canon S100 ($429) for a more portable camera. I was sorely disappointed with indoor pictures and lack of zoom. I sold the Canon on eBay and after lots of research, I&apos;m happy I purchased this Panasonic as a replacement. Images are sharp, but you have to be aware of where the lens is focusing. Depending on the settings, focus in on faces or in the center of the frame. You should read the manual and get used to how to focus and recompose your images. Other than this one glitch, I love all the auto settings, RAW image option, and manual controls. This camera is lightweight and easily portable in my purse. The long zoom makes this camera a fantastic all-around cam ... era for everything from indoor events to landscapes to far-away, fast-moving sports. I&apos;ve decided it is the best compromise between a limitations of a pocket-size camera and the weight/bulk of a dSLR. ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lynell</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very happy with this camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Short Lag Time; Good Image Stabilization; Good Image Quality; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Great Zoom

* Zoom better than expected - set it on a tripod (or flat surface) and zoom to 127x for an awesome pic (even automated)! 
* Many features/functions that other cameras don&apos;t have at this level. 
* Owners manual very detailed - still reading and learning - great for manual or auto.
* Very versatile!
* Excellent outdoor lcd screen, even in bright sun - very surprised by this as I&apos;m used to using the view finder instead - no need with this lcd screen - amazing!
* LCD screen rotates both ways so you can take personal portrait and see it - rotates to hide for protection when not in use.
* Lens cap stays on, unlike others.
* Great battery life.
* I have NOTHIN ... G negative to say about this camera - very, very happy with it! I researched the others and kept coming back to this. Actually bought the Nikon P500 and returned it, but it wasn&apos;t too bad, just didn&apos;t have lcd protection and focused weird on long zoom. This camera acts so much better!
* Videos are superb!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>NiceShotSteve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Travel Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Body is all plastic, but that&apos;s what makes it light and compact for travel. Good ergonomics for small hands. Leica lens leaves nothing to be desired. Flare and distortion well controlled. Be aware that the 600mm (equivalent) zoom requires a steady hand or an external support; shoot multiple copies at this long setting. Burst and auto bracketing are excellent and FAST. I gave up on the detachable lens cap and just substituted a good quality 52mm Skylight 1A filter.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>GoldPacific</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best camera I have purchased so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Disclaimer: I am a casual photographer and don&apos;t pay very high attention to finer details of the pictures. Review: I bought this (Panasonic FZ150) camera after a thoroughly checking blogs and other standard camera review websites. Most of them placed this camera at the top of list (in its class). And I am not dissapointed. Day time pictures that I have seen can proudly be viewed alongwith SLR pictures. And I am pretty sure, with proper settings in manual mode (This camera has tons of tweaks and settings possible for enthusiasts) even night time pictures will be beautiful (I have checked a FZ150 group on FLICKR and have seen some brilliant night photos). The focusing is beautiful and so is its optical zoom. The feature that has impressed me the most so far is the camera speed. It can take ... upto 12 pics a second (insane). I shot a Pinata breaking event at a kids birthday party @ 5.5 FPS ..Man the pictures have come out so lively and incredibly sharp. The Camera didn&apos;t cough for a single second while taking approx 300+ shots from this event and are well focused. I have still not explored the camera much due to lack of time, but whatever I have experienced so far is much much more than satisfactory. A must buy for those who are looking for a Non-SLR high end Point &amp; Shoot.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kare</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great all in one camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Just bought this camera a week ago, and have been testing it out. Taking it with me to South East Asia for a month. The positive - Ultra light, long zoom range, clear pictures, video effects are fantastic and the creative effects are nice. I love that it&apos;s a step up from a point and click, but a step down from a giant SLR. I don&apos;t need to be lugging around a heavy camera with multiple lenses when I&apos;m backpacking. This is a great compromise for me. The negative - .mts format for videos need conversion when uploaded to the computer. It was annoying to try and find the raw setting.. and am still shooting photos in jpeg. Menu&apos;s aren&apos;t the easiest to navigate, but once you&apos;ve found what you want it&apos;s quick to get back there if you need to. Overall, a great buy for me. I&apos;m quite happy with it ... .
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wildlife photographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I LOVE this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The zoom capability is incredible and the results are certainly acceptable, even at the extreme end of the zoom. The menus are extensive, but logically arranged and intuitive. Image stabilization is excellent. Close-ups are very sharp. I rarely get my big Nikon out of the bag any more. Two people have bought this camera upon my recommendation, and they love it as well. The sharp vari-angle LCD screen is a big plus for me, as well as RAW capability. It also does high def video. I don&apos;t carry a video camera any more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Birdman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Superzoom I&apos;ve Owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is my third superzoom and my first Lumix. The others were Canon Powershots (S2IS and SX10IS). Though I&apos;ve owned it only two months, the Lumix seems clearly superior to both the Canons (though they, of course, were earlier models). It zooms more smoothly, takes surprisingly sharp pictures in very low light, provides better focusing guidance in macro mode, and has menus that I find easier to use. Pictures are sharp at all focal lengths, color is accurate, and the autofocus seldom misses. I appreciate the 25 mm (equivalent) wide angle and the fact that you can screw a filter on to the lens to protect it, something neither of my Canons allowed (maybe corrected by now?). So far I&apos;ve found nothing that I don&apos;t like about the camera. I don&apos;t shoot video so can&apos;t comment on its video capabili ... ty.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>I Focus</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Features and Images cannot be beat for t</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>General photography and travel. Can&apos;t beat the size and weight for all those features. Build quality is exceptional. I love the qui8ck menu and the 3 preset setups. Can&apos;t think of any cons.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Art</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>FZ150 The Swiss Penknife</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I returned my FZ100 because the price dropped and they did not want to refund anything, and while waiting for a good price I got depressed about the negative reviews, especially the one saying it is unloved. The FZ150 is much better and with more features, and all reviewers seem to agree it is the best all around camera for stills/video that is also small and lightweight. I&apos;m still planning to use the rip offs CO179EP belt pouch (2oz) so the weight for everything is under 22oz which doesn&apos;t include a spare battery (kept in jacket pocket).. I may not use the lens hood or lens cover, but am going to use a nikon clear filter for lens protection. Still going to use case logic DCB-304 belt pouch for storing in carry on hand luggage and for use in a car-it has more padding and has more room but ... also more bulky. I&apos;m very pleased with the test shots -using the maximum zoom I can get sharp shots without a tripod even with iA on which gives about a 32X zoom. (Did lean against wall though). Some test shots include a power transformer on a nearby power pole down the street, and I can read the small label on the side and see the bolt head writing. Could not tell the difference in quality between regular and iA by the way. It&apos;s made in Japan.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>ireno</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Very Special Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had over 14 cameras over the years. This is very special indeed. Only 3 of my cameras have I &apos;fallen in love&apos; with. The weight (very light) great IQ, video 1080p with stereo 48Kps sound, useable 800 iso, burst, colors, and a super interface make this camera really fun to use. For me, it doesnn&apos;t get any better than this. Imagine! A product that have yet to find any cons. I love it. Go to the Panasonic forum on www.dpreview.com and see more about it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rondo</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After looking at the Panasonic GH2, G3, Sony&apos;s A55,65, &amp; 77, I decided on this camera because I don&apos;t want to be changing lenses. I am amazed at the quality of the photographs. The degree of settings and controls match any dslr. The EVF isn&apos;t great, but works. The raw images are great, and the speed of all functions is great, combined with outstanding auto-burst selections. Will never miss a shot with this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>DM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>disappointed after extended use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>I previously reviewed this camera after a couple weeks use and praised its features and image quality. I had some reservations regarding manual focus and a few relatively minor issues but was complimentary of its extreme telephoto performance. I have since uncovered a significant issue. At the extreme wide angle setting, there is pronounced softness consistently in one corner that strongly suggests an alignment problem. I have since purchased another identical camera from another dealer and find no evidence of this problem in that copy. After taking considerable care to document this defect, I returned the camera (at considerable expense to myself) to Panasonic for correction. They received the camera and further requested my original test photo sequence (all four corners with same sub ... ject and identical camera settings). They then essentially shined me on, refused to allow me to communicate with the technician, shipped the camera back without first informing me of their final findings (the inevitable line that the camera is working properly and pictures look normal). It should also be noted that this camera has on 2 occasions frozen with functionality regained only after rebooting. I do have high expectations, but my second copy, when put through the same rigor, performs quite well. If I were to revise my ratings based solely on customer service, I would give Pany a sound goose egg. What a shame to showcase a remarkable Leica optic with shoddy assembly and then be in denial even when provided with tangible evidence of the fact. My advice to purchasers is buy from a reputable dealer such as B&amp;H but do you testing within the return period, because otherwise you will be stuck with what you got.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>jimphil2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>light, compact, takes great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve used digital SLR cameras for years, wanted a smaller-lighter camera that I wouldn&apos;t need to carry extra lens for. This small lumix camers is solidly built, takes great pictures, has all the lens range you could ever need and shoots in raw. Another added bonus was I can use my Olympus accessories (flash) on the Lumix. Great buy for the money, love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tassie Kate</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent all-in-one camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve had this camera about a week and am so far very pleased with it. I tossed around the idea of purchasing a micro four thirds camera for a long time, but in the end, the desire to do any type of shot I want without having to change lenses had me looking at the latest batch of ultra-zooms. And I&apos;m very glad I chose this route. I&apos;m very impressed with the speed of the auto focus, the image stabilization is excellent, the photos I&apos;ve taken have been crisp and with excellent detail. Fully articulated LCD screen is a must-have feature. It has performed well in low light, taking a decent shot at 1/4 second handheld. Macro shots are very good. Even the face recognition has proved very useful, it was something I thought was a bit of a gimmick before. So far I can&apos;t fault this camera for ... my purposes and I expect it will do me for quite a few years.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>2 out of 2 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nicole aka Thirdeyemom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>LOVE my new camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this camera after using a friends older version on a trip when my mini camera ran out of batteries. It is an AMAZING camera! It takes extraordinary photos and has a new and improved zoom feature. It isn&apos;t too big that it is cumbersome and is easy to carry when traveling. I am extremely impressed with the camera and its abilities. I would highly recommend it to anyone who wants a step above a compact travel camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Casual shooter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best point and shoot in a long time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is light weight although looking at it you would think it was heavier. The photos are sharp and easy to hold steady when shooting long distances. All in all a wonderful point and shoot camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Maverick127</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this Panasonic DMC FZ150</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this camera for everything from still life&apos;s to action shots. I have only had it for about a week, so I will be spending a lot more time evaluating it, overall. So far, the intelligent auto works great, face detection is okay, and the shutter lag is very short. Quick start up and write time on a class 10 card.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Happy2Wander</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Alaskan Cruise Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased the LUMIX DMC-FZ150 as an upgrade to my current Olympus digital camera (which I love, but did not have the most current upgrades), primarily for use on a recent Alaskan cruise. The camera worked very well under all conditions during the cruise, and I was extremely happy with the camera and the purchase. The fact that the DMC-FZ150 Leica lens has both expansive telephoto and wide angle capabilities was a great selling point and both were used extensively during the cruise. Also, the camera did not fog even though it was taken from inside the ship to the outside deck when photographing the Sawyer Glacier. Perhaps the camera&apos;s best feature during the cruise was the ability to take fast burst shots. This feature came in extremely handy when taking photos of humpback whales obs ... erved doing bubble-net feeding. The telephoto capability plus fast burst enabled me to capture some awesome shots, including the wide open mouths of several whales as they were feeding more than 200 yards away from our sightseeing boat. I like the scene modes offered by the camera and have used several with great results. The overall picture quality is outstanding. I did purchase an extra battery and kept the charged backup with me. Having the peace of mind of an extra battery was important to me; as I was taking many shots each day and did not want to miss any opportunities due to lack of battery power. I would recommend the camera for anyone who would like a versatile, easy to use camera with both programmable and manual capabilities.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>SkiRunner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is my second Panasonic bridge camera. (The first one was FZ40 and it wasn&apos;t good enough). The FZ150 is much easy to use and it has much better picture quality. In between these cameras I had Fuji HS30. Probably it is good camera if you know how to find right settings, but every time it was guessing. Now I can appreciate Panny FZ150 what has lower zoom, resolution, etc., but can make really good pictures. It is still not easy as point&amp;shot, but in return it gives confidence. Of course, you need to learn how to use it and it will take time. How long? It depends much do you like to get from camera. You can have decent pictures in Intelligent Auto, and you can improve you skills almost indefinitely. Camera gives you this opportunity. The technical details can be found in many forums, ... but in any case you wouldn&apos;t regret to have FZ150.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>?</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great camera for the money.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s comfortable to carry and easy to use. Most of the controls make sense and are easy to access, and the photo quality is good - not auto-enhanced unless you want it that way. I had trouble getting the digital and optical zoom to work in concert and the manual was no help whatsoever in that regard. A summery of functions and where to find them would be tremendously helpful. I shoot almost entirely outdoors - wildlife and fairly low light. This wasn&apos;t the best choice for super crisp shots, but it was a pleasure to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>JR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Travel Zoom</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>When you have to get the shot, and you don&apos;t know it&apos;s coming, this is the just-in-case camera to walk around with. When you combine the 24X zoom capability of this product with the small form factor that makes it so unobtrusive and easy to carry around on long hikes in the wilderness, you get the ultimate idiot-proof all in one point-and-shoot. Yes, there are other superzooms out there with greater zooming range, but do they have the picture quality, small size, and ability to shoot in RAW all at once? No. All hail the king of the supperzooms; the ultimate blogging camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nubar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding Zoom Lens</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I already own the Lumix lx5 and have been very happy with it for general travel photography and have gotten some great landscape photos blown up to 16x20in. I added the FZ 150 based on reviews and the super-zoom feature. The lens is outstanding and I have been able to shoot stationary birds for example at the maximum 600+ zoom hand-held with very good results. I don&apos;t know what it is about these Leica lenses but they are the best.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>HUMMER</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I USE THIS CAMERA FOR WILDLIFE SHOTS MOSTLY. THE 24X ZOOM IS GREAT. I LOVE THE UPGRADES FROM PREVIOUS MODELS. I OWN TWO. PICTURE QUALITY IS GOOD AND COLORS BRIGHT AND CLEAR. I AM ENJOYING THE VIDEO, HAVEN&apos;T DONE MUCH OF THIS IN THE PAST. HAVEN&apos;T USE IT FOR TOO LONG BUT SO FAR I REALLY LIKE THIS CAMERA.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>HLA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Great Camera for the Money and Size</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I take this with me nearly everywhere. It is light, compact and takes excellent photos in a variety of lighting conditions. The zoom is outstanding. It is perfect for hiking, biking etc. where space and weight make a difference. The 12 frames per second is excellent for photo of birds. I cannot wait until the Hummingbird return. Photographing those rascals will be a true test of the power of the Lumix. I have a Canon 40D, G10, and the FZ150. I have not used the former since I got the FZ150. I cannot wait until Panasonic releases a 16 or 20 MP version.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeanene</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy enough for beginners, great pics</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is the first nice camera that I have owned and I am so impressed with the quality of pictures, especially without a flash. It has a lot of options, but the menu is easy to navigate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>LR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A lot of features in a small package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I did quite a bit of research before I bought the FZ-150 and I wasn&apos;t disapointed. Although I&apos;ve only had for a couple weeks I took it out the box and ran it through a few test. I took it out to the lake and photographed some Pelicans. Exposure was right on even in tough situations like bright sun shinning off the water. I was also impressed with the video. I videoed from the back of a church with half the lights off and was very impressed with the quality of the video in fairly low light. I will be taking it on vacation to CA in a couple weeks instead of lugging around my DSLR. I am excited to use it for both pictures and video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>The Soccer Dad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far so good!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We were in the market for a easy-to-use camera that offered exceptional zoom. After comparison shopping the similar Canon and Nikon products we selected the Panasonic DMC-FZ150. It was a great choice! Our primary use for the camera is documenting our family activities and we were looking forward to breaking it in during a weekend soccer tournament. It performed flawlessly. The high power zoom was great in picking up all the action from afar and the rapid shutter speed made it easy to take continuous shots. I can&apos;t comment on battery life yet as we are still working on the original charge, but I forsee the need for an additional battery because of the long (1.5 hr.) charge time - I would hate for the camera to run out of juice on Christmas morning! All in all we are very pleased with ... our purchase.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gloria</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lightweight and Sophisticated Superzoom</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great all around camera with incredible superzoom. I upgraded from the FZ28 and am delighted with the extra zoom length (24-600) and the swivel LCD. The range of options for customization are broad. This is a great travel camera. Too big to carry around in pocket.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Red</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The camera I&apos;ve been waiting for....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>After a decade of enjoying the simplest point and shoot digital cameras, I knew I was long overdue to move up in class and quality. A professional photographer friend recommended the Lumix FZ150 and I made the leap. I am only just starting to use this amazing camera but I completely love it! For me, it&apos;s like going from a Honda Civic to a Ferrari. The Leica lens and incredible zoom are worth it alone. I&apos;m getting pictures I&apos;d never get with my old camera and the ease and versatility are remarkable. That said, the instruction manual is nearly 200 pages and this thing does everything but the laundry and I have a serious learning curve to climb before I can feel that I&apos;m taking full advantage. All I can think of are the many trips to exotic places I would have killed to have this camera along ... with me. No point in lamenting the past. I&apos;m excited about the pictures yet to come.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>fhphoto</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DSLR backup</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Bought product to replace failing point &amp; shoot. Wanted raw format capability to include grab shots with DSLR submissions. Mega zoom increases versatility. Worried that it may not stand up to abuse and foul weather.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Outdoors Guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great So Far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I did extensive research on the ultrazoom options before deciding on this purchase. Narrowed it to the Canon SX40 or the Panasonic FZ150. I&apos;ve had the Canon SX3, SX5, SX10, and currently the SX30--so I felt some loyalty to Canon. But I decided to make this change because the Panasonic gets such strong reviews for performance and features, despite the shorter zoom range than the SX40. So far I&apos;m extremely happy with the Panasonic, for all the reasons that reviewers cited. The images are much sharper than my Canon SX30, I love the higher resolution LCD, shorter lag time, excellent autofocus plus handier manual focus capability, the external mic capability, and the comfortable feel of this camera. It was also very easy to learn how to use the FZ150. It was hard giving up that humongous ... Canon zoom range, but so far I&apos;ve had no regrets. Actually, the difference isn&apos;t all that great when I compare full zoom shots with my Canon SX30 versus the FZ150. B&amp;H continues to give prompt, excellent service. I&apos;m happy with B&amp;H, as always, and happy that I chose the Panasonic FX150.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Skeeter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic deal on a Fantastic camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have had this camera for a little over a week and have used it every day. It acts like it has a mini computer inside. It literally, will not allow you to take a bad picture. I&apos;ve played with all of the features and find a negative issue. At max zoom, the pictures are sharp and crisp. If I had it to buy again, I would by two!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>jgnova</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Although lighter and smaller than a D-SLR, this delivers great photos with a quality you&apos;d expect from a D-SLR. Being able to work with RAW files for finer tuning of the output is also great. The many automatic options - moving subject, low light, etc., are great when I want to be in the photo. And the viewfinder in addition to the LCD is great when it&apos;s bright outside. This is my 4th camera from this manufacturer and they keep getting better.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Safari Scott</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BrandsMart USA</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Bye Bye DSLR&apos;s!!! Syonara!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Zoom; Good in Low Light; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Ease of use; Good Image Stabilization; Excellerate Learning Curv; Amazing pictures

I researched cameras for an african safari. I looked at the Canon EOS 60D and the Nikon 3100 and 5100. The learning curve sucks, and the ease of use doesn&apos;t exist. 

The lumix is New Technology and leaves the DSLR camera&apos;s in the dust. With 24x&apos;s zoom on one lens, that&apos;s all I need.

What I don&apos;t need is a camera bag full of lenses and accessories and at the same time while I&apos;m trying to take a picture of an antelope speeding past. By the time I figured out what lens to use, my shot is long gone. 

The Lumix! 1,000 times better than a point and shoot. All of the quality of a DSLR but without the cumbersome bag ful ... l of accessories. 

Up to 50 picture bursts per second. You want fast? You got it! 

I love this camera. It makes me look like a rock star! Thank you Panasonic.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>crazy_aqua</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value for money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I just received the camera one week ago. I got the best results without using all the options, which are so many. It will need some time to learn how to best utilise all its functions. I used the AF and MF modes and was able to capture very clear and crisp photos. Also, the burst shooting mode is more than great. It captures images very fast without losing the focus and quality. I still have a lot to explore :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rangzen</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Digital Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Looking for an inexpensive camera that takes great photos--not professional but why settle for third rate results? The dial button on the right is in the wrong place-- keeps getting turned on. Focussing and saving to memory could improve.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>KJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A MARVELOUS Camera . . . .</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I needed an inexpensive camera to carry everyday, because like most aspiring Photographers, I always see pictures and do,&apos;t have a camera with me, because I don&apos;t want to carry my more expensive with me, like my EOS 5D Mark ll &amp; EOD 7D. Panasonic finally got it right, a Point and Shoot that has RAW capability, full HD video and supports a shutter release cable. This is one fine Camera for the pice and the bonus Carl Zeiss Lens makes it a a very good buy for me. I would HIGHLY recommend it to anyone. I have not found any cons about this camera. BIG Thanks Panasonic. I am a Fine Art Photographer and this Camera is Atlantis ~ ll ~ Design Studio</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>BestBuyGuy2012</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best camera I have own, quick, easy and great pics</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, pictures are stunning.

Cons: Nothing

I would recommend this camera for any one who wants to start getting into photograph, it fun, easy and the pictures are stunning, the IA feature on this camera produces great pictures with out having to know a lot of photograph. I can&apos;t wait until I start using the manual features of this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>GPDC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Versatile!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got this camera right before travelling to Southeast Asia, and got to test it out in a variety of settings- jungle, sea, beach, city. It is adaptable and easy to learn, and I was able to get a lot of great shots that I would have struggled with on a lot of cameras. I sometimes found difficulty with high-light situations, particularly if it was very sunny with a bit of haze. Would have been good to have a polarising filter, but I didn&apos;t manage to get one in time for the trip. In low light, it did ok, but was sometimes blurry (no more than most cameras I&apos;ve tried, though). The speed for AF is impressive, and the bursts are great: it is well worth getting a fast SD card if you will use it a lot. I noticed a big difference between my Extreme Pro SD card and a slower one I had as a back-up ... . Overall, I&apos;m extremely happy with this camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ernie the Travel Agent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Such a good camera, I bought it twice.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I recently purchased this camera for a 3 week trip to Europe - it was easy to use and the photos are clear and crisp. I especially like the fact that you can use either the LCD display or the electronic view finder to frame the picture. It takes excellent photos without the flash making it great for museums and other places that do not allow flash photography.The video recordings made a great addition and it&apos;s able to shoot a still photos while recording video. However, on a late night in Rome, I left the camera in the back seat of the taxi...now some cab driver in Rome has a great new camera. Thankfully we had Vacation Protection Insurance wich covered it under Lost Baggage and I just ordered another one. Best camera I&apos;ve ever owned.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Phoebus16</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I wanted a superzoom. Not a professional photographer here, but wanted something that would take great pictures and have the superzoom option but perform better than a small point and shoot. This is perfect for someone who wants better than average pictures who isn&apos;t educated in the ways of professional cameras. The zoom is great at 24x optical, and the image quality is astounding.Aside from feeling a little bit hollow, I love it. The Leica lenses are one of the best brands, so I hear... I look forward to capturing many moments.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Walt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Love the big zoom. Very fast lag time. I like having to press a button to get the flash to operate, rather than having to stop the flash from working This camera is quite light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Curtis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>In addition to taking really stunning pictures, I am very impressed with the features. If you are looking for a long zoom and are going to stick the camera on automatic, this isn&apos;t necessarily the camera for you - there are smaller ones. But if you are a semi-advanced photographer, you will love all sorts of features such as bracketing, etc. For a really high quality point and shoot without a super zoom (but that takes great pictures), try the Canon S100. REALLY nice not having to change lenses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zakman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Plenty to like about this camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use it mainly for Gun n run. Does everthing I need it to. Have had no problem. Zoom is plenty long enough for me. Video quality is quite good. Love the flip out LCD. That can&apos;t be beat. Raw files great if you need them. Mic input jack excellent. Makes for excellent audio when used with a short shotgun. Just took the camera to SXSW. Also perfect for traveling.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jptarks</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This camera takes good photos on the auto setting but I have not had time to mess with the various user settings. The reviews on this camera were all pretty positive and it was a good deal</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alan G</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Back On Top</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Long time fan of the Panasonic Lumix line of cameras, I was extremely disappointed in the previous DMC-FZ100 model but the new DMC-FZ150 in my opinion has put all those ills behind them with this new release. Great little light-weight camera with excellent photo taking qualities. The ISO limitations in the previous model have been greatly improved. I actually prefer this camera over my much more expensive Nikon D80 in many of my photo taking opportunities.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Deb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera does not disappoint</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I did a lot of research and read a lot of reviews of different cameras. I am very happy with this camera so far. I am taking a photography class and one of my pictures was voted best of the week this week in a class with quite a few DSLR&apos;s. It is easy to use and takes great pictures. My only complaint is with the Photo Fun editing program. Don&apos;t waste your time with it as there are free programs out there that do much more...much easier. Takes pictures quickly without lag time and the image stabilization is very good. Very pleased with this purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>SS1494</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is light and easy to access menus. I am using the camera for travel overseas since it has a great optical zoom. I only wish there was a more convenient way to carry the camera plus extra cards and batteries with carrying a camera bag but that goes with the territory when using a 24x super zoom camera. The software that comes with trhe camera only works with Windows except for one piece.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>jpmccormac</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Super Zoom Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The FZ150 is the best FZ so far. It&apos;s AF speed is all you&apos;ll ever need - and much faster than the Canon SX40. High ISO performance is improved and the ability to shoot RAW is a bonus. Handling is very good. Controls are good, though the rear control dial is stiff to operate. Unless I&apos;m mistaken Spot AF cannot be set as a default, but must be set back ON after powering down the camera. Some complain about the small EVF but I find it good with plenty of eye relief - for me (I&apos;m farsighted.)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Argos</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Seriously Good Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a superb Bridge camera for the beginner/amateur who wishes to get into photography without spending a fortune on an SLR. Has both automatic and manual options for focus/aperture etc with a decent 28x zoom, light yet sturdily built.
Lens not interchangeable but this is camera is fine for the type of photography I wish to do.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Porky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Panasonic</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Takes very good fast action shots. Bought for the long distance zoom with out having to change lens. We plan to use it when we trail ride. Having to carry along extra lens for the long distance shots while riding can be a pain.Plus it never fails by the time you change the lens the picture is lost(Deer aren&apos;t known for standing around too long once noticed.Haven&apos;t used the video yet.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Howard in Hawaii</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lumix FZ150</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>i&apos;m a hobbyist and use the camera to share photos with friends and family. this camera reminds me of my first consumber digital, but is so much more and of course way less expensive. its an impressive electronic mechanism and the results have been stunning. some day i hope to be able to use all of its features to the degree it is capable of. i haven&apos;t found anything i don&apos;t like about this unit and don&apos;t expect to.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nature Vision</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>don&apos;t think about it, this is it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Excellent camera!I was looking for something not so expensive as the lumix G series but with awesome qualities. This camera is for me THE BEST. Excellent settings, love it! and is hybrid so, you have 360?? of view</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Billison</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, poor weather sealing</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>I use this primarily for travel photography where a long zoom comes in handy. I use a Nikon D7000 for street and family pictures. The image quality is very close to the Nikon but suffers in low light. The problem I have with the camera is its poor weather sealing. I took many pictures at Niagara Falls and water obviously crept in. After several weeks, the internal components became corroded and the camera quit working. Panasonic said the camera was not repairable. So, do your best to keep the camera away from water. Mine is now a paperweight.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>BA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>A great little camera with lots of options for international travel and very light! A recent travel acquaintance had one and I loved his results, so I had to have one!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wanderin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have had limited experience with the camera so far but it certainly is living up to my expectation so far. I particularly like the auto features that are pretty much idiot proof.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Oregon Snapshots</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this camera again.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The FZ150 has everything I require in a point-and-shoot camera. It is light weight, easy to operate, has view finder, Leica lens, 24x zoom, shoots HD video, and shoots in RAW format--everything I was looking for, and B&amp;H had it first.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sany who loves wildlife.</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Everything one would want in a camera !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was looking for a camera to take photos on hikes, bird watching, kayaking, snowshoeing, etc., that would not be too heavy to carry and would take fantastic pictures. I feel the FZ150 fits the bill. So far, I am very satisfied with this purchase. I haven&apos;t had time yet to check out out it&apos;s bells &amp; whistles, but so far, so good. I did extensive research before asking for this specific camera as a gift. I picked the perfect camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sylvia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I love this camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a fantastic camera. My husband has always pestered me to use a tri-pod when taking close-up photos, but even he concedes that one just isn&apos;t needed with this amazing camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>REfotographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great all in one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>We purchased this camera for interior real estate shots and it seems to work pretty well so far. The photos are crisp and if you can get the ISO right, it takes great shots! So far so good after a week of use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>k9guy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Digital Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>If you&apos;re looking for a camera that has great flexability as well as great photographic results, I don&apos;t think that you can do better than the Panasonic FZ150. I&apos;ve had mine for three weeks and am very pleased with the camera. The only disappointment has been with the lack of an index with the pdf manual, but this is not a fault with the camera itself. All the features work fine and are well placed. I had to check the manual to discoved how to operate the manual focus, but once I set it up it has been fine. Probably most people will not use this function, but it was improtant for me. The photos that I have taken of wild birds are crisp and sharp even when cropped. I used the program mode (P mode), the AV mode, the TV mode, and the manual mode as well as auto focus and manual fo ... cus. Regardless of mode, the results were amazing. I haven&apos;t used the video mode, but from the reviews I understand that it takes great videos. This is not one of the lower prced super zooms, but it is worth every penny.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kae</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DMC-FZ150 Not a crowd pleaser</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Overall wonderful camera (quality, versitility, and price)- but large LCD looses critical benefits by swinging to the side instead of down. With previous models the LCD swung down, allowing one to hold the camera up above a crowd - but still see the LCD screen. Now when you hold the camera above a crowd - the LCD is at the same elevation as the camera. The attemp to gain a video camera feel by swinging the LCD to the side was a poor judgement in design. Disappointed - they ruined the versitility of an otherwise exceptional camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Back up for my Nikon D7000</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is for a vacation where lugging around DX lenses to match the performance of the FZ150&apos;s 25mm-600mm zoom would have been no fun and very expensive. So, far I have taken many pictures and I am quite surprised by the image quality for both stills and video, particularly at distances in excess of 500mm.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shokaku13</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I got this camera for my birthday, after deciding that I really wanted to make videos. I mostly use this camera to record video, but I have used it quite a bit for photos as well. The video is very nice, and the photos are wonderful as well. The zoom on this camera is amazing, when I went to Paris, some friends and I commented on the clothes people on the ground were wearing from the top of the Eiffel Tower using this camera&apos;s zoom. I have really enjoyed using this camera. My only complaints are that I wish it had a manual focus ring, but other than that it has served me wonderfully.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spamster</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very early review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We only just received this camera a week and a half ago, so I will come back and update this review. Out of the box, feels and looks great, does not feel plasticky at all. We were unable to find one in a store locally to try first, so we bought sight unseen. We also look at the Nikon P510 and the Sony DSC-HX200V. The selling point was the glowing reviews from all sources, and the simple fact that you are able to use other lenses and an external flash with this non-DSLR camera. So far we love it, but it is early, look for updates</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>MtnGirl56</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent bridge camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to use in place of my DSLR when hiking or traveling into areas where I did not want to carry all my gear. I put this camera to heavy use during a recent trip to Yellowstone and was not disappointed. I love the versatility of being able to photograph near, far and inbetween without having to change the lens and get a great photograph. The only complaint that I have is in regard to the viewfinder - no matter what I tried, I count not get a crisp clear view through it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>TTork</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this camera for a trip to Hawaii, because when you&apos;re island hopping and trekking around the last thing you need are 3 extra lenses. This camera with its 24x zoom and 25 mm wide angle starting point makes it the perfect vacation camera. The camera offers a multitude of seating, plus the option of customizable manual settings. I was able to take incredible night time images, portraits and landscapes. The video is also incredible.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>L. Harris</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My 4th Panasonic camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have two pocket 10x zoom Panasonic&apos;s and a FZ-100 That I really like. I bought the FZ-150 for my wife for she likes to take a lot of vedios and really likes the zoom on my FZ-100. So far she just loves this camera and is really happy I got it for her.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lyster</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>almost a DSLR</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this for outdoor shots . Portraits, Family and Pets. I recently shot a parade and was very happy with the still and video shots. It has been used for some indoor shots with very good results. The Leica lens is outstanding. The speed of the zoom is good and the auto focus is quick. I have a tendency to hit the menu dial when I am shooting but that is my newness to the camera. I purchased this because of the specs and the viewfinder. I have not been able to see the display on other point and shoot cameras so the view finder is an needed feature. This camera has extensive menu selections and I am still getting familar with them. I feel that this is almost as good as a DSLR.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent so far!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Exactly what I was looking for. Wasn&apos;t ready to go head first into a complicated DSLR, but was ready for more. This has it all! A full set of manual options where I can go crazy as well as the ease of a full array of automatic options that anyone can use. Great wide angle and telephoto pics, lots of regular settings and huge list of creative settings. This is not a small point and shoot camera. However, not as big as a DSLR. It is very convenient to hold, buttons all logically placed and easy to use. Has a great burst mode for taking action pics. Awsome video. Full rotating screen with easy and intuitive menu as well as a view finder. GREAT!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>RG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>very nice piece of equipment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>When deciding on buying a new camera it took a while for comparison of the different available kinds of cameras. Since i did not want to have a DSLR because i did not want to change lenses all time but a good zoom i had to buy the FZ 150. The camera is amazingly fast in auto focusing and shooting. There are all possible settings if you want to do it yourself but also a very good intelligent auto mode what is useful if you want to do snapshots. It&apos;s not to big, easy to use and the pictures and movies are very good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Richard</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Adorama</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small / Compact; Fast/accurate auto-focus; Good in Low Light; Great Zoom; Good Image Quality; Easy To Use; Short Lag Time; Nice Body Color; Large Clear LCD

Everything needed comes in the box, lens hood, lens cap, cables, charger, etc. Camera is lightweight, fast, easy to use, not much noise even at high ISO&apos;s, I love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>WimR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Multipurpose Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I purchased this unit ahead of an upcoming overseas trip. My main equipment consists of Canon 60D and 50D and whilst I love using them, carrying them overseas with a variety of lenses has proved impractical due to bulk and weight. It is also due to its size less conspicuous in places where conspicuousness could be a problem This camera gives me virtually all the options available on my other equipment, but does away with lens changes, and will at a pinch fit into my jacket pockets. The Leica lens is superb, giving beautiful imagery One needs to be a little careful of the buttons being placed close together, but this is simply a matter of becoming used to the unit. All in all a beautiful camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>JM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Purchased as a replacement for a Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ7 I&apos;ve had for many years. Tried a Cannon Rebel, but found it too complicated and cumbersome to use/carry. I am very happy with the features, photo quality and ease of use of the Panasonic, especially the multiple burst/sports modes they have added (as I take lost of sports photos at the high school and college levels).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dennis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Still learning but have an opinion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Use: quick pics of our dogs; easy to carry as an emergency backup when working Great: ease of use, no changing lenses, light weight, broad zoom range Not so great: 28 mm often not quite wide enough; limitations inherent in this kind of camera; camera might not allow for magnifying image on display screen after picture taken--but I can&apos;t be certain because I&apos;ve had camera only a few days and I&apos;m still learning</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ozdee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>more than expected by far.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>had been looking for a camera with similar properties as the FZ150, but not expecting quite as much and when i saw it at B&amp;H at the lowest price anywhere it was too good not to go for and am more than pleased with the purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>scratch0042</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AMAZING</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I haven&apos;t had the chance to fully try out my new fz150 but the features I did play with were very impressive,12Fps full resolution up to 60Fps at 2.5meg,the digital zoom very impressive.I&apos;m going to have a lot of fun with this GEM,Its going to be my new TRAVEL buddy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Camerabug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Takes Very Good Pix</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use the camera for all types of photo opportunities. I just need to learn the camera setting. Tlhe action of the shutter is fast, I like everything so far.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>jrawl004</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera for the normal people!!!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use this camera to take pictures that the average person takes. I love the quality of the stills and the video. The zoom and focus is great as well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Leicafan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Little Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have used the FZ 150 for a week mostly on wildlife and am very pleased with it.The Leica Lens is outstanding. Sample pictures are hand-held at maximum zoom.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>yeridoptero</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera,</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It is a fantastic photo camera as well as a very good video camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Larry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>everything works. macro, telephoto, color, low noise, etc</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>horse luvr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love the pictures I get. I love the video I shoot even inside at the gym. This camera will take care of you if you don&apos;t know much.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Illinijs</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been a big Pany fan having owned the FZ30 and FZ40. The FZ150 is a big step up. The bigger sensor really improves picture.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Millsy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>equilalent to 600mm lens</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Compact lightweight, excellent picture quality and clear LCD</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sparky</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I use the camera for family photos and for scenery. The camera is easy to use and takes excellent photos and videos</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gabby</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great pictures &amp; easy to use</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A light and very versitile camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I recently used this camera on vacation. No more hassle with changing lenses.The wide angle and telephoto levers are a little stiff.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ben</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Light weight, and easy to use!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Will be used for vacations abroad. If battery life is good, don&apos;t anticipate any problems. So far, so good!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dina</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>travel &amp; family photos</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ernest</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>[@] Price Per Dollars</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This is a great all round camera, very good picture quality and convenient to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>ppmin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m in love with this camera. The picture quality is great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Namret</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So far loving it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Since a previous Lumix owner, very easy and similar to operate as prior models. Pictures are crisp. Works well with Bower flash.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Android</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this again. Excellent!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Super video performance and image quality for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Amy the Sly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Lots of features in a mid-size camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is packed with features, focuses quickly, and has great image stabilization.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Doc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The DMC-FZ150 is ALL that I expected!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>We enjoy traveling &amp; cruises - so this camera will do everything and more than my Fugi 9000. The extended zoom works great!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>soulshaker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great service, Happy with camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I wish I would have bought from B&amp;H sooner. They were very fast in shipping product, and like the satisfaction guarantee.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>PhotoEnthusaist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This Camera is Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is everything it&apos;s advertised as and more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>ANN</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s very good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>It&apos;s one in a million. I love every thing about this camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photo Enthusiast</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would buy this product again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I just got the camera and have only used it briefly, but it seems to be perfect for my needs, it&apos;s lightweight and fast.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Efe Hellman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The best in its price and above</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I can use it like professional HD camera, with great results, in an amazing level of prize.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ150 12.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/13666275863948207763/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CJcCEPQCMAY</URL>
     <Reviewer>Juan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredible easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This product exactly matches what I was looking for</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

