<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Laldinfela Pachuau, PCWorld.in</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>PC Advisor</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 is an affordable compact camera equipped with a long zoom and many useful features to let you turn your moments into memorable ones. 

Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55: Design

Dressed in the complete black body, the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 has a front metallic body, and its sides and back covered with plastic. It is not as sleek and sexy as the Cyber-shot T-series nor as compact as the W-series, but it looks sturdy and serious. Due to the long zoom lens, the body is not ultra compact but would still fit in your trousers pocket unless you wear those tight EMO jeans. The build quality is excellent for its class and it is also a bit hefty at 198g approximately (with battery and memory card).

Controls placement is not much an issue and very easy to get us ... ed to. On top of the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 is a small power switch flushed with the surface, a shutter-release button with the zoom-ring, and a mode dial. The flash on the front is easy to block with fingers if not careful when it’s fired. The lens barrel covers almost half of its front and its AF-assist lamp on the corner is well-positioned as fingers would hardly find its way there.

The back of the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 is dominated by its large 3-inch LCD screen which is bright under sunlight and on its right, there is a circular 4-way directional key with the centre select button and three dedicated shortcuts – playback, menu and delete. A four-way controller changes can change Display settings, activate Smile shutter, changes Self timer and adjust the Flash. One slight issue here is the buttons placement at the back are a bit too cramped and are positioned a bit too far down which makes single handed operation slightly challenging at times. The bottom has a battery cum memory card compartment, a proprietary AV/data cable port and a tripod mount.

We are no strangers to Sony cameras, so we feel right at home using the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55. The icon-driven menu interface with tab-browsing is easy to navigate and each accompanying text for each feature made it easier to use. Even though we have to get to menu first to change commonly used settings like ISO and exposure, the menu is quite intuitive and is easy to get along. Even for first time users, this non-touchscreen interface with its accompanying explanatory-text for each features would not be an issue.

Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55: Features

The Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 is a 14.1Mp camera that uses a CCD sensor and is powered by a powerful 10x Sony’s G lens with a focal range of 25mm-250mm in 35mm term. It uses the BIONZ CCD sensor instead of the CMOS sensor found on other Cyber-shot models like Sony WX1 or TX7. Sony uses Optical Steady Shot image stabilization to reduce hand-shake effect on the images while shooting- it is available for while shooting still images and videos. It has a large 3-inch LCD screen and it supports 720p HD video recording. Sony includes its famous Sweep Panorama feature that enables shooting effortless panoramic images just by holding the shutter button and panning the camera either horizontally or vertically.

To make shooting with the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 easier, Sony included shooting modes like Intelligent Auto, Easy Mode and eleven scene modes. It also included the usual Face Detection feature with ability to find up to eight faces and there is also a Smile shutter plus Self Portrait Timer.

The Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 has Program Auto to let you adjust ISO, white balance, AF points, light metering and exposure values. Its ISO speed ranges include There is also Sony’s Dynamic Range Optimisation to bring out more shadow detail. To tinker more with the controls, there is a full manual shooting option that enable shooting with various shutter speeds and two-step aperture that ranges from F3.5 to F5.5. At wide angle, it also has option to shoot at F8 aperture stop. The included exposure bracketing feature which is a useful feature is also rarely seen on a sub 15k camera.

The Sony H55 can also record HD videos (720p) with mono audio and optical...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>deafcoder</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very easy to use and has plenty of features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy point and click, and great video.

Cons: battery use display is not proportional.

I bought this camera just before going on a trip to Paris. I was quite pleased with the performance of the camera. I could basically point and shoot just about anything. Sometimes I switched to scene or manual mode, but it does a pretty good job of recognizing what you want to and picks the mode automatically.

My only concern is the battery. It lasts a long time but the usage display is not proportional to how much time you have left. I would recommend making sure you get the extra battery so you don&apos;t get stuck on top of l&apos;Arc De Triomphe with a dead battery, like me!!

The video recording feature is also very good. Its hi def, and gets good quality. We used it to record ... sports, etc.

The drag-panoramic works pretty well but it works best for landscapes. If you try to get a person in the shot, the person may look a bit distorted because of the relative closeness to the shutter compared with the landscape.

I did a little experiement and took a 30 second exposure of the night sky on a tripod. It actually worked very well and got a nice shot of Orion.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rand</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Bang for the Buck!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My wife and I were looking for a small (pocket size) camera with high resolution and long zoom. If you done any searching yourself, you know that small size and long zoom don&apos;t usually go hand in hand. After doing a lot of research, we found and opted for this camera. 14.1 Megapixels is top-of-the-line for point and shoot cameras, and 10x zoom is fantastic for this size camera. While Sony may not be as much of a camera name brand as say, Nikon or Canon, this camera is quite impressive in it&apos;s own right. Other perks include the large 3 LCD display, panorama shoot mode, and HD Video. I also enjoy the ability to use SD cards, as opposed to having to buy all new Sony media (Memory Stick Pro). This will be used mostly for travel, leisure, and family photos, in addition to semi-pro applic ... ations through my videography business.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount>1 out of 1 found this review helpful.</HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>WooferDawg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Genuinely Impressed Again</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price for the quality and its simplicity to use

Cons: I&apos;d ahve liked to have had at least a 4GB SD/MS card

The DSC-H55 Cybershot demonstrates quality, solid results and simplicity CAN be had. There are MANY features most typical users wouldn&apos;t mess with, but you CAN get great results with it&apos;s simple automatic settings/monitoring features. Along with Sony adopting the SDHC cards WITH the MemoryStick Pro Duo format, they&apos;ve added CHOICES of media. No longer is Sony only proprietary format media use only. The upgrade to the WideAngle G-Lens (found on DSLRs) coupled with 14.1MegaPixels and HD video, gave me crisp, clear, true to color shots quickly and painlessly. Just when I thought they couldn&apos;t to much more, moving from my DSC-W290, I was proven wrong. This camera ... has been great on battery life, ease of use and some things I haven&apos;t played with yet. HD video was surprising when I found that the shake factor was removed when playing directly from the camera to an HDTV. My overall view, I guess, would be... if you want an excellent camera on a budget, this model delivers! It proves that quality, solid construction and consistent results can be had without breaking the bank. I added an example the first pictures taken with auto, even though the image most likely will be dialed back for the web.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The Sony H55 is a GREAT little camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The features.

Cons: The manual is on a CD.

The Sony H55 is a GREAT little camera. I bought the camera because I was going on vacation and wanted a better camera than the one I had. I sure is better than the old one. Here is what I like about the camera. It is small and can fit in a shirt pocket. The display screen shows you all of the information that you need such as ISO settings, flash setting, how many pictures are left on your SDHC card, battery time remaining battery time remaining. There is an auto shut off if you leave the camera on and that will save battery usage. The 10 times optical zoom range is really nice going from 25mm to 250mm. That is a BIG plus for a small camera.

I don&apos;t really make videos but I was pleasantly surprised with the quality of the ... video. You might want to read what others have written about the video quality since this is not something that I know a lot about.

One of the draw backs is that the manual is on a CD. When I was on vacation I accidentally messed up the white balance and was not sure as to get it working correctly. I missed a few good pictures but once I was settled down in my hotel room I was quickly able to figure out what the problem was and how to correct it. The easy menu made it quick for me to fix that little problem. You should buy an extra battery and SDHC card because the battery might not last too long when making videos. I bought an extra SDHC card just in case the first one failed. You can take 611 photos on one 4GB SDHC card at highest resolution. That is a ton of photos in my opinion.

So in summary this is a GOOD camera for a small price. Wait for it to go on sale like I did and it will be better!

I only rate a product 5 if it deserves to be a 5 and the H55 so far has been good. I have had it one month and so far nothing has gone bad with the camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Moretownrd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: auto and panoramic modes; ease of use; rechargeable battery; price

Cons: Wish the preview screen had a cover! Slight over-exposure in very bright light.

I really like this camera - and auto mode is truly automatic! It changes from macro to landscape in an instant. The panoramic mode is fun to use and produces great pictures. Clarity in still shots is remarkable. If you&apos;re looking for a reasonably priced point and shoot, the H-55 will serve nicely. You won&apos;t have to buy a million AA batteries either - the Sony battery is easily and quickly rechargeable. I owned a Sony before, and the technology in the H-55 is light-years beyond the old one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rodneysw</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great functionality and value in compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Functionality, compactness, price

This has become my go-to camera -- I rarely use my larger digital camera and mini-DV videocamera because the DSC-H55/B has the majority of their functions in a very light, shirt-pocket-sized body.

When traveling, I take it everywhere because it&apos;s so light and compact. The battery is postage-stamp sized, skinnier than a pencil, and recharge-able. If you tend to take hundreds of photos a day when traveling, carry an extra battery, as it weighs nothing and takes no space. The recharger is about the size of a deck of cards, but slightly thicker.

The 25mm lens can focus on objects as close as about 6 inches. Combined with a 10x optical zoom, this camera can take pictures of just about anything. It has settings for taking pictures at b ... eaches, of fireworks, and it has more obscure features like smile-detection settings.

The 720p video is not as fine as mini-DV, but the convenience of having photos and videos in one place that is a snap to download more than outweighs the image quality loss. I don&apos;t have hours of time to organize photos and videos from more than one electronic device.

The panoramic photo feature is great for landscapes and kids will love it because, with practice, you can get one person to appear in a panoramic photo twice, once on the left side and once on the right side!

P.S. if you put your camera in your pants pocket, don&apos;t carry keys or other hard objects in that pocket, as the screen can get scratched.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>californiaknick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A great camera for all members of the family</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, good price, manual mode, 10X zoom

Cons: Does not come with a camera case, you need to buy one separately.

I just recently bought this camera and there is much to learn. It has a manual mode over some other cameras that I looked at. You can simply leave in automatic and it takes good pictures. I bought the camera primarily for the 10X zoom lens. The smile feature is a bonus (the shutter clicks if it detects a smile from the subject). This camera was priced within the range that I wanted to spend and I still got features that are associated with higher priced cameras. I was sold on the camera when I found out it takes both SD and Memory stick media. Take this camera on your next vacation. I have not tested how long the battery is, but you can pick up an extra ... type G battery before heading out of town.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shawn143</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>HUGE Disappointment!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sweep panoramic mode

Cons: Everything Else!!!!

Have been looking for a point and shoot for about three months now and this was the first of four that I bought. I went to bb and asked the guy there for a camera that would take pics in low lighting, had little lag time and took great pics. He said that this camera was the one. Then I found out that this is the camera with the sweep panoramic mode and that made me even more excited. Before buying I even checked reviews online to see that the reviews were mostly great so I thought I found a winner!!! Went back to the hotel (we were on a trip when it was purchased) and went crazy taking pics. The screen was very pixleated and the color was horrible. Loaded pics onto my laptop and found them to be blurry with horrible color. ... And when they weren&apos;t blurry they were pixleated. Took it back in the morning and they said there was something wrong with the camera so I tried again and exchanged it for a new one. Took pics the rest of the day with pretty much the same results, (just not as extreme as the first camera). The lag time is horrible on this camera also so taking pics of kids is kinda pointless because you will never get the shot you are trying to with how long it takes to load in between pics. Even outside the pics turned out very washed out and very blah. Best part of the camera was the panoramic sweep. That did work amazingly and was sooo super easy to do. I was very sad to return the camera but I did end up with a camera that was the same price as this one but in a whole other league!!!! Samsung TL220 is the way to go!!! I am head over heels in love with my TL220!!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HiTechJD</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>For it&apos;s size and convenience, it is the best</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: High quality pictures in a small convenient package.

Cons: The instruction manual (on the CD) is not the easiest for anyone looking for easy entrance into the advanced feartures.

As a Zeiss lens fan, this latest iteration in the point and shoot Sony is an excellent choice. The ability to now use multi-media in Sony products is an excellent advance. It does not replace my DSLR, nor is it intended to, but the convenience and quality allows me to capture many more &quot;Sony&quot; picture moments. The Panorama feature is a nice addition, especially when you are in a tight space situation and you want to capture the entire scene in one exposure. Using Photoshop, or similar post photo prep, with this 14.1 MPX still results in excellent resolution of edited pictures. Having a single fu ... nction multi cable is also very convenient. If extensive video is contemplated, an extra battery is recommended, otherwise a full day of sightseeing and pictures has not been a problem. In my experience, this model is far superior to the equivalent Cannon and Nikon, which I also had occasion to use. It appears to come down to the Zeiss lens married well to the electronics package.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Eagle Lake Central</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Money well spent!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price; Get the extras; Nice pictures and video; Does what I want

Cons: None read instructions

Perfect for my uses. I don&apos;t see a problem with the battery life and am quite impressed at still having the same bat in the cam after 100 photos. Once you learn to set the settings correctly, I didn&apos;t see a problem with low light photo quality. GET THE BONUS PAK..spare bat, 8G card, case, tripod... save $200 by spending the extra $45. So far, So good. I really like the camera and spent a lot of time researching before purchasing it and it is perfect for my uses.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>swarup</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Picture quality is not good</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size of the product

Cons: picture quality

Camera performance on low light is worst. Captured pictured is not equal to original. Picture at edge is stratching. Its better to go with Canon - PowerShot 10.0-Megapixel Digital Camera - Black. Model SX120

The only positive point is its slimer compare to cannon &amp; it don&apos;t need extra investment for rechargable battery. Its panaroma mode is useless. No clarity.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GujuBoy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera for the Price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: HD Video, 10x Zoom, Panoramic Image Capture ,Price, Ease of Use

Cons: Slow shooting performance!

The Camera is a great buy for the price you pay. Plus its loaded with features like 10x Zoom, Panoramic Image, HD Video. The Picture Quality is real good.

Only complain is its slow shooting performance. There is considerable lag between the click of the button to the actual image capture. That is a real concern, but apart from that its a great buy...

For those who are looking for daily use and not really bothered about the shooting performance, go ahead and buy it! You won&apos;t be disappointed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BLee</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Soy has made a great camera!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The intelligent mode is a very key feature. Takes the guess work out of having to mess with the settings especially if you don&apos;t know or understand cameras. I love the iSweep feature for great panoramic shots. It takes pictures relatively fast, but my only gripe is while on the move you stop take a picture, but the shut down is a little slow. So it takes a few seconds to wait for it, before you can put the camera away. Battery life is great! I think the microphone placement for the video mode could be somewhere else, because how I naturally hold the camera my finger covers it. Overall I think it is a great camera for this price range. I have had canons in the same price range and the Sony has a vast load more feature and options. I took some shots while in a car ride going 65, and ... the stability took the picture like I was standing still. The camera lcd does take fingerprints very well, so I recommend a screen protector.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TurtleJim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Much better than what we had</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lots of features, great zoom, great quality pics

Cons: Too many features(?) flimsy construction

We had an older Sony CyberShot camera that had (by today&apos;s standards) poor resolution and no features. We loved it, but it was beginning to have issues and the pictures weren&apos;t as great as what we were becoming used to seeing. This new camera blew the old one out of the water.

The faults of the new camera are in the complexity of the features which include all sorts of features that are more for gimmick appeal than actual usefulness (smile detector, etc). Additionally, the camera saves movies to a different file than pictures. Our previous camera used this file for just random information and settings. Unfortunately, after moving the pictures to a computer, we deleted ... the memory card not realizing that the movies weren’t transferred as well. Our computer did not realize it either and made no recommendations as to what to do with the remaining material (as it usually does). Needless to say, this complexity resulted in the loss of several movies that are irreplaceable.

I was also surprised with how flimsy the battery/memory stick-hole cover is. I’m sure I will break this sooner than later. Why would anyone put something that fragile on the bottom of a nice camera? What was Sony thinking? It is my belief that the battery and memory stick will stay in without this cover (once it breaks), but I will still be ticked off. Of course, this will also be a gaping hole in the bottom of the camera that will introduce dust, moisture, and other goblins to the innards of the camera.

The internal memory is both a positive and negative feature. I (frequently) forget to put the memory stick back in the camera and the internal memory holds about as much as a roll of film (remember those? 24 per role for those of you who don’t) and comes in handy for those moments you don’t want to miss, despite your best efforts. Unfortunately, we haven’t found a good way to transferring those pictures to the memory stick, but have to hook the camera up directly to download them. This is annoying, b ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Marie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is a pocket sized camera that does alot more than point and shoot. I am used to a SLR camera so I wanted a bit of control, but I find it takes great pictures (very clear, good colour) even on auto mode. The 10X zoom is great, but you can get even closer using the digital zoom and the picture quality is still good. The movie feature was not a priority but I find I use it quite alot. While researching to purchase a small camera I found that this camera had alot of features, was reasonably priced, and had pretty good reviews. I am really happy with it and would highly recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>nothawaiian</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: All good

Cons: Nothing

Excellent camera. Very good picture quality, 10x zoom is excellent. Great look and feel, not the smallest or lightest but that&apos;s good because it doesn&apos;t feel cheap and too compact in your hands like the smaller compacts.

Panorama mode is a plus and so is the HD movie mode. 3 in. screen is nice and big and battery life is pretty good.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jdam33</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this camera! Soooo glad I stumbled upon it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything, I LOVE this camera!!! Simple to use, simple to upload pics. Takes FANTASTIC pictures!

Cons: The ONLY thing I don&apos;t like about this camera is that you have to have a special battery and can&apos;t use AA, AAA, etc.

I bought this camera on Mothers Day, got the battery charged, started taking pics and haven&apos;t put it down since. I absolutely LOVE this camera! It is EVERYTHING that I was hoping to find in a camera and more. We had a Sony Cybershot years ago, around 4-5 yrs, and got rid of it after the pics immediately after our daughters birth were fuzzy. It was the last straw and we were done with the camera. Needless to say, I was VERY skeptical to buy another Sony Cybershot. I am sooooo glad I decided to buy this camera because it has lived up to everything I wante ... d and was looking for in a camera. It is incredibly easy to learn how to use it. Pretty much just take it out of the box and start taking pics. The panoramic mode is awesome! It&apos;s a really neat feature. It is very small and compact and easily fits in a case in my purse, which was the main thing I was looking for. Small camera that had good zoom, good MP, and just overall took good pics. This camera does everything I hoped for. The only thing I don&apos;t necessarily like is that you have to use special batteries. I am the type that likes the ability to have the option to use regular batteries should the battery die, and you do not have that option with this camera. You can buy another battery for around $50 and always carry around the extra one. I can&apos;t be disappointed in the life of the battery though. It surprisingly has lasted MUCH longer than I anticipated, so it may not be such a bad thing overall. We were able to take 20 minutes of video and a couple hundred pics on one charge. I was really impressed with that, but will definitely be buying an extra battery as soon as I can. Overall, I love this camera. It has met every expectation I had in looking for a new camera and I am incredibly thankful that a Best Buy employee pointed me in the direction of it. I couldn&apos;t be happier with this purchase and without a doubt would, and already have, recommend/ed this camera to anyone in the market for a new one.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Dlane8</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice still camera with video</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Uses SD card, Great pictures, Great video

Cons: Must use Sony battery, higher end price

Very pleased with camera quality, size, and features. Video camera has great steady shot feature and zoom is allowed while filming. Nice zoom for getting closer to the subjects being shot. I bought this camera because I was looking for a nice digital video that took good stills but nothing had a flash, so I changed my focus for a nice camera that took great video and found this. Other than forced to use the Sony battery and charger, all other features of this camera are just what I was looking for. The camera is a bit larger and heavier than the smallest in this class, but with 14.1 MP and the size of the zoom, it is great and beats carrying my old 8MM video camera and digital camera ... to family events. The output of this camera is outstanding and I recommend it if you can afford it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>diggerdn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice bang for the buck</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Does many things for a good price

Cons: Flash too strong for indoor photos

I haven&apos;t fully explored the capabilities of the H-55 but so far it has met or exceeded my expectations. I wanted a relatively small small camera with at least ten X optical zoom and ease of use. The zoom and picture clarity has been fine. The panoramic feature is wonderful and easy to use. I haven&apos;t done much with the video function but from what I have done it is much better than my OLD video camera (and I do mean old). I am still printing out the user&apos;s manual of over 120 pages since I want a hard copy to refer to. So far, so good. The Best Buy price online with free shipping made it hard to pass up The local stores did not have the camera so I had to go elsewhere to see and try it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>K0810</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A little underwhelmed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, look, sweep panorama- for outside only

Cons: Picture quality, mode setup

I bought this camera to take as a 2nd camera for a photography trip (I also own a Nikon SLR). I bought it primarily because it of the optical zoom and I figured I could get a nice point-and-shoot for cheaper than another lens for my SLR. The panorama feature also seemed really cool

I haven&apos;t been on the trip yet, but after the few days of just playing with it I&apos;m a little underwhelmed. The panorama is cool but when I used it inside and uploaded it onto my computer it looked practically VGA-quality. Even in good lighting I&apos;m surprised this camera has 14.1 megapixel. I shudder to think what pictures in full optical zoom will look like.

The features and controls are easy to ... get a hang of. I feel as though some of the modes are redundant though, I&apos;m not sure what the difference between &quot;Easy&quot; and &quot;Auto&quot; is and whatnot.

I&apos;ve never owned a Sony but I&apos;ve used my friends and have always been really impressed. Now I&apos;m thinking I should have gone with the Nikon Coolpix S8000 as I originally wanted. I&apos;m a huge reader of reviews though, and the Sony just seemed better based on that

Bottom line: Not a bad camera. Looks good, easy to use, cool panorama feature, nice large diplay screen. A little slippery to hold if I had to be picky. A good point and shoot. Just thought I&apos;d get more for the money-- I feel a 150 dollar camera could&apos;ve achieved the same results
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MJ15</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worth Every Penny</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: zoom, compact size, typical sony setup, sweep panorama mode, easy mode, compatible with SD cards

Cons: lack of color modes such as black and white and sepia, lack of sunset scene mode

I am in love with the Sony H55. As an amateur photographer who mostly enjoys taking photos for the memories they capture this is beyond the perfect camera for me. I had outgrown my old Sony and was craving more from my camera and between the high zoom, rich colors, and easy mode this camera is more than I&apos;ll ever need. As an added bonus this Sony can actually take SD cards and who can complain about the 14.1 megapixels and 720p videos. I also love the compact size for such a powerful camera.

Although this camera is great, it is always a nuisance that Sony uses proprietary output con ... nectors. Also I was disappointed that this camera did not have some of the features that my old Sony had like black and white mode and sunset scene mode to name a few. Also, a more significant downfall is that pictures can become grainy without the flash.

Most of my complaints with this camera are superficial and I am very content with my purchase. I wouldn&apos;t trade this camera for any other (in this price range).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KRBsr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A MUST BUY CAMERA.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 14, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was worried about buying a camera that was not yet rated , but I am very happy I decided to go for it . I am proud to be the first person to write a review on this camera. I am average when it comes to the use of digital cameras. That said,this camera was very easy to use right out of the box. While it has several features which Dell does a fantastic job of describing to the last detail. It is not hard to use at all. I was concerned about buying a higher level camera like this one thinking it may be to advanced for me. While it does have advanced technology , it&apos;s design is very user friendly even for beginners. Once you charge the battery ,you are ready to start shooting great pictures right away.Just turn the dial to auto, point and click. It is really that easy. The camera will pick t ... he best settings for you . If you know your way around a camera, you will love the several settings and features. That is what is so great about this camera, it&apos;s for beginners, average , and advanced users. Without reading any info other then how long to charge the battery, I was able to turn the camera on and just start taking pictures. I actualy started taking action shots of my son running around playing. I then shot some stills of my garden. When I sat down and reviewed the pics I just shot, I was very happy. The actions shots were NOT blured except for one out of 15 or so. The stills looked amazing as well. That was the result of just turning the camera on and click , click , click. Great colors, crisp photos without grain showing when printed. The anti shake system works GREAT. My hands were shaking while taking the action and still shots. I thought , oh no they are going to have so much blur , yet NOT one picture was out of focus. I was very impressed. in the 5-10 minutes after turning this great camera on , I took action , stills , close-ups , and zoomed between 50 to 120 yards away as well and I only deleted 3-5 pictures out of several. The ones I did delete were because ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TechGuyintheOC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good overall point and shoot with 10x optical zoom</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Automatic mode takes good pics, fast boot up time, sweep panoramic mode, takes SD card

Cons: Flimsy battery cover, no sunset scene mode, proprietary computer/AV connection (no USB)

I&apos;ve gone through 4 cameras in a week. I started out with the new Canon SX210 which was great, just a little too big and heavy for what I needed, then two Kodak M580s (which both had different serious defects). Now here I am with the Sony. It was down to either this or the Panasonic FH22, and the Sony had a better optical zoom in the same rough size. The camera is easy to use and the menu system is overall intelligently laid out. In Intelligent mode, they hide access to more manual functions to keep things simple, but they are there (and handy) once you switch to Manual. Sony finally switched ... to allowing their cameras to accept SD cards, thankfully. The battery life is rated at 310 shots, which is good. If I get 250 out of that, I&apos;ll still consider myself happy.

The camera is comfortable to hold and seems sturdy. There is a small indent on the right side on the back for where your thumb goes. Surprisingly, it&apos;s quite comfortable and makes holding the camera one-handed a breeze if you want to take a quick shot of something that catches your eye.

Picture quality is good and from what I&apos;ve seen, overall noise-free.

Here are a few features I&apos;ve come across that are actually pretty slick. First, sweep panoramic mode. Instead of having to take 3-4 shots independently and make sure you line them up as you turn from left to right, you turn on Sweep Panoramic and press the shutter once, then turn. The camera stitches it all together on the fly. It&apos;s pretty cool. Another is the burst picture mode. It keeps taking pics while the shutter is pressed. NOTE: Get yourself a Class 6 SD card. With a class 4, I can get 4 shots off pretty quickly, but then it slows down quite a bit. This camera also has a Smile Detection feature which will take a picture when a smile is detected. You can set it for Slight Smile, Normal Smile or Big Smile, so you should be covered. Another feature that I haven&apos;t seen before is the option to set priority for which type of face to focus on, child or ad ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Rick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is conveniently sized and seems very intuitive to use. I haven&apos;t taken many shots yet but I am impressed what I have seen so far. The only negative I would give it concerns the operating manual. The booklet that comes with the camera just gives basic info like how to load the battery/memory card and identifies all the buttons and switches. All other info is on a cd so you have to have your computer available to learn all the tricky stuff. Either that or have a photographic memory.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hoggie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Compact size and weight. Takes some great pictures. Purchased for holiday use as DSLR wasnt always appropriate. The HD video was the best feature. The panorama sweep feature was simply great at the Grand Canyon</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jutta</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I stick this camera in my pocket and go. It takes wonderfully clear photos! The panorama feature is so much fun. Instructions are easy to read and remember. It is full of features. The big zoom ability is fabulous, and the pictures are clear even when the lens is zoomed all the way. The video works great. Megapixels are the feature I was most looking for in a pocket camera and this one hit the jackpot. I love it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>swingeja</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect camera for me</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 14.1 Megapixels, 10x zoom, 3&quot; LCD, Good battery life, G lens, Easy to use, Feels Solid

Cons: Small lag between taking picture and it showing on the LCD but not a real problem, only 1.8 pictures per second

I just picked this camera up yesterday ($170) and have taken over a hundred pictures. I am going on a trip to China this summer and wanted a fairly light camera with a good zoom and takes good quality pictures. It may be a little heavier than I want for traveling, but that&apos;s a small trade off for the quality and features that this camera has.
So far I like everything about it. Takes great videos, and allows you to zoom while you are recording. Sweep Panorama is super easy and fun to use. Manual mode lets you make many changes to aperture, shutter speed, iso level, e ... xposure. Intelligent Auto chooses scenes automatically and works very well. Smile detection works well as well as the face recognition.
I also looked at the Nikon Coolpix S8100, the Panasonic Lumix ZS7, and the Sony Cyber-shot DSC HX5V. S8100 has about 3 times the LCD resolution and bigger zoom, ZS7 is cheaper, HX5V has GPS, Compass, and Gyro. They all have their own qualities, but as far as one day of use goes I am glad I made the purchase I did.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>m3rcury2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Purchase of a Sony DSC-H55 Digital Camer</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use the camera for general photo taking, as I am not a profesional photographer. The camera is light, compact and easy to use. It takes great pictures and has an awesome panoramic photo option. The cons of this camera is the battery life, shutter and processing speed. Other than that it is a great camera giving you great value for your money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dj drew</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Price with many features.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I use this for point and shoot applications and for home videos. I haven&apos;t tried all of the features yet. Some have complained about the poor quality of photos in low light, but after playing with the setting a little I have not had this problem. My only complaint is that the battery life is very short. The battery seems to drain more than it should even when the camera is left off. I think this is a design flaw.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jiggyjoose</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Annoying camera for casual use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: small size, good resolution

Cons: processing speed/delays

Bought this camera to replace an incomprehensible Canon. Went with Sony because they are typically more user friendly.

This one was priced right but a few major drawbacks. The delay in photo and video processing leads to bad shots is the big one. We just can&apos;t seem to time it right. Could be a setting but gosh knows how to change that.

The other is the ridiculous amount of time I just spent loading and upgrading their 198 megs (seriously?) of software. (the good news is it gave me down time to write this review) The software itself if not as user friendly as you would hope.

Was hoping this camera was it. Probably not but we&apos;ll give it another chance.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jiro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, good price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Found good price and works great for me.

Cons: Movie files can be a problem, but do your homework.

I Iove this camera, high megapixels and high zoom. I find this camera
easy to use and I don&apos;t regret buying it. It does not come with a neck
strap[it&apos;s light enough for me]. I made one using a 30 lb stainless,6&quot; fishing leader, folded it in half, slid it behind the pin and I looped a
heavy, soft shoe lace[neck lanyards may work also] through both loops. Neck straps are hard to find, especially for these cameras with a small strap holder. Another obstacle is the mp4 format that the movies are recorded in. The newer computers will recognize and save the files. I can burn a dvd but it won&apos;t play on cheaper or older
dvd players. I&apos;m still experimenting with the sof ... tware. Some of the
photo labs will not put the movie files[mp4] on the cd. It may be on their dvd. Don&apos;t erase your media unless you can see them.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cleanupman</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera In Small Package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small Package and high quality pictures

Cons: Battery life

This is a good camera if you want to stay with just a point and shoot. It has good zoom features. I would say you will want to buy a spare battery as it uses special battery so nice to have a spare when away from home.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>randy2000</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, pictures, rechargeable and fits in your pocket.

Cons: Nothing.

I had forgotten to pack my SLR camera on my last vacation. I arrived at my destination and purchased this camera at Best Buy. Forget the inexpensive price of this camera. This Sony took great pictures. It was quick and easy to use in taking multiple pictures and downing loading them to my computer was easy. I like the fact that the batteries are rechargeable and that the camera is compact, sturdy and fits in your pocket. The cons: maybe the battery life could have lasted longer. I took hundreds of pictures, so I was satisfied.
Aloha...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>TinaLouise</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Pictures Easy to Use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This Sony 14pix camera takes great pictures, easy to use for someone that doesn&apos;t know all the techinal stuff. It has got photo software that is really cool. The zoom lense is awesome, the camera is small and light-weight. If you want great pictures without all the fuss, just use the auto program and the camera adjusts everything for you. I would recommend this. Also panaramic pictures! It&apos;s not complicated.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mabramsjf</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the beginner w/some pro-features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture Quality

Cons: Panoramic picture quality

I bought it, charged it up and used it and still have not opened the manual. The camera takes excellent pictures and the sweeping panoramic is incredible. I love that it gives you some shutter options in manual mode similar to the SLR models that cost $200.00 more.
I would recommend this to anyone who likes to shoot an occasional video as well but does not want to invest in a video camera separately. The video is very good also.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sparkly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use, excellent pictures

Cons: Nothing - it&apos;s all good

I do not use cameras much and feel intimidated by too many buttons and settings. This camera was easy for me to use and takes excellent pictures. It&apos;s a good size to carry and the battery lasts a long time. Highly recommended</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Urko</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Real nice point and shoot.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Image quality. Zoom and image stabilization.

Cons: Zoom during video.

I bought this camera as a second to my DSLR. This Sony has great picture quality and acts as a great camcorder also. The one negative is zooming during video recording. The sound of what ever you are recording cuts out for a few seconds. I tried doing some recording of a KISS concert and noticed after the fact. Within a few days I went to another show and didn&apos;t zoom. Vwala... No sound degradation. The image stabilization is also a big plus. The 10x optical zoom is great and does not blur the pictures at all. Battery seems to last a long time too and is easy to charge with the wall plug kit included. The extra charge feature does help with extended charge. Over all this is great camera. Two days after ... buying this camera, my daughter went out and picked one up too.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gabriel17</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera with some professional features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Its features

Cons: It is rather bulky

This camera has a group of features that make it an excellent tool for an amateur or professional photographer.
You can produce HDR photos with the appropriate software and the intensity feature. Panoramas come out good and the video option has good quality.
the battery has a long life giving you a long time to take your pictures.
It is a little heavy and bulky compared to other cameras that really do not have all these features.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alaskagirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The features and size.

Cons: Nothing so far.

This camera was bought for a 75 year old friend. She loves it! She can finally take photos and they turn out no matter how shaky she is. It is very easy for her to zoom in and focus on the subject. The screen is big enough that she can now see the subject and it be in the photo.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>H55HAPPY</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Compact Camera Ever!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent action shots, HD video, battery life and overall pic quality.

Cons: Noting important. Usually little things are due to user error, learn to use your settings : )

I did some research and read tons of reviews but still learned very little, too many choices! Ran down to best buy and picked up the Sony Cyber Shot W370.....took it back the next day. Horrible Zoom &amp; pic quality. Found a web link somehow that asked me every question possible and narrowed down my needs to 5 cameras that were best for me. I ended up getting the H55 just days before my river trip, I LOVE IT! Excellent battery life; action shots especially on the boat; HD video and overall pic quality! I just downloaded all the pics and videos and I&apos;m SUPER pleased! I took over 200 pics and 5 videos, ... only 2 shots were blurry...&quot;USER ERROR!&quot; I&apos;m VERY thankful I took the other camera back, this was my best investment ever. You never want to play around with the quality of a pic, you may never get another chance at that shot! Also, Best Buy price matched and I only paid an extra $30. Great Camera and easy to use features.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>2012Change</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect For Vacations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use. and battery last for some decent time

Cons: no ON button for flash, only AUTO

This camera is pretty sweet. I like everything about it. Except one thing but its not a big deal. The panorama thingy is pretty cool. You get to choose how big you want your pictures to come out, and videos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>janedoe77</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera and very low cost</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had an older Sony Cyber-shot and I really liked my camera. But then my camera was stolen so I ordered the new Sony Cyber-shot H55 and I love it! I received it just before a trip to NYC and was able to take some great shots with the panoramic view. The wide lens allowed me to take full view photos. And it&apos;s got 10 times zoom, so I was able to get some great shots at a concert and it looked like the performer was right in front of me.

It&apos;s so easy to use and turns on and off fast so you don&apos;t miss your shot. You can shoot long videos and can zoom in the video setting, which I couldn&apos;t do on my old camera. It also has a feature that accommodates your shaking hands, so you don&apos;t see it in the video or picture. The camera was lower cost than my basic cyber-shot was a few years ago and ... it does so much more. I love this camera! It&apos;s so easy to use. So far I haven&apos;t found any cons really other than it&apos;s a little larger than my last camera, but that&apos;s it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Don955</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Big Results in a Small Package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and Zoom

Cons: Weak flash when used in large rooms

Great camera for the price. Packs a 10x Optical Zoom Lens, Uses both the SD Cards and Sony card, Panoramic picture is easy and fun to use. After shopping around and looking at many cameras, this one has it all and I got it for a great price, on sale at Best Buy! Fits in your pocket and battery lasts till about 300 shots. Really good for all occasions.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nerd10</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Camera not worth the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compatible with old SDcard

Cons: Picture quality on screen

I went with this camera after initial reviews at dpreview.com but turned out to be not so good. The picture output was not satisfactory with low lights. Night vision on screen was too grany. Battery shutter was too weak and always at risk to be broken.

Good part of the camera was i could try it out with my old SDcard and didnt had to buy Sony&apos;s memory card.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MAR1VA</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fell Short of Expectations</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sleek Design, Great Display, Easy Functions

Cons: Picture Quality is terrible!

I recently bought this camera for my wife&apos;s birthday to replace our 3 year old other product. She really didn&apos;t like the size of the camera nor did she think that it took good pictures(I disagreed with both points, however, I wanted to make her happy since she uses it 80% of the time). I did a ton of research online and then went to the store. The Best Buy employee was extremely helpful and highly recommended the camera to me. I took several pictures on different setttings and on the very nice sized LCD display, they all looked great so I bought it. The first set of pictures that we took at home came out poor, but we chalked that up to new camera and just getting use to it. Mind you, I am no ... expert photographer but I love taking lots of pictures and knew that this was not a user error. We pushed on and the next day we started taking tons of pictures of our 2 little girls. We were lucky if 25% of the pictures came out DECENT!!!. I was so thoroughly disappointed in this camera. It is sleek, has easy to use functions, a great display and overall for the $$$ I thought it was a pretty good deal. Was I wrong. I also have come to find out why I would avoid Sony in the future. We originally had been using a 1 GB SD card with our old camera and will give Sony credit for finally getting on board. The problem was that Best Buy was running a deal on a bundle of camera, 4 GB Memory Stick ProDUO and case so I bought that. My wife is realizing right now that when you leave the cable at home 500 miles away that the memory card does not fit into our laptop.

Again, very disappointed.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pickypick</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great shots, li-ion battery, 10x zoom, ect

Cons: average battery life, dotted LCD.

I&apos;ve got a Nikon point-and shoot camera for four years and I think it needs to be replaced. I&apos;ve been looking for one that fits my budget till I see this Cybershot. It takes very good pics in daylight and good ones in dimmer conditions. Nevertheless, the LCD has a minor problem with scattered dots while viewing images, battery life lasts for about 200 shots with highest brightness setting. Plus, the tripod socket locates on the right may make it imbalance when used with a tripod. Overall, there are many advanced improvements that is found on this point-and-shoot camera. I prefer it to my old Nikon one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rukiddnme</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Camera, Not Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, ease of use, 720P video is good

Cons: wide - telephoto adjustment speed is slow, shutter lag, Display blacks out after all pictures for over a second

I bought this camera for the summer vacation. I&apos;m using it now to get familiar with it. So far this is what I found.
This is a good camera for non-action related photo&apos;s. The image quality is great. The camera is easy to use and movies are nice. If you are looking for a simple to use camera then this is it. After I bought the camera, I came home took pictures of my wife and kids and they look great. However, if you are looking to use this camera to capture sports action then there are some things to consider. First, the telephoto zoom is really slow. In my son&apos;s soccer game I would zoom in to get the pl ... ay on the opposite side of the field, but when the ball came over to my side the zoom was so slow I couldn&apos;t keep up to get any pictures. Second, Shutter lag is significant. Maybe I&apos;ll get better at anticipating the play and account for the shutter lag, but for now I miss a lot of good shots. Finally, the display blacks out when you take pictures. If you have burst mode on, you will not see what pictures you are taking. For this one, maybe I&apos;m missing something but it is annoying.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alejandro1972</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best camera never made.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great pics, Great video, Great ZOOM&gt;

Cons: To change some settings you need to entrer into the menu.

Best camera than I had, great zoom great colors.......................</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>shannonh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera with many options!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Editing feature

Normally I do a lot of research on things before I buy but I bought this camera on a whim. I LOVE it! The options are great. Takes excellent picture in low light. I have 3 small children and I am able to capture great pictures with them in motion. I love the editing options on the camera. The fact that you can lighten and darken skin tones directly on the camera saves so much editing time after they are uploaded to the computer! I would highly recommend this product</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Edward1101</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Potent Not Impotent</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Lots of pixels, many features, great HD movie mode @ 720.

Cons: When you take photos and press the shoot button, it takes a couple seconds to reset unless in burst or continuous mode

This is really a good versatile little camera. This will probably be the last Point N Shoot I buy as the pixels in tablets and smartphones increases.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mmmbio1685</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: wide angel lens, picture quality, panorama feature

I love the wide angel lens and the panorama feature. You can also use two different types of memory card with it</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lotus Gardner</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for travel</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought and used before trip. Light weight and easy to handle with my unsteady hands and to see with the large screen. Made great shots at dusk and sunsets. GREAT zoom feature for flowers.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>xoxoxo2345</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>good pics but video sucks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pictures are of good quality but I dislike the lag time from when you take the picture to when you can view it on the screen. My other cheaper Sony cybershot cam did not do this. Great pics even at dim light.
Hate the video. Very choppy when viewed.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture Quality

Cons: understanding features

Sony finally got with the times and ditched their propreitary format which if they had not, I would never have purchased it. This is an SD card which I like to be able to pop out on trips and readily back up to my laptop in case my camera gets lost, damaged, or stolen.

I haven&apos;t delved in to advance options so I&apos;ve only been using the basic easy shots. Most photos have been great, but I have had a few blurry ones if you don&apos;t focus/hold it just right.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>IMAZ2007</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera overall, low light ok</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>owned this camera for about a few weeks. took great pictures in DC. Panorama shots are cool and easy to take. Shutter speed is great; low light pictures not that great, but still learning the camera controls. video looks great and reason I bought it was the ability to zoom in during video recording. case is somewhat bulky, so you may need to get something different.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RAB2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, picture and video quality

Cons: Battery, not a standard AAA or AA

I&apos;m very happy with this camera. Small enough size to be able to fit in a pocket. The pictures and video are great. Overall very happy with this purchase.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lapd</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>SLOW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use

Cons: slow, grainy picture, inaccurate color.

I&apos;m not a professional photographer, just a regular guy wanting an easy to use camera. I will try not to make any judgment, just present the facts.

1) SLOW!, there is good 3-5 seconds lag time before second shot can be taken.
2) SLOW! When deleting a picture, it takes few seconds to think about it
3) SLOW! after taking the picture, your hand will have to hang at the same pose for about a second before you can move it, otherwise your picture come out blurry.
4) GRAINY! Picture came out very grainy, whether indoor, outdoor, with or without flash, auto or manual mode. Geek squad guy took a look and took several picture himself and checked it out for good 5-10 minutes and concur that the picture quali ... ty is stunningly bad.
5) COLOR! It&apos;s off! it generally give you the correct color but always off by a bit. My 2 years old Canon SD1100 had better color than this.

Feature was simple enough, anyone that knows how to use a cell phone can use this camera within 5 seconds of picking it up. It has been returned.

Even though the camera was not broken, Duarte Bestbuy was stunned by the horrible quality of picture they waived the 15% restocking fee, thank you!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sandy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Simply a best pack of features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is simply a best pack of features (10X, 14.1MP) but most importantly for a reasonable price. Most people said in reviews that it has a washed look at the dark light photoes. But i would say its there in all point and shoot cameras. For me night time also giving good shots. Very clear. I would recommend this to anyone without any hesitations.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SUSAN, THE NATURE LOVER</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>THIS CAMERA IS MY NEW BEST FRIEND</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>THIS CAMERA WAS SO NICE AND COMPACT YET ENABLED ME TO TAKE EXCELLENT TELEPHOTO SHOTS. I JUST TOOK IT TO EGYPT AND IT PERFORMED BEAUTIFULLY! IT JUST WAS SO EASY TO USE AND THE FEATURES TO BE ABLE TO EDIT THE PICTURE RIGHT IN THE CAMERA WERE WONDERFUL. IT WILL GO WITH ME EVERYWHERE NOW AND I WON&apos;T MISS THOSE UNEXPECTED SHOTS BECAUSE I DIDN&apos;T FEEL LIKE DRAGGING MY LARGER CAMERAS AND ALL THE LENSES. LOVE IT LOVE IT LOVE IT !!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>delurgio</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Too many settings</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features

Cons: Can mess up settings with too many options

My first pictures were coming out over-exposed... so I played with the settings. You really need to read every page of the manual on the disk. The camera works well, but it is easy to click on a setting that will throw the whole camera off. If this happens, click on &quot;initialize&quot; and start all over with re-setting date, etc.

I dropped my first camera at a Rental Car Counter... bad news... plastic rim had a chip... sold the camera at a used camera store for $50 and bought a second camera. The dropped camera still worked. I just didn&apos;t like it that the camera had been dropped. I didn&apos;t buy the accidental coverage the first time.

So, the lessons learned are: don&apos;t drop the camera, and be sure to know wh ... at you are doing when you change settings.

The panarama feature works well, but the height of the photo is kind of skinny. You can bracket the exposure which is a feature that is not usually on point and shoot cameras. Also you can shoot continously instead of a single image. This is good for sports or action.

This is a good camera for a beginner and advanced amateur.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Norm1414</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Movies didn&apos;t record</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Average ~ no different than other brand&apos;s cameras

Cons: What you see is not what you get

Aside from a few other dislikes about this camera such as unnatural coloring when &apos;auto&apos;, the tenancy to stretch the picture like it was a fish-eye lens, and difficulty in macro focusing... I have had a number of times when it didn&apos;t record the movie I was trying to get. This is because of the way the camera communicates that it is started/stopped recording. Pressing the shutter to start the recording displays a small red &quot;Rec&quot; in the corner. Pressing it again displays a large red ribbon across the screen saying &quot;Recording...&quot;. ...which tells me that the recording has begun, especially when I double-tapped the shutter button, didn&apos;t realize it, thought it was &quot;Recording...&quot;, and the ... n quickly held the camera above my head to film the action (viewfinder out of my site). Sony needs to seriously fix this so as not to allude to &quot;Recording...&quot; when in fact it has &quot;Stopped Recording&quot;. [grrrr!] Yes, I&apos;ve learned from this and won&apos;t have it happen again but why should I have to? I&apos;m going back to Canon for cameras. I never had any complaints with theirs.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RoyceT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>sony cyber shot DSC-H55/B</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>camera was received on time and was in good shape. Comes with a small start up manuel. Full manuel is on disk that came with camera and can be used on-line or printed out. I owned an old cyber-shot camera and this camera works a lot better and has more features. I have not tried all of the features and may never use them all. I like to just point and shoot and this camera sets everything auto so works well for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PJJP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not a true point and shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, 10X optical zoom

Cons: Requires manual EV adjust for outdoor shots, SONY battery

I purchased this camera because I used to shoot with a Sony Cyber-shot that produced really nice photos without a lot of fuss. This new camera is not a simple point and shoot. Almost all the pictures I take outside require compensating for lighting or the shot is overexposed. Regardless of using the &apos;easy&apos; mode, &apos;intelligent auto adjust&apos; mode or scene mode, the EV needs to be adjusted by -.7 to -1.3 or the shot is overexposed. This is very inconvienient and you run the risk of missing a good shot unless you remember to change the EV. This camera also was defective when I originally purchased it. A fine vertical line appeared in the photos when I zoomed in with greater than 5X magnific ... ation. Also, I would much rather use rechargeable AA batteries vice the SONY rechargeable battery.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>shemp123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good things in a small package</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 2, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Nice improvements over other Sony cameras.

Cons: There is such a thing as too many features.

This is my third Sony digital point and shoot. Some nice improvements including the ability to use SD card in addition to Memory Stick. Overall a very nice camera for the money.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shelbreez</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>It&apos;s an okay camera....</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The video, price, look of camera

Cons: picture quality, flash, screen image quality

I&apos;ve been looking for a camera to buy for my boyfriend, and this one has good video quality and sounded like it took great photos. However when we got it, and tested it out, it fell far from expectations.
We first tried the panorama, it greats but it has a bubbled effect in the middle. They still need to work on that aspect of the camera.
The video is awesome, the only reason I would have kept it. Good zoom and amazing quality.
We took some portrait shots and tried many different setting trying to make it look better. They were either to bright, too dark or when it was nice lighting it was poor quality pictures.
Then I tried to capture him jumping his bicycle and every one wa ... s blurry no matter what settings. Even burst didn&apos;t capture a good enough shot. The screen had a very pix-elated look and had kind of a blurry look to it.
I returned this camera and I definitely would not recommend it to anyone.
Hope this helps =)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nandan</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DSC-H55 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I am a Photo Enthusiast who has owned Sony products for over 8 years now. With DSC-H55 I was looking for a compact camera that had the best Optical zoom I can get from a Point and Shoot Camera. Comparing a similar product from Canon and Nikon, I decided to go with Sony because of its easy use, rechargeable batteries and Wide zoom feature. Having a lot of fun with this baby!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Red Knight</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great value for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>This Sony compact camera is in my opinion a good money for the value. The reason why I bought it is because I want a pack of good features in a user-friendly camera and I have had a good Sony camera&apos;s experience so far. The best features are the 14MP and the 10x optical zoom lens. The 720p video is also a great add to this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>UAScientist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 18, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, Sweep Panorama

Cons: Shutter lag

I bought this camera for sweep panorama feature. Overall, I am happy with the camera so far. But I am disappointed with the shutter lag time. I am missing my new born baby&apos;s action. Also be aware that this camera needs Sony&apos;s proprietary cable ( not the mini USB) to connect with the computer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BeckiQuilt</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great camera for the money!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 10x optical zoom and sweep panorama mode.

Cons: Lag time in the shutter release.

I&apos;ve been using Sony point &amp; shoots for years and they just keep improving. I got this one because I wanted a little higher ZOOM without having to bring along my Sony DSLR. Having the 10X optical zoom is awesome... really brings you closer to things without giving up clarity. This is the first camera I&apos;ve had with the &quot;sweep panoramic&quot; and it&apos;s a really nice feature. Bought this just beore leaving for a cruise and it was cool to sweep the entire port and beachline while we floated around the Western Caribbean. Haven&apos;t played with many of the features, but so far... so good. I&apos;d buy it again in a heartbeat. The only thing I&apos;m not loving is the lag time from when I push the shutter button ... to when the camera actually takes the picture. With a three year old grandbaby, I miss some of the most wonderful faces because of lag time - this camera is no worse than other point and shoots I&apos;ve owned, but no better either.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Helomom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Great color! Fast Auto Focus. Love the sweep panorama mode. Smile detector really works. It has a fairly quick recovery time between shots in Auto mode. I wanted a camera I could hand to anyone and get a clear non blurry photo. Yay!! It works!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fdparamed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Features, Function

Cons: On Off Button location and sensitivity

The Sony Cybershot DSC-H55 is a great camera for the cost. High Megapixel 14.1. Lots of good features including one shot panoramic pictures. Easy to use. Very good pictures in various condictions and lighting.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KingDad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>completely satisfied with sony cyber-shot camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: high quality pix (14megapixels)

Cons: carrying case

After examining many camera&apos;s across a wide price range I selected this Sony Cyber-shot Digital camera. the Picture Quality is excellent, lens and shutter speed is quite sufficient fore almost every need or use as my recent trip to Las Vegas &amp; the Grand Canyon will attest too.

I bought it as a package with expanded memory card, extra battery &amp; carrying case, this saved a few dollars. Only knock is the case is a tad small of this camera. Camera fits but extra battery makes for an extremely tight fit to the point where you are concerned about trying to fully zip the case without it ripping. Camera and the other parts are all A-OK! I&apos;d recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fishnut99</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Tiny equals BIG</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Video is excellent.

Cons: Glare can obscure the screen, making a foto difficult.

When I first started with this camera I had problems with the size. I was used to camera&apos;s a bit bigger/bulkier. But as I got used to it I found it performed quite well. Biggest problem was not having a viewfinder, but I managed. I don&apos;t need to carry the instructions as it is quite simple to manage the setting. Sunlight on the screen can be a problem, but so far it&apos;s the only on I&apos;ve found. A good camera to carry around for all purpose use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rockgirl</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great EASY to use, high quality camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: All around...Great. Price, functions, ease of use

I want my electronics to do a lot without being difficult. This camera is great! The panoramic function is fun. You really get more out of each shot. The battery life is super long! I recommend this to anyone.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Kermode73</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony goofed this one</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>The camera falls way short. A 14mp camera, yet photos are quite grainy, even in full Phoenix, AZ summer sun. The flash is right in front of the wide-tele switch, so you will often cover the flash. And the flash is quite useless, no power at all, forget anything beyond 4ft. The panoramic shot, while really neat feature, is a typical picture cropped to a small strip, so the picture goes down to about a 2mp quality. I used to own a Sony DSC-707 and it took much better pictures than this one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mzkwazi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, ease to use

Cons: No &quot;on&quot; feature for the Flash (auto setting). It&apos;s only auto &amp; off

Purchased this camera as a bundle special in June. Great price! I just returned from a trip (Jamaica &amp; Cayman Islands) and the pictures came out wonderful! Vivid colors and picture quality is good! The only I would like is for the automatic settings to allow you the ability to change the flash to &quot;on&quot;. The flash is only has the auto &amp; off function (very minor complaint). I&apos;m pleased the camera. Still exploring all of the features on the camera). One unique feature I am really enjoying is the music feature when viewing the pictures in a slide show.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bigeyedbear</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a Great camera for anyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Intelligent auto, movie mode, smile feature, price

Cons: If I set the camera correctly I have not found anything wrong yet.

I bought my Sony camera a few weeks ago and, I am still learning more about this camera each day. I have found this camera to be a very good all around camera. The flash is out of the way of your fingers and, the battery last quite a while. If you want you can buy the white charger which will charge your lithium battery about twice as fast as the supplied black charger. I learned that I needed to buy a fast memory card so, I started with an SDHC class iv but I want the fastest which would be the Sony duo HG memory card so I will be able to take pictures faster. This camera can be easy to use but, be carefull with program auto or, manual as they are ... a bit more complicated.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My opinion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 1, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Well, I got this camera after reading some reviews out there. I confirmed that they are true... The images show a lot of noise on the screen when shooting indoors. Greatest advantage is the zoom. I also found that the videos are quite better than I expected in really low light. I filmed a night light parade at disney and the videos look good. However in daylight i found the video quality to be mediocre. I have a canon sd780 and the video mode is significantly better than the sony. I would say it&apos;s a pretty avarage camera. and would recomend it only to the people that want to shoot tourist pictures, general things and people in front of land marks. That&apos;s it. The panorama mode is great, but only works with lowresolution..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jdlegg</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 10x optical zoom

Cons: low-light image quality

Researched cameras for my dad &amp; found this gem. After ~15 minutes of using his camera, ended up buying one for our family road trip. It was bundled with extra battery &amp; case for ~$250. Panorama feature is pretty cool &amp; was used extensively on our trip to nat&apos;l parks. Self-timer allowed for &quot;family photos&quot; along the trip as well. 10x optical zoom is fantastic / works well with steady-shot -- helps see detail (when reviewing pics) that you didn&apos;t realize was there. Marginal low-light image quality, but would definitely recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JMMariotti23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, but ...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: See &quot;My Review&quot; above.

Cons: See &quot;My Review&quot; above.

I really think this is a great camera! Especially for its price! It just takes time getting used to, and knowing the camera. One thing I do not like however is where the flash is located. Although it’s on the front of the camera (like all cameras), it is by the &quot;shoot function&quot; button. Because of this, you might easily, accidentally block or cover the flash with your fingers. That can result in a bad quality, dark photograph. But maybe this is just something that&apos;s curbed with time and practice! Overall, I think you’ll be happy with camera.

P.S. Prior to this camera, I was a loyal Cannon guy for years! I did not even like a Sony camera I was gifted back in 2004. But as of date, I’m happy with my Sony purchase. T ... his camera definitely lives up to Cannon quality, and compact.

P.S. II. This is not an ultra slim camera which easily fits in your pants pockets. It is a bit bulkier, particularly because of its zoom lens. I recommend a carrying case to keep it wrapped around your wrist or neck.

JM
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NishNish</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cant ask for more..</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Nothing

I got my camera today and I absolutely love it! I had a Sony camera before for 2 years and lost it recently so I bought Sony H55. I was scared whether it might be good or not but it proved me wrong. It&apos;s crystal clear and the camera itself looks gorgeous (better in person than the pics online). The best feature is the panorama.. its so cool. If you&apos;re a Sony camera fan, you&apos;ll love it and the camera is worth the price. And also the shutter speed is fast.. you don&apos;t have to wait like 5 seconds to take the picture. The zooming is also very good. So, I would recommend any one to buy this camera especially if you&apos;re interested in photography. 5 stars from me! :)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrsHang</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Clearity of pictures, features and ease of use.

Cons: Everything is great!

I just exchanged the Olympus Stylus for this one today and so far I&apos;m satisfied with it. The picture is super clear, I love all the features such as the sweep panorama, smile detection and so on. It&apos;s super easy to use and is convenient due to it&apos;s smaller size. It&apos;s not replacing my Canon DSLR but its great for just everyday shooting so I don&apos;t have to bring that huge thing around with the lens and all.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bonnell1330</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Worst Camera Ever Owned</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The Panoramic Feature

Cons: Very short battery life, LCD screen has spots, everything becomes red, low quality pictures

This camera is one of the worst cameras I have ever bought. The pictures come out red, or fuzzy. There is a horrible delay, if you want to take a picture at that moment to catch something spectacular... you cant! Bought the camera to take for my vacation in Disney, I was so disapointed. In very bright sun light the pictures do come out better and the camera does snap faster (sometimes). Even outside they come out blurry. I had to take the same picture 3 or 4 times till it finally took a decent picture.
There arent really any features on the camera besides the panaromic thing. Which is pretty cool, dont get me wrong, but the camera seems really cheap ... . Especially for the price. There are cheaper cameras with more features and better quality.
The LCD screen has a big spot that came out of no where.
Overall, its a very frustrating camera and so not worth the money spent. I&apos;m returning it and getting myself a cannon.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Prae</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The panoramic capture, no light pictures, SDHC card instead of standard Pro Duo

Cons: Battery life and lcd is a fingerprint magnet

Okay I purchased this camera after reading several reviews on it. I knew the battery life was not that great so I did not hesitate and purchased a second battery. First off right out of the box the camera took absolutely beautiful pictures outside. Crisp and clean. Once you get indoors you need to work with the settings a bit to get the best picture quality that you personally like. Overall a great camera. Can be used right out of the box. One of the major reasons I bought this camera was because I have always liked Sony personally but never cared for their memory cards. With this camera you have the option to use either the Pro Duo card or ... the SDHC. I also got this camera on sale as well so it was an even better deal.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Hula</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Unrealable camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 17, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: New features and the look

Cons: LCD screen fulll of dots, everything becomes red, low quality pictures

This camera is one of the worst cameras I have ever bought. I had polaroid five years ago and gave it out for making everthing blue. I have sony 7 MP it has beter pictures than this 14 MP also it has better abs clear LCD while this camera&apos;s LCD doesn&apos;t show real pictures it has dots jumping all over the screen. Pictures becomes red. In bright light it can give clear pictures but this scenario doesn&apos;t inldude taking picture inside a normal house or to a party or when not standing direct under the sun rays. This camera does not have quality better than low megapixels and cheap cameras. The manual mentions dots on LCD are normal to this model, but I wanted clarity of both ... pictures and LCD not dots. This was going to be my second Sony but I&apos;m disappointed and shifted to panasonic 12 MP that is a bit expensive but it has nice pictures and is reliable. I did return Sony the next day. Dispite new features I wouldn&apos;t advice someone to buy this model even for a cheaper price.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Big Mark</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for beginners, Good for pro&apos;s</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera to use at an upcoming wedding, but also to replace my old mega-zoom digital panasonic. This camera exceeded my expectations for a compact mega-zoomer. The colors are great, the shake-reduction technology is terrific and the sweeping panorama option is unique and it works well. As with all non-dslr, there is noise at low light, but still takes good shots if you give it time and up the iso. Overall, compact, long battery life, many options for memory (I went with an 8gig memory stick, but it will take sd cards) and easy camera-to-computer transfer make this a powerful compact mega-zoom and the HD video aint bad either.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ashok</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>It gives very good pictures as it has the power of 14 MP backed up by 10x optical zoom. We also have the provision to set the resolution/MP to a specific level e.g. 10MP. Really a good to have stuff. I tested it for recording video also ... gives MP4 format and good quality videos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LiveMusicStudent</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing camera for the money, sound is great too!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros

This Sony camera is not only easy to use and has many customizable options, but it has been perfect for the live music shows and student events I document on a nearly-daily basis. Musicians who request footage from me after shows have been very vocal about how good the sound quality is, especially for such a light consumer camera.

Cons

The only problems I have had with the camera are under extreme conditions, such as poor lighting or heavy movement. This is not the camera&apos;s fault and is more of a consumer-camera issue than anything. It is not an SLR-replacement, so be aware that if you try to take still pictures in low light or with movement, blurring or graininess may occur.

As a Sony product, this item uses a memory card that may not be compatible with an ... y other brand so that may also be a con (though it will work with many Sony products, which can be considered a plus).

Overall Review

As a student on a budget who was in need of his first camera in order to take pictures and videos of events and shows, I can say that I am very happy with choosing this camera. This camera makes you want to use it, which is the best endorsement I can make.

Based on my experience with this camera, I want to stress the importance of buying two large memory cards (8 gigabytes each or higher) and an extra battery. If you intend on taking a lot of video, especially for live shows and events like I do, you will find it invaluable to have an extra card and battery in your pocket. Make sure to buy them on sale though.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DANomite</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera performs well,exellent pric.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Out of all tbe cameras I previewed the sony cyber shot is the best camera you could find. I love the sony panoramic setting is an amzing feature, its zoom is good. There is only one thing with the camera that I am not so impressed with, there is a lag between the time you press the button take a picture and the time the it actually take the picture. I find myself moving the camera to see if it is working properly just takes a few takes befor you get used to it. All and all a great camera for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cutiiex0</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good Camera except for one problem.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality of pictures and different settings

Cons: Weird half moon shape on the LCD screen that happened for no reason...

The camera I purchased was excellent besides the fact after having it for a month and using it on two different occasions this half moon spot appeared on my LCD screen as if something damaged it which was impossible since it was kept in the case and had not been dropped or anything. I brought it back to best buy and it has been sent out to have the LCD replaced rather then getting a factory reburbished camera. Hopefully this will fix the problem because I love the camera and was so sad to see that happened to it for some unknown reason.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>diane175sewing</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: size, viewing screen, shooting speed

Cons: nothing yet.

This is a great camera. I previously owned a Sony Cybershot, but it was larger, and I was looking for a smaller camera. This one fits in my pocket, was very user friendly, and it shoots faster than my old one. I would recommend this camera. so far the battery is holding up well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Morrie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>[...]</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 22, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>My new Sony camera is easy to use, good instructions. It is small with big features. It will be used on our future river cruise to Germany,and other parts of Europe. The prints will be okay to enlarge to poster size.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>oldmomof6</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony camera for the helpless</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I appreciated this camera immediately since it took clear pictures of family members in poor light conditions. I was tires of grainy, unclear family photos. This camera, on automatic, chooses the best settings so I don&apos;t have to guess. I can just point and shoot indoors and out, in all kinds of light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Grandma Paparazzi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera bundle is worth the money!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I really enjoy this camera. It could use a few more features, but it is the perfect no nonsense, shoot anywhere without guess-work camera. I like the light weight and the picture clarity.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Spandauer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features

Cons: Nothing yet.

My old Sony camera finally gave out and I temporarily replaced it with a Cannon and hated it. I bought this camera about a month ago and have yet to regret it. The pictures come out great. Even the ones taken in very low light. The menu is easy to understand.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Suncity</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Megapixels, great features, user friendly

Cons: battery life

Sony has always produced good cameras, this is another one. Im satisfied with the quality of pics it takes and how user friendly it is to operate. Only complaint is short battery life.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cptpk</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great and easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use

I didnt like using my husbands Nikon D-- SLR, to much camera for me, so he bought this for me for Christmas. I have used it several times in still photo and video mode. Luv it. Thanks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DjRebelXtreme</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High Quality Photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great all around

Cons: No internal memory

I was shopping around for a well priced, high quality photo taking with a nice looking camera not bulky or large.... If you&apos;re looking for great pics with some nice features try this camera, No problems with it so far, It seems to be the camera I have been looking for. I have been looking for a camera like this for a long time, and it takes great 720p Video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VeryDisappointedInSony</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: nothing

Cons: everything

I had high hopes for the Sony H55, I even tried to force myself to like the picture quality. But... I just couldn&apos;t do it to myself. Reds, greens and blues are heavily saturated. Browns, oranges and reds all come out looking red. Flesh tones don&apos;t even look real. And it gets even worse when the flash is used. I wanted to upgrade cameras to have memories, the H55 takes reality and puts a fake color scheme over it. The zoom is good and so is the 3&quot; screen, that is about it. Just returned it today. Save yourself the time and look elsewhere.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lynn123</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not good for fast photo shooting.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: bulky/heavy, slow, and blurry

I purchased two Sony 14.1 Cyber Shot cameras as Christmas presents for my daughters. We are very disappointed with the shutter speed. It takes about 8 seconds to take one photo. We recently visited the city, and it was impossible to take a group picture without it blurring. The colors were distorted, not defined and blurry. There&apos;s no way you can take candid action photos either. For example, if you see something you would like to capture with your new camera, it takes so long to shoot that your subject has already moved. I&apos;m very disappointed and surprised at Sony, the Cyber Shot has one of the best lenses out there for it&apos;s size, but what good is a G lens if you are unable to take a good picture!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KLR7247</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use, holds battery charge</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good picture, good battery life.

I love this camera, the battery stays charged for a long time so I&apos;m not constantly trying to charge it. It&apos;s easy to use and small enough to fit in my pocket or purse. Would definately recommend if you want a good picture from a small camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Naebovi4</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>That lens is sucks</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy in use.

Cons: Lens

This camera easy in use, has a big screen and bla bla bla, but biggest problem is lens! I bought this model only because I lost my previous Sony camera with Carl zeiss lens, and I really like it, but this one I want to return. So problem is, picture is stretched at the corners (like longer than normal).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hedlund19</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, ease of use

Cons: Dosent display the time and date.

Great Camera with a great picture! Ease of use and clarity is great. I couldn&apos;t ask for better. Price was right!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BlancoCooper</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera for What I Use it For</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I needed a camera that had 10x or better optical zoom but was still a pocket camera, and it needed to have a mix of point-and-shoot and quasi-professional features. I use it for high-resolution covers for audio CD cases, family photos, and for web-page content. This one works extremely well in all lighting situations. It gives you as much or as little control as you want over image size in pixels, manual or automatic settings, etc. On rare occasions when I use the digital zoom, the ability to select a 14 Megapixel image file means that cropped photos still have excellent resolution. This camera&apos;s ability to shoot at extremely close range is also a plus. And the price was right. The PDF manual is very well organized and easy to understand. I would recommend it to anyone who needs a quality ... pocket camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>eahaas</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Somewhat disappointed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is very attractive and the body is well designed. Battery life is excellent. However, the picture quality of flash pictures is very grainy. My old 5MP camera&apos;s flash pictures are sharper. Also, there is a substantial delay between shots when using the flash which results in lost opportunities.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Clarese</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I LOVE THIS CAMERA!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is capable not only of taking beautiful pictures but also great videos! I have taken pictures that I needed the zoom for, and they come out as clear as if I was standing there.
II use it for everything as it is small enough for mmy pocket and easy to operate.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DarPal</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Camera for Good Price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>As every other Sony camera, image quality is great. It&apos;s a very good point and shoot camera with 10x zoom and 14MP. It would have been great if it would have viewfinder as well, but you can live without it. Easy to operate and carry! Thanksgiving deal made it an easy option to purchase</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>grandma2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, easy to use, so many features!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 10, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, great pictures.

Cons: haven&apos;t found anything wrong with it yet.

Really love this camera! Great for the price. The pictures are clear, even in a darker room. I rarely need the flash. The panoramic feature is cool. Highly recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Too much Blur, motion</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Compact for a 10X Camera

Cons: Pictures with too much motion and/or blur

It is simply impossible to get consistently good pictures.

About half the time they have blur, motion streaks. When they do not have motion, they are not sharp or clear, dark. I am very dissapointed since I was lookig for a compact camera, with high zoom, lightweight and not too bulky, but it simply does not consistently take good pictures.

Pros are that it has good video recording with good sound and I like the panoramic feature.

Unfortunalety I will return.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jhdrumhead</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good features for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The zoom ratio was my primary motivator for this purchase. Pixel rating was an incentive also. The features for manual settings(shutter speed and the like)seems decent, although not all that familiar w/ it. Ease of use for the standard operations was pretty much the norm and performed rather smoothly.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrScott</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I like it a lot...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 25, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 10X Zoom, SDHC or Memory Stick storage options

Cons: On a 1-10 scale battery life is a 5.5 so buy a spare battery

This camera was purchased as a replacement for a Sony DSC5 that finally gave up the ghost after nearly 6 years of use. I was specifically looking for a H-20 but those are hard to come by and this is the obvious successor (albeit smaller and slightly less capable). Picture quality is good especially when using &apos;pet mode&apos; . The 10X zoom was the big selling point and works well.

I&apos;ve read some negative reviews of this camera and can only say this: Never base your opinion of a new product on any failure of performance within the first month or so. That one item (or group of shipped items) may have suffered a catastrophic event in handling prior to purchas ... e. If you purchase from stores like BestBuy or Target or Walmart the return/replacement policy will give you at least one more chance on which to base a more accurate opinion.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>njb80</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Complicated; needs a class in the use of it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Panorama shots possible.

Cons: Learning how to use the features.

I like the panorama feature. The camera itself is complicated so I have not had much success with it. It is certainly versatile; takes stills, movies and panoramas. It has much promise.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>115</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VAGrandad</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: High resolution, great zoom, reasonable price

Cons: Too many modes, shutter lag, red-eye flash leaves shadows

I bought this to replace my 4 year old Kodak - I was looking for more megapixels and a better zoom lens in a compact camera. The camera takes very sharp pictures (with one exception - see below), and the zoom lens is great (10X). The camera has many different modes, including full manual, &quot;Easy&quot;, program mode, and something called Intellegent Auto Adjust - too many for most users. The casual user will never need them all - I&apos;m still tying to learn what they are after 3 weeks. The Intellegent Auto Adjust mode has a red-eye reduction flash that seemed to leave shadows of the subject on the image - I changed to the Program mode and the problem went away. There is a ... noticeable lag between pressing the shutter and seeing the picture in the view finder - somewhat annoying. Also, realize that the &quot;10X&quot; zoom is not really 10X, since the camera starts at a wide ange (which is nice) - the actual zoom from normal view is about 8X. All in all I&apos;m very pleased with the camera - a good buy.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>116</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>merle</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So faf I love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 3, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I really enjoyed this camera. The images are excellent. The Sweep Pan feature is a great feature, I will use it over and over again. I would recommend this camera to anyone, it fits into my shirt pocket.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>117</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JimJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Incredibly easy touse and get high quality results</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything

Cons: nothing

the auto scene selection makes this camera very easy to use and get great results. HD movie mode plays back great on my HD TV. Steady shot feature is the best.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>118</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NMBP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>We really like the camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>My husband and I got this camera and really love using it. Picture quality is very good and the special features rock (we have gotten so many pan. shots!) Can be a little complicate to navagate the first time using it. Long battery life. Only thing we aren&apos;t crazy about is that the time betwen pictures is a bit long.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>119</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>amurphy327</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quailty and Ease

Cons: software

I go to lots of Nascar races and sit front row so getting great pictures are very hard. This camera was very easy to use and my pictures are excellent quality even the picture on the LCD is great. I am not to fond of the software but I am getting use to it so it is getting easier.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>120</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: everything, esp. the manual setting

Cons: nothing so far

I bought this camera for twos reasons. One I needed a new camera and two I needed a new camera that took good pictures at concerts. I bought the camera last Wednesday and I went to the American Idol concert last Saturday. Before the concert I messed around with the camera and loved it. But I told myself that if this doesn&apos;t work well at the concert, I&apos;m returning it. Lucky enough it worked wonderful at the concert. The Manual setting is wonderful. Having that feature on the camera made my concert so worth it. I had 3rd and got some amazing pictures.

oh and the video setting takes amazing videos. I took 3 videos at the concert and the sound and picture is so clear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>121</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>carnut3</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera even for a beginner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was really nervous. I bought this camera 2 days before heading to Hawaii. I had no time to practice or even charge the battery. Took great pictures, no problem.
My only complaint was the owner&apos;s manual for anything advanced was on CD. I thought I would read on the plane. I didn&apos;t know how to operate Panoramic or other features.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>122</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bob</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This little camera can DO BIG THINGS</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera never ceases to amaze me. I have owned it about 2 months and I have taken over 1200 pictures under all circumstances. I carry it with me everywhere. I am a serious amateur photographer who owns 3 digital cameras, and has owned many more. I take hundreds of pictures a month, and my specialty is journal photography of events and nature shots(lots of indoor, outdoor and macro shots). The image stabilization is incredible (supposedly double stabilization). I got great shots from a moving boat of moving skier. The wide angle (35mm equivalent f 25mm, yes 25mm) is so convenient for indoors and scenic shots. The flash looks so tiny yet can fill a room even a wide angle. It can do automatic scene selection almost perfectly, face recognition too. It goes to macro mode with no se ... tting change. The 10X optical zoom is smooth and accurate, and with IS I have gotten incredible hand held pictures. If you take a lots of pictures, get a spare battery (under $10 on line). You will love this camera. I hope this one lasts A LONG TIME. Bob in Florida
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>123</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CrazyMe2010</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>What a wonderful camera...!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: HD videos and quality pics

Cons: none

After shopping around and looking at many cameras, this one has it all and I got it for a great price. You get to choose how big you want your pictures and videos to come out. HD videos and overall picture quality…!!!

Take this camera in your next vacation...!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>124</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pianom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very easy to use!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use...right out of the box.

Cons: Battery life. But, I did use it all day, so not so bad!!

This was a great camera for my trip. It is easy to use and the features are great. I think the best feature is the panoramic option....great pictures! Glad the bundle included an extra battery. Battery last for a good day, but you will need a backup. This is the only negative to this great camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>125</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Asher</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera with quality shots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The camera features are cool and the panoramic Sony feature is wonderful. Video clips made up pretty nice (720p). The only thing that I notice about that it is a little bit slow when shooting serial pictures (one by one on short intervals).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>126</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LostinTransit</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not enough time.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 9, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 14.1M and all the features oh and 720 video WOW

Cons: nothing that I know of.

I bought my camera at the end of June and it was lost/stolen at the airport by the 4th of July weekend. I loved my camera and was looking forward to taking it with me to Afghanistan. The features were just what I was looking for in a smaller camera. I love that you can use the manual exposer and the easy panoramic shot. I just wish we had a little more time to be together. :-(</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>127</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dragonf1re</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Panorama setting is brilliant!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 29, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this particular model because it used the same memory card and battery as my other camera, but is much, much smaller for when I want to just grab a camera for small trips or random use. I found out that this camera had more than I expected than just a small, fit-in-you-pocket size. I love the panorama setting! I&apos;ve used it several times now and it&apos;s so convenient! I used to have to paste together a series of pictures in photoshop if I wanted an extended shot, now I just click, sweep, and upload my pics!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>128</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Looking-for-the-best-inexpensive-camera</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Have had 4 excellent Sony cameras and this is the best of all. Incredibly low price for the many features and quality of the camera. I thoroughly researched to find the camera I wanted and found this at a bottom low price. Just returned fron a vacation trip with my children and took over 500 photos with excellent results in all different types of situations.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>129</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gunni</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for a beginner</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 27, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: User friendly and clarity is excellent

Great camera for a beginner. Excellent clarity and user friendly. Can take images as well as video. I have used 8 GB memory card hence its good for both video &amp; camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>130</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jim</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not quite as good as I had expected.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>In the Intelligent Auto Adjust mode it tends to wash out objects in bright sunlight...often times I have to manually lower the brightness setting. Sometimes it seems that the pictures are not as crisp as they should be...almost as if it is not in correct focus. (I am careful not to take the picture until I get the green light.)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>131</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ktrc88</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I LOVE THIS CAMERA!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 16, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this camera right before visiting San Francisco, California. My favorite features are the panoramic and auto-focus(not sure about the name). It automatically recognizes what setting the camera should be on (landscape, back light, nighttime...etc). The panoramic is AWESOME... I absolutely love hanging pictures and I took one of the Giants baseball stadium... it looks professional. I plan on blowing it up and hanging it in my house somewhere!!! The zoom is also incredible. We we sitting pretty high up in the stadium and I could zoom in enough to see facial features of the players. You will have NO regrets!!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>132</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wilson929</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME camera!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 4, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, great zoom, wonderful picture quality.

Cons: Battery life is on the short side.

I have always had Kodak camera&apos;s...I loved my kodak camara that I got from my parents as a graduation gift. So four years later when the camera stopped working clearly. I went straight to kodak&apos;s website and chose a camera. My husband surprised me with the camera I wanted. Well from day one the camera&apos;s picture were poor, the camera froze up all the time and was just awful. After several month I took it to best buy and they tried repairing it three times. Finally they gave me a store credit and I was able to choose another camera. Well I wasnt sure what I wanted and the sales associate asked what I wanted I told her I wanted something to take awesome pictures but that wasnt as b ... ig and expensive as a DSLR. She took me right to the Sony Cybershot and I fell in love. It takes awesome pictures, easy to use and the panaroma feature is so awesome!!! Love the camera!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>133</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>lovepictures2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 10x optical

Cons: panorama mode needs more develoupment to improve image quality.

10x optical gives great pictures at any distance. the panorama mode is really neat, i gave picture quality as 4 stars because that feature doesn&apos;t have great quality, but what can you expect with a new feature, it works good though. regular pictures have great quality. over all a really great camera, especially for the price tag</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>134</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pnut22</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent value and easy use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, and takes wonderful pictures

Cons: Only thing is dial for settings will turn while in pocket so you have to make sure setting is still correct

I just got this camera a month ago and took it on vacation to Spain. It takes wonderful pictures with great ease and I didn&apos;t have to do a lot of fiddling with settings. It&apos;s lightweight and easy to carry and when you have neck arthritis it helps to not have a heavy camera around your neck. Only drawback it that the dial for the picture settings turns easily so you have to be sure to check settings when you get it out of pocket or camera pouch. Otherwise, it&apos;s a wonderful deal.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>135</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JessT55303</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 31, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to Use, good price, great pictures

Cons: Battery life could be longer

I received this camera for Mothers Day and I absolutely love it. Every time I use it I find something else new about it. I usually go with Kodak cameras but thought we would try something new and the gentlemen at Best Buy was very helpful and recommended this camera and we couldn&apos;t be happier, we absolutely love this camera. We have used it for kids sports, a Twins game, etc.. It doesn&apos;t matter if it is light or dark it works great.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>136</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paytonsmommy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent P&amp;S Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 26, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I replaced my aging point and shoot camera with this Sony. It is fantastic. The Sweep Panorama feature is so nice and takes a really wide angle. Pictures are clear and crisp, the level of detail that can be achieved is amazing. The face and smile detection features are very accurate and make snapping a few quick pics a breeze. I have owned it less than a month and my friends are already buying the same camera when they see the results. Have yet to find any drawbacks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>137</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>DenverGuy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very satisfied</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love the 10x zoom and panorama features

Cons: slow on time between shots

I am very satisfied with this camera! The panorama feature is great, so easy to use and very cool play back that pans left to right exactly as you shot it. Really like the small size and 10x zoom. Also, using the &quot;Easy&quot; mode without flash gives me pretty bright shots in dim light situations - much better than another camera a family member was using side by side.

My only complaint, and it&apos;s a minor one: the &quot;reload&quot; time between shots is a little slow. Otherwise, this camera has been fantastic.

I&apos;d buy it again!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>138</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>zxpilot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>OK Auto Focus Camera for Under $300.00</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 21, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome Daylight Pics

Cons: VERY POOR low light pics

I am hard on cameras, had 4 in the last 8 yrs. I like the AUTO cameras, the more it does in automatic the better for me, I&apos;m NOT a professional photographer
This camera has a Intelligent auto mode which I tried outside and inside my home during daylight hours, it worked awesome ! great pics!, then I took it to my 17 yr. old daughter&apos;s high school Senior Ring Ceremony in a dimly lit auditorium , in the Intelligent auto mode in low light I didn&apos;t get any of the ONCE IN A LIFETIME shots I bought the camera for, pics were so blurred they weren&apos;t worth keeping. The camera took too long to focus, &amp; shoot again. The manual said that in the I-Auto mode , it would shoot anywhere, anytime, auto adjust for scene selection ... . I thought it would do just that, that&apos;s why I bought it in the first place!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>139</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Truth176</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love This Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use, you just turn it on and go. It automatically adjusts in ANY setting even the living room with just a lamp.

Cons: Battery life seems short but I may not have charged it all the way.

Ths camera is the best camera I have ever owned. All you do is turn it on and shoot. It even takes great pcitures in the livingroom with nothing but a lamp for light. I&apos;m not at all electronics savy and this camera works great for me. The panormaic shot mode is awesome.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>140</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>alia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great product, though a bit bulky</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 19, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Overall this is a great camera and much better than my previous Sony camera. I had compared this camera to others and even experts at retailers were telling me this is a better camera.

The HD movie feature with zoom is great though, the sounds is recorded in &quot;mono&quot; as oppose to &quot;stereo&quot; mode.

The pictures are very good and the iAuto scene selection feature is quite impressive. It automatically detects the scene and picks the appropriate setting.

The panarama feature is nice though the details of the picture can be fuzzy.

Overall, this is a good buy and I recommend it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>141</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CrystalT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great picture quality, zoom, easy to use

Cons: The red light when flash isn&apos;t on

This is my third digital camera in 3.5 years. The first one I got was when I didn&apos;t know anything about digital cameras and it was only 6gb. I sold it and bought a Kodak M1093 IS that worked amazingly but after a while I noticed things about it I did not like, and then 2 weeks ago I bought this camera. I was focusing on mp when I bought this camera and picture quality as well as zoom. So far this camera has done wonders and I have really enjoyed it. I&apos;m 22 years old and in college and working a full time job so when I am not busy, I am pretty much always taking pictures. Yes, in the future I would love to upgrade to more of a professional camera, but for now, this is just what I need. The p ... icture quality is amazing and it just what I want. I definitely reccomend it for anyone who wants to capture all the moments in their life.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>142</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Photo man on all Vacations</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My sony cyber-shot camera is great.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good Value; Charges Quickly; Reliable Performance; Long Lasting

My original purchase included a back-up battery. It would not charge. Buydig replaced the faulty battery. Once shipped, the replacement battery arrived in a few days. It charged overnight and has been working well. Thanks buydig for replacing the faulty battery, no questions asked..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>143</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Paula</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice images.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Good Image Quality

This camera has an excellent Optical 10X zoom, images can be seen clearly and with rich colours. Also using the 20X digital zoom photos have many details, you can apreciate like lines in a wall or symbols in a stone. 720p video looks great when played in my laptop and it does not have blur or moving lines like in other camera&apos;s brands, thanks for the mp4 format, very, very portable. Nice panoramic photos, I use them as wallpapers. Only one thing I couldn&apos;t do with this camera was shooting the moon or filming it, may be I have to 
read the manual with more calm. SD Cards supported, nice move!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>144</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GmasterFJ</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Beach Camera</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony all the Way</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Mega Zoom; Flawless Finish; great

Cons: Focusing takes a while

So far the camera is great. Since it is a Sony I expect it to last for a while. It looks amazing and the pictures are fantastic.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>145</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Sam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>True value for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>finally i got something that gives me great pictures with both daylight and night modes. I can still say this camera is compact inspite of the 14X zoom it provides, sweep panaroma moode is an added advantage (not sure how much that helps for quality photos). Just get used to the right modes and settings, and u will have the best pics out of these for you favourite albums.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>146</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BdRet</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>New camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the sharpness of the pictures

Cons: the size is a bit big

The Sony camera is very easy to use and takes beautiful pictures. Even at full zoom, the pictures are sharp and clear.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>147</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>feather</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>VERY IMPRESSIVE!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is, beyond a shadow of doubt, the nicest little camera I have owned to date. I have owned at least 7 digi cameras over that last 15 years of varying degrees of technology - This is on the top of the list. The zoom is amazing. the panoramic feature is impressive. The clarity of each pic is astounding. It is so easy to get perfect results! BRAVO!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>148</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nancb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Sony camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The grip and reputation of the Sony name brand

Cons: have no complaints so far

My choice was between a Canon and the Sony Camera. What helped my decision was the grip of this Sony camera. I think it is important to have a comfortable fitting camera. I&apos;m quite happy with picture quality and menu selection. This is our first quality digital camera so we don&apos;t have too much experience as other writers and nothing to really compare it to. So far so good. It sure is easier using these smaller cameras compared to our former 35 mm that used film. Therefore, we have no complaints. I tried the Canon but it felt like it would have just fallen right out of my hands.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>149</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Blurrrr</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I would purchase this all over again if had to</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: awesome camera with all the features you will ever need

Cons: zoom button is decent for men&apos;s fingers

I love this camera...Have had nothing but awesome pictures from it...many awesome options for such a small camera. Only thing I&apos;m not excited about is the zoom button. These small cameras are great, but really are not made for men. Most men have big fingers &amp; even though this is the best one that I found for this situation, it&apos;s still not ideal. Not to say I wouldn&apos;t purchase this camera again, cause I would in a heart beat.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>150</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jerry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good Camera.. Decent pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Camera gives very good and clear pictures. Good for indoor and generic outdoor photography... The add-ons that come with the package is a good deal for the money. The Tripod could have been a little bigger. Though it is good shaky hands to get perfect pics, not really good for others.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>151</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>allenlid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Stunning and fast and uses SD cards!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy, quick, high quality, durable, panoramic

Cons: Only 720p video, proprietary data cable, external charger

This camera was bought for a specific purpose. I went to New York and wanted something that could stand up to the rigors of shooting 200+ pictures a day and be able to be small and also have 10x optical zoom and a high pixel count.

I bought an extra battery for this purpose and it worked out great and my pictures are absolutely stunning.

Sometimes when shooting in low light with the flash off, if you&apos;re not used to the camera it takes blurry shots. I had someone take a picture of me inside that had never taken a picture before with this camera and that shot was ruined. Too bad I can&apos;t get it done over again.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>152</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lastochka</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good product. Takes great pictures!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I like this camera for the ease of use and it makes great pictures. We are using it for video too, and during the day it makes great videos. But I haven&apos;t figured out yet, if there is a way to record video at night. Otherwise good picture quality, clear and sharp pictures.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>153</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>scoopable</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera easy to use, high quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Battery life

Cons: Didn&apos;t come with a carry case

Point and shoot, thats the best part of it. Very easy to use, and the battery lasts a long time. This camera replaced a camera where I had to replace a battery every time I used it or charge batteries after every use, this camera is awesome, have owned it for 1 month and haven&apos;t had to recharge the battery yet. Highly recommend this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>154</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Willsey63</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>The camera is a very good compact unit.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: compact and easy to use

We bought the camera for our daughter and she really likes it! It has some amazing features and she is playing with it all the time. She broke her old camera several months ago and was using her phone for pictures.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>155</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Judeanew</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I was surprised at how much I love this camera. You definitely need to use the manual but it was easy to use and read. One time through and I had it! The video&apos;s are crisp and the pics wonderful. The hardest part was figuring out the camera to computer to Facebook. I got it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>156</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HappyBoy1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Dell</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome Picture quality + good deal for the bundle</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 22, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I bought this as gift for my girl friend&apos;s mom and she loved it, Personally my favorite is the Sweep Panorama mode. It has good picture quality and very useful features like bracketing for somebody who needs more than a basic P&amp;S camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>157</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>L_LM</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera !</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Overall it&apos;s a great camera with a good picture quality. The 10x zoom is amazing. The only thing is the shutter delay; it takes several seconds more (compared with other cameras) to take the picture. However, once you get accustomed it doesn&apos;t really bother.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>158</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>69Camaro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera, Good Quality Pictures &amp; Videos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: HD Video

Cons: Nothing

I bought this camera for my daughter&apos;s birthday. She loves it! It&apos;s easy to use and takes great quality stills and HD video. Can&apos;t beat it for the price! Can&apos;t beat Sony products for vesatility. We only buy Sony Digital Cameras.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>159</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>juanettam</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 12, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent pictures, 10x optical zoom, panorama capability

Cons: Haven&apos;t found any negatives yet.

Purchased this camera while waiting for my Nikon D3100 to arrive. I wanted to capture pictures of Thanksgiving Day. I was amazed at the quality of the pictures and the zoom capabilities. The panoramic scene is great. I have attached 2 pictures taken, one with zoom and the other using panorama. The zoom picture was taken of a stop sign a block away while standing on my porch. The car in the driveway was so close using the zoom. I am not disappointed with my purchase. The negative reviews are just that, negative. The camera is easy to operate and has some nice features so a beginning can use it right out of the box.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>160</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-H55 14.1 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/312792261530707062/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CLYCEPQCMAg4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shutterbug</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>More Than Enough Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 15, 2010</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Originally ordered the Sony WX-5 and sent it back. This camera DSC-H55 is every bit as good and with the BuyDig package got a spare battery and case for $100 LESS !! Camera is compact and easy to use. Can be used Manually or Automatically and seems to have good battery life. So far my only problem is the software provided for downloading pictures, they download but still having some minor problems with sorting them, E-mailing them, etc. The camera itself though is GREAT !!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

