<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff Keller</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>DCResource.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DCRP Review: Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good photo quality for target audience; Packs a 20X zoom lens into a compact body; Optical image stabilization, with 3-way &quot;active mode&quot; for movies; Super-sharp 3-inch LCD display; Very snappy performance, especially autofocus; Good set of manual controls, which include white balance fine-tuning and bracketing; Two &quot;intelligent&quot; auto modes pick the scene mode for you; Built-in GPS with compass; Anti Motion Blur and Handheld Twilight modes produce usable photos in very low light situations; HDR feature dramatically improves image contrast; Fun sweep panorama feature (now with high res option), works in 2D and 3D; Continuous shooting as fast as 10 frames/second; Helpful in-camera guide; Records Full HD video at 1080/60p with stereo sound and use of optical zoom, continuous AF, and imag ... e stabilizer; Best-in-class battery life

Cons: Lots of detail smudging, even at ISO 100; Tends to underexpose -- highlight clipping can be an issue at times; Redeye a problem, though it can be removed in playback mode; Only two apertures to choose from at any one time -- no shutter or aperture priority modes, or RAW support; No manual controls in movie mode; Ten shot limit in burst mode, even at 2 frames/sec; Design annoyances: custom button hard to reach, controls on back of camera are small and cramped, no room for fingers when flash is raised, USB port on bottom of camera, memory card slot inaccessible when using tripod; Internal battery charger is slow, prevents you from charging a spare; Deafening &quot;beep&quot; sound when buttons are pressed (it can be turned off); Full manual only available on the Internet

Overall, I enjoyed using the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V, and had the same response to it as I did to their HX200V super zoom. It&apos;s a responsive, fun-to-use camera with some genuinely useful extra features (HDR, Anti Motion Blur, Sweep Panorama), a decent set of manual controls, and a top-notch movie mode. It&apos;ll never win awards for its photo quality, though it&apos;s super high resolution means that downsized photos look very good. If you&apos;re looking for a GPS-equipped travel zoom camera, then the HX20V is well worth considering.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HX20V Happy time!</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Newegg.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Zoom, obviously. 
Great Low light shooting. 
Very quick with proper Class 10 memory. 
Great macro for getting tight clean detail @ 5mm I think. 
Great video @ 1080p. The mp4 compression is not bad, also does AVHC and looks great. 
Sound recording is surprisingly good. 
Good size
GPS Taging, Tracking
Awesome panorama feature. Very effective application on this camera. 
30&quot; exposure time, with caveats.
Easy to navigate and operate
On camera help to get you going fast
Lots of bells and whistles

Cons: Price drop of $40.00 @ &quot;big box&quot; retail chain within the time it took to ship. 

Weight is left of your grip, feels unsteady @ times. Not a deal breaker @ all just say&apos;n.

Paper instructions are worthless. Just use the in camera help. &lt; ... br&gt;
Will only do 4 sec exposure on the highest save format. 30 second exposure possible with downgrade of save format. 

At magnification, the normal &quot;grain&quot; of a digital photo is very modeled. Built in software seems to try and blur and group color pixels rather than defuse it. Looks great @ 100%, but once you go beyond 150% the digital messing about it evident. 

No raw format. All images are jpg. A result of what they do above I would imagine. 

Feature can not be turned off, it&apos;s part of the brand now I guess.

Just buy the HX30V. The are other differences, but the main being Wi-Fi. Big advantage to have.

Would like to have the ability to turn off and on the rendering it does to individual pixels. Maybe have other choices for that. 

It&apos;s a very impressive camera. Very nice overall results in both stills and video. Great image stabilization for video too.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SonyGotBetter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT camera - HIGHLY recommend it!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: excellent low-light pics, HD video, powerful zoom

Cons: price.

as many have already mentioned, it&apos;s expensive, but it&apos;s worth the money if you can handle the price. you get what you pay for. The low-light pictures are fantastic for a point &amp; shoot--much better than my old sony DSC-T100 that always had orange backgrounds in low light or flash shots. i find myself taking much more pics w/o flash now compared to previous cameras. the flash is very powerful, too, which is great for dark settings. I took a test pic of my living room (which is fairly large) w/ the lights off at night and the flash made it as bright, if not brighter than, the room w/ the lights on! the zoom is great and the clear image zoom really does produce smoother pictures than traditional digital zoo ... m. it has a background soft/blur feature that simulates an SLR camera, which is nice. the video is great, too--HD is so sharp. Actually, the VGA video looks not too bad and takes much less memory. being able to take stills while recording video is a convenient feature, too. the digital leveler and cross grid features for setting up your photos are also very nice features. battery life is pretty good. if anything, one minor drawback is that there are so many options/features that it can be overwhelming and takes time to adjust all the settings if you care to do so. overall this is exactly what i wanted: a camera that is better than a cheap point&amp;shoot, but not as big nor as pricy as an SLR or those hybrid-SLR&apos;s w/ interchangeable lenses.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pug1311</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Huge Zoom! Fun 3D Many Options! Solid in Feel

Cons: Manual online only

This camera is wonderful. Solid in feel which helps holding it steady. Zoom is incredible. The 3D pictures, when viewed on my Bravia 3D TV are really impressive. Not native 3D but very, very close to it and very impressed that this 3D is created on the fly in the software. Tons of options. Took a day or two to learn the menu and still learning it but it&apos;s mostly intuitive. I like the built-in help guide for each feature. The manual is fairly good but it&apos;s only online. That&apos;s about the only thing that I can fault. For the money, a manual on CD would be appropriate. Otherwise, an excellent camera. If you have a Mac, you need a program to bring the 1080/60p/i video into iMovie. ClipWrap from the App Sto ... re works great.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AQMartin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good, but pricey</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: zoom, video, low-light performance, features

Cons: pricey

First, there is no problem with the door to the battery/SD card locations.

I find this a great little camera with lots of features and very decent image quality for a mega-zoom point&amp;shoot. The auto-focus is good, the flash works well, macros shots work well. For me, this is an upgrade from an HX5V, which was ok, but often too slow to use. This one is much better. I just wished it costs less...there are a lot of features make make this camera not as easy to use as it might be, but hey, at least you have options. There should be a decent manual here some place so you can study up on the usage to get the most out of the purchase. I hope Sony releases one soon.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tute2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An excellent camera for travellers</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>The product has very image quality and many useful functions. It has a great zoom, above the average from similar cameras; also the digital zoom is ice, but not the best. Sony seems to have corrected a problem with the battery lid (in earlier models, camera powers down when the lid is touched). I found two cons: the flash pops-up from inside the camera body and it&apos;s wrongly placed (just where the finger holds the camera). The other cons is that battery won&apos;t last much when 1080p HD movies are recorded, as it consumes too much energy</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>VDOMKR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Nice but missing some things</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Phot and Video Quality

Cons: Missing cables and acc. that should be included

Camera is great and takes awesome pictures and video, problem is their is no external charger so if you buy an extra battery like I did you have to charge it in the phone which prevents you from charging a battery while you are shooting. They make an external charger, but of course, you have to pay extra for it. The camera has a mini HDMI port for viewing on a television, but this is also NOT included and is sold as an extra accessory. I&apos;ve always been loyal to Sony and prefer Sony cameras. I also own the A55, which I love and I&apos;ve owed other Sony Point ans Shoot cameras that came with all of the accessories needed. Sony really dropped the ball on this one by forcing you to buy extra accessorie ... s that should have been included, especially at this price. I&apos;m going to use it over the weekend as I have a concert I wanted to take it to, but this goes back to the store the next day. If you don&apos;t mind not getting the once provided accessories I mentioned or if you simply don&apos;t need them, you will love this camera. It takes exceptional video and photos, but it really is overpriced for what&apos;s included.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wartoni</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best compact digital ever...if you can afford it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pictures, zoom, HD movies, in camera charging.

Cons: Nothing

Few cameras are great and this one is better than its predecessor (HX9V). One of the best features is you only need one battery and never need to take it out. You charge it in the camera via a simple mini USB cable ( I charge it from my MAC USB port!. I also charge it int eh car while driving on trips so it is already charged when I want it. The battery life is good and I have never ran out of battery.

The HD video is great and the pictures are excellent with the auto mode.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>newwin</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>One of the best point and shoot fameras</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Many Features, Good Pictures, Easy to Use

Cons: Bulky and expensive

Loved this camera from day one and it is exactly as advertised. Easy to use and the pictures come out beautifully. Camera does use up battery quickly, is bulky, and is expensive. Luckily, Best Buy had this on display so I knew what I was getting into. Take advantage of the Price match deal that includes pricing online.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>LoveSummerPhotoOps</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love this camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome pictures for a point and shoot

Cons: Where the flash is located

I wanted the compact DSLR but it was out of my price range. I settled on this little gem instead and I&apos;m so happy with my purchase. In fact I&apos;m glad I didn&apos;t go with the DSLR this camera suits my life. Fits in my purse perfectly and takes awesome pictures!!
My one and only complaint is the flash. I know its there but friends don&apos;t - when I hand them my camera to take a picture the first one is always dark....
Overall it was a great purchase and I don&apos;t think it was too expensive. The quality is that of a DSLR and have you seen the price for those??</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Reconguru</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best in Class</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: This camera does fantastic in low light conditions

Cons: Nothing comes to mind

Purchased this camera to replace Sony HX9 that was loaned to friend. This is hands down the best Sony camera of its class that I have owned. While it is a point and shoot, you have complete control over the camera settings if you want or need the. The video is amazing, especially at night. Low light images are spectacular and seldom blurred. While I use the camera for business, I took it on vacation to practice and learn more about it. Over 1400 images of superior quality. This camera is super easy to use and has great battery life. You will also love the zoom, for such a little camera, it has a lot of wow factors. Expensive yes, but you get what you pay for.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shakxxx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Oh yeah.Great digital camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I was in rush and wanted to get a good, small but I wanted something that I can zoom farther. Lucky me!! I found this camera out of no where, just what I wanted. Soooo many function that satisfy your desire. Only one very small issue, if you are taking a photo of something very small thing, u might have issue with foucsing. It takes a while till to get the focusing right.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BremertonGuy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera for everyday shooting</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 30, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: panorama feature is the best

Cons: Manual mode is hard to get used to

I am a still life / landscape photographer who bought this camera after testing it in the store. I was amazed at the stitchless panorama feature and have found the picture quality to be excellent for the sensor size.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lweberfoed</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Compact size with quality pictures.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size is small, but quality is top notch. Has a lot of special features if needed.

Cons: Battery does not last as long as I had hoped, but recharges quickly.

The camera is small, but takes great quality pictures. There are many features to the camera and is fairly easy to use. Love it!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MadSquabbles</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Features, Poor Image Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Video is the best among the P&amp;S I&apos;ve tried

Cons: Over aggressive noise reduction and sharpening causes images to have an impressionistic affect when zoomed in.

Out of the box this is probably the camera that gave me the best looking photos (not including the m4/3 or dslrs) that i&apos;ve tried out so far. The only disappointing feature is the noise reduction Sony uses. It&apos;s far too aggressive and gives the images an impressionistic look. Everything looks fine when reducing the resolution, but looking at the images at 100% you get some terrible quality. I have a tendency to look at images at 100% because i work in printing and I always edit images at 100% magnification and I&apos;ve never seen images look so terrible at full size.

I went through a lot of soul searching ... before i decided to keep the HX20V. I&apos;ve had the Lumix ZS20, Samsung WB150F, and the Canon SX260. Of all 4 cameras the Canon wins hands down. The quality is far from DSLR or m4/3 but the best of the group. The Canon&apos;s IQ was so much better than the Sony that I could actually blow up the photos to 6000x resolution and have better detail that the Sony at 4890x resolution. Everything about the Canon was better except GPS acquisition and video quality.

Originally I had no intentions of using the camera&apos;s video recording capabilities, but after doing a few of my daughter I found it extremely convenient. And this is where the Sony won me over. The Sony records in full High Profile L4 at 1980x 60fps. The Canon&apos;s quality doesn&apos;t come in the video department. Because of this one feature the Sony is the keeper. I really wish the Canon&apos;s video quality was better because its photo quality is tons better than the Sony. The saturation and contrast that the Sony displays can be mimicked with bit of tweaking.

So, basically, if you want a good camera that takes great pictures if you&apos;re not going to zoom in - get the Sony. If you want great pictures that look good at all zoom levels, but may need a bit of PP to sharpen up get the Canon.

I&apos;m hoping I don&apos;t end up regretting my decision. Every time I zoom in I cry inside a little.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JAWS2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great so far</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: anti-shake system

Cons: nothing so far

Just got this a day ago and it took some great pics at the ball game. Fireworks pictures came out awesome just using the fireworks setting, didn&apos;t have to change to manual. Pictures are nice &amp; clear, even the action shots.

Was able to charge it up and use it the same night in about 2-hours. User friendly...didn&apos;t have to read the whole book. If you&apos;re familiar with cameras at all, you will be able to use this one easily.

Grip is good, you can hold it with one hand. Only thing I had to adjust to (and they all seem to have this now) is that the flash pops up right where you tend to hold the camera.
Not sure what one of the other reviewers was talking about with the battery compartment door not being flush. Mine i ... s flush. There is sort of a lip, but the door is flush.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KCOLOR</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>DESIGN FLAW</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Creative features: sepia / bw / vivid / watercolor tool / illustrative tool. Good Zoom, Great Auto-Macro feature

Cons: Battery compartment cover designed flaw.. Flash position. Price

I have only owned Sony cameras and was very excited about this model: GPS, CREATIVE TOOLS, PIXELS, ZOOM. However, I was surprised and disappointed when I brought the camera home and inserted the battery. The battery cover does not sit flush with the bottom of the camera and I could actually see the memory stick sensor light when I closed the cover.The spring is weak and the cover is sloppy. Worried about dust, moisture, etc.. getting into the camera. Returned it for another one which was a bit better but still not flush--I can not see this camera lasting for more than a year or a few vacati ... ons. Tried diferrent memory sticks in it too, and it still didn&apos;t sit flush. Worse with an SD Ultra stick which was what was recommended. Actually think I will have to duct tape it when on vacay in windy / dusty / moist areas. Is this a design flaw because of the TransferJet feature? Don&apos;t know if I will keep this camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wiesiu2012</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>High Quality Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent Photo - Video Quality, Easy to use

Cons: Expensive

This is an excellent, easy to use camera with high photo and video quality. This camera does it all with a very simple to use menu system. The lens is very sharp and zoom is perfect for everyday use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tweetie</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>TOP NOTCH CAMERA</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Before I purchased this camera I did a lot of research. I was looking for a small handy camera that I can carry around ,take images that would print out looking like SLR shots , and that wasn&apos;t too pricy . Seemed impossible first but then I found the Sony hx20v. I read a lot of information on many cameras. Some of which had RAW imaging and where cheaper than this camera- imparticular the canon S100. But as I did further research I realized that the pros that this camera had outweighed the pros of canon S100. This little camera is a great steal. Firstly the price is right. Secondly the image quality is totally out of this world! I take it wherever I go and I&apos;m able to take amazing pictures- pictures that look like they were taken with a big heavy SLR!!!! People were so amazed that such a li ... ttle camera could take such good pics. There are many different features that compliment this camera. It is very useful that Sony tells you what each mode does so you are able to search easily for which mode is best in each circumstance! One of my favorite features is the blurred background which makes the picture look real professional. Also after you take a picture you can save a second image and make it look like someone drew it or you can make it look like someone made a watercolor painting of it-- it&apos;s really cool! Sony&apos;s special clear zoom feature is incredible it enables you to take pictures at 40x with the same depth and quality as if the scene were right near you!!! No need to worry about blurry zoom anymore!! Besides for the superb image quality in every situation and besides for its awesome zoom and great features this camera is superrrrr fast!!! You are able to take up to 10 pics in 1 second!!! Now how is that to top it all off?? This camera has absolutely no cons whatsoever!! It has only brought happy clear memories. Buy this super amazing camera --- you&apos;ll have no regrets!!!!!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeff3030</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Video Should Have Been 12MP</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Video quality

Cons: Image quality

To start with, if you have this camera or purchase this camera you should turn the sharpening to low when photographing. This option is available in the P and M modes. If you&apos;ve read reviews from camera review sites you know when zoomed in to 100% at 18MP the image is not sharp at all. In customer reviews I&apos;ve read many of them mention &quot;watercolor effect&quot; and &quot;artifacts&quot; when viewing an image the HX20V at 100%. There are actually 2 things going on with this. First the camera CCD/lens absolutely can not produce quality images at 18MP. Sony I&apos;m sure was aware of this but likely thought they could sell more units if the camera was 18MP vs 12MP, which it should have been. To compensate for this Sony in the image processing software has the ... camera sharpening the images way beyond what it should in order to try and give the poor quality images the effect of sharpness. This is creating the majority of the artifacts in the images and heightens the watercolor effect. Before purchasing the camera I made sure it had a sharpness adjustment and tested my theory with the camera. I wasn&apos;t going to purchase it unless it did have the adjustment. When you go from low to standard to high sharpening, you can see the artifacts and watercolor effect get worse and worse in camera when zooming in all the way to an image in playback. No real resolution is gained by increasing the sharpness, the lines actually look more jagged and the images just look splotchier.

I did a image test comparison between my Canon 12MP 300HS, which is 1 1/2 years old, and the Sony HX20V. At 12MP the images from the Canon are just starting to get soft. The HX20V at 100% as I stated earlier look very poor. Downsized to 12MP (4000x3000) the resolution of Sony images look equal to the Canon&apos;s. Some areas of the frame look better on the Sony while others better on the Canon. Increasing the resolution of the HX20V&apos;s images from 12MP does nothing but create larger files, no true resolution is gained. I wish there was a ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mntmama</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love the zoom

Cons: Needs better battery life.

Love the camera, especially the zoom. Have Canon powershot bought this due to better zoom. Like many of the features. Have a Nikon DSLR camera, using this Sony more often than the Nikon.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>flipicaneze</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A lot of features, great pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great photo and videos, GPS

Cons: Top quality video recording is jumpy on playback

I buy the HX series for the GPS tagging features, I stick to Sony for the quality. This camera does take great shots and has quite a few features not in the HX9V, the camera I upgraded from. The GPS lock-in is far faster than the last generation.

The video recording seemed to look jumpy on playback, even with a TYPE 10 SD Card, might have to get a faster card to make that work better.

I just wish someone in Best Buy&apos;s marketing department would&apos;ve included the HX30V in their selection so I could have the WI-Fi features. Best Buy won&apos;t let you have it all I guess.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MichiganBuyer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fantastic product!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome picture quality, zoom, slow shutter delay, great in low light

Cons: Nothing

I purchase this product after being disappointed with a Fuji Finepix S2950. This camera has really high picture quality and even under low light the pictures are good. No photo noise is observed even at ISO800 which is what the automatic settings use when running at moderately low light levels. Photos do not get blur due to slow hand movement during capturing. (Well they obviously will in any camera if we move too fast). But a fairly steady hand is good enough for this camera. You can avoid having to use a tripod for most part. Fits in pocket!. So its really good for travel.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Panther05</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera for Sports</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Continous Shooting mode, ease of use

Cons: ???not sure yet

I bought this camera to shoot my son&apos;s sporting events. I was looking at an SLR but did not want the bulk and I wanted something I could put in my pocket. I have taken pictures of baseball and basketball games and the shots are amazing. People are amazed at the speed of the camera and the shots that I can get in such a small, compact camera. I like that it fits in your pocket and is easy to use. I would recommend to anyone who wants a small camera for sports.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>vernonfish</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Travel Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 18, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Long zoom for a compact camera with sharp pictures. Very good low light performance. Very good image stabilization.

Cons: Sometimes pictures look like paintings or mosaics. I wish there was a raw option.

This is a great camera for its size. Generally, the pictures are pretty good. I don&apos;t see why there needs to be so many pixelsm though. 18 Mega pixels isn&apos;t useful in my opinion.
As for ease of use, this camera is pretty easy to use, but if you study every function, you could see how there are many benefits to make every situation easy to photograph.
I doubt, however, that you&apos;ll be able to take pictures that are worthy of magazine covers with this camera. When you pixel peep, you&apos;ll see why.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Thoughtful</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is a great all around camera.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 7, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: It is easy to use. Takes great pet photos. Has an &quot;onboard&quot; help system.

Cons: The pop up flash is placed where you naturally hold the camera. The panaromic setting is difficult to get right.

We bought this camera for our vacation, but also wanted a camera that would take good pictures of our pets. It provided excellent shots on of both land and water pictures while on vacation and does an excellent job of pet taking pet pictures.

The &quot;onboard&quot; help system was very useful in learning how to use the various settings on the camera. There are many settings which help you taylor this point and shoot camera to get the best pictures possible, w/o purchesing a prosumer or professional camera.

My main disappointment is in the panaromic setting. You have to actuall ... y &quot;pan&quot; the camera across the scenery you want to get a picture of. If you don&apos;t move the camera at just the right speed and angle it does not work. Also if anything moves, like a tourist, in front of the camera&apos;s view it messes of the panaromic shot.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>heehee62</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera overall but with some weaknesses</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: picture quality, high zoom, light and compact

Cons: can hear zooming in recorded video, port covers, flash location

Overall an excellent camera. Great still and video quality. Love the high zoom and many features in such a light and compact camera.

The one thing that really bugs me about this camera is that you can often hear the camera zooming sound in recorded videos if you zoom too quickly while recording. To reduce the amount of sound, zoom in slower (but even with that, you&apos;ll often still hear sound if you are in a quiet room).

Some other things that I wish were a little better but aren&apos;t deal breakers are, the popup flash is not located well (your finger naturally covers that spot), the hdmi cover is flimsy, the battery latch is also flimsy. I think ... it also only records 1980x1080p/60 fps resolution in AVCHD format (lower resolutions for mp4) though confirm this yourself. I&apos;m afraid that avchd format will be more inconvenient in terms of editing though I&apos;m not really well versed in video editing.

FYI, there is a wifi version of this camera as well called the hx30V instead of hx20V. Best buy doesn&apos;t sell it but you can google search or go on Sony&apos;s webpage if you want to read more about it.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera is a joy to use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 25, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>In May 2011, I ordered Sony&apos;s new Cyber-shot DSC-Hx100V Digital Camera from B &amp; H. As a companion to this full-featured camera, I recently ordered from B &amp; H, Sony&apos;s new Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V Digital Camera. Although pocket-sized, it&apos;s a giant in features. I rate this amazing camera, and B &amp; H&apos;s fast and friendly service, as par excellence.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>m14j16</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera but Sony dropped the ball</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great pictures, even in lowest light

Cons: No manual!

I upgraded from the HX5V to the HX20V because it is the latest model and I loved my previous one. I love all the features, but my only gripe - a big one - is that there is NO manual, only a quick reference guide which does not explain the features. More puzzling is that this quick guide refers users to Sony&apos;s website for an in-depth guide, which does not exist. I contacted Sony (via chat) and the representative stated Sony is aware of the issue and will solve it &quot;very soon&quot; (verbatim). However, I have owned the camera for about two weeks and there&apos;s no online manual. How does Sony expect users how to use the camera&apos;s full features if there is no information available? Sony is the WORST when it comes to customer servi ... ce!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Picc</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>great camera...beginner or expert</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use and setup...not a bad price for this camera

Cons: small in size and the flash is in a bad place

I would highly recommend this camera to a friend. Great stills and videos. I also like the ease of use of the zoom lens....I can&apos;t say enough about this camera. It&apos;s a relief from carrying my SLR around....you won&apos;t regret buying this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SPIDERXXX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>EASY CAMERA FOR SOMEONE THAT LIKES IT SIMPLE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: CAMERA HAS ALOT OF FEATURES. I&apos;M STILL GETTING FAMIAL WITH IT. SO FAR VERY HAPPY. TAKES GREAT PICTURES EVEN IN LOW LITE.

Cons: SLOW WRITE SPEED EVEN WITH A CLASS 10 CARD. DOESN&apos;T COME WITH A MANUAL ON A CD-ROM.

OVERALL HAPPY WITH CAMERA. I CAN&apos;T WAIT BECOME MORE FAMILIAR SO THAT I CAN START TAKING MORE ADVANTAGE OF THE MANY FEATURES.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera in Pocket</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality is very good like PRO

Cons: Flash Position

This is excellent camera, finally i had after tried so many other brand models such Panasonic, Canon. This camera has excellent video and Picture quality indoor/outdoor or at Night time.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>gdagostini</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great travel camera indeed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Zoom, features, easy to use, speed

Cons: All Sony Cameras I had has the same issue. LCD scratched too easily!

I always wanted to have a SLR camera ( and I will ) by it picture&apos;s quality.
But thinking of me carrying that huge packet around on my trips makes me chill.
So I went ahead and bought this as it has great zoom for it&apos;s size, not a SLR picture quality but far enought and a bunch of other features like GPS, filters etc
Cost benefit ? Well it&apos;s a Sony so you know. But it&apos;s worthy. I just wanted Sony to make better quality LCDs or provide some protection to it. My last camera T200 had this same issue and after a couple day using it scratches were all around the LCD.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Frodomare</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This beats my digital slr. I used it on a trip to</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: the size and features plus an excellent picture make this a travel camera supreme

Cons: Menues could be better

For the size this camera is packed with features. Even the movie function is great. It really is an ideal travel camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>starbaby62</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for low lights</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: zoom and low light photos

Cons: have not found anything yet

Originally I went in to buy a Olympus camera but the rep suggested this one because of its low light capability and superior zoom capabilities. I took it to a Lita Ford concert and the pics were so good you would have thought I was on the stage with her. Finally a camera that produces what they promised.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use with excellent pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 5, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great quality pictures

Cons: Not WiFi

This is an excellent camera. It&apos;s very affordable yet doesn&apos;t compromise on the capabilities of the camera. Downloading photos to my camera is as easy as 1- 2- 3. I would recommend this camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>angelsloveselvis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I&apos;m so happy with my new Camera by Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>I only can say that I started using my new camera in Memphis, during the Elvis Week, and I got beautiful pictures. I&apos;m so happy with it. That&apos;s what I was looking for: a good camera that takes good pictures.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Scarfoot</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This is an excellent camera for quick on the go ph</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 28, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Portable and easy to use.

We needed a camera for my wife who wants to be able to take quick pics on the go without lugging her SLR about continuously. This camera fit the bill extremely well.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BigKidBuck</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great for the Novice and Advanced</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Out of the box, charge and you&apos;re set

Really this is a right out of the box charge and ready camera! After I charged it I turned it on and 1.9 sec it was ready to take a picture (after inital set-up). Pictures were crisp and sharp with the optical zoom but got a little fuzzy with the digital but still better than most I&apos;ve used. The 20x zoom gets you up close and personal with anything you&apos;re looking to image and the steady shot keeps it smooth. More bells and whistles than a novice will ever use and enough for the advanced person to have a lot a fun with.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>putz4tasha</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>outstanding product for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: unbelievable number and quality of functions to use

Cons: the flas comes up where your finger is

great camera tons of functions easy to use with the upgraded memory card can basically record a full length film of my dogs</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mocha14</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Ive had many Cameras and this one beets them all</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Love the pics it takes in the evening

Cons: the only thing i dont like is where the record botten is..im always pushing it

this is a great all around camera, great day and night shots for a small camera..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HOBBIEST</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

Cons: Battery life

This is a great camera. Seems a bit heavy but very sturdy. Takes excellent photos. The only bad photos taken were from my error. Seems a bit complicated at times with all of the features but the auto setting works well for me. Great low light photos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Josh</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Superior Value for a Superior Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;ve been able to use this camera for two affairs so far, and the real test will be on our honeymoon in a few weeks. I did a lot of research on cameras being a gadgets and gizmos geek, including CNET and multiple in-store trials. Net net - this is a versatile product with remarkable control for a point and shoot, spectacular detailing, color accuracy, and ease of use (some might find the menu overwhelming, I don&apos;t think it takes long to learn at all...you have to play with your toy if you want to fully appreciate it people). If you want a camera that packs a lot into a small device, and that maximizes value for the money, buy this camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mr.Pike</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>AWESOME CAMERA</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had several digitals cameras and this one are the best.The video quality is incredible.The pictures are amazing.Great product and very easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ckopsa</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera sitar has been great. The features are awesome, and the design is very attractive and comfortable.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Johnnyboy6859</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera, highly recommended!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 4, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome pictures in all types of situations.

Cons: Nothing

My wife finds this camera easy to use and the picture quality is fantastic!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Chao</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very nice DC</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 2, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>As a starter gear, really easy to handle. Considering the price is good to have.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Atsabor</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, love it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture clarity.

Cons: Nothing so far

I had an earlier version. But this one is amazing.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-HX20V 18.2 MP Digital Camera</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/15774557037718111403/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=784&amp;bih=747&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.9&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=r4KRUK6OC6Wc2AWz4oCwCQ&amp;ved=0CIkCEPQCMAU4Cg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Maria</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>B&amp;H</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Close to Perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Great: ease of use; access to menus; zoom capability; not too heavy. Not-so-great: still need a tripod to shoot fireworks.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

