<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Items>

   <Item>
     <ID>1</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer> </Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy> </ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle></ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate></ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>0</Rating>
     <Review></Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>2</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ConsumerSearch</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>ConsumerSearch</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview>Editorial review</EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 Review</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Large, bright LCD screen, variety of shooting modes, colorful images, excellent HD video recording, 3D image mode

Cons: Blurring in image corners, noise at ISO 800 and above, small controls and buttons

With its 16.2-megapixel Exmor R backside-illuminated CMOS sensor and Bionz processor, the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 packs a lot of photographic power into a lightweight point-and-shoot digital camera that&apos;s not larger than a cell phone. Despite its small size, the WX9 has a high-resolution 3-inch LCD screen for framing (though it doea lack a viewfinder). ...</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>3</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ThirdCyber</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cheap Decent Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: picture quality, features

Cons: usability, overall feel

This is my third Sony Cybershot. My first was a bulky early model that worked good, but eventually became obsolete because of its size and picture quality. Second was a W150 which was a great little camera until I fell and broke my fall with it, smashing the lens. When I needed a quick replacement, I found the WX9 on sale for about a buck and a half.

While it&apos;s a decent camera that takes good pictures and videos, I felt gypped by the overall quality, in particular the usability and feel. Compared to the W150, gone is the viewfinder. So what, you might say; it does have a nice LCD screen. But when it&apos;s really bright outside, you&apos;ll miss the viewfinder. This was probably a corner cut to keep the price appealin ... g. Second corner cut: the battery door. It&apos;s not the well-built door of the W150 that just feels right when opening and closing, but a cheesy fragile door that is opened and closed by a tiny lever. Another corner cut to save money. Third gripe: the zooming is now a circular control around the trigger instead of the well placed rocker zoom control of the W150. It&apos;s awkward and takes some getting used to.

The WX9 does support SD cards though (in addition to the Sony cards). The WX9 uses a different battery from the W150, so I couldn&apos;t use my old batteries. It comes with one, but as with the W150, you really need another one to avoid being powerless out in the wild. The W150 came with a nice battery wall charger. The WX9 does not (battery has to be in the camera to charge). Another corner cut and extra expense likely needed afterwards.

That all said, the zoom is about the same as the W150, though the digital zoom seems improved on the WX9. The picture quality is good if not better than the W150, but the picture sizes are bigger. There is no 3M mode for the WX9. Videos are recorded in MP4 vs. MPG. That&apos;s an issue if your software doesn&apos;t support MP4. (The supplied software supports it though). The WX9 can now zoom while recording video and take snapshots while rec ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>4</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PuppetShow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Crisp images, Great features, Perfectly compact</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Honestly, everything!

Cons: Can&apos;t think of anything not great about it

I am a shutterbug and I love my cameras...but I needed a smaller compact camera that was easier to carry around with me everywhere I go. The camera I&apos;ve been using is just a bit too big to comfortably fit in my purse. So, I ventured into my local Best Buy and found a small, 16 mega pixel, 100 dollar Canon point and shoot. I bought it out of impulse because I love Canon cameras (And I still do!) But this one just didn&apos;t seem very high quality...I thought there had to be a catch with it being such a cheap price for a 16mp camera. So, I returned it when I found this Sony cyber-shot WX9 (16.2mp). Yes, It was 70 dollars more (on sale..) but I knew that would make a world of difference. And it really has!&lt; ... br&gt;
I got home, opened the packaging, and started up the camera as soon as I could. The styling of the camera is very sleek, the screen is very clear and a nice size. The nice thing about the camera is when you first start it up, it sort of gives you a tutorial of how everything works. There is a wheel that you turn on the back that lets you browse through the different camera settings; scene, background defocus, intelligent auto, superior auto, program auto, and 3D still image. That is very convenient. There is also a little switch that lets you transition from regular camera mode to the &quot;iSweep panorama&quot; mode and then to the video recording mode.

In video mode you can choose from a variety of different &quot;scene&quot; options for the appropriate look and artistic effects you may want. There are some other interesting photo settings you can use, such as smile detection and smile shutter. If you have it set with smile shutter on and you choose to have smile detection set for either &quot;slight smile, normal smile, or big smile&quot; the camera will automatically detect if someone in the line of sight is smiling to that specific degree. When that happens, the camera automatically takes a photo on its own. That is a very clever way of catching those perfect candid moments.

The shutter speed ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>5</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bobby44</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good n Handy Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, good look, great pictures

Cons: Battery life, on/off switch, shutter speed

Camera is good for my day to day use and fits my pocket well. Features are good but we need time to get used to it. Worth the price we pay. I have been using it since 6 weeks and till now I have no problem with it. Picture quality is very good as I see on the screen, yet to see how that transforms into printing. I would refer it to my friends definitely.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>6</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Phillip44</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love This Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 3, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Very easy to use and get great pictures! Very compact!

Cons: Controls are a bit small!

Got the WX9 at a great price! There have been some reviewers that claim the WX9 has poor battery life. However, I have not found that to be the case at all. I recently took over 100 indoor shots with flash set to auto and there was plenty of power left in the battery. Thus, just to be on the safe side I did manage to buy (2) extra batteries and a charger. As such, I doubt I will ever run into any battery issues. Keep in mind, that I have NOT taken any video as of yet. I bought this camera mainly for taking pics! So far so good. The pictures have turned out really well. This was my first Sony camera purchase. I used to own a Canon A570IS which was a great camera, but it used AA batteri ... es and was a bit bulky. The WX9 is small and compact that uses a Lithium Ion battery. The controls are a bit too small, but with continued use I am sure most would get used to them. All in all, I am very happy with my purchase. Great price, Great pictures, Great service! Very happy camper here. What&apos;s not to love?
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>7</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>turbowilly</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>finally a keeper</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: price to performance ratio cant be topped

Cons: The sony software is ok

I have found the keeper at last. This is the fourth camera I have tried in the last 2 months. I tried the canon ELPH 310 based on reviews and was let down. It just did not live up to the reviews. A Nikon 8100 and 8200 and even though the worked well I could not live with the flash popping up under your finger when you hold the camera. This little gem on the other hand is great. It has very quick response when you hit the button to snap a picture. Faster on aveage than the others I tried. Crisp pictures and good video along with a ton of settings. The panoramic feature is amazing in how well it works. A fun feature to have. The 5x zoom is ok, more would be better but on the other cameras the image qu ... ality seemed to go down at the extreme zoom the had. So that is ok by me. Lets face it, for what most of us do we dont need the ultra zoom. It has very good battery life and is easy to charge form the outlet or computer. AND, the price cant be beat. More than half the price of so called better cameras that dont perform as well.139 with case and memory card. FANTASTIC !!!! I am sure that there are and will be bad apples in all camers on the market and if you get this one and it does not work as well for you as it does for me you probably just got a bad one and should swap it for a new one. I hope this helps all the other people trying to find the right camera. We all need to remember that they are NOT SLR&apos;s and should not expect them to be as good but this one sure does try.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>8</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tandrb</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little &quot;point &amp; shoot&quot; camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: very good resolution, colors have a lot of &quot;pop&quot;, very small and very light and does 1080i HD video

Cons: battery life is relatively short, due to small battery, but battery is small enough to carry several extras in a pocket.

I have had about 10 digital cameras, and this is my all-time favorite &quot;point &amp; shoot&quot; camera. The low light capability is excellent and the sharpness is much better than my Canon SD4000. The hi-def video (AVCHD format, 1080i) capability is very nice to have. It does not replace a true, dedicated HD video camera, but it is nice to be able to capture spontaneous high-def videos with something so small. The videos tend to be a little &quot;shaky&quot;, as this camera is very small and the anti-shake mechanism is designed for still photos, but the video det ... ail level is surprisingly good, from such a small camera. You just have to be careful to hold the camera as steady as possible, when shooting video.

This little camera is not a substitute for a digital SLR. With such a small image sensor, the details and graininess are not as sharp, when an image is blown up, as a dSLR, but are very good for such a small camera, and it can fit in a pocket and you hardly know it&apos;s there. I use this much more often than my dSLR.

The colors seem somewhat &quot;bigger than life&quot;, which might bother some purists, but they really &quot;pop&quot;. Pictures of grass look greener than the grass actually looks, but it looks the way I WISH my grass looked.

The only downsides that I can think of are that booting it up takes significantly longer than my Canon SD4000, so I have missed a few shots, waiting for it to get ready. The JPG compression level is set to a very high quality setting (94%) which means there is very little in the way of compression artifacts, which is nice, but it ends up creating files that are generally between 3.5 - 5 megabytes, each, so it tends to fill up the memory card much more quickly than my Canon SD4000, and there is no setting to change the compression level, for some reason. I would like the option to have more compression and smaller file size for most &quot;snapshot&quot; pictures.

All in all, it&apos;s a wonderful little &quot;snapshot&quot; or vacation camera. It is so small and light that it never gets in ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>9</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Singalicious</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Small package with a little kick!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 17, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use, amount of features, decent price.

Cons: Needs a screen protector.

For the last six or seven years, I&apos;ve owned a Sony DSC-W7 which is still a great camera but I felt it was definitely time to upgrade. So as I shopped around in the store and played with the large selection of cameras, I came across this little puppy and I fell in LOVE. I loved the look and feel as well as the ease of use. The picture quality was awesome especially compared to the other choices available at my local store. I recently made a trip to Trinidad and this little puppy was everything I could ask for in a camera this size. The auto sensor for the settings is a great feature. I used the panorama function which produced some great pictures as well but I was especially pleased with the v ... ideo function. Compared to my old Sony, I was able to zoom in and out and the video quality is absolutely great. As far as battery, I was able to use my camera for about two days before needing to recharge (that&apos;s with use throughout the day). So far, the only con that I have is not having something to protect the LCD screen but that&apos;s what cases are for I guess. Overall, I think it&apos;s a great buy for the price (I got it for $199) especially compared to the other choices that I had that were in the same price range or some that were a little more expensive. If you&apos;re looking for a great camera for a decent price, this is it! Anything you buy will have its pros and cons but the pros far outweigh the cons on this little puppy. My next trip is coming soon and I planned on borrowing a buddies professional series Nikon but I probably won&apos;t be now.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>10</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>coverkid</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Camera, But A Disappointment</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 26, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Features I mentioned

Cons: Image Quality, Zoom is weak at 5X

Pictures look great on the screen, but when viewed at full size or quite frequently or under 100% there&apos;s evidence of color inaccuacy with reds and blues being oversaturated, noise, lack of sharpness.

The pictures look like watercolor paintings as one reviewer stated and this is indeed true. Even on a bright sunny day there&apos;s details (i.e. leaves# that look soft or gain painting like.

Videos sucks also with low lighting and while camera does good with backlighting and low light, images still look crummy.

However, if you care less and want a very cheap point and shoot with features I would say its okay.

Working for the camera is the features and price.

I bought this for the pa ... noramic mode and while it works, I wish Sony would let people hold the camera horizontally vs. vertically for the HD panoramic mode.

Printing pictures are decent, but when looked at critically one will see noise and off colors. Best results ares shooting on a clear day with lots of daylight, but those pics also look terrible at 100%.

Another thing that&apos;s stupid is the battery charging process and Sony recommending you to use the USB cable to download pics to the computer. You can get away by taking the memory card out, but noticed the PMB software doesn&apos;t let one play back a panorama shot like a video or let you save it as a movie file por QTVR.

I know a lot of people rated this camera high, but likley they didn&apos;t look at the pictures taken at 100%. Pictures above 400 ISO from my experience will show a great deal of noise regardless of the camera manufacture. But even at 100 ISO, I was noticing a high level of noise more so in low light areas #i.e. shadows), but its also present in sufficient light.

In closing, tthe image quality can be cleaned up using noise reduction software and graphics programs, but the amount of errors this camera has equals very time consuming and thus, not worth the time. Nor is the average consumer or beginner should deal with hours of trying to clean jup photo ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>11</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Gene422</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great &quot;P &amp; S&quot; camera when compactness is important</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good value from a quality manufacturer

This is my third SONY point and shoot camera. Fantastic results from such a compact camera. I use it when I don&apos;t want to lug my SONY digital SLR around. Easy to &quot;master&quot; if one has used digital P &amp; S cameras. Battery life seems impressive but the top selling points for a camera in this price range is the quality of the photo images and the &quot;large&quot; LCD screen. (Haven&apos;t used the video feature yet.)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>12</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jazzy122</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>picture quality and hd video are so clear &amp; vivid</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality for the price

Cons: can&apos;t make a still picture from a video.. but thats it!

This Sony cyber shot 16.2 mp is the best digital camera I have yet to own. The clarity and color that comes through in the pictures amazes me. The HD video is an added plus. I had no idea what I was missing until I watched a short video that my 14 y.o. son shot with this camera. Panoramic is just as phenomenol as an added feature.
I recommend this sony for every day use. It&apos;s light weight and the battery keeps it&apos;s charge.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>13</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Brioog</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I usually read reviews, not write them...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: HD, 3D, multiple scene options, low light, panorama, HDMI output, accepts both SD and Memory Stick

Cons: Zoom button

...but I had to write my first ever online review for this camera.

Did a lot of research before buying the WX9. I was originally looking for an HD video camera for an upcoming vacation, but once I realized today&apos;s digital still cameras were shooting 1080 HD video, I decided to upgrade from my Sony W290 (another great camera at its release time).

PROS: For the beginner, average user, or above average user (shy of using DSLR), this camera has everything you could possibly want.

1080i HD video - You&apos;ll need a mini-HDMI to HDMI cable (sold seperately, but only 30 bucks) to hook this unit up to your tv. It&apos;s worth it. The picture quality i ... s money and Sony&apos;s steady-shot feature smooths out all the mini-shakes from my hands that always plagues my video capturing.

**SOUND** For a long time, Sony DSC&apos;s only recorded mono sound, and it was horrible. It&apos;s good to finally see them incorporate stereo mics at the top of the unit (and in a place your fingers will not cover them up.
HD playback on tv: It&apos;s great, whether its a still picture or video clip, it&apos;s sharp. I love being able to give a HD picture slide show directly off the camera.

A cool thing about this camera is the 3D panorama recording. I dont have a 3D tv, but you can view the image in a semi-3D viewing mode on the camera itself by tilting left to right, or you can really notice it when you hook it up to a tv. Took some outdoor shots in this mode with people and cars, and this playback feature animated people walking and cars driving on the street. It brought the scene to life, shy of a video, in a way that a still 3D image could not do.

Low light shots: When you choose one of the low light settings, this thing fires off 4 or 5 shots instantly and combines them automatically to record great low light shots, with or without tripod, there&apos;s a different setting for both. No complaints at all.

The LCD screen high pixel count picture quality is great! I don&apos;t understand why Sony reduced the pixel count so much in t ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>14</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tatertot808</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use, Vivid, Compact.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 30, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: All in all, A Great investment

Cons: forward facing zoom switch, small buttons.

Prior to this purchase we had a DSC H1 and a DSC 730. Both Great cameras that came to an abrupt end due to misuse. I purchased this for a gift to replace the 2 I had broken.

Compared to what those older 2 could do, I am amazed at what this tiny camera can accomplish!

The screen is vibrant and playback is high quality. The pictures are great quality and the videos is superb. Night time shots without the flash are Awesome to boot!

I could seriously go on about this camera but you&apos;ll just have to experience it for yourself. My Other choices were a Canon and a Samsung of comparable price. I do not regret my decision thus far.

Cons: Im used to a thumb controlled zoom b ... utton on the backside of the camera. This one has it integrated around the capture button. Its just a personal thing.

A night time shot without flash that was taken after sunset at 7:50PM and a macro shot of a white orchid should be shown with this review.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>15</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ghostassociate</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera, review from Ghost-Associate</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great performance, many features, exmor image sensor.

The sony wx9 is a great camera for multiple reasons. This camera in my opinion is the best point and shoot camera that sony has put out this season. This camera offers a world of features including sonys great panorama mode and the burst mode which allows you to take close to 10 pictures in about one second. Also what most customers dont realize is that this camera has the Exmor image sensor. Sony uses this sensor in only their high end cameras and high definition camcorders. This sensor works great in low light conditions. The zoom is only 5x but thats the best you will see for a camera of that size. I would def. recommend a high speed memory card for this card because of the burst mode and the HD video. As for a case, no ... camera comes with a case, whether it be $50 or $1500 (unless a special promotional deal comes your way), so you will also need a case. For cameras in or around the $200 this is my personal favorite, a close comparison would be the canon elph100hs and possibly the canon sd 1400, also the sony W series are a great way to go if your looking for something cheaper though they lack many graet qualitites of the wx9. I only most my reviews to help consumers find somethign they&apos;ll be happy with.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>16</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SallyNG</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Couldn&apos;t find a better pocket size camera!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 24, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I have owned this camera for almost two months now and while I am still exploring and discovering more features as i go, I am truly impressed with the camera so far. Amazing features packed in a tiny package! This is what has been the most impressive:

Size - the camera is small enough to fit into a small clutch purse for a night out. It is very easy to slip into the pocket for day to day picture taking.

Excellent picture quality - The images are crisp and sharp. The fine LCD monitor on the camera displays great images that look just as crisp on the computer/TV. Works very well in low light settings well. There are several scenes mode to pick from to ensure the best picture quality for your setting.

Optical steady shot optimization - ensures non-blurry images/vid even w ... hen you&apos;re not as steady while shooting.

Full HD movie mode - amazing resolution on video clips even in low light settings.

I-Sweep Panorama mode - what&apos;s not to love? Wide angle 180 degree shot for a panoramic view that can be shot horizontally or vertically. The camera takes 15 images at different angles as the camera sweeps across the scene.

Burst shooting mode.

What I have not liked BUT was not a deal-breaker:
&gt; The software provide (Picture Motion Browser) is not Mac compatible:(
&gt; No Black &amp; White feature on the camera - with the many picture editing software available, it&apos;s an easy fix but it should&apos;t have been left out!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>17</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>moraleke20</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Cannot Get Over All the Awesome Features!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to set-up/use and great price.

Picture quality is absolutely fantastic! Some settings I really like are the burst photo setting where it just snaps a whole bunch all at once within a second, which is nice if you want to capture something in motion or to make sure you don&apos;t miss something good!

Another setting I fell in love with is the sweep panorama, which gets a wide landscape view.

Yet another setting takes pictures automatically when it sees a smile.

And finally for those of us who like to take pictures of ourselves with a friend, but there&apos;s no one around to take them, there is a two-person face recognition timer that snaps when two faces are in the camera view so when you have the camera extended out in front of you, at least you&apos;ll know your fa ... ces will be in the picture.

Price is definitely reasonable (I got it on sale for 159.99), quality is outstanding, and the unique features are what I love best. Have not used the video yet. Battery life seems decent so far, I&apos;ll probably have an extra handy just in case.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>18</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>twc75</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice Camera with Good Features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 13, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good features and easy to use

Cons: Short battery life, blurry pictures at times

Excellent camera with all the bells and whistles. The camera is easy to use for most functions and is easy to use as both a still and a movie camera. All of the functions are easy to find and the menu is very intuitive. The pictures were of good quality, but I found them to be slightly blurry at times (probably due to my usage rather than the camera). This may have to do with the fast lens time.
The only issue that I would note is that the battery is a little quick to discharge especially when using the movie function.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>19</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>msphx602</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera for the money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, image quality, lots of options

Cons: Need more explanation of features

I have only had this camera for about a month-and-a-half. I wanted an easy-to-use point and shoot camera for use on vacations, holidays and for family occasions. I also wanted a good price, which I got. The clarity of images is great and there are lots of options and features to choose from. The panoramic shooting is particularly impressive and easy. Unfortunately, the wide array of features/options can be confusing and difficult to figure out and get to. Although the on screen display is helpful, it would be more helpful to have an actual manual with more thorough explanations. As a casual photographer, I lack the technical knowledge to know which features are best in unusual lighting or ... other situations. I haven&apos;t used the video feature yet. The screen is a magnet for fingerprints and smudges, so I will be looking into getting a screen protector. Generally, I have had success with this camera and still feel like I got a good camera for what I paid.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>20</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steelvalve1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera for the price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Image quality

Cons: video capture.

When I bought this camera I wanted something small that took really good pictures and was easy for my wife and i to use. I found all of those things with this camera. This is my first Sony point and shoot camera and I must say I&apos;m very impressed. The picture quality is excellent. The colors are clear, vibrant and at 16.2 megapixels I can enlarge without any the changes in the picture quality. The only reason I didn&apos;t give this camera 5 stars is the video quality. It&apos;s supposed to be HD video quality but the first couple of videos I took the image was just ok. I may have to play with the settings to improve the quality. Overall a great camera for under $200.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>21</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sbdfresno</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>So Disappointed...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy of use and size

Cons: The picture quality.

I have been waiting a few months to buy this camera and replace my Sony DSC-W290. I wanted a camera that took great pictures, especially in really low light. I was so excited to finally buy the WX9 after reading all the great reviews. The WX9 is easy to use (especially if you have owned a Sony before) and it &quot;appears&quot; to take great pictures. The LCD screen is great and shows sharp colorful pictures. However, upon downloading to my computer and printing, the pictures are HORRIBLE! They look nothing like the preview on the camera. The preview shows them as sharp, bright and colorful. The opposite of the actual print. All the wonderful features of this camera just don&apos;t make up for the softness of the pictures. I think I will ... be sticking with my W290. My pictures are always nice and sharp and as they appear on the preview screen!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>22</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Patpat1</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great, Lightweight Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size, weight and ease of use.

Cons: Some of the buttons are a bit small.

I have found this camera to be perfect for point and shoot photos and the video is very good HD quality. However, if you use a lot of the video features, it eats the battery life. Now that I have this small camera, I take more photos because it fits in a pocket or purse, vs. my SLR camera that is a pain to carry. All in all, a great buy!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>23</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JJWTSP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Outstanding picture quality and features</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Shutter speed, Video, Overall quality, Uses SD (not just Sony cards)

Cons: Nothing..

I new as soon as I looked this camera over in Best Buy that it was the one I wanted. I got it on sale the next week and have loved it ever since. It just takes these amazing looking photos that just blow you away with the clarity and quality. The &quot;skin mode&quot; is fantastic and like adds make up to the subject. I have had dozens of cameras, point and shoot and SLR and this is my favorite by far because of the size and convenience with great quality.

The film quality is also wonderful. Love this camera and may buy a second for a back up. :p

Thanks Sony for coming through for me again.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>24</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dbnr102756</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: battery life, lens, picture choices

Cons: You need to take some time to read the manual and practice with it.

My Sony Cyber-Shot camera is an excellent camera.

It has many choices to choose from when taking a picture.

The battery life is good, and the movie mode works great.

The price is the same as Wal-Mart&apos;s, and the brand name makes for good confidence in the product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>25</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EventVideoGuy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Nice features BAD battery Life</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Multiple megapixel modes and various video formats MP4 1080/30p and AVCHD 1080i. Lots of manual controls.

Cons: TERRIBLE battery life when using video.

Pro:
I was very pleased with the camera&apos;s funtions overall. it does so many things. HD video 1080/30P in MP4. As well as 1080/60i (which is just normal 30 fps video) in AVCHD format. Don&apos;t let them fool you with the fancy lingo. 60 interlaced frames is the standard DV speed. But I digress. There are many user controlled features on this camera. A nice scrolling wheel and a separate button for recording video and taking pictures. This camera can also take still pictures while recording video. I accidentally found this feature although it&apos;s not in the manual.
It&apos;s got a built in wide angel lens as well.

Con: ... r&gt;The battery life on this camera SUCKS! I had to buy 2 extra batteries. If I use the video for longer than about 25 minutes, the battery will be completely drained no matter which recording mode you&apos;re in. If you are just taking pictures, the battery life is just OKAY. But the video will drain it in a heartbeat. And I think the 25 minutes is a generous liberal estimation.
Note: If you plan to buy more batteries, go to a popular auction site to purchase them. I bought two 900mAh batteries for $6. Compared that to $50 for one of the Sony brand. The battery provided when you buy the camera is only 600mAh.

Conclusion:
If you can get past the low battery life, it is a really neat little camera.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>26</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MikeMD1965</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great snapshot &amp; video camera for everyday use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Image quality, features, ease of use.

Cons: Very minor issue with color saturation in some lighting.

I own several DSLR cameras as well as HD video cameras. On a recent Disney vacation, I decided I didn&apos;t want to carry my larger cameras with multiple lenses, etc. so I did some research and choose the Sony as a well featured &apos;pocket&apos; camera with video capacity. In almost every way the Sony impressed me with image quality, speed and ease of use. I especially was impressed with it&apos;s low light performance without producing large amounts of noise in these pictures. The video was likewise crisp and good quality for a &apos;pocket&apos; camera. Included features like &apos;fireworks&apos; mode and panoramic photo were nice. Some color saturation was a little off, but not so much as to be noticeab ... le to most. Overall Sony has built a solid &apos;pocket&apos; camera here, and it would be a perfect take along camera for anyone on holiday or just on the go.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>27</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mydadthebuilder</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very good but not perfect</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture Quality &amp; Panoramic View

Cons: Filming video quickly - Lag time &amp; too many steps.

I love the camera and its picture quality but controls are not ver intutitive and it can take a few button pushes to get video working. Also it turns on easily when shuffled around in pockets.

Panoramic is GREAT. Wish screen was touch controls.

3D is OK but not really sure what you can do with it so we don&apos;t use it. Pictures are about memories for us not special effects.

Not displeased by it and think for the price it was a good buy.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>28</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>RnRHart</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My friends love this camera a tad more than I do.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Ease of use and features such as Panorama and HD.

Cons: Not very exciting and picture quality not what I&apos;m used to.

This camera is easy to use, not too expensive and my friends love the picture quality. Actually, I prefer the print quality. I just can&apos;t get used to the bright, bright, colorful picture I see through the lens. Perhaps it&apos;s me. I&apos;m using the Easy Mode. I also love the Panorama feature. It just amazes me. If you want afordable, point and shoot with HD and Panorama, get this. I usually buy touch screen gadgets. This time I resisted the temptation and I&apos;m glad I did. For me, it&apos;s easier and slightly better to take snaps with my iPhone, but my friends get great, non-blurry shots every time. I can now star in my own photo albums.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>29</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>balancemom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera! No regrets!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Modes,3in screen,Light weight,HD movies,Parorama Shots,Blink an Smile Detection

Cons: only bad part...charging spot is on the button, so have to lay down to charge or lay it against something.

Finally got the camera i want without having any regrets. It does everything i need it too. Takes great pics in low lighting, makes everything bright. Love the smile and blink detecting, using parorama pics too..very easy to use. has lots of different modes for different lights and areas. the buttons are easy to use kinda small, but i have small hands so its easy for me. nice 3in screen, nice and clear. zoom is kinda touchy but nothing to fret about.it was between Sony Cybershot or Panasonic FH24..Sony won, after using it in the store. Great Buy! if you wanna pay $188 buy it onlin ... e not in store. Not bad price. Great Birthday gift!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>30</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Shanem201</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Way more than I expected out of a Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Night shots, great price, variety of features for different pictures

Cons: Battery life can be short at times

I got this to replace a Fujifilm XP20, which wasn&apos;t as waterproof as it said it was. I knew this one wasn&apos;t waterproof, but after my fiasco with the XP20, I just wanted to get a good camera and forget about having it waterproof. After bringing it on a hiking trip in upstate NY and to Longwood Gardens in PA, I was blown away by the quality, even during a fountain light show at dusk. While it does not even come close to some of the picture quality I can get with my Canon SLR, it is much easier to handle and peforms excellent for more than most shots. I am also amazed by the amount of features it has as well. While (unfortunately) I do not have a 3D TV (I am still ... in the market for one), the DSC-WX9 is ready with 3D Panorama and 3D pictures. You also have access to white balance, exposure variance, and partly to ISO speeds to make your pictures as wonderful as possible.

The only problem I had was that the battery went after about 5 hours of heavy use. While this is very good in my eyes for a point and shoot, I recommend at least one extra battery that you can charge and keep on snapping.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>31</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HobbyVideographer</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Stills, Not So Great Video</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Still shots are fantastic!

Cons: Video quality not up to par and format my not be compatible with your editing software.

I never had a Sony Camera, but it seemed according to the specs that the Sony WX9 was the better option over the Cannon ELPH 300. However, after testing both. The Canon came out on top. The Sony produced better stills. But the Canon produced much better video and also took great photos. I was surprised that this was the case since the specs were so much more than the Canon specs. I also found that the video format of the Sony WX9 was not compatible with the my video editing software. I would have to spend a lot of money upgrading. I found a lot written about the formats compatiblity on the internet. But I&apos;m sure with newer systems, this won&apos;t be so mu ... ch of an issue in the future.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>32</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>sdhusker</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera -- Kudos To Sony</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great picture results, small size, great price, great features.

Cons: None so far.

I recently purchased both the Sony Cybershot WX9 and the Canon SX95 with the intent of keeping the best of the two and returning the other. Both are excellent cameras but after taking both indoor and outdoor pictures I found the Sony pictures were much better than the Canon&apos;s on the computer screen. I shot the pictures on both cameras in the auto mode. Given the better quality of the pictures, the smaller size, and especially huge price difference between the two cameras I am keeping the Sony and returning the Canon. I highly recommend the Sony WX9.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>33</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Mwro</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome features for a great price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Shoots fast, perfect for kid photos, great in dark situations.

Cons: Nothing yet.

I love this camera because it does everything I always wish a camera would do for me. It shoots ten frames a second, so I can shoot my kids on the move. It previews my shots quickly after I press the shutter. It&apos;s affordable.
This baby also shoots 1080 HD video. This is the first camera I have had that also shoots video, and the quality is excellent.
It&apos;s small enough that I can throw it in my pocket and always have it with me.
Last but not least is that it takes nice rich color photos! The low light shots are very good.I took it to my nephew&apos;s birthday party and was so happy with my pictures I made a few prints for gifts.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>34</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>00Hank00</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to use, Excellent quaility photos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality of photos, Easy to use Menu

Cons: On / Off button is hard to find (its very small)

Love this camera. It’s very easy to use. The menu system is very intuitive and allows for a wide range of photo scenarios.. It even lets you can take snap shots while you shoot a movie. Prints are nicer than pictures taken with my Canon 40D, and since it fits in my pocket, I&apos;ll be using this one more.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>35</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Camerashy007</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A lot of camera for a great price!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Was pleasantly surprised at the qualtiy of pictures coming from a camera so small. Not to mention the HD quality videos that can be taken with this little gem. More features that I will ever use, but nice to know I can get variations with all of the gadgetry. The software was easy to download and use. I&apos;d recommend....</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>36</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>xjxvx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I... LOVE... THIS... CAMERA!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 17, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent picture quality, especially in dark environments

Cons: No novelty settings

This is my 5th camera in 6 years and I&apos;ve finally found everything I need. First of all, the picture quality is incredible; definitely closer in quality to a DSLR than a point-and-shoot. It has a bunch of really great features to get the perfect picture. I love the way I can actually SEE things in dark pictures. For example, I took a picture of the night sky and could actually see stars! And I don&apos;t even need to use the flash, pretty much ever. And if you have experience with cameras, you know flash really sucks the life out of pictures. The backlight setting is also really cool; it brightens up the foreground really well AND, I discovered, if you use it in motion, there&apos;s this really c ... ool ghost effect. Most of the time, though, I just use the automatic setting and the camera does all the work for me. Basically, THIS CAMERA RULES.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>37</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SpyderT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great overall P&amp;S camera for everyday use.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Small, compact, lots of nice features. Love the portrait mode.

Cons: Battery life can be a little short.

I bought this camera and a Nikon P&amp;S at the same time to compare pictures/value. Overall, I think the Sony is a great value for the money. The color is actually a little more vibrant (some might say oversaturated), but I think it makes for good travel, scenic, and portrait pictures (I&apos;d rather have more vibrant color than washed out colors#. There are several settings -- either point and shoot with no worries about programming the camera, or several specialized settings such as portrait, landscape, twilight, etc.. Two of my favorite settings are the portrait mode which softens the skin tone -- trust me, this is a nice feature #as it smooths out the skin and reduc ... es imperfections such as redness, acne, scars, etc.) Also, I took some night time panoramic pictures without a tripod and the camera takes several pictures at once and overlays them to produce one image with more clarity without the typical handheld blurring problem.
The only problem I notice is that the battery life can be a little short at times. But overall, great value for $140!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>38</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>swam29</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome little camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Pics are very clear, easy to use &amp; lots of different settings!

Cons: Have to plug the whole camera into the wall, may be inconvenient at times but doesn&apos;t waste AA batteries

I wanted something new &amp; have a hard time making decisions. I went &amp; got a fujifilm finepix s3280 from Walmart thinking it would be similar to a dslr for a lot less but you definitely get what you pay for. I really did not want a big bulky camera &amp; was not impressed with pics so I returned it. I continued to read reviews on lots of other cameras &amp; one day browsing Best Buy I saw the Sony WX9 at the top with high reviews. I clicked on it &amp; was very impressed. I went to Amazon to view more customer sample pics &amp; that is what got me. I really wanted a camera that focuses &amp;am ... p; blurs the background...I think that is so cool &amp; this does it with the defocus setting. It is very easy to use &amp; takes great shots that are very clear! I have not printed any yet so I hope they come out that clear. It seems to snap pretty quickly &amp; has lots of different settings. I am still learning but so far I am impressed &amp; it is nice that it is a small pocket type camera that you can take with you anywhere. I don&apos;t think you can go wrong with this little camera. If you don&apos;t like it then maybe you need to spend $600 &amp; get a DSLR. My boyfriend just got the Canon Rebel T3 and I love it but do not want something like that everyday to take pics of my 2-year old. I wanted something I can throw in my purse, my pocket or whatever and get pics in a flash. Of course we will be using the Rebel a lot as well &amp; hopefully can get some nice family photos but this little Sony is comparable if you want nice shots for way less.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>39</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>126478224</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing little camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 13, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything so far!

I just got this camera yesterday and I can&apos;t stop playing with it! The picture quality is insane, it seriously looks better than real life. Even in low lighting most pictures look like daytime and the flash completely illuminates a pitch black room and looks nice. The features are very good too, Panorama and blur background are my favorites. The camera also looks very attractive, sleek, and small. The pictures I&apos;ve taken so far aren&apos;t even of anything interesting but they look phenomenal! I can&apos;t believe the price, at only $140, this definitely was a best buy!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>40</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PAULO64</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great pictures with little or no effort</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Bought this to replace an older version cybershot for an upcoming vacation. The screen resolution, picture quality and HD video quality are incredible. I especially like the panoramic feature. The intelligent picture mode adjusts automatically to the environment (low light, landscape, etc) and works great. I would absolutely recommend this to anyone considering a new camera. Great value for the price.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>41</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>catseye</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>bought it but returned it</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: quality and ease

Cons: zoom

I gave it good reviews if price is an issue. otherwise, why not pay the extra and upgrade to the Sony Cypershot 16x zoom. Now thats a great camera.

This camera served its purpose. It is very easy to use, picture quality good, and video good too. I used it only for a week, until i decided that i needed the 16x zoom feature. I didn&apos;t want a dslr camera - too bulky.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>42</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mshank</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good pictures but complicated in HD Videos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great image clarity, easy to use shooting modes, handy

Cons: Low battery life, Full HD video not supported in many media players and pricing is a bit high

I was looking for a camera and a camcorder. Came across this in Bestbuy stores and found out that this can be a good hybrid of a digital camera along with a HD Video shooting camcorder.

The image clarity and modes are good. The only drawback I found was in the panorama which gives a sweep mode. You have to sweep throughout the marking given by the camera to complete the picture.
The rest of the modes are selected automatically by the camera and this is helpful.

The camera also records HD Video and I shot a couple of them, but when I downloaded them on to my computer and played it using
VLC Player, ... the video got stuck. Probably my choice of using VLC wasnt appropriate, but I faced problems playing videos recorded in full HD. Later I changed the Video Quality in the camera setting and recorded which played easily. Sony needs to fix this issue.

Pros : Great image clarity, easy to use shooting modes, handy.
Cons : Low battery life, Full HD video not supported in many media players and pricing is a bit high.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>43</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>miamitom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little video camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent audio and video!

Cons: Not enough zoom

The WX9 replaces a broken Lumix DMC-ZS3 which I loved. I bought the WX9 for 2 purposes, primarily for video, secondly as a handy still camera to keep with me where ever I go.

This little camera is a beast! You have to get past the size - it is truly quite capable of getting great results not just with video but the audio is amazing as well. It&apos;s a very close contender with the Zoom Q3HD.

My primary purpose for video is to capture live music events, as a stationary camera and as walk around - right up near the stage.

I was prepared to be disappointed with the audio - audio has been an afterthought on most of these small cameras, but Sony comes through again with excellent audio.( I had a Sony V3 that h ... ad awesome sound capability - I have MPEG videos with awesome sound - because Sony does sound so well.)

It may seem humorous to have 2 stereo mics on top of the camera, but they do capture excellently, and the automatic gain control works excellently. I have stood in front of mains speakers and not been clobbered - (unlike my more expensive Nikon D90 which has mediocre audio in comparison - the D90&apos;s audio is like good AM radio comparatively. Audio/Video on the D90 was an afterthought to begin with.)

Plus with the WX9 you&apos;re shooting 60fps. The video files on this camera are AVCHD, which is like the Lumix - you get .MTS files - meaning you will have to convert them to MOV before importing into iMovie. (MTS = MPEG Transport Stream). I would say in my experience the MTS format seems to be higher quality than AVI.

If you&apos;d like to see what the Sony WX9 is capable of with video, I have a youtube account &quot;tomslounge&quot; - check out the Richard Griffin videos.

The only complaints I have is not enough zoom - it&apos;s only 5x, loved the long lens on the Lumix. You&apos;re getting Carl Zeiss glass in the WX9 so the image quality is excellent.

The zoom the WX9 does have is a bit too quick, and slow to activate. Meaning, if you hit the zoom it seems to take a bit longer than expected ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>44</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Pidao</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great point and shoot camera. Battery ends fast</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 20, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great picture and movie quality. Lots of features for a point-n-shoot

Cons: Short Battery life

If you want a point and shoot digital camera, this is a GREAT one.

It is not expensive, has lots of features (off course it doesn&apos;t have as many features as a compact camera), some features are pretty simple and intuitive to use. It also has great picture and video quality. Moreover, this camera is extremely portable and have a great design.

The only bad thing I have experienced so far with this camera was that, in a trip, I made a 20 minute HD movie and the battery didn&apos;t last much longer after that (something that didn&apos;t use to happen with my old cybershot, however it didn&apos;t record HD movies).</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>45</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Manny12039</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Just your avg. picture taker</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Attractive LCD, great HD video, Good quality pictures while fully zoomed.

Cons: Battery could always be improved (as with all devices)

I have owned my Sony Cyber-shot WX9 for 2 weeks now and I am absolutely impressed with it. I really don&apos;t know anything about the pixel densities or shutter speed, I am just your typical person wanting to capture the moment every now and then and this camera is perfect!

What I love:
- Slim and attractive build
- Feels durable
- Excellent LCD screen quality!
- Full HD video mode ( I recommend a higher end SD card for this)
- Panorama sweet and 3D pictures (I don&apos;t have a 3D tv but it&apos;s awesome what you can do with a point and shoot camera now)
- The price felt appropriate, most other brands will run you the same p ... rice for this quality, comes down to preference really

What I don&apos;t love:
- For $220 I would have liked it to come with some kind of case, even a sleeve of some sort to protect the screen would have been nice. (Oh well, I&apos;ll splurge and spend $5 for one, haha)
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>46</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lovescamera</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great function, easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Many functions, ease of use, speed, compact size

Cons: Hard to use if one has large hands.

I decided to get a smaller camera, I expected to lose function, but I found this camera rich in function, and easy to use. The quality of photo is excellent. The settings are intuitive, and the on board help very useful. I like having the video camera and still camera in one device. The panorama function is easy to use. I found this camera especially useful in low light, and turned off the flash most of the time. I found the review function fast, and did not take an exceptional amount of battery. As the card reached about half full, I noted a few second delay in opening the photos, but not annoying. The camera speed kept up with my shooting.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>47</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Yano</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Could be the best point and shoot out there</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Photo Quality

Cons: It really has nothing not good...

The photo quality of this camera is astonishing. It matches up to some of the entry-mid level DSLR systems out there. The Sony Exmor R CMOS sensor does it. Even though this is a point and shoot camera, the Zeiss lens Sony uses for their point and shoot cameras are not just a logo, there is a true difference when you compare to some of Canon&apos;s point and shoot (non-Zeiss lens), the photo does not curve even slightly on the edges and the color is very brilliant. The video function is great too at 1920x1080/60i, shoots crystal clear videos, produces better video than most consumer camcorders out there.

This camera no longer comes with a separate battery charger like many Sony&apos;s point and shoot, it uses the USB cab ... le to charge with a AC adapter, so for those who swaps batteries, you may need to get a battery charger.

It is a little thicker than the W350, but still small in size. Fits well in pockets with a small protective bag.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>48</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>someladyyoudontknow</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good easy camera for non-techno people</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great price!

Cons: Battery

I bought this camera for my mom before she went on a vacation. She is not very techno, and she found the camera easy to use. What you get for the money is well worth it. Pictures are great quality and print clear. My only complaint is the battery is not holding a charge. Although I do believe its just a bad battery, we will be going back to bestbuy to get a new one! Lets hope thats the issue, good luck!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>49</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>greenstx</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>if my wife can use it, anyone can</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 27, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy use for even the non tech savy

Cons: too many buttons to hold firmly. full price is a bit much IMO

bought this for my wife for Christmas because it seemed simple to use AND was on sale. then it went on sale again and BB refunded the difference. i got this camera dirt cheap!! my wife loves it. she was takin pics on a bumpy car ride and both of us couldnt believe how clean the pics turned out. bottom line is..... this camera is simple to operate and takes great pics on the basic settings, but also has enough settings to keep the curious busy. panoramic mode is very nice/simple and 3D mode is ok a little weird but ok. the only complaint i have isnt just this camera, but all of the point and shoot cameras, is that with all the buttons they have all over them they all a ... re difficult to hold firmly. make sure you use the strap. with 16+ mp &amp; 1080 vid you&apos;ll need a big micro sd card or a few
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>50</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mmgalls</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Compact Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 21, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Size and features.

Cons: battery life could be better as with all cameras this size.

I bought this camera for a Christmas gift for my daughter. Its great to have in your bag because of its size. Prints are clean and clear and the features are great. This is the second one we have, I bought a similiar Sony one last year for my son for a gift.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>51</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jigi</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Good camera but image quality is poor</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 16, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Sharp Screen, Panaromic feature, compactness

Cons: Image quality

I bought this camera before thanks giving. Very nice, slim, compact. It has so many advance feature. Menu navigation is also nice and Panoramic feature is great.
As feature wise no other bran can beat Sony but when it comes to picture quality i was not happy. I tried so many different photos in all different condition but ....it is 16 Mega pixel camera then i was expecting picture quality would be much better than my other 10 MP Olympus camera but it was not even close. I would out of 10 pictures hardly 1 or 2 photos come satisfactory. If you take any shot which is outdoor in full sunlight and specially for landscaping or steady photography all pictures comes very sharp, clear no doubt about it. But whe ... n it comes to any indoor, kids, party kind of photography I was disappointed. I have my DSLR camera and I bought sony for easy of use and carrying but ultimately i had to return it and I bought Canon ELPH 300 HS.

Problem what i see in Sony is for any indoor or low light photography it uses very high level of ISO so when you see actual picture on laptop/computer you can clearly see noise (grainy picture).
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>52</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SPENCERWASHERE</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Awesome!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great picture quality, very simple, HD movies

Cons: Semi short battery life, no black &amp; white photos, not that good of zoom

Reallly nice camera! Very fast to get use to all the features, extremely crisp picture quality, HD movies that show up as 1080p on youtube! The only thing i would have to criticise about it is that it does NOT have the option to shoot photos in black &amp; white, and it doesn&apos;t really tell you about that when your shopping for it. But other than that, its an extremely nice camera and i dont regret my purchase at all</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>53</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MimiC</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Easy to Use; Good Quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 11, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I had tried other digital cameras and found them to be inconsistent in their picture quality. This is not the case with the Sony Cybershot. It takes great pictures both indoors and outdoors. The video is also great for short clips (10-30 seconds). I use it mostly on the auto function where the camera will adjust for flash, background lighting, etc and I&apos;ve pleased with the pictures. For the casual photographer, I think this is an excellent choice.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>54</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PaulTBI</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Owners Manual built in!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This camera is very user-friendly and even has the owners manual built right into the camera. It has many different modes with a range of control to achieve the best photos. A great camera at a great price!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>55</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Vlad96</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent buy!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, lots of features, ease of use, optical zoom

Cons: Higher-resolution picture quality

Overall, this camera has everything you need (and more) for everyday picture-taking, and the tripod mount is useful for more &quot;professional&quot; photography.

I like the built-in battery with USB charging (the camera comes with an AC charger, but it can also be charged through a PC). And battery life is just fine (on par for digital cameras in general).

It&apos;s very quick and easy to use, especially once you go through the manual a bit to set basic settings relating to light-sensitivity, e.g. The face finder seems to find my cat&apos;s face as well. With so many options, it can seem overwhelming, but setting the resolution size would probably be the main one to pay attention ... to (at least for casual users like me).

The picture quality at higher resolutions is not great compared to higher-end cameras, but it&apos;s just fine for me since I typically take pictures at the 2MP and VGA (640px x 480px) levels.

I still prefer working with Picasa over the software that comes with the camera, since it allows more picture refinements, but the calendar feature in the included software is pretty good too, especially if you take a lot of photos of different people--it can tag photos by face/person (maybe Picasa does this too).

For the price, features, and ease-of-use, I would recommend to the non-professional photographer.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>56</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jthomps</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>picture perfect pictures</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great h.d. and 3-d

Cons: needs longer zoom range

great pictures, wish it had higher zoom level. love the 3-d option, 16.2 meg. is awesome for the price. small and lightweight, but sony makes durable equipment.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>57</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>dderek</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Wonderful camera for the price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: image clearity

Cons: nothing

I just recently purchased a Fujifilm camarea from Walmart. Boy, was I disappointed. Not only did it seem too bulky, but everything just seemed too complicated and the picture quality didn&apos;t seem that great either. I decided to return it and purchase a Sony WX9 from Best Buy. It was about 30.00 cheaper and very easy to use. I am no camera expert or critic by any means. This has got to be one of the best point and shoot cameras that I have ever owned. The HD video is extremely clear and easy to use. I enjoy playing around with the different functions that this camera offers. The image quality and clearity of the pictures I think are pretty good if not great. I especially like the panoramic option. Very simple to use. Only minor draw back would ... be the selection dial that gets a little awkward with my fat fingers. Highly recommended
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>58</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>rebelartist</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>GREAT CAMERA,GREAT FEATURES</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: BURST MODE

Very happy with this little jewel. Takes crisp clear shots! The movie rec mode is in HD! The BURST mode takes up to 10 Burst shot pics at a time! You can sift easily to delete the unwanted pics. Cool interface.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>59</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Ladyjenn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>I have finally found my Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Incredible photos, easy to use, compact, large bright LCD screen

Cons: Wish it had a wall battery charger, wish it came in more colors!

Thank you Sony! I tried the Panasonic Lumix ZS10, which I still have, and just returned the Canon Powershot Elf 100HS after trying this camera. I just happen to read some good reviews for it and thought, well I&apos;ve always wanted a Sony, there are just so many I had no idea which ones to try... well let me just say that I was able to get gorgeous pictures the first time I used it! It usually takes me quite a while to test a camera, but this was pretty easy though I still have more to learn! I even got some beautiful panoramic shots, but I guess I stopped too short, but they still turned out gorgeous, way better than my other cameras. Pics ... of my pets do not come out blurry, indoor pictures are great and the camera is fast, not slow like some of the other Sony model reviews I&apos;ve seen. The sharpness and clarity one me over. I would have liked a pink or purple camera, but black will do because of the end result. The 3 inch 921k dots LCD is gorgeous. Even the zoom doesn&apos;t seem to blur the photos I&apos;ve taken so far. I have been searching for over a year now, thinking that in 2011 I should be able to get a higher pixel camera that takes sharp pictures...and I&apos;ve found my camera! It will fit in my purse, unlike my Panasonic and it also takes regular SD cards, though wish it had a separate charger instead of charging through a USB cord, but it&apos;s ok! I love this camera that much! Get this camera if you want clear perfect shots!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>60</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>GOKKUS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect but...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 2, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>The camera is really good and very easy to use. It&apos;s small for ladies to carry in small purses.
It&apos;s really cheap for a camera having these features.
The only thing that I&apos;m not pleased is its charge. You can&apos;t take out the battery and charge it. You have to connect the camera with the usb cable to the plug.

But I really like my camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>61</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EllynnRaeLove</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Reasonable price, great high quality pictures and video, great new features, zoom in while recording

Cons: Short battery life when filming, bad video record button

So I wanted to wait 3 months before I gave a review despite the emails I received from Best Buy so here ya go!

Absolutely beautiful camera! I love photography and design programs like Adobe photoshop. Although I haven&apos;t tapped into the professional side of it yet, I enjoy having the latest cameras with best features as I am definitely the photographer out of my group of friends.

The pictures are beautiful. I love the settings that they give you for practically any kind of picture. They even have a pets setting which is perfect when I I want to take pictures of my little beagle. Every time I take ... pictures, people are always amazed with how clear and sharp the pictures are. It takes beautiful landscape pictures and I LOVE the panorama setting for those long landscape photos. The camera is so nice that you barely will have to use your flash button. In fact, you&apos;re not going to want to use it because it looks so much better without it even in low-light areas.

The HD video is gorgeous. It&apos;s great that sony allows you to even take pictures while you&apos;re recording so now you don&apos;t have to do it once you use a video editing program. Just hit the picture button while you&apos;re filming and it tucks it away without any interference with the video. Another thing is that finally Sony has pumped out a great camera that allows me to zoom in and out during film time. The only annoying part is the little whirl sound when you zoom in. So if you&apos;re recording something that&apos;s really quiet, you&apos;ll definitely hear the sound during playback. It&apos;s not loud but it is noticeable. Another thing about the HD video is trying to activate it on the camera. There&apos;s a specially made red record button for video but it stalls a bit before it records. So you&apos;ll hit the button, a second or two goes by without a response so you may hit it again thinking that maybe you just didn&apos;t hit it correctly when finally it begins to record but then stops since technically you hit the button twice. Moral of the stor ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>62</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>HAZEL1221</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A fun point and shoot camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 6, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: lightweight, easy to use

Cons: not waterproof

We have a Canon DSLR camera that we LOVE, it takes amazing photos. BUT because of it size (and price tag) we can&apos;t bring it everywhere for fear of damaging it. We were in the market for a small, point and shoot camera that we could bring anywhere (I said I wanted something I could keep in my purse at all times, you never know when you might want a picture!). The powershot brand was recommended to us by friends, and it really is exactly what we were looking for. It&apos;s portable, easy to use, and I can bring it to concerts and outdoor events where I would be hesitant with our &quot;nicer&quot; camera. I&apos;ve experience good picture quality so far, just what we wanted. We were hoping to find something waterproof but couldn&apos;t find one reasona ... bly priced out there, so we settled for this and couldn&apos;t be happier.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>63</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>bnclpn07</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: picture quality, price, features, setting options

Cons: program

love this camera. best one I have purchsed to date. the only thing I do not like is you can only upload and edit pic from camera through certain kodak program. if you dont register camera/program you can not upload video at all. great product, just bad they force you to use certain program.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>64</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SonyLoverButHateThis</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not so great camera to own!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Cons: Too small to handle

This camera is not so great to own especially considering the ease of use. I felt its too small to fit in your hand and its difficult to operate its very smaller parts. I&apos;m not satisfied with its picture quality too. I bought this camera to take pictures of child who is one year old and it didn&apos;t take good pictures - the burst mode wasn&apos;t that great as described in the features. The button to operate the zoom is too small for you to operate and was difficult to adjust. I dont know if other cameras in this price range are better compared to this but, I would only recommend this if you dont find better camera than this in the same price range. I&apos;d to finally retun this and decided to go for better camera with some additional price. When it doesn&apos;t deliver wha ... t you need whats the point in compromising?!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>65</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>CaptureTheMemory</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Made me a convert!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 18, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything!

Cons: Nothing!

I&apos;d always been a loyal Canon customer. Recently my camera broke and I was forced into the market for a new one. I did quite a bit of research and took a leap of faith on the Sony Cybershot 16.2 MP camera and am so glad that I did! The clarity is amazing and the color is so vivid. I don&apos;t know why I didn&apos;t switch over years ago. I am no professional photographer and you don&apos;t have to be. This camera works great as a point and shoot and does exceptionally well in dim lighting (where my prior Canon digital elph fell short). I would recommend this to anyone from novice to pro!!!

P.S. I never write reviews and was compelled to write one on this camera. That counts for something!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>66</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BusyTNMom</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Not very impressed</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 3, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use, great features, great photos, rechargable battery

Cons: not compatible with my adobe photoshop software, shutter speed is slow, overpriced

I am not very impressed with this camera. I researched various cameras before making a purchase and have to say that I am disappointed in this camera. The shutter speed is not quick enough to catch the shot of my 15 month old before she is on to doing something else. Also, it is not compatible with my Adobe Photoshop software. If I had it to do over, I would purchase a Nikon. My Nikon Coolpix is very compatible to this Sony but at a fraction of the cost. The Nikon is compatible with Adobe Photoshop. Unfortunately, I missed the 14 day window to return this camera so now I am stuck with it.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>67</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ScottOHIO</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera and Upgrade</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 28, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Picture clarity is excellent, upgraded from a 3 year old Sony Cybershot and very pleased with the results. Panaramic mode is a little tricky to use and figure out so do your reading prior to use. Video quality is outstanding! No need for a Video Camera in our family, Make sure you get a 32 gig or larger card, because video takes a lot of your memory.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>68</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>azwildcat55</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Price, Picture Quality, SD Card capability

Cons: zooming in when viewing the photo

This is the first Sony I&apos;ve ever purchased. The price is excellent, so I knew it wasn&apos;t a big risk. It&apos;s a wonderful camera. Picture quality is fantastic and the video quality is fantastic as well. I have terrible buyers remorse, but this one didn&apos;t go back. I really like the fact that I didn&apos;t have to buy another memory card because this camera uses SD cards. A+ !!! I really enjoy taking photos and video with it.
There is one negative with the camera. When viewing photos, it is very slow to zoom in. Not enough to be a deal breaker.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>69</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SonyWX9Lover</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent camera, all around.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 11, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent low light pictures, Cool panoramic mode, Gorgeous display, Great video quality, Supurb picture quality

Cons: Battery life, but a spare can be purchased for a relatively low price.

The last time I bought a camera was in 2006 (Sony DSC-W30) so I decided it was about time to get a new one. After looking around at a few different cameras, I settled on this one. After taking over 700 pictures with it (within 2 weeks), I can safely say that this camera does everything I could have possibly wanted it to do and more. The biggest highlights for me are the excellent low light performance (I hate using flash because I feel it ruins just about anything buy a portrait), all around great image quality (I would say almost every picture looks good, and those taken in good lig ... hting look spectacular), panoramic mode (you really don&apos;t realize how neat this feature is till you try it), and a beautiful display. The 3D feature is also pretty cool to have, but I don&apos;t have anything to view those pictures on as of yet (I really wish I could see what they look like). All of my friends are thoroughly impressed by the pictures I take with this, and a few of them own DSLRs (of course the pictures taken on the wx9 aren&apos;t as good as a DSLR, but they&apos;re amazing for a point and shoot).

The only major downside to this camera is battery life. You almost need to buy a spare battery if you plan on having it last the whole day, and if you take any videos on the highest quality those two may not even get you all the way there (The HD video destroys battery life, although the quality is excellent). Aside from that, the only minor frustrations I&apos;ve run into are that the high resolution panoramic mode is difficult to use (there&apos;s a regular mode and a high resolution mode, and while the former works perfectly, the later is really difficult to take pictures on without noticing where the individual photos were merged; although when you do succeed, it looks beautiful), and that it can&apos;t really focus on small objects that are far away when you zoom in (though that seems to be a problem with most point and shoots I&apos;ve tried.

I would not hesitate to say that this is one of the best point ...
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>70</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JukeSter</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great small point n shoot camera...BUT!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: small and feature pack

Cons: slow!!! slow!!! slow!!!

I love this camera at first... my friends love it also specially the anti blemish shots.
A few issue i found is its a bit slow
Then after a few weeks of use the zoom tends to get slower when it zoom in and out, worst sometimes the lens jam.
I read a few other forums and review about this camera and some of them also have the lag or lens jam issue. Too late for me to exchange or return to the store i just have to deal with the slow issue as long as its not as often the lens jam.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>71</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AGTX</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 3&quot; screen, HD recording, Picture quality

Cons: Nothing

The best Sony camera I&apos;ve owned. Great pictures and easy to use. Same features as with my previous Sony camera plus some. Awesome camera for $199. Don&apos;t forget to buy the higher class memory card for better HD recording. I got a class 10, 8GB for 24.99. If you&apos;ve never owned a Sony, this is the one to start with!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>72</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Zeus99</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>WOW!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture quality, Nice modes, Full HD video

Cons: none yet.

Great camera, beautiful pictures, excellent settings. A great buy for your money. A couple of days pass by, and the quiality of the pictures and videos is amazing. I used to have only Canon, because my old camera was good, but I could&apos;t find what a wanted it in Canon this time, so I took a chance with Sony. My fist word &quot;WOW!&quot;.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>73</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Busymomof5</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for anyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 29, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to work

Bought this camera for my 75 yr old dad for Christmas after finally giving up his 35millimeter camera! He loves it and has not had any complaints. He said it is so easy to use and takes clear pictures. He loves the fact that he can email us all the pictures he is taking and print pictures right from his computer.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>74</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Better than the comparable Canon model</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Feb 1, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I originally purchased a Canon based on many friends/family recommendations. However, I was disappointed with the quality of the pics so I returned it and bought this one. This camera takes great pictures... My dog is very hard to get a pic of because on most cameras the flash goes off and then there is a delay before the picture actually registers. This gives my dog time to move around and ruin the picture in the mean time. The Sony is alot faster than the other ones I&apos;ve tried,,, not sure if its the shutter speed or what its called but all I know is that it works great!! Best camera for a non tech saavy person who wants great pictures w/vivid colors and spend $200- or less if its on sale.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>75</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great low light shooting</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: worth its price

Cons: slow start up and viewing time

Nice camera for the price. Excellent with low light, indoor shots, without flash. Flash tends to overexpose, so I tend to avoid using it. Holding steady in dark areas without flash, this camera tends to produce good quality, non-blurry pictures. Continual burst mode it also great. Camera is a little slow to open and close and to switch to viewing mode. Far away scenic scenes with zoom feature loses some clarity and looks a little fuzzy. Very little distortion with zoom however (no fisheye effect)</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>76</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>An excellent camera for the price.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Great Video quality.

A gave to my son as a Christmas gift and so far he loves the camera. The 1080 HD camera as a great quality picture and video. It was a great deal with the 4 gig card, camera case and a $10.00 egift certificate. Best Buy so far this Holiday Season!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>77</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Anonymous</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great price for a superb camera (16.2mp)!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 14, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: in a simple word, &quot;everything&quot;!!!

Very handy camera, many good features (must read the manual), stylish and compact, awesome quality pictures and videos... no regrets!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>78</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>KrAnn</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Amazing picture and video quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 10, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love this camera! I have always had Sony cameras, so figuring out how to use it wasn&apos;t difficult since it&apos;s very similar to other Sonys. I would definitely recommend this camera. The only thing is using the video can drain the battery more quickly, but I guess that&apos;s probably the case with all cameras.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>79</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>mireia</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent purchase.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I&apos;m still getting to know this camera, but I have found it easy to use and at the same time flexible in the effects and possibilities it offers to the user. The price seems reasonable to me considering the quality of the images and video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>80</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>smd3284</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>EXCELLENT SMALL CAMERA FOR A GREAT PRICE</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 9, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: affordable, great for video and pix

Cons: you will need to read the manual to understand each feature

This is the best camera I have owned. It&apos;s definitely an affordable camera, with excellent quality pictures, and an even better video camera. The features are exceptional, but it takes some time to familiarize yourself with what settings to use. I highly recommend this as a camera/video, !!! and it lasts for weeks without charging,</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>81</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Alex1982</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 8, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Decent price for the quality

Cons: Rather short battery life for my taste

This camera takes really good pictures. Crisp,clean, very good quality. It is easy to use, also very lightweight. In my opinion, the only fault is the battery life which seems a bit short.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>82</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jeragape</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best point-shoot camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jan 6, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture and video quality

Cons: Nothing so far

Great camera. High quality pictures and hd video is amazing for the such small camera. I got it used for only 100 bucks. I highly recommend it. Take a look on the quality of pictures, they speak by themselves. Thanks Sony for continuing producing high quality products.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>83</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>pinkerton85</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect Point and Shoot</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I love this camera and all of it&apos;s features. I&apos;m not good with cameras at all and have found this easy to use (never have opened manual) and I&apos;m able to capture wonderful pictures. I especially love the gourmet and panaramic modes. The gourmet mode although for food takes very detailed photos. I got some beautiful Christmas tree photos using that mode. Oh and the skin feature is so cool! It automatically clears people&apos;s complexions :)

It&apos;s true test will be Disney World fireworks which I always have struggled getting perfect shots with other cameras in the past. I have a feeling this one will get me some good shots.

My only complaint would be I wish the software allowed for more editing than what it does which is hardly anything.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>84</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jerry</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>BuyDig.com</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Sony wx9</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Dec 19, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy To Use; Small / Compact

Cons: Limited Zoom; Poor Image Quality

Would not recomand, go with the g lens much better camer and made in japan. Imiage quality does not satisfy at all even when compared to my old 5 year sony camera</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>85</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Tangara</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 23, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is one of the best picture era revolution. I will recommend every body to buy of this cameras. because it an investment and you won&apos;t regret for your money. then for any occasion you will enjoy every body with perfect pictures quality.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>86</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>jones678</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 10, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Shutter speed and picture quality were super important in my purchase. This camera has fulfilled my expectations. I have owned the camera for over a month and used it in many different lighting situations including low light and it took great photos. I would definitely recommend this camera to anyone looking for an easy to use good quality photo camera. The only negative is the video quality wasn&apos;t exactly what I thought it would be; low light it was horrible. Normal light is good, but not great. That is to be said in the context that it is a camera and not a</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>87</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Datety</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Nov 9, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The size and ease of use.

Cons: Video is too short.

Two days after purchasing this camera i took it to MLK, Jr Memorial in D.C. The camera was easy to use and the pictures are stunning.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>88</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Micahel23</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Perfect for every day use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Oct 27, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good price, relatively easy to use

Cons: Long range zoom

I have only had this camera for about 3 weeks, but I&apos;m already in love with it...especially the panoramic shot mode! I have yet to explore all the many features, but the intelligent auto feature has been useful. It takes great pictures in direct sunlight or low light. The smile and face detection is great for pics with friends. For you techies, this camera has 3D capability so you can take 3D pics and view them on your 3D hdtv. I don&apos;t have one but it is a great feature. My favorite is by far the panoramic mode. It takes multiple pictures and compiles them into one long view photo. I am anxious to test this out at a football game.

Next...the price. I was debating on getting this camera or staying with a Can ... non by buying the PowerShot 300HS. The prices were vary similar and so were the features, but the 3D and panoramic mode, plus the Carl Zeiss lens leaned me toward the Sony. In addition, I got the camera, battery, extra battery, case, 4gig memory card, and 2 year protection plan for just around $250 so I got everything I needed for a decent price. If you are just getting into photography, this camera will give you many options and won&apos;t leave you disappointed. I cannot wait until I have mastered the features so I can take even better photos.
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>89</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>barefoot2013</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Love it.</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 21, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: easy to use, great pictures!

Cons: a little bit pricey - especially after buying the warranty!

The pictures on the camera almost appear more clear than after they are uploaded, but it was very impressive! First time I used it, I was easily able to find and use the self timer. GREAT camera, with awesome pictures even in low light settings :) Def recommend.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>90</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>hollogram1111</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Takes Terrible People Shots</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;1 star (Hated it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>1</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Takes Good SCENERY Shots

Cons: Takes Horrible People Shots (skin) and Short Battery

I bought this camera after spending 2 hours in Best Buy. This is the most expensive camera I have ever purchased and if I could return it I would. Every picture I take of a person makes them look RED and Like they have Terrible skin, i&apos;ve tried every setting and they are all bad. My 100.00 camera from 5 years ago takes better portrait pictures. I have gone thru the help manual tried all the settings and still every person is red and looks like they have a skin disease. Very disappointed because when I bought It I explained it was for people shots. The scenery shots are great but I bought it for PEOPLE. Now I am stuck paying it off and the warranty.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>91</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Steveq2</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great overall camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: picture quality and screen

Cons: battery

This is our second sony camera and this one is even better than the first. It takes great pictures and has a beautiful screen for showing them off. Very easy to use.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>92</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Jack737</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Dont waste your money</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 4, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;2 stars (Disliked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>2</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: nothing

Cons: eveything

I hate everything about this camera. It is the most cumbersome one I have ever owned, from charging the battery to accessing the menu options. I lost my Panasonic Lumina on vacation and decided to replace it with this one. My regret is I didnt take it back soon enough.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>93</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>SonyLover2011</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great picture quality for a Point &amp; Shot camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Sep 1, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Build quality, pricture quality, small size, and easy to use

Cons: None so far.

I have purchased many point &amp; shot cameras from both Sony and Canon. But the Sony WX-9 changed my perspect about the pciture quality of the point &amp; shot camera, specially under the low light condition. I took this camera for a trip for China and was very satisfied with the picture quality of the camera.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>94</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Lynn147</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera for price</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 25, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I find this camera easy to use. Wish the zoom was better, but overall, easy to navigate through the settings. The smile detection feature is awesome. Video quality is great - used for a concert: able to take a picture while recording video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>95</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>ermaho</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Fool proof</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 24, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Just about the whole thing

Cons: nothing

Easy to operate. Takes great pictures and the Hi Def video is just as satisfying. For the price, you can&apos;t beat this one.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>96</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>BlackHockeyStar</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>This camera has bomb picture quality</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Point and click perfection

Cons: Nothing

Look no further. This is the camera for you. The price is way under the picture quality. The low lighting pictures come out remarkable, such as at the bar/club, or at dusk on the lake....etc. The video is dope too, and the software that comes with the camera is nice too.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>97</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>cabriggs112</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality, price, easy to use

I bought this camera right before taking a trip to Lake Michigan. This camera takes great pictures in any light conditions. The panoramic pictures are amazing. Video quality is awesome. My wife and I have gotten so many compliments on the quality of the pictures and videos. Greatest camera I&apos;ve ever owned.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>98</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>PictureHappy</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Very Fast!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Aug 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Speed

Cons: can&apos;t change the display time of the pic you just took &amp; you cant force flash

I love this camera. It takes very fast shots even indoors! I love the fact that I can video tape &amp; snap a pic @ the same time!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>99</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Raven0280</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>My Best Decision</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 31, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Shutter speed, crystal clear images, tons of features!

Cons: Nothing that I&apos;ve found yet!!

I bought this camera to replace an Olympus that I was tired of bc the shutter speed was horrible (I&apos;d miss great shots) &amp; the low light images were grainy &amp; terrible. I spent weeks deciding on a digital camera &amp; boy am I glad I got this one!!! I absolutely LOVE this camera &amp; all of its features! I used it for the first time yesterday at a Motley Crue concert that was outdoors at night and the images were crystal clear as if I were right next to the stage! The night time pics came out great &amp; clear and the shutter speed was exactly what i was looking for (I FNALLY got some great shots)!!! I strongly recommend you get this camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>100</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>coneycone</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Gift</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 26, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: 3d capable, Panaramic sweep, big MP

Cons: nothing so far

I bought this camera for my girlfriend for her birthday. She is a sony cyber-shot only type of gal - has owned 3 others prior to this! She absolutely loves this camera. The features are great including the panaromic sweep. The 16.2MP is great quality. Overall for the price it is great product.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>101</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>JayDS</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent videos</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 15, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Excellent videos

I went to a big concert event and made videos and the videos came out crystal clear and the sound was excellent. I had purchased a Panasonic and the camera had a hard time focusing on the concert lights and lasers and the sound was horrible. The Sony is small enough to put in my purse.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>102</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>EastCoast843</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great compact camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jul 12, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>This is the fourth compact SONY digital camera that I have owned and each one has been better than the previous model. This has a super fun &quot;panorama&quot; feature that allows you to pan at least 270 degrees and then magically produces a cool panoramic image. This camera also performs better in low light than my last model. It&apos;s small and light.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>103</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>tan00001</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Short Battery Life, &quot;Processing&quot; All the Time</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;3 stars (It was okay)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>3</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture qualtity

Cons: Battery life, slow picture processing

The battery life of this camera is much worse than the Kodak V1253 that I had before. Even two batteries cannot last as long as the Kodak V1253. The Kodak V1253 records 720p HD video, comparing to the Sony&apos;s 1080. But even at the lowest resolution the Sony can recod video only half as long.

The Sony keeps putting up &quot;Processing&quot; messages between pictures. If you are impatient, you need a different camra.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>104</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Siren717</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>In love</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: The picture quality

Cons: Can&apos;t think of anything.

This is the best PS for the price, I love the infocus blurry background effect. We use that setting the most. I had bought a Nikon Coopixs 6100 at first but the picture quality was to say the least... bad. So I returned it and got the Sony and have been in love ever since.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>105</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Cooper25</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 7, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture Quality, easy to use.

Cons: Nothing so far

This is a great camera. Picture quality is great. Panoramic feature is pretty cool for outdoor picture were you wanna capture a wide view. I haven&apos;t tried the 3D still pictures yet because I do not have a 3D TV to display it on.

READ the manual. There are different features that make your pictures come out better in different lighting situations. They have been very handy for me.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>106</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fhs08</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great camera!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>I researched quite a few cameras before purchasing this one. Love LOVE it! Superb picture plus video quality. I think its a huge bargain for the price. Stylish and sleek little camera!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>107</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Nancy2Hector</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>May 5, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything

I bought this camera for my Trip to Las Vegas... This is my First Sony Camera and I Love It !! I love the ease of use, my favorite color black and size. It takes Clear and Nice pictures and is easy to use. Would really Recommended!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>108</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Bok3hT</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>A Pocketful of Extras .. From a Compact Price Valu</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 29, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Awesome Low Light Pictures

Cons: Camera Speaker for playback is weak but great mic for stereo recording!

Sony WX9 is without a doubt A GREAT COMPACT CAMERA (with a remarkable and surprisingly value price). This is great for those emergency, gotta have moment picture shots that you can just pull it out of your pocket!
I am a Semi Pro Photog and I use my Nikon D700 (although it can&apos;t compete with this cam in terms of pic quality; it does take remarkable depth pictures) so I was in the market of a small cam that has great low light w/o paying a lot of money and I tell ya; so glad I chose this cam cuz performance of it is so awesome! HIGHLY RECOMMENDED!

Pros: HDR, AVCHD Video is superb, Ease of Panorama capture, Features like 10fps,defocus backround, 3.0 LCD is so ... clear, rugged feel, GREAT STEREO REC. and most of all..AWESOME LOW LIGHT Pics.

Cons: Buttons are small (if you have huge fingers), Panorama capture sometimes have wrong overlapping pics (just practice on a continuous motion &amp; you&apos;ll be fine), only 5X ZOOM and the only bad thing THE SPEAKER IS NOT SO LOUD WHEN REC MOVIE PLAYED ON THE CAMERA but Rec. sound is pretty excellent when played on a computer.

NOTE: Best Buy .. you guys rock cuz my camera was ready for pick up 5 days before the actual expected date (and this is the second time BBuy did it on another separate order of mine)! WELL EXCEEDED MY EXPECTATIONS and more!
I strongly suggest for you to just be deliver it to one of the store locations as I did not pay for shipping plus it is faster to receive your items!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>109</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>aut9169</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Excellent Camera and Great Quality Pics!!!!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 16, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Quality

Cons: Everything is great!!!!

This is the best camera I have ever had and I have had cameras that cost more. The pics are amazing and the video is equally as good. I absolutely love this camera!!!</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>110</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>fixitsteve</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera For Saving Memories...</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Apr 8, 2011</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: great indoor pictures in low light..great hd movie mode..

Cons: have not found anything bad...........

i,ve had several sony cameras and mostly had good luck with them..how ever my last sony was missing features i needed and that was for indoor low light pictures..this new model wx9 took care of that problem and added great new features such as the 3d panorama options..fits in my pocket and is always ready for that special picture of puget sound or the mountains that surround us here..great point and shoot camera, fast recovery for that next special pic..very small camera but for the features and the price it,s well worth it..</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>111</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>MrMestizo1981</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great Camera</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;4 stars (Liked it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-unstarred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>4</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Picture and video quality.

Cons: No compliants.

I bought this camera on the advise of a family relative and it was actually their 2nd camera as their first one broke due their fault. So we bought it together at the same time.

Ever since it&apos;s been great camera that takes very good pictures and video.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>112</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>AimKep</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Great little camera for anyone</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Jun 12, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Easy to use

Cons: Don&apos;t know yet

I love this camera. I wanted something tiny that still takes great photos and video. It is easy to take anywhere and does a great job on my evening/dusk photos.</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>113</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>Wesley27</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>Best Pocket Camera I&apos;ve Seen Yet!</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 23, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Everything!

Cons: Nothing!

I&apos;ve had this camera for about 4 months now and I think it&apos;s about time I tell how absolutely amazing this Camera is! I purchased the Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 with a 16GB SanDisk Ultra SDHC Card and together they make pure magic! The picture quality on this camera is wonderful, it takes very clear and crisp pictures, as well as the HD video that shoots an amazing 1080p resolution and records sound that picks up very well! I love the 5x Optical Zoom, and I am astounded that Sony was able to put so many amazing features into a pocket camera this size, this camera is just as good as some DSLR&apos;s, maybe even better! Also, not only was the price right, but this camera is very easy to operate, so easy a child can use it! I would definitively recommend ... this camera to any one who either travels often, likes to store memories of family, friends, and events, or do both!
expand » « collapse</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

   <Item>
     <ID>114</ID>
     <Item>Sony Cyber-shot DSC-WX9 16.2 MP Digital Camera (Black)</Item>
     <URL>http://www.google.com/shopping/product/14079012977999333634/reviews?q=camera&amp;hl=en&amp;bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_qf.&amp;fp=b286705da7ea78c8&amp;bpcl=36601534&amp;biw=1600&amp;bih=775&amp;tch=1&amp;ech=1&amp;psi=2n6RUJnHN-T42gXD2YHIDw.1351712470468.3&amp;sa=X&amp;ei=_36RULiYKfSk2gWH0oGwCA&amp;ved=0CLUCEPQCMAg</URL>
     <Reviewer>NanaP</Reviewer>
     <ProvidedBy>Best Buy</ProvidedBy>
     <EditorialReview></EditorialReview>
     <ReviewTitle>easy to use</ReviewTitle>
     <ReviewDate>Mar 15, 2012</ReviewDate>
     <RatingHTML>&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-stars-small&quot; title=&quot;5 stars (Loved it)&quot; ga:type=&quot;UserRating&quot;&gt;  &lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;rsw-starred&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;</RatingHTML>
     <Rating>5</Rating>
     <Review>Pros: Good value for the price; easy to use

Cons: short battery life; touch screen would enhance features

Brought on vacation; battery died sooner than expected. Last camera had touch screen- missed that with this camera, but stll a good value for the price</Review>
     <HelpfulCount></HelpfulCount>
 </Item>

</Items>

